I have a confession.
During our marriage interview,
there was a side of me that I kept secret from you.
It's something I can never let you find out.
My true self.
Hey...
H-Honey?
What's wrong?
Umm...
I can't, I can't say it.
They say it's going to rain later today,
so take an umbrella.
Ok, thanks.
Ishida
Well, I'm going to get going.
Take care!
If you find out...
who I really am...
I know I can't keep this from you forever.
Even so...
I...
Mesu Saga
Wife
Okay, I'm turning on the camera!
No...
Yumicchi, that's a good face you have on there.
Come on Miss, look at the camera.
No, I can't, it's embarrassing.
These are some big breasts.
They've got to be at least G-Cup.
Not there... No!
Miss... You're all sloppy.
No, stop... Not like this...
Your legs are wide open.
What an embarrassing sight.
No! Don't say that!
I heard you're newly married?
Without telling you,
I became the guarantor for a friend's debt.
What would your husband do if he
found out you were doing this?
Before I realized it, it became a 3,000,000 yen debt.
Come on Miss, open your mouth.
It's so soft, rubbing against my dick. How lewd!
Dear, I'm currently an AV actress.
Your stockings are sticking against my dick.
I heard that you were quite a slut
back in your university days.
I heard that too.
You were probably the Director's favorite, weren't you?
As expected from someone trained by the Director,
you really know how to use your tongue.
I'm cumming,
someone other than your husband
is going to cum all over your legs.
Besides, there no way one man can
keep this slutty body happy.
We'll be sure to fill the void.
l am having sex with other men for money.
Does your husband know that his wife's a slut?
You've already taken in more than
half the guys in this circle.
Some people even call you the Energizer Bunny.
Without you knowing I've had many
men's things in my mouth.
I had used other men's things to pleasure myself.
Miss, it's okay to cum inside you, right?
It's fine.
Cum inside me.
Getting so excited over a dick that's not your husband's...
If you found out what I was doing right now,
what would you think of me?
If you found out that I was such a slut,
what would you do?
I can't... I'm going to cum soon.
Miss, you are so erotic.
I want to cum more.
I'm so sorry, dear.
Point of View
Hey, the video you did last time was really popular.
As I thought, Yumicchi is really sexy.
I was right to ask you to star in my new video.
Yabe-kun, don't talk about it so much...
It's embarrassing.
What are you talking about, you were so into it.
You're secretly happy, aren't you?
The whole country's jacking off to your slutty body.
You're enjoying it and you're paying back you debt,
It's like killing two birds with one stone!
Honey... I'm filming an AV again.
Alright then Yumicchi, I'm turning on the camera.
Just be natural and relax.
While keeping it a secret from you...
A point of view AV.
No...
Look, your nipples became so hard
before you even knew it.
You can't!
Letting someone other than you play with my nipples.
This feeling...
You're as sensitive as ever.
It's because, if you do that...
I fear it'll become a habit.
Having a lewd body like this...
Can you satisfy your elite salary man of a husband?
No, don't say that!
What no, even though you like it this way.
I remember it well, you back in your school days.
Everyone was having sex with you like it was a game.
If I remember correctly, Sugiyama won that one.
He was so turned on by you that time, he
came three times in front of everyone.
Well after that, everyone
got their turn to cum inside you.
Stop talking about stuff that happened so long ago.
How's it a long time ago?
Just remembering it makes you wet.
I decided when I took that AV back then,
It'd be a shame if we couldn't share
this slutty body with everyone.
Wow, it's twitching so badly.
Yabe-kun, instead of talking about that...
What, you can't take it anymore?
Come on, show me how much you
love it in front of the camera.
We plan to share this with lots of men all over the place.
Yes!
Dear, I wonder if I'm a horrible woman.
Yes...
It's so fun when other men are using me as they like.
Yes!
I've always loved sex,
and played around with a lot of guys.
But then I met you, and thought I could change.
Yes!
Yes, that's the spot!
Your cock feels so good!
Stir me up more!
I can't... it's so good!
Getting so excited by some other guy's cock...
No...
It's because you're fucking me with your cock.
Oh, no... I'm going to cum soon.
Yes!
It's coming...
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
Together... Let's cum together!
Okay, I'll let it all out on you.
If I keep this up... I'll go back to who I was before.
I got some good stuff today too, Yumicchi.
Keep it up, I'm counting on you next time too.
Are you afraid of your husband finding out?
If l keep this up, I'll go back to who I was before...
Go back?
You never changed in the first place.
You're still the same person
who has sex with random guys.
That's... That's not true.
As proof of that, you jumped at the chance
when I asked you about doing AV, didn't you?
That's because I had to return the debt.
Was it really the only reason?
Wasn't it because you weren't satisfied
with the sex with your husband?
You aren't the type of girl
to be satisfied with just one penis.
It's impossible.
What should I do?
Just follow your heart.
Well, I'll text you next time I need you.
Outdoor Exposure
I lied to you today about having dinner with a friend.
Instead, I came to a large park nearby our house...
In order to film a public AV.
Sorry for being late.
You're here, Yumicchi.
This is Katou-san, the famous Eagle.
Nice to meet you, Yumi-san.
Pleased to meet you too.
We're done preparing for the shoot so let's
move to a different location and start!
Okay.
I already prepared dinner, so just heat
it up in the microwave, okay?
Sure.
I don't think I'll be too late coming home.
I'm going now.
How many videos has it been now?
The more I shoot, the less guilty
I feel towards cheating on you.
The excitement and happiness are driving my body,
I can't be without it anymore.
All right, this area is quiet and not too
many people come around here.
Okay.
I've been looking forward to meeting you, Yumi-san.
I've also seen the previous AVs you've starred in,
and I thought, this women is an innocent devil.
Wait...
I heard you're making AVs to pay
back a debt, but the truth is...
No...
You just get a thrill from cheating
on your husband, don't you?
No!
Stop! It's embarrassing.
You're just a naughty girl.
You act all prim and proper,
but the truth is, you just can't wait to provoke a man.
No, that's no true...
Come on, lean over this bench.
We're doing it here?
No, someone will see.
If it's Yumi-san's perverted body,
I'm ﻿sure they'll be delighted to watch.
No!
What are you talking about?
There may even be someone close watching right now.
No... No! You can't!
This is the first time I've been so stirred up.
No! I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
No!
Wait!
I just came, if you keep touching me like that...
If I keep touching?
Come on, cum again!
It's coming... It's coming out!
If I keep doing this, I won't be able to
contain myself in front of you anymore!
Let's take a good look at Yumi-san's vagina.
No, you can't.
You can't just put it in so suddenly!
What are saying when your pussy is this wet?
Amazing!
Yes! It feels too good!
W-Wait!
Someone's watching from over there!
Stop...
It's fine.
Let them watch all they want.
Let them see you going crazy over a cock
other than your husband's.
No!
Oh, no! I can't hold my voice in!
I'm being too loud.
They're seeing me in this embarrassing position.
Are you sure you should be talking in such a loud voice?
You'll only attract more people.
I don't care.
They can watch me all they want.
Just do me more!
Thrust your dick in deeper!
I want to feel even better!
I want more!
Amazing, it's going so deep!
No, I can't...
It's coming...
I'm cumming!
What should I do?
It took longer than I thought.
I need to hurry home.
Yumi.
Dear...
W-What are you doing here?
Yumi.
Perversion
Stop! Honey...
No! Not so suddenly!
Shut up! Don't order me around!
No! Please, don't be so rough!
Yumi, how much time did you spend with them here?
Ten? Twenty?
30 minutes?
It's delicious, your big dick is really delicious!
It's so energetic!
How is it, watching your own AV while
being used by your husband?
I'm sorry!
Dear, I...
Yumi.
You can still feel it, even at a time like this?
I'm sorry, but I'm that kind of woman.
The truth is, I'm a slutty whore who loves sex.
That's why...
At first, I only did it for the money,
but then I started to enjoy it﻿,
tasting so many different ﻿men, it felt really good.
I'm sorry. Please punish my slutty body with your cock!
It's overflowing with cum!
More, ﻿fill me up more!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Dear...
Let's divorce.
Wow, that was great acting!
Sir, you'd be a great actor.
Y-Yabe-kun..
Did you take it properly, Yabe-san?
Yeah, perfectly!
Other than this camera, I have a bunch
of hidden cameras as well.
This will be a masterpiece.
Wh-What's this about?
The truth is, the person who asked me to
make these AVs was your husband.
Your husband is actually a pervert
who loves watching your videos.
This is the first time I've ever felt so good.
Honey...
Yumi...
You're not the only one with a different face.