Class is starting. We'll be picking up
from where we left off last time.
Hey, quiet down!
Sorry.
What were they trying to do?
I'll just have to wait and see.
I won't be responsible for
whatever happens next, okay?
Don't worry. With the way you are now,
there'll be no problem.
Huh? I'm not quite sure I understand.
Well, what I mean to ask is, do you know
when the headmaster usually leaves?
No, not really.
Why would you want to
know something like that?
I-It's not like I really need to know, I was just curious!
H-Hold on a second, I'm getting a call.
Headmaster's Office
What do you think you're doing,
sneaking around the headmaster's office?
Um, well... I can explain...
You've been acting very strange recently.
Tell me what's going...
I was so scared!
That was third-tier acting,
but you still did well, Miyu.
L-Let me go! Wait, you're...
Yup, that's right.
Miyu, just do everything according to plan now.
I know, I know!
I don't wanna stick around for this anyway.
So you really were pulling the strings.
What are you planning?
You know already.
This school belongs to Yuuri.
I won't let you or Shirakawa have their way with it.
So now that you're here,
who's going to protect your precious Yuuri?
You... If you dare lay a finger on Yuuri...
What do you want from me?
Glad you pick up on things quickly.
I want to fuck you.
I want to see that strong-willed face
turn into that of a lustful animal.
What the hell?
You're taking Yuuri hostage for something like that?
That's just how much I want your body.
So, what's it gonna be?
Fine, do what you want.
There's no need to even think
if it means saving Yuuri.
Not bad, knight. I'm gonna enjoy this.
Being stared daggers at really gets my heart pumping.
Good for you. I'm so glad you're pleased.
I'm surprise these buttons haven't popped.
It can't be easy keeping these babies
from busting out of their confinement.
Thanks for your sympathy.
Your tits are so sinful,
but your nipples seem more innocent.
You're scum beyond redemption.
You little... What are you doing?
Don't know what a tit flick is?
You bastard. How dare you ruin a woman's
pride with this kind of demeaning action?
What's the matter? Your face is softening, sensei.
It's a good look for you.
Men like you are scum!
Yep, and that scum's cock is taking your tits' virginity.
His hard thing is tunneling through my boobs.
There's something wet coming out from the tip too.
Looks like your tits and my cock
make a good match for each other.
There's so much pre-cum coming out, I can't stop it.
Screw you!
What's happening? It's so hot and it's starting
to bulge. It's pushing into my boobs.
Seeing women get scared of a cock
about to cum really turns me on.
It's so hot and it smells so bad.
It's still coming out. It's making me so dirty!
I like what I'm seeing.
Semen looks really good on a fox like you.
If you think this makes me happy,
you have the worst imagination in the world.
Are you satisfied now?
You're not broken yet? Well, that's fine.
I'm a ways off from being done anyway.
Keep me company, okay?
You're pretty calm.
I prepared myself for this,
so I'm not gonna cry about it now.
After being stuck with this,
you think you can still stay so stoic?
It's really tight. It's a lot better than I...
Oh? So even with this hot body of yours, you're a virgin?
I was sure that you already had some experience.
Yeah, I'm a virgin. What are you trying to say?
It's a happy mistake. I bet you've been
frustrated that you're still a virgin.
Being violated by scum like you
is the ultimate disgrace for me.
I respect that.
Let me help you feel more of that disgrace.
Your tip is destroying my stomach!
Looks like you're in pain.
If you beg, I'll be more gentle.
Why would I? If it's for Yuuri, I'll bear any pain.
You make me want to cum inside your pussy.
You lowlife. How can you look so happy when
you're tormenting a woman the way you are?
It's about time. I'll make sure
to cum a lot in your virgin pussy.
You finish fast, huh?
You don't mind getting cummed inside of?
If it'll save Yuuri and the academy,
it's a small price to pay.
So just hurry up and cum, and end this already!
Okay, till cum to my heart's content.
It's coming out! There's so much hot stuff
flowing out inside me. So this is semen?
It feels so disgusting!
It's going all the way to my womb!
This is such an unsettling sensation.
Having your virgin pussy fucked was fun, wasn't it?
Well, for me, at least.
If something like that is fun for you,
then you're one twisted man.
Looks like you still got some fight left in you.
Come on, bring your tits this way.
I wanna look at them while we're doing it.
What? You're not done yet?
Look at this.
This doesn't end until I'm satisfied.
I love looking at you while you
make these pathetic sounds.
You animal. Violating my body wasn't enough,
now you're verbally abusing me?
Do I hear you whining?
Saying that you can't take it anymore?
Like hell I am. I'm not whining.
If you really want to prove that,
then raise your voice.
Shut up. Just move.
What are you doing?!
What? Just by sucking on your boobs,
I got you to make a really nice sound.
You're wrong. I only made that sound
because it feels disgusting!
If it feels good, just say so.
It's not good to hold these things in.
Like hell it does. Having my boobs sucked
by scum like you is just... humiliating.
It's bulgihg again.
Does this mean we're going to be done soon?
Yeah, I'll make this the last creampie.
That's music to my ears.
Just cum already! Cum as much as you want.
It's shooting into me!
His filthy cum is... this animal's cum is...
Just keep cumming.
I can take it, it doesn't bother me!
You're quite the woman.
Looks like we'll have even more fun from here on out.
You really are incorrigible scum.
So you're going to use that
to blackmail me from now on?
Correct. If you disobey me or do anything stupid,
I'll have you removed from this academy.
Fine. I'll listen to you.
She's too strong willed.
I'm going to have to find a way to tighten my hold on her.
Who can answer this question?
I can. It's a system for handling food.
Yes, that's correct.
They ate their food with their hands.
This was the proper eating etiquette at the time.
Dirty hands were wiped on clothes,
and food was thrown away just like that.
You came.
What do you need from me
so early in the morning, sensei?
I wanted to talk about our deal. If you can't guarantee
that Shirakawa won't do anything, the deal's off.
I get why you'd be suspicious, but if you won't
listen to me, I'll spread that photo around.
Fine, I understand.
I'll listen to you for now.
However, if anything happens to Yuuri, I'll take it
into my own hands to make sure you're eliminated.
Let's see just how much resolution you have with this.
Three-fourths of the population
were either slaves or freed slaves.
Excuse me.
The freed slaves were those who lost their master
and were consequently, released from the slavery system.
Fellow freed slaves would...
They would wed each other and bear children.
Face forward and do your job?
After the slaves' death,
there was a compensation system for them.
Sorry, I'm just feeling a bit under the weather.
Stop your whispering.
Circumstances...
Yes, they're... important things to remember.
They will be on the test.
Make sure you review well.
You still can't find what you dropped?
Sorry, I'm just about done.
Keep teaching.
If you're done then go back to your seat!
Yes, I'm sorry.
Stand. Bow.
Sensei, I have a question.
It's time to continue where we
left off in class. Let's have some fun.
You scum! You're planning on doing something
perverted to me again, aren't you?!
The way you look right now
is the very definition of perverted.
You're the one who did this to me!
You did it with this thing deep inside me!
If you're this wet with just the toy,
it must've felt really great.
Like hell it did. It felt horrible, you piece of trash!
That's disgusting! How dare you let that
filthy thing pulse inside me like that!
I wanted to hear you make that sound.
I'm not getting aroused from you doing this to me!
It's just a biological response that I can't control!
Yeah, keep acting tough.
His hard thing is going so deep inside me!
He's fucking me so hard, acting like he owns me!
His filthy thing is going so deep,
like it's digging for something!
Needless to say, I'm enjoying myself right now.
But that perverted act you're putting on isn't that great.
Shut up! What are you going to do now?!
It... It's twirling around my breasts!
You're playing with my breasts like they're toys again!
Just how far are you going to go to humiliate me?!
While they might not have known, you did just teach
an entire class while having a vibrator in you.
Shut up! How dare you make me
experience such humiliation!
You're a real lowlife, through and through!
But it seems like because of that,
you're really wet and ready to go.
Shut up, don't talk!
You're lower than even the lowest lowlifes!
You're just saying that this is
all for your own amusement!
This... Your movements...
As you requested,
I'll end this by cumming inside you.
Hurry up and cum! End this already!
You're not cumming yet?!
This isn't over yet?
My womb... wherever is fine...
Just hurry up and cum and end this!
I'll take you up on that then.
Oh my god, it's coming out with such vigor!
It's being poured directly into my womb...
Awaken to the pleasures of being a lustful animal.
It's so deep!
This will never go the way you want it to!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hdr
editor: aux
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч