Ak-kun!
Yes?
I'm coming in.
I'm sorry.
I know I should have cleaned up Kousuke-san's things.
Nah, don't worry about it.
I volunteered to do it,
and I am the one using this room.
This isn't a problem.
Thank you, Ak-kun.
Your face is all red.
Do you have a cold or something?
Oh, yes.
I need you to get me something.
It's too high. I can't reach it.
O-Okay.
It's been four years since her husband,
Kyousuke-san, passed away.
I became Ayako-san's bodyguard,
for she lives alone in a huge mansion.
You wore this suit when you were a tutor, right?
I wear it when I'm job hunting, too.
Didn't I wear it when I first came to your house?
Umm... There are still some things up here though.
Ayako-san, I'll do it instead.
I think I can get this.
Are you okay?
Here! Just a little more...
Are you all right?
I-I'm sorry.
I'm such a klutz.
I thought I could get it...
Yes?
Widow Diaries
~Under one house with that person I admire~
It's been awhile,
so I might've made too much.
No problem. I'll eat it all.
I may not look like it, but I'm in top
form because of the Kendo Club.
Well, I may be late with this,
but welcome, Akito-kun.
I'll be staying here for a while.
Cheers!
I ate a lot!
I can't eat anymore.
Ayako-san...
Is she drunk?
Ak-kun...
For some reason,
I haven't been invited to drinking sessions.
It's been a long time since I got drunk.
Is Ayako-san susceptible to liquor?
It's hot.
Ayako-san, let's get to sleep.
Don't you have a girlfriend, Ak-kun?
I don't have one.
Oh, is that so?
Then, are you a virgin?
V-Virgin?!
Which is it?
I-I'm a virgin...
Well, I'll go ahead and confirm that.
Ayako-san...
I...
Your thing is big...
Ayako-san...
It's going to go in here this time.
Wow...
Ayako-san's thing is see-through and wet.
Try tracing a line...
Ak-kun...
That's...
That's very good.
Then, next...
Would you like to touch...
my breasts?
Ak-kun, it looks like you know what you're doing.
Are you really a virgin?
You haven't
seen the thing a woman
has down there, have you?
Ayako-san...
Even though your thing is so responsive,
are you really a virgin?
It's true...
Good reaction...
Your cock wants to burst.
It wants to shoot it out already, doesn't it?
Y-Yes...
You don't need to hold back.
No. I'm about to...
You can cum.
Release everything out of your big cock
into my mouth.
It's...
It's coming out!
Wow. How wonderful!
Is this the first time you've seen a woman like this?
Yes.
Then come closer and have a better look.
Can you see how wet I'm down there?
Women become like this when they desire a man.
Don't just stare.
Touch it.
Can you feel my warmth?
That feels good.
I don't think this is your first time...
Oh, not there...
Ak-kun,
I'm going to let you lose your virginity.
I want to do it with you!
I want you to take my virginity!
I can't resist a plea from my cute Ak-kun...
Surprised?
This is how a lady puts it on.
Oh, I see...
Okay, come to me.
I'll take your virginity.
Come.
Come inside me!
Is it all the way in?
Congratulations. You're no longer a virgin.
Start by moving gently.
A-Ak-kun...
My breasts, my breasts...
If you grab my breasts this hard,
their shape will change.
Just because you're young
doesn't mean you need to be rough.
If something that hard gets deep inside me...
My pussy will...
My pussy will get hot!
I'm... about to...
– Ayako-san!
– Wait. Don't cum yet.
I want you to cum when I'm facing you.
Ayako-san...
You're beautiful.
You're about to cum, right?
You're about to burst, right?
I'm also about to cum...
So hold on...
Just a bit more!
Just a little more.
I'm going to cum.
My first orgasm in a long time
is coming...
It's coming!
I need to clean this up, okay?
It's being sucked out!
It tastes good when swallowed.
Ayako-san...
Umm... Ayako-san...
About last night...
– I've already been in love with...
– Ak-kun.
Ak-kun, I had Kousuke-san.
That's why you'll never be more than a cousin.
I was happy that I was able to have
meals with someone else again.
I kinda lost it back then...
So forget about what happened and
look at it as a one night stand.
You can find a much better and younger partner.
But I'm in love with...
It's time... for your job.
I'm serious about this.
What's wrong? Why are you so depressed?
F-Fumika-san!
Why are you here?
Oh, is it wrong for a clerk to be in the employee's room?
Oh my, you're staring at my breasts...
No, I already have Ayako...
I think you should come and eat out with me.
Fumika-san!
Oh!
Please stop this...
We're just getting started.
No, you can't do this...
I'm going to cum...
It's okay.
Let it burst out of your cock into my pussy-mouth...
Ayaka-san
S-Sorry, I have something to do.
See you later. Have a nice day!
Ah, that was bad.
Ayako-san.
The sake that you bought tastes great.
Ak-kun, are you alright?
I understand you'll never be able to forget Kousuke-san.
Still, I love you, Ayako-san.
I'm fine with being a replacement.
I don't care if you use me to wash your loneliness
away like a pillow or a vibrator.
I want to be with Ayako-san!
Ak-kun!
Ayako-san, I have a request.
Can you wear that for me?
I never thought I'd wear this again.
I feel like...
I'm back in the past.
Time is so cruet.
Ak-kun,
I'm sorry.
I'm not the same person I used to be.
You're beautiful.
You're really...
You look a lot better now.
Ak-kun, do you love your teacher?
Yes, I love you.
I love you, sensei.
Then, what do you think sensei wants to do?
Don't...
Sensei didn't say anything about wanting to do this.
Seems like I need to punish the naughty boy.
I think the naughty boy deserves it.
Well...
Looks like the naughty boy can no longer hold it.
I'm sorry.
I'm... about to...
No!
Hold it in a bit more!
I'm going to disappear here,
so do it gently.
Ak-kun, play with my nipples a bit more.
Ak-kun, don't you want to put it in?
Yes, Ayako-san.
But I'm not wearing a condom.
It's okay, Ak-kun.
Put it in like that.
Eh? But...
It's okay.
It's okay if it's you.
Ayako-san, I...
I'm going to do my...
Don't think about that now.
Let me hear it later.
Cum inside me.
Make me your woman.
It's finally in!
Your cock...
I'm inside you, Ayako-san.
That's good.
Your cock feels good!
Ayako-san, it's warm... inside you.
It's so tight down there.
Push it in.
Push it in more, Ak-kun!
Push it in more!
I'm going to cum.
This is great!
Ayako-san, I'm at my limit.
It's coming out!
Ak-kun,
cum in me.
Cum inside me.
Keep it up. Let it release inside me.
I don't care if I get pregnant!
Ayako-san...
It's okay.
I want Ak-kun's semen in my womb!
I can't hold it anymore.
Ak-kun, I love you!!
Ayako-san! Ayako-san!
Cum in me.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to climax.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Ak-kun, you came a lot...
You did a really good job.
Ayako! Ayako!
I'm going to be with Ayako forever.
Ak-kun, embrace me.
Make me our woman!
More and more.
I'm going to make you my woman.
I'm already at my limit.
I can't live without Ak-kun anymore!
Ayako, you're now mine!
Release it.
Release what you have in your thing.
I'm cumming!!
My womb is filled with your juice.
It's Ak-kun's personal hole now...
I'll be going to work now.
Ak-kun.
Ayako!
Hey, your work...
You're going to be late.
I'm going to finish this quickly.