My brother... Bad...
Lukish!
Lukish. Lukish.
My brother...
Lukish...?!
What's the matter?
I got bitten by
a poisonous spider.
You have such white skin.
Your legs are so white...
like a woman's...
My dear brother,
I can't tell you this, but...
I AM female...
My brother...
Are you hiding something
from me...?
It's been so many years..
It was the morning after
a vicious storm.
A calm and beautiful morning
just like this.
Lou, you were half dead,
lying right over...
Here we go again...
You were so weak,
you wouldn't have survived
for too long.
But I saved your life with
this most specific remedy -
- concocted from
Brown Dragon's poison.
For seven days and seven nights, I simmered and stewed the mix.
Thus, here you are.
Thanks to that witches' brew,
I suffered for seven days and
seven nights, not to mention -
- my darker complexion and
internal imbalance!!
Don't forget your unwomanly
strength and savagery.
Sleepy...
That's it!
You've gone too far this time!
Ya think?
She's right, Kei.
You can't blame Lou's
sexual dysfuntion -
- nor her lack of thought for
her violent behavior.
Why, you!
Good medicine tastes bitter.
Lou, don't you know -
- that a great benefit always
comes with a price?
A HEFTY price, you mean!!
Oh, my skin was so beautifully
pale and transparent!!
Your target, Bad Eroheem
Gibal the Second, -
- is a child of the late
king's concubine.
The throne was promised to
his younger half-brother -
- who was the legitimate prince.
Unsatisfied, Kind Bad revolted and killed his own father, -
- the Queen and the young Prince to take the throne by force.
That was four years ago, just
around the time we found you.
Kind Bad is an extremely
suspicious man.
He is always accompanied by
a cunning retinue -
- and a sturdy bodyguard.
You mean those...?
Get out! Get out! Get out!!
Clear the grounds!!
His Majesty the King of the Blue
Dragon Kingdom, -
- Bad Eroheem Gibal II,
has ordered -
- that this dam be demolished!
The work starts immediately!!
We're only humans!
So, that's who they were.
Do you know the men?
Yup. Chop! Chop! Chop!
The guard sliced and diced
three guys just like that!
Pretty skillful, I'd say,
Right, Sonya?
He had such gloomy eyes...
Just as I thought.
You must attack Kind Bad
when he is all alone.
I guess that means
his bedroom...
I really don't think Lou can
handle a heavy duty like this.
Whaddaya say..?
King Bad is mine!
I'll be damned!
She's dead serious!
Why not? Let her have him.
Let's see...
Since you're an amateur,
I'd better teach you an easy
foolproof trick.
Foolproof trick?
Yeah! Tell us! Tell us!
You grab the guy's head and
pull him right into your chest.
And while his tongue is
working your body up and down,
you hold him real tight
so that he can't move.
Oh, my lord!
You have such a dirty mind!
Hold him real tight and
don't let him go.
Can I really kill someone
that way?
It's perfect.
With a little help from your
chemically-altered "condition."
Oh, I see!!
I never imagined we could
use that as an advantage...
How could I have missed it!
Listen, Lou.
Just remember you're NOT
going against a mere monster.
You are killing a man -
- whom you just made love to,
however brief the encounter.
- The Prime Minister?
- Is he being executed?
What did he do?
Captain Guardsman!
What the hell are you doing
so early in the morning?
Sir, we are executing a traitor!
Traitor?
He was planning a conspiracy
against you, sir!
Conspiracy against me?
Yes, sir! That's correct!
I guess I'm not feared
as much as I used to...
Wher are Lou and Old Lady?
They should know this job
requires meticulous preparation.
Can you believe it?
Lou's going against a MAN
for the first time!
Old Lady was so excited, saying,
"This would be her true trial!"
Well, it is.
Hey, Sonya. The town square is swarming with people.
I wonder what happened.
Shall we take a look?
Hey, we know him! Making a fool
out of himself again.
Ouch! My handsome face!
Ahem!
Despite his position as
Prime Minister,
this man has conspired agains
His Majesty the Kind -
- of Dragon Kingdom,
Bad Eroheem Gibal the Second!
That's not true!
I merely expressed my wish to
remonstrate with His Majesty...
It's the same thing.
This country needs -
That's enough!
You have committed
an unforgivable crime!
I sentence you to death!
KILL HIM!
What are you waiting for?
Cowards! Give it to me!
An imminent disorder awaits
this Kingdom...
Shut up, you dead bastard!
You might silence me, but...
...your evil deeds shall meet
their just punishment!
Shut up already!!
QUIET!!
Augh! Disgusting! You shit!
If things go on this way,
this country cannot avoid
self-destruction.
DIE! DIE!
What a slime!
Kei, calm down.
I'm counting on you,
the Midnight Panther!
I've seen enough!
They just might be
the source of all evil...
The Pussycats?
Yes, sir!
They say it's the hottest
idol group right now.
I have a feeling you would
really enjoy it.
I guarantee you will!
Stop that, you ghastly old hag!
I have groomed those three women
to be the world's finest.
First, you start the evening
with some singing and dancing.
Then, when the night falls,
you're entering a dream world.
The climax is just pure heaven,
if you know what I mean...
I'll see about that.
Let them in!
With your permission!
It's show time!
Hi!
I'm Lou.
I'm Kei.
And I'm Sonya.
We are the Pussycats!
Cutie pies!
Lukish...
She looks so much like
Forget the formalities tonight!
Everybody drink up and party!
Now, come over here!
Lately, I've seen quite a few
female assassins.
So, first...
I'll have to search your body,
inside and out.
Women are much tricker
than men.
They can conceal a weapon
under these skimpy clothes.
Cutie pie!
Where are you?
You hide very well,
little pussycat.
Damn, she turns me on!
Is she here?
Or, is she...here!!
I will find you,
wherever you are!
Darn it! Why did I end up
with such a pervert?
Where are you,
my little pussy?
I ain't little AND
I ain't your pussy!
"Let's play hide and seek!"
MY ASS!!
How much longer can he
stay awake anyhow?
There's plenty more to go
around! Refill, anyone?
C'mon, drink it all up!
There's nothing like
Aqua Blue Dragon's poison -
- to make sleeping potion with!
Now, the whole castle
is fast asleep -
- except for King Bad who
retired without a drink.
Hell, I'm not worried about
that spineless non-drinker.
This job is a piece of cake!!
You know...these women
can be stripped bare.
But she could still use her hair
and nails, or anything -
- as a weapon.
One woman tried to chew off
my tongue while we kissed.
Little pussycat, I'm coming
to get you any moment!
Am I getting hot?
I can feel your presence...
Damn, I don't think he's touched Old Lady's potion at all.
This isn't going to work...
Yum, yum, yum.
I can smell my little pussycat.
I can smell her pheromone juice
excreted by Bartholin's gland.
Her fragrance is calling me!
I am so drunk - not with liquor
but with her sweet fragrance!
I found you, little pussycat!
OUCH!
Gotcha!
What the fuck?
You ruined my costume!!
I like it real rough, you see.
We can do without this, too!
Here I come!
NOOOOOOOOOO!!
Show yourself!!
It's me, Sonya.
What are you doing,
all alone and sober?
This is King Bad's bedroom,
not a playpen for your kind.
I love your eyes...
I love those cold eyes that seem
to stare into a vacuum...
Sonya...you say?
I'll have to search your cloak.
Take your time.
You're great.
You look like my brother.
I am.
Don't you recognize me?
It's me, my brother.
This kingdom only allows
male successors.
That's why my mother
brought me up as a male.
Thinking back now, I guess
she just couldn't face -
- the disgrace of seeing
the throne be passed on -
- to an illegitimate child.
Lukish...so you were alive!
And a woman, to boot!
Lukish.
Your body belongs to me!
Aw hurts.
Little pussycat?
I'm gonna come!!
Woman, you're an assassin.
The Midnight Panther...
Lukish...
You belong to me.
Do whatever you want,
my brother.
I'm all yours.
Take your time and enjoy it.
Here we go...Lukish.
I'm ready, my brother...
Lukish!
Finally, we become one!!
Poison? When did you...?
It was on your skin...!!
That's right.
I'm completely covered
in the deadly poison -
- taken from Basilisk,
the Purple Dragon.
A normal human being would
absorb the poison -
- through the skin and die,
but not me.
Do you get it?
I've traded my old pale skin
for a chance to survive.
My body also suffered
a total transformation.
Since then, I have become
immune to any poison.
Doesn't it feel awful?
You can't die fast, either.
You must suffer for my father
and my mother -
- and all the people you have
murdered until now.
This poison was made to inflict
a slow and painful death.
I can't breath!
Suffer! Suffer!
Suffer...
My brother...
Lukish...
My brother, Bad...
Hey, Sonya...
I kinda like that song now.
Let's talk about the next job.
What?! Gimme a break!
What's up with this shit again!!
Augh! I'm all slimy with mucus!!
Oh, gross!!
That was refreshing!
What's this?
Bad?!
Why are you here?
I've killed you!!
You've been calling me.
I have?!
You are keeping me from passing
onto the next world.
No way!
It's true.
You've always loved me
as long as I can remember.
Don't you want to
let me die in peace?
There's only one way!
Just this once,
you gotta let me -
- screw you!
No way!!!
Go to hell - AGAIN!!
For Pete's sake!
Gosh! Don't look!!