Damn, I'm drunk!
I'm buzzed!
There's nothing like getting
buzzed on the money -
- you swindle from
some asshole.
Am I right?
Uh-huh.
Is he trying to mug us
or something?
Not to worry. This is precisely
what you hired me for.
Oh, that's right.
My, my, what do we have here?
Are you out for a walk
at this hour.
Little Red Riding Hood..?
I'm no Little Red Riding Hood.
I am a she-panther.
Damn! Is this for real?
You creep!
Tonight...
...I will...
...love you...
...to death.
Why does this always
happen to me?!
Why do I always have to
bust my ass like this?!
Phew, I'm beat.
One...two...three...
...four...five...
...six...seven...
...eight...nine...
...and ten!!!
You scored big again
today, my dears!!
What a stud he was!
Almost too good to be wasted.
Oh, well,
because he was a priest,
I thought hanging him from
his church bell was a nice touch.
My catches were just delicious!
So fatty and juicy!
One of them was a bit stringy
and tough, though.
It's great that you enjoy
your work so much.
Why else would we do it?
Why else, indeed.
Easy for you to say...
'Cause your targets are
all humans!
Why do I always end up with
those yucky, slimy monsters?!
You never had it so tough!!
Well, Lou, that's because...
Hmm?
...you are not sexy.
You need "technique" to seduce a man to death, you know?
On the other hand, you're
blessed with physical strength.
You're built for monsters.
I'm built for monsters...
Lou, my dear...
Let me tell you something.
Did you know there was a time when dragons didn't exist?
Think about it.
Isn't that a scary thought?
Without the dragons to supply
for my poison-making,
how would I have made a living
and survived?
A little old woman like me who makes poison out of dragons -
- must depend on someone
special like you.
I understand, Old Lady.
You do?!
Hey, you're scaring me!!
You sure don't know manners.
Here!
What the hell?!
Still so green!
If you want to kill men,
you've got to stop -
- being so naive and
get used to them.
The men who have contracts on them are all scumbags, anyway.
You've got to hate them!
See? You don't understnad
a thing...
Of course, everybody hates
those scumbags.
That's exactly why we have to
send them off with some lovin'.
It's been four years already...
Huh?
Lukish...
Hey, everyone! Come on over!
Come see the traveling idol
group, the Pussycats!!
Back for the first time
in six months!
- What? The Pussycats?!
- Sonya and the girls are back?
- I've been waiting for this!!
- This is what I live for!
Drop the admission fee in here and see the Pussycats inside!
I'm Kei.
I'm Lou.
And I'm Sonya.
We are the Pussycats!
A sweet breez caresses
your heart at night.
I'll love you to death.
Let me shoot down your hear.
Tell me.
Can you feel my fingertips
when I touch you like that?
You see?
Can you feel the different
vibe from yesterday?
You don't need words to express the magic of love.
Can they rake in money
or what!?
Oh, good.
Another job order...
Not another monster!!
Hey, watch where you dribble!
Augh! What's this stuff?
It's disgusting!
Damn! How can I beat
this thing?!
I'm alive but this is gross!
Hey, stop!
That was gross but I'm alive!
Hey, I got him!!
But, wait a second...
I have to bring Old Lady his
eyeballs and gills!
What do I do now?!
There's got to be an easy way
down somewhere... Let's see...
That's the...
...Blue Dragon Castle.
I shall be the king of this
country someday.
And then...
...you will become my right hand
and my chief supporter, Lukish.
I promise, my brother, Bad!
I will always be by your side!
Lukish...
Lukish?!
Get off me!
- Oh, no!!
- Run! Hurry up!!
Help!!
Get out! Get lost NOW!
Sir Bad!!
What is going on?
It's nothing.
Get out of here.
But, sir...
Shut up!
I said, GET OUT!
Is he in a bad mood!
Does this mean I can't
achieve an orgasm -
- with a regular woman?
Lukish...
Why do I keepseeing
my brother's face in bed?
Could I be...not straight?
That's ridiculous!
Oh, no...
Oooo, Sonya, you're the best!
What's wrong?
I hate it when dragons cry.
I get a chill listening to them.
You're scared of dragons?
You're a woman after all.
I have something scarier
to tell you.
What's that?
The Midnight Panther.
The Midnight Panther...?
What's that?
Don't you know?
They're the female assassins
everybody's been talking about.
They would kill anyone and
anything for a fee.
Are they good-looking?
In the next town,
they've already killed two guys.
This is no bedroom talk...
There's a big prize
on their heads.
Women like you don't
come cheap.
I'm gonna find them...
...and bump them off myself.
Damn the Midnight Panther!
You fool... You don't have to
look too far.
There's one right in front
of your eyes!
Tired, Sonya my sister?
It's because of that
talkative jerk.
We didn't get into bed until
dawn, for God's sake.
Jeez, I'm sorry.
Anyway, where's Lou?
She's late.
Maybe she's being seduced
by a dragon -
- and can't get him off her.
That could be.
That just go me hungry.
Why don't we go ahead and
meet up with Old Lady?
She should be waiting
with some eats.
Didn't you eat the guy
from this last job?
He was a bit on a skinny side.
Besides, he had these big
nasty tendons.
Sorry to hear that.
But let's just wait
a little longer.
All right...
Get out! Get out! Get out!!
Clear the grounds!!
His Majesty the King of
Dragon Kingdom, -
- Bad Eroheem Gibal II,
has ordered -
- that this dam be demolished!
The work starts immediately!!
Does anyone dare have
any objections?
Unless you intend to help,
don't stick around.
Go ahead, be gone!!
Are they deaf of what?
Anyhow, this is a great spot
for a nice big lake -
and a water park.
This should get me on a good
side with Sir Bad...huh?
Right.
Please wait!
If you destroy the dam,
our village and our crop -
- will end up on the bottom
of the lake!
Shut up, gramps!
If we don't harvest the crop,
you'll starve to death, too.
Then, why don't you start
harvesting right now?
My god, you're merciless!
- You bastard!
- I won't stand for this!
You want mercy?
I give you till tomorrow to
harvest all the crop!
- Damn you! We are only human!
- This is outrageous!!
Stop it!
They'll get killed...
See that?
Hurry up and finish
harvesting TODAY!
Then I'll spare your lives.
Anybody who objects will
follow the same fate -
- as these three!
Get going NOW!!
What's the matter,
Chief Guardsman?
Wow! Two beauties!
Hi there, cutie pies!
Ladies, come over here!
Hey, aren't we waiting
for Lou?
Hey, Sonya!
They're leaving?
That's too bad...
Why me? Why such a mess?
I'm beat.
Kei and Sonya didn't wait
for me at our meeting spot.
I'm so tired...and hungry.
Hmm...yammy.
The chow!!
Old Lady waited for me
with my meal!
What a thoughtful gesture!
I can't eat any more!!
Why, you ate it all up
without me!!
There you are!
Finally, you're back.
You were gone so long,
I was worried sick...
Not too sick to eat,
I see!!
Forget about it! Now that
you're all together, -
- we better talk business!
Yikes! I can't argue
with that face...
Don't be silly.
C'mon! Wake up, ladies!!
What about my chow?
How nostalgic...
It's been so many years.
I found Lou beached up
on this riverbank.
Traveling performers by day,
assassins by night...
...our lifestyle
isn't exactly easy.
You ain't kiddin'.
She was so skinny, badly
injured and almost dead.
I was willing to take a few
risks to save her!
So, that's how I got to making
this very specific remedy!
First, I take the liver
of a live dragon...
- Boy, am I stuffed!
- I feel kinda sleepy...
LISTEN TO ME WHEN I TALK,
DAMN IT!
Lemme nap...
Enough with the old time.
Tell us about the new job, huh?
Oh, I forgot...
Already then!
Our next target is pretty big.
C'mon, who is it already?
You ready? The target is...
...the King of the Blue
Dragon Kingdom!!
Hey, he IS big!
Sounds yummy!!
The King of the Blue Dragon
Kingdome...?
That's right!
The King of the Blue
Dragon Kingdom...
His name is Bad Eroheem
Gibal the Second!
Let me take this job!
I want to kill him myself!!