What happened, Chizuru-san?
Nema Torazou-san has been killed
Both of his arms were cut off
What're you doing, Tomoe-san?
As always. your breasts are amazing
If you keep doing this, we won't have time
To find Morimatsu-san
I can't believe that Nema
Torazou-san was killed
You're right, we were like at first (??)
BTW Tomoe-san
What?
Could you remove your hands?
Sorry, sorry, they felt great
Don't do these things to take
advantage of Shigeno-san
She hasn't returned yet
She called saying she would
stay at Shizuto-san's house
Let's go then and see
Yes, right
But first let me enjoy this feeling again
Please stop
Stay calm
Like this Shigeno-san?
She fell asleep after mourning all night
I see.
I'll make sure to take care of Shigeno-san
You all continue the investigation
There are no tracks
I regret having you come for nothing
Where's the other girl?
She's not feeling very well
I see
For now, tell her what we've to report
Well, we'll talk later
If you find something out, let me know
I think there's something else
His arms, his arms disappeared
The man in the shop was shocked
by the disappearance of the arms
That's why had Torazou-san had tattoos
Tattoos?
Torazou-san had tattoos on both arms
He thought they would bring him good luck
People around here really believe that
There's no one sad about
the death of Torazou-san
This... We haven't found Mimaska Isue-san?
Isue-san? She was working
somewhere else yesterday
I see
Eh? Going out?
You could do what you wanted, because
you were Torazou-san's woman
But if you keep doing it...
What's with that face?
I know
If you want to go as you please...
You'll have to do what I say. Understand?
Isuzu-san
In this way, you'll be mine
From now on, you should
always have that in you
Need something?
You've been following us for awhile, right?
No, not at all
Then you're not following us?
Ah, well, there's a reason
Who asked you to do it?
Now, now calm down
What happened?
Why are you here?
Do you know her?
I'm his sister, Fanglan-san
Sister?
You have a younger sister?
Yes, this is my sister Fanglan-san
I'm the one who is caring for Tokitou-san
What do you mean?
The sensei needs treatment
We took him elsewhere
And Fanglan-san is the caregiver
If you need to contact him,
do it through Fanglan-san
Nice to meet you
If that's the case, you should
have said so before
Well, I'm very shy
Fanglan-san, you were ashamed
But I've got the impression
that I've seen you before
That's true
Not true
Then we will go as well
Sorry for saying strange things
Well done. Now I'll give you a great reward
The new priest, Kaburaki-san, seemed
like a very serious guy
That's right, and his wife was very friendly
Tomoe-san, look!
It's Mimasaka Isue-san
What's she doing?
It seems like she's crying
Let's go talk to her
Yeah, she managed to get away last time
What does this mean, Isue-san?
What's up?
It seems to be something serious
I'm not a nuisance
If money is all you want, here you go
You okay?
Hell, is this how you treat your family?
Yes, I am her mother
Her brother was brutally murdered
And she wasn't even sad about it
Wait a sec, perhaps her brother was...
His name was Reiji. The priest of
the church, Hatanaka Reiji-san
That means Hatanaka-san was her brother
I don't accept it, I won't accept it
I am a despicable woman
Even so, I love Tokitou-sama
Brother, have you been here all along?
When you were younger,
If there was something you didn't
like, you'd cry non-stop,
And when you got tired, you slept
But you'd never give up
Now matter how difficult, you'd
stay true to your ideals
I thought the same when you started
working with Tokitou-san
That's why I was a little jealous, Shigeno-san
No matter if it was a difficult situation,
You'd always come through in the end
That's why I'm proud of you, sister
You should continue with the investigation
Of course
Even in this situation, I'm a member
of the Mikagura Detective Agency
Then go
I am
It's getting late
What's with those deceptive faces? (?)
Shigeno-san!
Feeling well?
I'm perfectly fine
Changing the subject, how is Tokitou-sama?
He's in treatment now
We can go visit him
Do you want to come too, Kumiyama-san?
I'd like to talk to Morimatsu-san first
See you later
It looks like you've got what you wanted
I've got to cover each of Hayasumi-san's
Kanto managers
That's something we could
do for Torazou-san
I will not give up
I know
The guest has arrived
Why, it's Hayasumi-san
Come and say hello
Well, this looks interesting
Hayasumi Renji-san is the deputy
director of the welfare office
He has connections with many ruffians
Morimatsu-san, that's enough
In fact, he had commented to his brother
You said something?
That man is threatening my brother?
Yes, but Kumiyama-san hasn't
ceded to the pressure
As expected, it was something illegal
Certainly, my brother is so...
Hayasumi-san has recently taken
over the business of Kotora
After the death of Torazou-san,
Kumiyama-san has tried to leave to Kanto
Could it be that Hayasumi-san
murdered Torazou-san?
We have no evidence of that
How can we catch him?
However, it's clear that Kotojiro-san
of Kotora planned everything
Is this also linked to the
death of Hatanaka-san?
I'm afraid so
Hayasumi Renji-san
I see, now we know that
everything was related
It was only a matter of time to relate the
cases of Hatanaka-san and Torazou-san
We've got to finish clarifying
But don't risk too much, okay?
This could be very dangerous,
so we better not separate
Thanks a lot, but come on
Heavens
I'm going now
Good work
But I've got something else
to ask of you, Ranmaru-kun
Yes, but sensei?
What's up?
Do I have to keep using this disguise?
Well, you look pretty, so it's no problem!
Se-seriously?! Well, I'm going now
Where can I find Hayasumi-san?
I knew it! I will expose this man
If I don't, I won't be able to look
at the faces of the others
Lately everything has been very hectic
That boy's no problem Kumiyama-san
It'll be finished soon, so don't worry
Soon everything will be as
I wanted, as I've ordered
Leave it to me
Let's have some fun. Hey!
Quickly turn around and
show it to Hayasumi-san
It can't be
What's up? Do it fast
Forgive me please!
Bastards!
Just what I expected from a family
girl, it tastes completely different
Stop!
What would your brother do if he saw you?
My brother's got nothing to do with this!
Don't resist. You'll pay for
the sins of your brother
Try anything, and my brother
will never forgive you!
Your dear brother will meet you soon
Have a taste Hayasumi-san
What do you think of her ass?
Go ahead and take her once in the ass!
Brother, help me!
Her ass is so tight!
Soon, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!!!
Hey, don't you want to have
some? Won't you?
Down here seems more than ready
These siblings will meet soon in hell
Fuck!!!
Isue-san!
I'll kill you!
Tokitou-sama!
I cannot allow you to continue your crimes!
Tokitou-sama, I, I...
I know
You'd better tell us everything
in great detail, Hayasumi-san
Isue-san, you killed Torazou Nema-san,
And it was you who cut off his arms, right?
Then who killed Hatanaka-san was...
You're wrong, she didn't kill Hatanaka-san
Hatanaka-san loved her and she loved him
So who was it?
It was a suicide
But aren't priests prohibited
from committing suicide?
Yes, and for that reason
he committed suicide
Because we could never be happy
We were siblings, though we were
separated when we were young
My mother sold him to work
And I was sold to Torazou-san
Since then, life has been hell
I became Torazou-san's mistress
Everyday Torazou-san treated me like a toy
Around that time, I met my brother
Despite being siblings, we fell in love
I didn't know that he was my brother
until I read the suicide note
Torazou-san knew he was my
brother, and threatened him
But why were the arms of
Hatanaka-san cut off?
Because I didn't want anyone to
know he had committed suicide
I wanted him to be remembered
for the good person he was
And you killed Torazou-san
for revenge, right?
And you cut off his arms
Well, let's go
Take good care of your brother
Of course
Everything is concluded, right?
No. We still must discover
who is behind all of this