Tomoe-san!
What's wrong, Chizuru-chan?
Nema Torazou has been murdered,
and both of his arms were severed!
Mikagura Detective Agency
Translation: Tamesuu & akutsu | Timing: PlasticYakuza | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
What do you think you're doing, Tomoe-san!?
Your boobs are awesome.
Stop!
If you mess around like this, we'll be late to
our appointment with Inspector Morimatsu.
Tomoe-san.
Who would've thought that Nema
Torazou would be murdered.
Yeah, this puts us right back where we started.
By the way, Tomoe-san.
What?
Would you mind letting go now?
Sorry, sorry. It's just that they're so perfect.
Don't tease me just because Shigeno-san's not around.
Now that you mention it, she still hasn't come back.
I got a call saying she was staying at
her brother Shizuto-san's house.
Let's drop by later.
Good idea.
But before that,
I'll savor this feeling one more time.
Hey, please stop.
Don't resist!
– No!
– Come on.
How is Shigeno-san doing?
She cried herself to sleep.
I see.
I'll take care of her,
so you two can continue the investigation.
Okay.
We don't have any clues at the moment.
Is that so...
I'm sorry for making you come out here for nothing.
Not at all.
What happened to that other girl who was with you?
Umm... She wasn't feeling very well today.
I see.
I really wanted to talk to her about this,
but I guess I'll contact her later.
I'll let you know if we learn anything new.
Umm, there is something that's been bothering me.
His arms... His arms are gone...
The witness seemed shocked that
Torazou's arms had been cut off.
That's because of the tattoos he had.
Tattoos?
Nema Torazou had tattoos on both his arms.
They were supposed to bring him good fortune.
People around here really believe in that sort of thing.
There's no one who'd actually be
upset about Torazou's death.
What about Mimasaka Sue-san?
Sue? I heard she started working
at a different shop yesterday.
I see.
Are you going somewhere?
The reason you were free to come and go
was that you were Torazou's woman.
If you want it to stay that way...
Don't look at me like that.
I know everything.
If you want to keep your privileges,
you will obey me. Understand?
Isuzu.
What are you...
This will make you my woman.
N-No!
No!!
Make sure to keep that inside you from now on.
Do you want something?
You've been watching us for a while now.
No, I wasn't, really.
So why were you following us?
W-Well, I can explain.
Who ordered you to follow us?
Calm down.
What's going on here?
Shinbu-san!
What are you doing here?
Do you know her?
I'm his little sister Houran.
His sister?
I didn't know you had a sister.
Uh, yeah, that's right. She's my sister Houran.
I'm taking care of Tokito-san right now.
Tokito-san?
What's going on?
We've moved the detective to another
location so he can fully recover.
Houran's been looking after him in the meantime.
So if you have any messages for
Tokito, she can deliver them.
Nice to meet you all.
You should've said so sooner.
I-I was just embarrassed.
You're the shy type, huh?
You know, I get the feeling I've
seen you somewhere before.
Me too.
That can't be.
Goodbye!
We should get going too.
Shinbu-san...
Thanks for playing along.
N-No problem.
No!
Good job.
As your reward, I'll punish you
to your heart's content today.
The new priest, Kaburagi-san, seems
like a kind and dedicated person.
His wife is very nice too.
Tomoe-san, look at that.
It's Mimasaka Sue.
What's she doing here?
It looks like she's crying.
We should go and talk to her.
Yes. She got away from us last time.
What do you think you're doing, Sue?
I wonder what they're talking about.
It looks like they're arguing over something.
Does seeing me bother you that much?
If it's money you want, you can have it.
Are you all right?
How can she treat her own flesh and blood that way?
You're family?
Yes, I'm her mother.
Her older brother was brutally murdered.
I thought she'd be devastated, so I came to console her.
Wait a second. Did you just say her brother?
His name was Reiji.
Hatanaka Reiji-san. He was the priest here.
Hatanaka-san was Mimasaka Sue's brother?
I don't believe it. I won't believe it!
I'm a terrible woman.
But I still feel the same way about Tokito-sama.
Onii-sama, you've been here this whole time?
You've been the same since you were small.
When something didn't go your way,
you'd cry, cry, and cry some more.
And then you'd get tired of crying and fall asleep.
Onii-sama.
But you'd never give up.
Now matter how much you were scolded,
you did what you believed in.
You were the same way when you said
you wanted to work for Tokito-san.
I couldn't help but be envious of your persistence.
No matter what kind of problems
you encountered along the way,
you always followed through on your decisions.
I'm proud to have a sister like that.
Onii-sama...
You're going to keep investigating, right?
Of course.
I'm still a member of the Mikagura Detective Agency.
What are you waiting for?
I'll get going.
Onii-sama...
Thank you.
Houran really is late.
Why the long faces?
Shigeno-san!
Are you feeling better now?
Oh? I'm perfectly fine.
More importantly, how is Tokito-sama?
Tokito-san...
I mean, Sensei is still recovering.
We were about to go visit him.
You're coming too, aren't you?
I-I have to go see Morimatsu-san right now.
I'll join you later.
That's the expression of a man
who's obtained what he wanted.
That's right.
I've got Hayasumi-san, a government
official, covering my back.
Even Torazou couldn't get this far.
Don't throw me out.
I won't.
You have a visitor.
What a surprise, Hayasumi-san.
Come on, greet our guest.
What a welcome sight.
Hayasumi Renji, the undersecretary
for local business liaisons?
He's the poster child for selfish self-interest.
Be careful about what you say, Inspector.
I, for one, support your brother.
Actually, that's what I wanted to talk to you about.
That man is trying to get my brother demoted?
Yes, your brother is very vigilant when it comes
to other bureaucrats being involved in fraud.
That does sound like my brother.
Apparently Hayasumi's been seen at Kotora a lot lately.
It seems that since Torazou died,
he's been especially persistent about getting
your brother dismissed from his office.
Could Hayasumi be the one who murdered Torazou?
We don't have any proof.
If we did, we'd have arrested him.
But we do know that he's teamed
up with Kotojiro from Kotora,
and that they're now plotting something together.
Is that related to Hatanaka-san's murder?
Probably.
Hayasumi Renji...
I see. Now everything is starting to make sense.
It's only a matter of time before Hatanaka
and Torazou's murders are solved.
Have another go at it,
but be careful.
Of course!
This is a bad neighborhood, so stay close to me.
We're counting on you. Let's head out.
Jeez.
See you later!
Umm...
Y-You've done great.
I've got one more job for you, Ranmaru-kun.
Sure thing, Sensei. There's just one small matter...
What is it?
Do I really need to cross-dress?
You look cute like that, so what's the harm?
I-I guess you're right. I'm off then!
See ya!
Kantou Government Office
Where can I find Hayasumi-san?
Hayasumi-san, right?
I knew it.
I'm going to expose this man.
If I don't, I won't be able to face them again.
There's been a lot of interest in this place lately.
Kumiyama and the girls aren't a problem.
I'll take care of them right away.
There's no need to worry.
I knew I could depend on you.
Let's make this a lasting relationship.
Leave it to me.
Enjoy yourself today.
Hey!
Hurry up and show Hayasumi-san.
No way. That's gross.
What's wrong? Get on with it!
Please let me go.
How could they...
No!
I can tell by the taste that she
comes from a good household.
Stop it!
What would your brother think if he saw you like this?
Leave my brother out of this!
Don't act tough. Your brother brought
it on himself by being too righteous.
If you do anything to my brother, I'll, never forgive you!
I'll let you see how your precious brother
becomes an outcast of society.
Onii-san.
– Let's leave the chatting at that and move on.
– No!
So you prefer the tighter hole.
Give her a taste of that thick dick of yours.
No! Don't do it!
Onii-sama...
Save me, Onii-sama!
Onii-san...
A lady's a lot tighter than your common tramp.
I'm gonna cum already.
I'm shooting it inside!
Do you want a go at her, too?
May I?
She's ready for you up front.
No! Stop!
I'll send both you and your brother to hell.
You... bitch...
Sue-san...
Sue-san!
I'll kill you!
Don't do it!
Tokito-sama!
It's all over.
Tokito-sama! I... I...
I know.
Hayasumi-san, we'll need you to explain
yourself at the police station.
Sue-san. Were you the one who killed Torazou,
and cut off his arms?
Yes.
So the one who killed Hatanaka-san...
That wasn't her.
Sue wouldn't kill Hatanaka-san.
She was in love with Hatanaka-san, and he with her.
Then who did it?
He committed suicide.
But doesn't Christianity forbid suicide?
That's correct. And that's exactly why he did it.
To make sure he didn't receive God's blessing.
We were separated from each
other when we were children.
When my brother was old enough
to work, my mother sold him off.
And later, she sold me to Torazou.
That's when my life turned into a living hell.
Torazou made me his mistress.
He treated me like a sex toy, day after day.
It was around that time that I found my brother.
My brother and I fell in love without
realizing we were siblings.
I learned he was my brother from the suicide
note he left after slitting his own throat.
Torazou was the one who told my brother.
He was using that information to blackmail my brother.
Then why did you cut off Hatanaka-san's arms?
I didn't want everyone to know
that he committed suicide.
I wanted people to remember
him as a righteous person.
Then you killed Torazou and
cut off his arms for revenge.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
Cherish your brother.
Of course I will.
This means it's finally over.
No.
There's still the man who's been pulling all the strings.
hoshi no tame nara then you mou sorenai
If the stars have decided it then I can't avoid you.
nani mo kurenai anata no hitomi
Your eyes give nothing away.
kurakura suru youna koi ni inochi wo kezuri
A dizzying love whittles away at my life.
ato to kara no kuro ni houhou yosete memorii
I store my confused memories in the
blackness of scars and my shell.
hai no tamago no nani mo kowakunai
There's nothing to be afraid of in an egg of ash.
dare mo mienai anata no kokoro
No one can see your heart.
furafura suru youna koi ni inochi wo azuke
I give my life to a dizzying love.
awatadashii watashi donna toboke iru ka
Flustered as I am am I deluding myself?