I can't take it anymore. Put it inside me!
Hurry! I don't care who it is!
This man's no good. Please...
Anyone... Anyone is fine, so please...
Begin the ritual.
Please... Stick it inside me.
No, don't stall, just stick it in.
Please, I'm losing my mind!
Yes, that's the way.
Your sins will be forgiven this way.
That woman is a devil that took the shape of a person.
Now finish it, of your own free will.
Mikagura Detective Agency
Translation: Tamesuu & akutsu | Timing: PlasticYakuza | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Shrike
Detective!
Hello there. What are you ladies doing here?
Tokito-san sent us to investigate.
He thinks Tokiwa Shougo is involved in all this.
I see.
It's not a pleasant sight, but I
suppose you'll want to see it.
Yes, please.
How cruel.
It looks like she was impaled
after being strangled to death.
Who could do this?
What about that word "shrike" on her stomach?
We have no idea at this point.
I can't forgive someone who'd do something so cruel.
I feel the same way.
Unless we find the culprit quickly,
there will be another victim.
Are you ladies going to help us?
Yes.
I'm counting on you, then.
Akane!
Tomoe-san!
You're looking a lot better.
I am. I'm working here as a waitress now.
I see! So this place has become a normal restaurant?
Yes.
By the way, do you know what a shrike is?
A shrike?
No, I don't know.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you.
No, don't worry about it. I'll see you later.
Take care!
No! Please stop!
It seems to have a strong effect on you.
She'll be a good bait.
Do whatever you want with her.
Excuse me. Please let us through!
Calm down!
Where is Akane?
Akane!
It can't be. Just when she was doing so well...
This is unforgivable. I will find them!
You don't need to worry about that.
We already know who the culprit is.
A witness saw a man fleeing from the scene.
Kawaba's heading there now.
Kawaba! Good job.
He didn't even put up a fight. It was an easy catch.
That's the mimic.
Yes, his name's Gonzo.
People say the shrike is good at mimicry.
He probably wrote that word on the corpse
as a hint that he was responsible.
When I saw that word, of course
I immediately knew it was him.
He confessed, too. He admitted killing two women.
God... told me to do it.
Shinbu-san.
Shinbu's not here.
He hasn't been around for several days.
Is that so.
Did you need something from him?
No, it's just that I hadn't seen him in
a while, and I was getting worried.
Wait.
What is it?
Are you going to see Mikagura-sensei now?
Y-Yes.
Take this.
What is it?
It's smelling salts. There will probably
be opium fumes where you're going.
Someone who has no tolerance to opium
will be very susceptible to its effects.
If you start to hallucinate, sniff that,
and get out of there right away.
I'll do that! Thank you very much!
This isn't a very good shower.
Maybe I should've stayed with my brother after all.
But I couldn't just leave her like this.
Cheer up. It's not like you to get so depressed.
You're late. I was worried.
I'm sorry. I had to take care of something.
Do you really think Gonzo is the culprit?
What do you mean?
I did some research or him.
He's good at mimicry, but he's not educated.
He doesn't know how to write.
But "shrike" was written on the bodies.
Someone else wrote it.
In other words, you think that
the culprit is someone else?
Yes.
He won't get away with it.
He blamed his crime on someone else and
is walking around carefree as can be!
I swear I'll catch him!
But what should we do?
We're going to use bait.
Bait?
The culprit will repeat his crime.
If someone hangs around where he's likely to appear,
he'll fall for the bait.
Who should do it?
Me, of course!
Uh, what's with that look?
There's no way you could do it.
What are you implying?
The murderer only targets beautiful women.
You don't fit the role.
I'll step forward and...
You're so flat-chested that at night,
he'd mistake you for a man!
What did you say!?
You know it's true!
Stop it, you two.
I know. Let's decide the matter fairly by drawing lots.
Okay? Let's do it.
No hard feelings for whoever gets it.
What? Me?
Will she be all right? Maybe I should've gone.
I already told you that you don't fit the role.
Why?
Behind you!
Dammit!
Chizuru-chan!
Let her go!
Shigeno-san.
Chizuru-chan...
What's going on over there?
Are you all right?
Tokito-san.
I'm sorry.
There's no point in moping because of
something that's already happened.
Right now, we have to focus on rescuing her.
You're right.
Houran-chan.
Y-Yes?
Go to Shinbu-san and ask him to
help us look for Chizuru-chan.
Well, the thing is, Shinbu-san...
I mean, my brother, hasn't been around in days.
He hasn't been home?
He'll be fine. Now let's get going.
Where?
To the place where Gonzo said God
told him to commit his crimes.
Where am I?
Oh no, this smell is...
My body feels... hot!
Shinbu-san!
No!
No! Stop!
Shinbu-san, snap out of it! Don't you recognize me?
Shinbu-san!
What am I...
I'm so glad. You've regained your senses.
I... I...
It's okay. Calm down.
But...
What's wrong?
My body won't stop throbbing.
If I leave it like this, it'll feel painful for you, too.
If you touch me right now...
You still have more, don't you?
Are you all right? Get a hold of...
You don't want to?
No, it's not that.
What a relief.
Did that feel good?
Please make me feel good too.
That feels so good!
Shinbu-san!
I'm cumming!
Shinbu-san.
Are you all right?
I'm still a little giddy, but I'll be okay.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for it to be this way.
Don't worry. I'm glad it was you.
A-Anyway, we have to get out of here.
My friends will definitely find this place.
Let's wait for them here.
Okay. I promise I'll protect you.
I know you will.
Have you come to confess?
Yes.
Then confess your sins and pray to God.
I'm not the one who'll be confessing to his crimes.
You will.
You used Gonzo to kill your wife, Chizue-san,
and Kuramoto Akane-san, didn't you?
Why? Why would you do those things?
It's that woman's fault! It's all her fault!
Yes! That's good.
Yes! Shove it into me!
Yes! I'm cumming!
What are you doing!?
You can see for yourself.
You...
What? Do you have something to say?
You don't?
Not that you have any right to
complain in the first place.
You're not even capable of doing
what makes me happy.
Does it bother you?
If it does, you should make that useless
thing between your legs work.
If you can do that, I'll take you right here.
But that will never happen.
I wanted to kill her, but I couldn't.
Then I heard that man's voice.
"If you can't do it yourself, make someone else do it."
It was easy to plant the idea of killing
my wife into that dimwit, Gonzo.
"That woman is the devil. That's
why she sleeps with you."
"But at this rate, you'll be possessed by a devil, too."
That's all I had to say.
I wrote "shrike" on the corpses to hint that
Gonzo was responsible and cause his arrest.
I impaled her because my desire for
revenge overpowered my love for her.
But as I was impaling her body,
something unbelievable happened!
My useless dick was revived!
I couldn't forget that feeling, so I...
You used Gonzo to kill Akane!
I didn't care who it was. It could have been anyone.
That's terrible!
Kaburagi-san, it couldn't have been just anyone.
A man taught you how to kill.
His name is Tokiwa Shougo. Where is he now?
Tokito-san.
Is this...
Yes, it looks like a passage that leads
to Tokiwa Shougo's hideout.
Let's go!
It'll be extremely dangerous from here on.
I have to go anyway, for Akane's sake.
And I can't leave you alone.
Let's go, then.
Shigeno-san and Houran,
please stay with Morimatsu-san.
Tokito-sama, please be careful.
Who'd have thought there was
a cave like this underground.
Let's keep going.
What is this?
What the...
Welcome.
Tokiwa Shougo!
It's been a while.
I didn't think we'd meet again.
But now that you're here...
You can't get away!
Give yourself up!
Enjoy yourselves.
He's got us!
Is it kicking in?
It's not a taste you can easily forget.
Ouch...
No!
No! Don't!
No! Stop!
Stop it!
Let's have some fun.
Please...
Please let me go!
How does it feel to watch the person you love
being raped, while being raped yourself?
Isn't it wonderful?
It's about time to wrap things up.
It hurts... Someone, please...
Akane...
Tomoe-san, you're just like me.
Like you?
You were sold off too, weren't you?
Sold? I wasn't...
But you're having the same things
done to you that they did to me.
Tomoe-san, you were sold off.
Sold...
We can't keep living like this.
We don't have any choice but to sell Tomoe.
You're right. We have to sell her.
No! I don't want to!
I have to work! If I don't work, they'll sell me off!
Tokito-san, help me! Tokito-san!
It's useless. Nobody will come to save you.
That's how it was for me.
You're the only one you can depend on.
You have to defend yourself.
I'm sure you can do it!
Akane...
If you kill him, everything will turn out fine.
Tomoe-kun!
I'm passing out.
Once a person's been hypnotized, it's easy
to make them re-enter a hypnotic state,
although it didn't work last time.
Now kill the man in front of you and free yourself.
Tomoe-san! Snap out of it!
– Get a hold of yourself, Tomoe-san!
– Are you okay?
– Have some of this.
– Snap out of it!
That hurts you know!
Do you have any idea what you were about to do?
But let's not talk about that.
It's over! Give up!
This keeps getting more interesting.
I'll just finish all of you together.
Tokito-san!
Die, Mikagura Tokito!
Farewell.
Tomoe-kun!
Tokiwa Shougo!
It's over, Tokiwa Shougo!
We've sealed off all of your escape routes.
You have nowhere to run.
I've lost this time.
Mikagura Tokito. This was a fun game.
Is it... over?
Yes. Now he'll pay for all of his crimes.
Let's go back to Japan.
Yeah.
We're finally going back to Japan!
Houran, you're coming too?
Shigeno-san?
You really didn't notice?
Umm, I'm actually Ranmaru.
She didn't notice.
H-How could you say that? Of course I noticed.
Let's go, Tokito-san.
Have a safe trip.
Thank you for everything.
Take care, Shakuryuu-san.
Shinbu-san, thank you for everything.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
I'll remember you and your
friends for the rest of my life.
You two seem very close.
Maybe you should stay here.
Stop teasing me.
Geez, Shigeno-san...
We should get going.
Okay.
anata ni todoke watashi no kokoro
I send my heart to you.
kanashii yoru wa hitori namida ga ko to ko to ko
On a sorrowful night, alone, my tears go drip, drop, drip, drop.
anata ni todoke watashi no kokoro
I send my heart to you.
shizukana yoru ni hikaru tobira no oto oto oto oto
On a quiet night, the sound of a door –
the sound, the sound, the sound, the sound!
Good morning!
Good morning.
It's only morning, and you're already so noisy.
Has your wound healed?
Yeah, I'm better than ever.
Tomoe-kun, a new job has come in.
Will you come with us?
Yes, Tokito-san!