Those times were very happy
But why did it end?
Professor, where are you?
What's up with you, Kanase-san?
Why do you cry? If your only
asset is always being happy...
I am not crying!
Furthermore, what do you mean
my only quality is to be happy?
It goes, you stopped mourning
and are now angry.
I told you I wasn't crying!
Okay, okay girls calm down
We came on this trip to look for sensei
For that reason, let's not fight now
True.
I received a letter from Oniisama
stating she got a job with the civil
administration of Manchuria.
Moreover, she said that there
we could find Tokitou-sama
And you could come as
an extra, Kanase-san
Who the hell is an extra?
Who paid for this trip?
Enough!
If we continue to fight, we won't find sensei
If the sensei has been imprisoned, or is ill...
What'll we do?
We must find and avenge Tokitou-sama
You're right, so we must find
sensei as fast as possible
That's right
Let's do it
That girl?
She was on the boat
Who was that?
They didn't seem to be familiar
She was surely sold
It's good that you all came,
you must be tired
We're fine
More importantly, where is Tokitou-sama?
Always in such a hurry
For now please accompany
me, and talk in the car
A church?
Here we will find Tokitou-sama, no?
Yes, though its no sure thing
Lost among so many people
Did you talk to the people there?
Many told me knew nothing
Apparently there's some sort of secret
I think so
Therefore I sent the letter to Shigeno-san
We'll find Tokitou-sama
There's enough people
I'll go ask them
It's rare to have visitors. Are you Japanese?
What're you doing here?
We always come here to
ask for accommodations
But it seems that today it's closed
There's no one?
That's a problem
We wanted to talk to the people here
When this happens, do you pray?
Isuzu-san's doors are closed
Excuse me, we'd like to talk to the manager
That's no problem. Wait one moment
I'll go in. Please wait a moment and see
How awful
So, you are the detectives
from the Mikagura agency
If so, no problem...
We're short-staffed
Morimatsu-san, you can't say that
It's okay, Kawaba-san
They will be of great help
Well, I leave it in your hands
Who was the victim?
His name was Hatanaka Reiji
He was a very serious person who
had no problems with neighbors
But to have been killed in this way,
must have been hiding something
That's right
Perhaps because of this secret... sensei
is missing
But in truth, this is well?
Although you're members of the Mikagura
agency, here is very different
from the capital
There are many places that are
too dangerous for girls like you
We'll be fine
If we leave we will not be able
to find Tokitou-sama
I'll do everything possible to help
But be very careful
Kotora? Refers to this property?
It's the name of a part of the organization
owned by a man named Nema Torazou
Yes, my name is Nema Torazou
This, of what we were talking before...
It's true, it was I who wanted
to buy their land
But I was not the one who killed him
If he died he could not negotiate
the sale of the land
By the way, for detectives
you are quite beautiful
Especially your girl that you're a family (?)
I won't keep listening
We're leaving
Then she...
It's nothing. Let's hurry up to Shigeno-san
No, please stop this!
Hey, you're not wet
Master, you are very rude
Leave it to me
So cute
How are you down here?
No, please stop!
Starting to like this, right?
Do you want more?
You like me touching here, right?
I beg you, forgive me please
You're sensitive. It'll feel much better
I think you're pretty wet
Already this wet
Now you'll feel much better
Apparently already used to it
As always, the girls are the best
Come on, do it properly
Quite good. Kotojiro-san, immediately
set her to work
Those detectives are going to be a nuisance
for our plans for this area
Let the women take charge of that
I understand, we'll punish them
until they do what you say
Good evening. Where's Kanase-san?
Tomoe-san's taking a shower,
and seemed very happy
I'll keep working
Well, where to start?
So far Nema Torazou is the prime suspect
That kind of guy...
Although he wouldn't mind killing someone
I agree with you
We need someone to blame, and he's the
only one the victim had problems with
But apparently there was someone
else in the church, I think
Find out anything?
A woman named Mimasaka lsue
was often at the church
But no one was seen that night
I think it could have been
a lovers' rendezvous
Are you saying that she had a
relationship with the priest?
He was also a man
You sound like you know so much
But the truth is you do not have
experience in relationships
What's that?! You and I are
equal Kumiyama-san!
I've always loved just Tokitou-sama
Isn't that the same as having
no experience then?
I am different from you!
Are not!
Girls, enough!
BTW, some people have seen sensei
Seriously?!
Someone from the library said so
Does that mean that if we go there,
we can find the sensei?
Well, see... We don't know
if we're allowed there
But if we hope a little insurance to find it
Just when I thought we had the sensei found
But now we know he's in this city
If we continue this case, we're
sure to find Tokitou-sama
Thats right... Well, now what to do?
We confirm that Mimasaka Isue
was at church that night
We don't know if Hatanaka was involved
So we must find the culprit
You look very good Izusu
You like that? You're soaked
You understand? The deal for
the land, and it's closed
According to my research, yes
Let's move
Who're you guys?
Don't move!
Stay away!
No, let go!
Enough!
No, stop
No, anything but that!
You... saved us
Thanks for saving us
It's dangerous here. Get out
and don't come back
Do you know a Mikagura-sensei?
You know Tokitou-sama?
He saved my life
Where's sensei now?
I've not seen him lately
We came from Japan to look for him
We know he's been seen near a church
But we have not seen him
What's that?
Follow me!
I see, you're seeking the Mikagura-sensei
My name is Liu Shakuryu
This is my son Zhenwu
If we help you to seek, we'll find him quickly
I hate the Japanese, but this is different
I find no faults, so no worries
Excuse me, is it ok if we
are also going to look?
There are many sites that you can't enter
Go back to your hotel and wait for our call
So slow! I'm worried if I'll
see Shakuryu-san again
Don't do that Tomoe-san
We promised we would
wait for him at our hotel
I trust them, hopefully a little more
We found him
Don't tell me... that sensei is dead
No, but it's pretty bad
Come with me
What is this place?
Is sensei in a place like this?
Over here
In here
There...
Please resist, sensei
Sensei, do you recognize me?
Oh no...
I can't believe it
I won't believe it!
Tomoe-san, care for sensei
This is my room, take all the time you need
Sensei, what's wrong? Are you in pain?
No, sensei, don't smoke more opium!
Please resist!
Sensei, stop!
No, sensei, stop
Don't worry, I'll take care of everything
I'm cumming!!!
This is...
I did this!!!
Don't go
Tomoe-san, we've got problems!
What's up, Chizuru-san? I'm busy
Nema Torazou has been killed
Both arms were cut off