I can't stand it anymore, do it faster!
I don't care who it is!
I don't want to go without it, please!
Whoever, whatever is fine, please!
It's time to begin the ritual
Please, give it to me!
Don't play with me, just give it to me!
Please, rape me!
Yeah, that's it
So you cast your sins
This woman is the Devil in human form
Well, let's rid us of her evil
Detective!
What do you girls want?
Tokitou-san asked that we investigate
He still thinks that Tokiwa
Shogo is behind all of this
I see. I have no problem, go ahead
Yes, thanks
How cruel!
Apparently, the cause of death was
strangulation, followed by the pole insertion
How horrible!
What's the signifigance of "Motsu"?
Don't know. But we're investigating
Inexcusable! How could someone
do something like this?!
You're right, if we don't quickly
find the culprit...
There may soon be another victim
Do you need our help?
Well, we'll count on you
Akane!
Tomoe-san
You're looking good
Yes, I'm now working at this place
I see, this is a common everyday inn, no?
BTW, do you know what "Motsu" means?
"Motsu?"
I don't know
I feel like I haven't been helpful
No worries, thanks. See ya
Take care
No, please stop!
Just a little was enough
Excellent bait!
Ask your child what she wants
So sorry! Move, please!
Calm down
Where is Akane?
Akane!
It can't be, when she was finally happy
I can't forgive this, I will find you without fail!
You don't have to worry.
We've found the culprit
Kawaba-san followed the man who left
the body in the river and I caugh him
Good work Kawaba-san!
He didn't resist arrest, so it was easy
It's that imitator from the fair
His name is Gonzo
He does a great imitation of the Motsu bird,
That would explain why he drew
"Motsu" on the bodies
When I saw him, I knew he was the culprit
He declared his guilt
Of the murders of the two women
I did what God told me to do
Zhenwu-san
Zhenwu-san isn't here
He hasn't returned for several days
I see.
What do you need?
No, I haven't seen him in several
days, so I was worried
Wait
Are you going where Mikagura-sensei is?
Take this
What's this?
It's special powder that neutralizes
the effects of opium. Because someone
is using it as a weapon
For most people the opium
causes hallucinations
If you start to hallucinate, use it
and walk away fast from there
Okay, thanks a lot!
I knew a shower wouldn't be enough,
I should have gone to Onii-sama
But I couldn't just leave her alone
We're animated, so being so depressed
is not normal for you
You're so late, I was worried
Sorry, there was something
that I had to find out
Does Gonzo really seem like
the kind of guy to blame?
Say what?
I was looking into that Gonzo
He was good at imitating things, not creating
them, so I don't think it was him
But the bodies had "Motsu" written on them
There must be someone else
who wrote "Motsu" on them
In other words, the criminal is someone else
I'll never forgive him! I won't
let these criminals get away!
I'm going to get you!
But what'll we do?
We'll use some bait
Bait?! Bait?!
The culprit will probably attack again!
It should be safe to get him if you wait
near the scenes of the crimes!
And who will?
I will, of course
Huh?
So how can you do that, Kanase-san?
What do you mean?!
The criminal attacks only beautiful girls
And you don't fit that profile
So it should be me who...
With your flat chest and the darkness,
he's bound to think you're a man
Say what?!
I speak the truth!
Girls, calm down
I know, let's have a lottery
to see who'll go, okay?
Let's do that?
Well, without records, yes?
M-Me?
Will she be alright? I should have gone
But I told you that you aren't
attractive enough
Say what?!
Behind you!
Damn it!
Chizuru-chan!
Let Chizuru-chan go!
S-Shigeno-san
Chizuru-chan
They're over there!
Are you alright?
Tokitou-san
I'm sorry
We can't lament what happened
with Sugita-san
Now we must concentrate on her rescue
Fanglan-chan
Ask Zhenwu-san to look for Chizuru-chan!
Is that Zhenwu-san... No, my brother
hasn't returned home in three days
He hasn't returned?
That's fine, let's go
But, where?
To see where Gonzo said he talked to God
That's where we'll go
Where am I?
That smell! It can't be!
My body is... heating up
Zhenwu-san!
No, stop!
Zhenwu-san, resist! Don't
you recognize me?!
Good, you woke up
I... I...
Okay, please calm down
But...
What's going on?
I can't control my body
Being like this must be very
painful, right Zhenwu-san?
If you keep rubbing it like that...
It's still hard
Is this okay? Won't resist?
Don't you want this?
It's... not that
That's good
Do you like? Make me feel good too, please!
Zhenwu-san!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Are you okay?
I'm still a bit dazed, but I'm fine
I'm sorry I've done something so...
Don't worry, I didn't mind doing it with you
An-Anyway, we've got to get out of here
My friends are probably on their way,
so let's wait here until they arrive
I understand, until then I'll protect you
I trust you
Are you here to confess?
Then confess your sins, and
pray for God's forgiveness
I'm not the one to confess any
sins. How about you?!
You're the one who used Gonzo-san
to kill your wife Shisue-san
and Kuramoto Akane-san
Why?! Why did you do it?!
That woman was guilty, it was all her fault!
Yes, that's nice!
Yes, give me more, harder!
Yes, I'm cumming!
What the hell are you doing?!
Exactly what it looks like!
YOU!!!
What, got a problem? Didn't think so
Also, you're not the one to complain
No matter what you do, you can't satisfy me
Does that upset you?
If it bothers you, why not you
use that shit you've got?
If that's your goal, put it here
Although, that's impossible
I wanted to kill my wife, but I couldn't
And then I listened to the voice of this man
If you can't do it, let someone
else do it for you
If you make Gonzo-san go out of his mind,
killing your wife would be easy
That woman is a devil, that's
why you should do it
But if you go through with
it, you'll also be a demon
But if you do as I say, you'll be fine
I wrote "Motsu" to incriminate Gonzo
so he would be arrested
While writing it, I felt better,
because I had my revenge
But putting the spike in Shisue-san's
body made me feel good
After doing that, I felt liberated
After that, I couldn't forget that feeling, so...
You used Gonzo-san to kill
Akane-san, didn't you?
I didn't care who it was, that didn't matter
How horrible!
Kaburagi-san, that's a lie, isn't it?
Somebody told you to assassinate them
Tell me, where is Tokiwa Shogo?
Tokitou-san
This is...
Yes, this is a passage that leads to
Tokiwa Shogo's secret hideout
Then let's go!
Moving forward could be very dangerous
Even so I must go, for Akane-san's sake!
I cannot let you go alone, Tokitou-san
Then, let's go
Shigeno-san and Fanglan-chan
can stay with Morimatsu-san
Be careful, Tokitou-sama
I didn't think this cave would be so deep
Let's go
This is?
What is this?
Welcome
Tokiwa Shogo!
It's been awhile
We meet again
I welcome you
You can't escape! Surrender!
You'll enjoy this
This shit is opium!
Did you notice? You've tried something
you won't soon forget
No, stop, no!
Let's have some fun
Please, let me go!
Your beloved is being raped in
front of you... Isn't this fun?
It's time to end this
It hurts, somebody...
Akane
You're just like me, Tomoe-san
Like you?
Because you've also been sold, right?
Sold? You're wrong
But you're doing the same thing as me
You've been sold, Tomoe-san
I was sold
If we continue like this, we won't survive
We've no choice but to sell Tomoe
That's right, we'll sell her
No, I don't want this!
I won't work, if I'm sold, I won't work!
Save me Tokitou-san! Tokitou-san!
It's useless, nobody will come to save you
That was my fate
You can only rely on yourself,
and protect yourself alone
You can do it, Tomoe-san
Akane
If you kill him, everything will be alright
Tomoe-kun!
My mind is...
Once someone has been hypnotized,
it's very easy to do it again
It never fails
Come on, kill this man in
front of you and be free!
Tomoe-san, wake up!
Wake up, Tomoe-san!
Are you okay?
Use this, sensei
I told you to wake up
That hurts! What the hell are you doing?!
Heavens, don't you know
what you were doing?
We'll deal with that later
Not so fast, surrender at once!
I was having so much fun, but now
I'll finish it with my own hands
Tokitou-san!
Die, Mikagura Tokitou!
Good riddance
Tomoe-kun!
Tokiwa Shogo!
Stop there, Tokiwa Shogo!
We've blocked all of your escape routes
There's no escape for you!
This time, I've been defeated
It was a pretty fun game, Mikagura Tokitou
It's finished, right?
Yes, I will ensure that he pays
for his crimes, I swear it!
Let's head back to Japan
We're finally going back to Japan?
Fanglan, you're coming to Japan too?
Shigeno-san?
Didn't you notice?
It's me, Ranmaru
She hadn't noticed
S-Sure, of course I had noticed!
Well, shall we go Tokitou-san?
Take care
Thanks a lot, for all of your help
Take care, Shakuryu-san
Thank you for all of your help, Zhenwu-san
No, thank you
I'll never forget you Chizuru-san,
or Mikagura-sensei
They get along well!
Don't you want to stay here?
Please don't make fun of me
Jeez, Shigeno-san!
Well, now's the time to go
Yes. Yes. Yes
Good morning!
Little early to be scandalous, eh?
Your wounds are already healed?
Yes! I feel perfect!
Tomoe-kun, we have a new case.
Will you come with me?
Sure, Tokitou-san!