Mikagura Detective Agency
Translation: Tamesuu & akutsu | Timing: PlasticYakuza | Editing: Collectr | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Those were the good times.
Why did it have to turn out like that?
I wonder where Sensei ran off to.
What's going on, Kanase-san?
Optimism's supposed to be your one redeeming
feature, and here you are shedding tears.
I'm not crying!
And what's that about optimism being
my only redeeming feature?
Wow, straight from tears to anger
with nothing in between!
I said I wasn't crying!
Calm down, you two.
Since we're all crossing the ocean to look for Sensei,
we shouldn't fight with each other.
You're absolutely right!
And it was my brother, the government official
in Manchuria, who sent me that letter.
the one saying that someone had seen
Detective Mikagura Tokito there.
In other words, you two are just tagging along.
Who's tagging along?
Do I have to remind you that I paid for this trip?
Just let it go.
If we fight among ourselves, it'll just
take us longer to find Sensei.
Tokiwa Shougo, who headed the League of the Bizarre,
and whom Sensei sent to jail, has escaped.
If you think about it...
...he'll try to get revenge on the
person who imprisoned him.
Exactly. That's why we have to let Sensei
know about it as soon as possible.
You're right.
All right, let's do it!
Look at that girl.
She was on the ship with us.
It's Akane.
Who was that man?
He didn't look like her father.
That girl's probably been sold to him.
Shigeno!
Onii-sama!
I'm glad to see all of you. I'm sure you're tired.
We're fine.
More importantly, where's Tokito-sama?
You really get to the point quickly.
Let's talk in the car.
Thank you.
A chapel?
That's where you saw Tokito-sama?
Yes, I hurried to follow him,
but I lost him in the crowd.
Did you talk to the other people who were around?
I tried, but everyone claimed ignorance.
Someone must be hiding something.
I felt the same way.
That's why I sent that letter to Shigeno.
Thank you, Onii-sama.
You've done more than enough.
Now it's our turn to find him.
It seems like some people have gathered here.
I'll try talking to them.
Excuse me!
You're a rare kind of visitor. Are you Japanese?
Yes.
May I ask why everyone's standing out here?
They always let us use this place for our gatherings.
But for some reason, it isn't open today.
So there's no one inside?
That's unfortunate.
We wanted to talk to the person in charge.
Is something wrong?
Isude-san, the door won't open.
How strange. Is it locked?
Excuse me. We'd like to speak
to the person in charge here.
Of course, that's not a problem.
Please wait here for a moment.
I'll go take a look around, so please wait here.
Are you all right?
How terrible.
You're from the famous Mikagura Detective Agency?
If that's the case, I'll gladly accept your help.
We're short on people anyway.
Morimatsu-san!
You can't make that decision by yourself.
Why not, Kawaba?
It's worth it if they can help speed up the search.
So that's how it's going to be. Good luck.
Thank you.
Do you know anything about the murder victim?
His name was Hatanaka Reiji.
He was a serious, earnest man who had a good
reputation with the people in the neighborhood.
But judging by how brutally he was murdered,
he must've been hiding something.
I agree.
And Sensei might be involved in that secret as well.
Will you really be all right?
You may be members of the
Mikagura Detective Agency,
but this place isn't like the Imperial capital.
Many places here are dangerous
for unaccompanied girls.
I don't mind.
As long as we're actively searching,
we might bump into Tokito-sama.
All right.
I'll help you as much as I can.
Just be careful.
Kotora?
So you're saying he was pressured to sell that land?
Yes, by the man who runs the high-end
Japanese restaurant called Kotora.
His name is Nema Torazou.
Kotora. Nema Torazou.
Welcome.
I'm Nema Torazou.
U-Umm, back to what we were
talking about a minute ago...
Yeah, it's true I asked him to sell
me his land, but I didn't kill him.
After all, you can't negotiate with a dead man.
On a different note, all three of you
are too pretty to be detectives.
Especially you. You're a lady from
some rich family, aren't you?
I don't have anything else to ask you!
Let's go.
Shigeno-san...
Wait up.
Akane...
That girl... I knew it.
What's wrong, Tomoe-san?
N-Nothing. Let's catch up to Shigeno-san.
Tomoe-san...
No! Please stop!
Ouch!
She's not getting wet.
You're too rough.
Let me handle this.
No!
You have cute breasts.
What about down here?
Stop! No. Don't!
That felt good, didn't it? And this will feel even better.
You see? You really feel it when
I play with you down here.
No...
Please, I beg of you. Let me go.
So you admit you're feeling good.
That's good. Enjoy it.
Look at how wet you are.
You're more than wet enough.
She's ready for you.
What's coming next will feel even better.
No...
She seems to be getting used to it.
The girls Seiichi brings me are always great.
No!
Come on, serve him properly.
Lick it.
This girl is quite a find.
Kotoshido, pay Seiichi the usual amount.
That nosy detective looking into
the land finally disappeared,
and things were starting to go well.
But now we've got trouble again.
Before this gets out of hand, go to
that woman you've been training,
and get the land rights from her.
As you wish.
If I punish her enough, she'll do anything I ask.
Welcome back.
Where's Kanase-san?
She's in the shower. She's really taken a liking to it.
Ah, welcome back.
I guess we should get some work done.
So where should we start?
Nema Torazou is the most suspicious at this point.
I agree completely.
He's a vulgar excuse for a man.
I'm sure he'd murder someone
without a second thought.
I don't think we should jump to conclusions so quickly.
It's true he's the only one who seemed
to have a grudge against the victim.
There's actually someone else I find
suspicious, but I don't know if it's related.
Did you discover something?
A woman named Mimasaka Sue
apparently went to the chapel often.
She always picked times when no
one was around, like late at night.
There were rumors she was
having an affair with the priest.
That can't be! A priest devotes his life to God!
A man will always be a man.
Wow, you sure sound like you
know what you're talking about,
even though you have no experience to draw on.
Right back at you, Kumiyama-san!
Tokito-sama is the only one for me.
In other words, you don't have any
romantic experience either.
I'm not like you!
What exactly is different?
Please stop it, you two.
By the way, apparently someone who looked
like Sensei stopped by the chapel before.
Really!?
Yes. Based on the description, I think it was him.
So if we hang around there, we'll be able to meet him?
I'm not sure about that.
From what I was told, he used to visit the chapel often.
but nobody has seen him for a while.
And here I thought we'd finally found him.
At least we know that he's somewhere nearby.
I'm sure this case will lead us to him.
You're right.
So what should we do now?
Let's try to find that woman named Mimasaka Sue.
We can't decide whether she's a suspect or not
until we discover what her relationship
with Hatanaka was.
Okay.
You're quite a sight, Isuzu.
Was it that good for you?
You're already sopping wet.
Do you understand?
You're to bring me the property rights to this land.
Is that her?
Yes, but I don't know much else about her.
Let's follow her.
What do you want from us?
Get out of our way.
Don't move!
Stay away!
No! Let me go!
No!
Chizuru-chan!
S-Stop...
You'd better stop!
No!
No! Don't!
No, anything but that!
No!
Sensei...
You...
saved us.
Thank you so much for rescuing us!
This place is dangerous.
Get out of here and don't ever come back.
You're acquaintances of Detective-sensei?
Do you know Tokito-sama?
You could say I owe him my life.
Where is he now?
I haven't seen him recently.
We've come all the way from Japan to look for him.
We know that he used to
frequent the chapel near here,
but lately he hasn't been showing up there, either.
Are you serious?
Follow me.
I see, so you're looking for Mikagura-sensei.
My name is Ryou Shakuryuu.
And he's my son Shinbu.
If we, the natives of this city, put our
full effort into looking for him,
we'll find him right away.
I hate Japanese people, but that man is an exception.
Rest assured that I'll find him.
Can we help them with the search?
There are many places that ladies like you can't enter.
Go back to your hotel, and wait for us to contact you.
They're taking too long!?
I'm really worried.
I'm going to Shakuryuu-san's place.
You shouldn't do that, Tomoe-san.
We promised Shakuryuu-san that we'd wait here.
But...
Let's believe in them and wait a little longer.
Okay.
We found Mikagura-sensei.
Please don't tell me he's dead.
No.
What happened to him might be worse than death.
Anyway, please follow me.
What is this place?
This is terrible.
Sensei is here?
This way.
Over there.
Over there?
Sensei?
– Sensei!
– Tokito-sama!
Sensei!
Please snap out of it!
Don't you recognize us?
No way.
I don't believe it.
I don't believe this!
Shigeno-san!
Tomoe-san, please take care of Sensei.
Sensei...
This is my room.
Use it however you like, for as long as you need.
Thank you.
Sensei...
What's wrong? Does it hurt?
Pull yourself together!
Opium...
No! You can't have any more opium!
Please snap out of it!
Miwa...
Sensei, no!
No... Sensei... don't...
It's okay now. I'll accept everything you have.
I'm... I'm cumming!
I...
How could I? What have I done?
Tokito-san!
Don't go...
Tomoe-san, something horrible has happened!
What's wrong, Chizuru-chan?
Nema Torazou has been murdered,
and both of his arms were severed!
anata ni todoke watashi no kokoro
I send my heart to you.
kanashii yoru wa hitori namida ga ko to ko to ko
On a sorrowful night, alone, my tears go drip, drop, drip, drop.
anata ni todoke watashi no kokoro
I send my heart to you.
shizukana yoru ni hikaru tobira no oto oto oto oto
On a quiet night, the sound of a door –
the sound, the sound, the sound, the sound!