Girl's Locker Room Lust.
There!
No!
Come on, please.
Okay!
If you don't do good as our setter, we can't win the next tournament.
Yes, I understand.
Come on, you can't even handle this ball.
This one too, come on.
Listen, I have scouts from companies that are giving me love calls.
Yes, I will do my best so not to pull any legs.
Enough talking and get it right.
Yes!
Hey, that was horrible.
If we can't enter the nationals, I'm blaming it on you.
If you don't toss right Madoka, I can't spike the ball.
Understand?
Yes.
Then stop farting around and get back to practice.
Come on, get the ball! Come on!
Ah, don't hit it all at once...
You have something to say?
Come on, get it! Toss me a ball so I can easily spike it.
You can't depend on anything on the court. Only yourself.
Yes.
You're so pathetic, because you hang out with guys.
Cut your connection with guys.
Okay?
Now, get this.
Umm...
What's up, Yuuna, calling me to come out here.
Ah, I'm sorry.
Let's talk in the classroom.
Ah, yes.
So what is your story?
Ah, yeah... I, I, uh... for the longest time I...
So, I mean, I really care about...
Hey hey, I have a girlfriend named Madoka. You know that right?
That, yes, I know. But...
What do you mean but?
I have nothing more to talk with you.
Bye.
Ah, Noboru.
Just forget about the conversation we had.
I don't want Madoka to trouble me by getting the wrong ideas.
All right?
Okay.
You're so cruel when I confronted you with courage.
Of course, I knew of your girlfriend Madoka. But I love you as much as she does.
Yoko.
You woke up.
Did I pass out?
Yes, with your pretty face.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. I was being emotional for the win.
I overdid it.
No, I didn't meet your expectation.
Don't worry. You're my best partner, Madoka.
Yoko.
Madoka.
Your lips are so soft, Madoka.
Yoko.
I love you, Madoka.
Yoko, you smell good.
So beautiful, Madoka.
Yoko.
Let me touch you here.
Ah, Yoko.
Wow, it's so big, Madoka.
No Yoko, No, not right there...
It's so soft and so white.
The tip is so pink.
I haven't seen any beautiful nipples like these.
What about here? What's going on?
Aah, what are you doing, Yoko. Doing it right here...
All good, all good. Not one person will come here.
You're so wet. Right here.
Wow, why are you so wet, Madoka?
That's because... Ahh!
There, spread wider so I can see...
The pretty pussy.
Ah, I didn't know you were like this.
Hey, females are way better than males.
That...
You're more beautiful than those sweaty animals.
I can't believe Yoko and Mamoru's girlfriend, Madoka, is doing this.
Aah, no Yoko! Don't touch me there...
It's so slimy.
How pathetic!
What, Madoka?
It's been a long time, so be nicer to me.
Because I'm not even dressed after my club.
The sweaty smell is the good thing.
Don't be so weird.
We haven't done it for a week.
Don't say it like that.
Since you might not give me some action.
It can't be helped. I have a match coming up.
Matches after matches, it's always matches.
It's an important match for Yoko.
Who cares about Yoko.
I'm the setter, and Yoko's my partner, so I care about her.
What happens to me? To me?
What are you doing? Stop it!
It's all right, no one will come.
It's not that. I don't like it, not in this mood.
I'm in the mood to fuck!
No, stop it.
What? You're so wet already.
No.
Hey, your body's honest.
It's not that.
Yeah, this. This! So warm.
How does it feel to have my cock in you once again? Isn't it great?
Yes, yes, slobber all over it.
The tip also.
I'll fuck you later.
Ah, what's this? Tighter, ah... Madoka... I came.
Not on me!
Come on, if you do it all at once, you'll spoil the fun.
What do you want me to do?
Besides, is that something to say to your lover?
What do you mean?
Should it be please you to cum over me.
You're so weird, Noboru.
You're the weird one. Aah, I lost the mood.
I'll leave.
Come on, you're supposed to say that I don't want to leave.
I'm leaving.
Shit.
Ah, No, Noboru.
No, no... Oh, no... Noboru.
There, Noboru.
That's my private part.
Ah... my private part...
Ah, don't do that. It's going to break.
Noboru, don't rush.
I don't do it anywhere. Please do it gently.
Ah... Noboru... Don't do it too hard.
So nasty... love juice... I... I... I can't stop it...
Don't push it too rough. Please... Please, gently..
I'm going to cum if you keep doing it. I'm going to cum... Noboru...
Ah... Noboru... more, more...
Noboru, more softly...
What? Who?
Oh, my...
Yoko.
Yuuna, you like Noboru.
No.
Noboru, I'm cummig...
Don't worry.
Nice body.
Ummm... very smooth...
Ah... no... I'm not interested.
Be quiet. I won't say anything about Noboru.
It's good doing by yourself, but... Don't you feel good if I do this...?
See, you have a enough sense.
No.
Next is my turn. Lick this... here...
I haven't been licked by a lovely girl.
Lick?
Yea... I feel good with a young girl's soft tongue.
Hurry. Don't be so surprised.
Yes... you're good, Yuuna.
Here?
Yea... there... so nasty... woof...
Ah... you're so good.
You're so wet, Yoko.
Ah... you have a talent, Yuuna. Because you're very good.
I feel wired now.
Make a circle with your fingers next.
Like this?
How about this?
Ah... it's good... good, too.
So wet... it's filled up... Yoko.
Ah... so cute... so lovely, Yuuna. Playing my pussy with the fingers of a lovely girl...
Yoko...
Ah... ah... cumming...
Hah... ah... Yoko... ouch... ouch... Yoko, pain...
Next day.
I came here so early.
Yoko... I couldn't sleep well because of her.
What is this feeling? Do I like her?
Am I a lesbian?
But I didn't feel excited when I saw Noboru yesterday. Instead, I felt ill.
What happened to me?
Madoka?
Ah, Yoko.
What's the matter? You look red.
Ah, never mind.
Good. Very cute... like using lipstick.
Yoko...
I couldn't sleep yesterday because of you.
Me either, Yoko.
Ummm, very cute...
Ah, Yoko...
What nice breasts! I feel good touching them.
Ah... no... I'm feeling it...
Here, right? Ummmm, I know it.
It's getting hard...
Um, really getting hard.
Oh, shit! Yuuna sent me this letter. What? Madoka? What? With Yoko? Oh, shit!
Good, good, good.
Ah... Are we abnormal doing this, aren't we?
Yes, abnormal, but... it's okay. I feel good.
Ah, don't move it so hard.
No...
Ah... there... so hot... I'm feeling it.
I feel like melting...
Ah... no... Yoko... no...
Ah... I feel good.
Madoka... ah... Yoko... nice...
Let me lick it...
Ah... Yoko's slobber and my pussy juice are mixing up...
Great... you're so excited, Madoka.
Ah, Yoko.
Ah... lick my pussy, too.
Ah... smells good... so good, Yoko.
Ah, good, Yoko... good... Ah... good... there...
Ah, no... don't lick it so hard.
Ah... good, Yoko.
See. I told you.
What the heck!
Look at that.
Look at what?
They are lesbians. So nasty.
Lesbians?
Yes, they're not interested in men. So fool!
Madoka has a very nice guy, but...
Yuuna.
I really love you, Noboru.
Yuuna...
I really wanted this. Ah... delicious.
Here... more... lick it like you die for...
I really wanted this...
Okay. Lick it so hard, it makes you full.
Delicious!
Ah... great... she is doing so good.
Ah... I want you to lick my pussy, too.
Ah... Yuuna, very good...
Ah... my dream boy is licking my pussy...
Yuuna, you're so wet...
Noboru... good, good.
I want to fuck you, Yuuna.
Really? You really want to fuck me?
Of course! I want to fuck you.
Great! So tight.
Noboru is in me.
Warm...
Your dick is so big.
Really?
Ah... I'm happy. He is in me...
Oh, no... I'm going to move it, Yuuna.
Noboru, please.
Fuck me, fuck me.
Ah... great. I can feel it.
Noboru.
Hey, I'm going to fuck you everyday. Is it okay? Everyday.
I'm so happy.
Ah... so tight.
Noboru, please more, more...
Great, Yuuna, great...
My Noboru...
Yes.
How nice!
I really want to fuck you every day.
Please fuck me more... more...
Really?
Please.
Really hard? Harder?
More, more...
Okay, I'm going to fuck you until you feel faint.
No... no more... Ah... Noboru...
Ah... cumming...
Cum inside...
But...
Please...
No... it's going to be a mistake.
No, please. Please, Noboru.
Ah... more... harder...
Fuck me more... please.
Cum inside...
No, I can't...
Please... more... more...
Cumming, cumming...
Noboru... I felt too much.
Terrible! I can't believe it. See, man is like that. I trusted him...
We need to do something.
What?
About Yuuna. She is cute, isn't she?
Man is shit, but Yuuna is going to be lovely by us.
I'm going to separate from Madoka. We going to have sex everyday, Yuuna.
I can fuck two times a day.
Two times?
Oh, three or four times, if you like.
Noboru, you only want my body, don't you?
What? First, body, no?
Okay? Fuck everyday? Okay?
He sure is terrible.
You're right.
This is your punishment.
Be ready.
What? I'm doing nothing wrong.
I'm going to teach you how to behave.
Are you upset because you lost your man?
What?
Take this! Take it!
Come on!
Um, I give it sexual punishment now.
See? You can't move.
Wow, her pussy is very small.
Cute, isn't it?
Look! It's already wet.
No... No...
Very cute...
Yoko, don't say too much. It turns me off.
You know, I have seen her jerking off in the restroom.
It was great.
Let's take our clothes off. Okay? Let's play together.
Ummmm, you're choking me.
Can you lick me like before?
Ah... don't say it...
Yoko, you did it before?
Never mind.
Ah... I feel something.
Ah... Yuuna, there... more... more...
I like her pussy.
Wow, her tongue is touching my spot.
I want to do it, too.
Me too.
I'm having fun.
How about you, Yuuna?
I'm getting better.
Keep going!
Oh... what are you doing?
I'm going to help you, Yuuna?
What?
Wait for me.
No...
I now understand how you feel.
What?
I prefer girls. Sorry for you. You fool.
We're going to have lots of sex from now on. We don't need you. Go away!