I'm getting hungry.
Yuuto, it's your day off from your part-time job today, right?
Why don't we eat out today? We haven't done so in a while.
Ow!
Hey, you're ogling other women too much!
Well, you haven't let us do it in the last few days.
It's been continuing for a while so I can't help it.
Th-Then, at least.
This is an express train.
This won't stop at each station.
Hey, I think we really should stop doing it here.
No can do.
We've already agreed to it, right?
In exchange for missing out on sex so much.
That may be so, but.
Hey!
I never thought that the deal he would make,
would be a train molester play.
Please remember that this train will not stop at each station.
Th-They'll notice.
Only externally like we agreed, okay?
Alright.
I'm going to kill you if you suddenly insert your hand inside.
Feeling horny yet?
Of course not.
Huh, this feeling.
You're not wearing a bra?
Oh crap.
I didn't wear any because they're swelling due to my period.
Hey, you're doing it again.
Though,
it seems quite wet despite your protests, don't you think?
Your love juices are overflowing too.
Idiot, that can't possibly be!
This is bad.
I'm starting to feel weird.
Whoa.
That surprised me.
Huh?
Wh-What's he up to suddenly?
Hey!
That Yuuto.
In the heat of the moment he just.
Hey, I said only externally.
You're getting too cocky.
Huh?
You're the girl I was supposed to meet, right?
The one at the train molester forum.
Wh-Who are you?
N-No, I'm not.
I'm!
Wh-Where did you go, Yuuto?
Oh? Wrong person, you say?
Now, now.
You were moaning earlier while being groped.
With you already wet like this, it's us men's turn to feel good.
Us men?
Oh, you're very cute.
Th-There's two of them?
We've been watching, you know.
Are you always playing around like this?
Stop... stop.
I have to say it.
No.
My voice won't come out.
Hey, it'd be bothersome for the others if you moan aloud.
H-His fingers,
please don't put them inside me.
Your moans are becoming really wild.
You can't let out your moans like that.
It's... going deep inside.
The sloshing noises down here are
so loud, people might notice.
Oh?
I see, you're on your period now.
You sure made quite the mess down there.
Yuuto?
Yuuto!
I'm right here!
Now then, it's time for the main course.
Gotta make sure I don't slip and fall down with your love juices.
We'll need a nice line of contact.
S-Save me.
Here, can you see it?
You're about the only girl having secret sex in this kind of place.
I go in and out,
as the train shakes.
It's hitting me in the back.
With this smooth ass right in front of me,
I'm just unable to resist.
The front hole's occupied, so I guess.
I'll just have to take this one.
You're drenched in love juices already, so even if it's small.
It won't fit.
That part is.
It won't it there!
Try to relax a bit, okay?
Alright, I'll be moving bit by bit.
Your pussy's starting to twitch and wrap around me tightly.
So thick.
O-Ouch.
You're getting tired from all that standing, right?
Just hold on tight to me.
Just lean on us until we get to the station.
I'm going to stay like this until I get to the station?
It's hitting my... very depths.
It's dangerous, so move a bit closer to me.
We're nearing the end of the line.
We will be arriving at the end of the line shortly.
Please exercise caution as we approach the station.
We're at the end of the line over here too.
This is the end of the line.
Please remember to take note of your belongings.
Let's play again sometime, okay?
This train will be taking the express route once again.
I-I have to go out.
I'm sure Yuuto's at the central station too.
Going out already?
Come play with us next.
– Hey, it's okay, right?
– Hey, please no...
– Come on, just for a short while.
Let me go!
Closing doors.
Please take caution.