I'm starving.
Yuuta, you don't have work today, right?
It's been a while since you were last free.
Do you wanna go get some food together?
Ouch!
Hey, what's with all the ogling you're doing?!
Because you haven't let me do it with you in a while.
That's true, but that's because I'm
on my you-know-what, so we can't.
H-How about...
Hm?
This is the express train.
This train will not stop at the local stations.
Hey, maybe we shouldn't do it here.
No, you promised me we could, since we can't have sex.
Yeah, but...
Hey...
I really didn't expect him to ask
for roleplay groping on a train.
This train will not be making
any small stops. Please be careful.
People are gonna see!
Just do as you promised. Only over the clothes, okay?
Yeah, I know.
Stick your hands underneath and I'm gonna kill you.
Does it feel good?
Why would it?
Huh? This feeling... No bra?
Crap! I'm not wearing a bra because
my boobs are swollen from my period!
What? My ass again?
You might say that you don't like it, but aren't you wet?
It's already making noises.
You idiot, that's not true!
Crap...
I'm starting to feel weird...
Oh god, that scared me.
What now?
Hey!
Yuuto, you bastard!
What do you think you're doing?!
Hey, didn't I tell you that you could only touch me
over my clothes? You're getting too into this.
So you're the plain old high-school
girl who's down to be molested?
Who's that?!
No, I'm not! I'm...
Yuuto, where'd you go?
You really aren't? You can drop the act.
You've been getting excited
ever since I started touching you.
You're getting so wet.
Are you gonna let us have some fun?
"Us?"
Oh man, you're really cute.
Both of them?
I've had my eye on you for a while.
Do you always play by yourself like this out here?
No, stop!
I need to tell them!
Oh no, I can't even make a sound!
Hey now, stay still.
You're gonna bother the people around you.
No! Don't put your finger inside me!
Hey, you're getting too loud.
You need to calm down a little.
He's going... so deep!
Looks like it's flooding a lot downstairs.
People might notice.
What's this? Oh, I see, you're on your period.
Look at the mess you've made.
Yuuto? Yuuto? I'm over here!
All right then, how about we get
into the main attraction now?
Gotta do this right, otherwise I might slip
and fall into the mess you've made on the floor.
Help me!
Took a good look? You're about the only chick
I know who'd do this on a train.
Gotta go along with the rhythm
of the train... In... Out... In... Out...
He's hitting me on my backside too.
If you show me your smooth ass like that,
I won't be able to hold myself back either.
Your front's currently in use,
so I guess this is my only other option.
Even if this hole is tight, it's drenched in your fluids, so...
No... It won't fit!
There's no way!
Relax a bit.
See? I'll take this slowly.
Her front's starting to twitch and squeeze on me.
No...
Aren't you tired from standing?
Just hold on tight.
Leave your body to us until we get to the station.
I have to stay like this all the way until the station?
It's hitting me at my deepest point!
No...
It's dangerous, so get closer to me.
We will soon reach the end of the line.
Please be careful as the train stops.
I'm about to reach the end of my line as well.
We have arrived at the end of the line. Please do not
forget your belongings before exiting the train.
Let's play again sometime.
This train is an express train with no stops.
I need to get off. I'm sure I'll be able to see Yuuto at home.
Getting off already? Play with us next.
– No, stop...
– Come on.
– Just a little, okay?
– No, stop...
– Let go of me!
What's the harm? Don't you like it?
The doors are closing.
No, don't shut them!
Please be careful of the closing doors.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: bakarpoxy
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч