Yahiro!
We've returned.
Kureha, I have been waiting for you.
I am Princess Sue, the one who has spent
these nights making love to you.
Princess Sue!
Speak, what is your status?
My Lord, the Three Jingi will soon be ours.
I can hardly wait.
Yes, Lord.
Tell me... How do Utsumi women taste?
I can hear the sounds perfectly.
The sounds of many Utsumi women being tasted near me.
Well, we were only doing that to search for the Jingi.
Well, never mind.
Once the Three Jingi are in my grasp, this world will turn inside-out.
I will then be the ruler of Yamato.
Note: Yamato is the old name for Japan.
From there, I will become the ruler of the entire world!
Mitama Nin
Part 2
If I reflect this crystal ball in the Fire Mirror,
I should be able to see the other two balls.
Nothing's... happening.
How strange.
Um...
"If the image of a bonding man and woman is projected through
the crystal ball into the Fire Mirror and reflected back...
... then the whereabouts shall appear and thou
shalt be granted with the Dragon Crystal."
That's what it says.
You're as slow as usual, I see. It means we have to do this.
Your penis... it's already so big.
My boobs... feel great...
My... my nipples... feel great...
Yes...
I can't hold back any longer! Princess Sue...
The Mirror needs to reflect a man and a woman merging...
But I can't stop my feelings anymore... Kureha!
Ran...
Yahiro...
Yes... Yes...
Yahiro is inside of me...
Yahiro... Yahiro...!
Found it!
Is it yummy, Princess Sue...
It feels wonderful! Yes!
Deeper... deeper... put it in deeper!
I've always been waiting for this moment.
Yes...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Deeper... It feels great...
Does it feel good, Princess Sue?
No good...
I'm... I'm cumming!
That was great, Yahiro.
So this is the Dragon Crystal?
That's one of the Jingi. Meaning we now have two.
Princess Sue, it's said that Kusanagi's Sword is at Katsuta Shrine.
Is that true?
I know nothing of the Sword.
Yahiro, let's just check it out. Let's go to Katsuta Shrine.
But we already have two, isn't that good enough?
We need to have all three, otherwise we can't call it the Three Jingi.
You sure?
That Mirror and Crystal shall be mine!
Hand over the Mirror and Crystal!
We've worked hard to get these two, and we're gonna get our reward!
You're just the nobility, anyway... big baby.
Still, she's one hell of a babe!
I-I'm cold!
Kureha!
In time, everything here will freeze. No matter how much
you protest, you will turn into solid ice by my will!
Yahiro! Ran! Open the door at once! Hurry!
Like I'd let you!
Yahiro!
Well, that was unfortunate... but forget I said that.
Yeah.
Stop it! Stop it!
No! Don’t put it in!
No! Stop it!
Stop it, please!
Where is the Sword? If you tell me where it is, I'll spare your priestesses.
There is no Sword here!
My, are you stubborn. Get them too!
Please... stop this!
No! Stop it!
Not that... don't put that in!
No... Not down there...
Don't lick down there... Please...
No!
Someone, help...
No... stop it... please forgive me!
Save me!
Father! Please save us! Fa-!
It's burnt black...
Kusanagi's Sword can’t be here, then...
What happened here!?
Maybe Kusanagi's Sword burned up here.
Could that be... the Fire Mirror and the Crystal?
It appears so.
Oboro! Ran!
You're both Locusts, so you shouldn't fight!
The true enemy is someone else.
You are...!
Oboro... Oboro, please save me.
The one I always dream about?
Yes. I am Princess Sue, I have been calling out to you.
Princess Sue... So, what did you want of me?
I wanted you to bring this woman to me.
Me?
Yes. I wanted to see the tattoo on your back.
I already read it.
What you read could have only been a small
part of it, you Locust. Come, let's go.
I'm coming too!
What does she mean by "Locust"?
The guys in the Yomi Kingdom seem to call us that.
The Yomi Kingdom?
Right there!
No... Not there... Don't lick there...
Oh, yes!
Don't suck too hard... Not so hard...
Yes...
Shiho...
You're still just a child, eh.
Does it trouble you? Kusanagi's Sword.
Or perhaps, were you thinking about Shiho-san?
You’re jealous.
But... your body doesn't lie, does it?
It feels great...
That tickles...
Wow... More... Yes...
This... feels great, right?
Yes, more down there...
Yes!
Y-Yes!
Delicious!
This feels great.
Yes... down there!
More...
Yes...
Yes... Right there...
Do you feel it?
You're really good at this.
Thank you.
Right there!
This feels wonderful!
I'm cumming! I-I'm cumming!
I-I'm cumming!
So thick! It's messing up my insides!
I'm cumming... I'm gonna cum!
"Amidst the rages of red fire, the divine beam of light shall shoot forth.
At the light's cease, the Sword of Kusanagi shall yield its true form."
Delicious...
Bad boys.
One, two, three, four, five...
Then, four steps towards the Sheep-Monkey.
Note: According to the Chinese Astrogical Chart,
this direction roughly southwest-west.
Kureha, bring the Fire Mirror here.
That’s...
That's Kusanagi's Sword.
But why was it in my sheath?
I get it now. No one would expect a noble's good-for-nothing
son to have Kusanagi's Sword.
Hey, that didn't sound like a compliment!
Ran!
Who're these guys!?
They're bastards from the Yomi Kingdom!
I'll take the Fire Mirror off your hands.
Shit!
Unhand me, bastards!
Stop it! You stupid... Don't lick me with those dirty tongues!
Let go of me! Stop it!
No!
Don't...
With this, we have collected all three of the Jingi. Very well done.
Now, hand over Kusanagi's Sword at once.
Princess Sue, don’t do it!
Come, hand it over.
Take it yourself!
You bitch!
Get the Sword!
On sora soba tei ei sowaka! On sora soba tei ei sowaka!
Note: This is the mantra for Benzaiten (弁才天, 弁財天), the Japanese name
for Saraswati, the Hindu goddess of knowledge, music, and arts.
Wh-What's that monster?
That's... the Eight-Forked Serpent!?
Note: The Yamata no Orochi (八岐の大蛇) is a legendary 8-headed,
8-tailed Japanese dragon that was slain by the Shinto god Susanoo.
Princess Sue! Suppress it!
Rin, pyou, tou, sha, kai, jin, retsu, zai, zen!
Note: She is chanting the Kuji-in (九字印: Nine Hand Seals),
a specialized form of Buddhist meditation.
On i sha na ya sowaka! On i sha na ya sowaka! On i sha na ya sowaka!!
Note: A short form of the mantra for Gozan Yasha Myo-o (降三夜叉明王),
one of the Wrathful Kings of Mystic Wisdom in Vajrayana Buddhism.
Ran! Above you!
You're not getting away!
Shit, you're persistent
Shiho!
N-No... Stop it...!
No!
Shiho!
No... Save me... Oboro!
I said that you're not getting away!
No...
Frogs... I hate frogs!!
Stop it... Not my nipples...
They're getting sticky...
Don't...
Ribbit, ribbit...
Eww, it feels so gross...
Ribbit, I'm gonna make you feel good.
Stop it!
This feels gross...
Let me see that.
Stop it...
Oh no... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Yes... Yes!!
Susanoo!
Note: Also known as Tatehaya Susanoo-no-Mikoto (建速須佐之男命),
he is the Shinto god of the storms and seas.
This is supposed to feel gross... but... it kinda feels good...
Don't touch my boobs...
No!
Stop it...
N-No more...
I hate it...
Y-You're hurting me...
Not... Not so deep... It hurts...
Oh no, now I'm coming...
No! I don't want to disappear!
Oboro. You've become a man.
Hey, Oboro.
Shiho...
He's hopeless.
I will now go to the Yomi Kingdom to purify
their corruption with the Three Jingi.
And I'm going with her!
Yahiro, Oboro, and Ran, thank you!
The Three Jingi are off in the Yomi Kingdom...
What should I do from now on?
Yahiro! Oboro! Come over here!
To think that Princess Sue's gifts were two of the Three Jingi...
Even though they're fakes, they're very well made.
Both the North and the South thought that their Jingi were genuine.
There really wasn't anything to fight about in the first place, though.
Shall we go then?
See you later!
Yeah.
With this we'll be able to eat a huge feast!
Ran, you're such a glutton.
On nights when the moon is red, all is beautiful.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa suteki
On nights when the moon is red, all is tragic.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa higeki
The sweet smell that climbs up from that river
ano kawa kara tachi noboru amai ka wa
Slowly, slowly travels into my eyes.
watashi no me no oku o yukkuri yukkuri to
And rots them.
kusarasete yuku
The scream of bullets, the light of the red moon,
dangan no sakebi akai tsuki no hikari
Your burning eyes.
anata no moeru hitomi
I'll take any of them.
mou dore demo ii
Destroy me with one thought, please.
hito omoi ni kowashite yo wakashi o
On nights when the moon is red, all is beautiful.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa suteki
On nights when the moon is red, all is tragic.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa higeki
On nights when the moon is red, all is beautiful.
tsuki ga akai yoru...