Y-You're gonna kill me...
This one's not it...
Not this one either.
Nothing here!
It's... it's  spreading...!
Yes... I love it... I love it!
More... get it deeper!
Shit! It's not on any of their backs!
Mitama Nin
Part 1
I begged to Takauji, but the new Emperor shall still be throned.
What? What about the Three Jingi?
I apologize, my Lord. They have been stolen.
Stolen, you say? The Mirror, the Crystal,
the Sword, everything was stolen!?
Yes, it appears so.
He who possesses the Three Jingi is the true Emperor.
I will not let Takauji have it! You must steal it back from him at once!
But, my lord! If you stay here, your life will be in danger!
For now, please leave this matter to Yoshino.
Very well, I will let Yoshino handle this.
But I will still retrieve the Three Jingi!
Damn you, Takauji!!
Save me... Please, save me!
Yahiro, please save me!
It's that dream again...
What's wrong?
Does something hurt?
M-My heart..
Oh no!
Are you all right?
Well? Do you feel better now?
Yes. Thanks to you.
Ran?
I suspected something like this might happen, so I stayed close by.
Good for you.
She's a quick runner!
I could've handled that, you know. I knew she was suspicious.
There you go again, acting macho. It's too
late to fight back if you're already dead.
I know already.
But if she attacked you, Yahiro, doesn't that mean
she was trying to hinder your mission?
There's tons of guys already looking for the Three Jingi, aren't there?
Even then, not one of them know the whereabouts of the real ones now.
If I did know where it was, I could just easily sell it in the North or South.
Don'tcha think the Jingi are in the North?
It's rumored that a fake Jingi is in the North.
It's also basically confirmed that it's not in the South either.
I was ordered to search for it in the South, though...
Well then, go look for it quickly!
I intend to do that. Let's go.
What's that?
Civil Officer! Some Locusts have found their way here!
You mean I captured them.
Throw the man out. Let's have a better look at the woman.
What's the big idea!?
Cut it out! Let me go!
Don't look at me! Stop...
No! No! Stop it!
Keep up that cute voice while I fuck you.
No, I don't wanna feel it...
Oh no...
No! No!
That tickles...
Stop that!
You dirty fool.
Ow! That hurts!
No! Don't! Don't look!
Don’t put that in there! Stop it!
You're messing me up...
It's inside... all the way...
It's... scratching me... deep...
Oh no! I'm cumming! I don't wanna cum because of this!
It's not this woman. We no longer have use for her.
Wait! Let me have possession of that woman.
Your name is Ran, right?
You don't need to worry. Wait here.
You're Yahiro, right?
Please save me!
It's you...
Yes. I am Princess Sue.
And I have a favor to ask.
The Fire Mirror is in Mie Shrine.
At Mie Shrine?
Once you retrieve the Fire Mirror, please return here. Promise me.
I need your help.
I understand. I promise we'll return.
The Three Jingi?
Correct.
But weren't the Three Jingi in your hands...?
They were stolen.
However, this information must not be publicized.
It was our secret mission to retrieve them.
Then are the Jingi in the northern area of Yoshino?
Maybe.
The one thing we know is this: The Mirror, the Crystal, the
Sword... at every location, there is a woman involved.
A woman?
Oboro... please save me. Please, save me...
Um, excuse me...
Is that so. So you came all the way from Yoshino to see Mie Shrine?
Please, feel free to rest in this room.
Someone beat us to it...
What?
Who are you... who...?
Please, hurry and find me.
More... more... more!
Kureha! Are you okay? Snap out of it! Hello? Hello?
No... stop it!
Doesn't it feel good? You're so wet.
I'll make you feel even better.
Your skin is so smooth and pretty.
More.. use the bottom of your tongue more...
No...
Ran... you feel it, don't you. Don't you want me?
I'm... gonna lose it!
Me too, I'm cumming!
Come here.
Are you sure?
So this is what a man feels like...
Inside of me... is Yahiro!
Does it hurt?
No, I'm okay. Just be gentle.
Does it feel good?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! Let's cum together!
I cannot stay here any longer.
Why is that?
Once I know a man, I can no longer be a priestess.
Oh... sorry.
I'm fine with it.
Inside of my dreams, I was always being loved half-heartedly.
That mirror!
Yahiro, this is the Fire Mirror!
But what's it doing here!?
Note: He was making a pun here. "Kure"
from Kureha can also mean "Give me!"
Kureha, can I please have the mirror? Please...
No you may not! I like to use this mirror when I apply my makeup!
Ummm...
This is one of the Jingi! Hand it over!
I refuse!
You sure are stubborn.
Come on, Kureha. Cooperate and I'll do good things with you again.
Well then, if you help me find my Princess, I'll give it to you!
Your princess?
Yes. I always see her in my dreams. She loves me!
Oh, she means Princess Sue...
Wait a moment, please!
Oh dear, I'm sorry.
Listen... you're looking for the Three Jingi, aren't you?
There is no Jingi in Yoshino.
How do you know that?
Not "how", but "where", right?
That's what you should be asking me.
Yeah...
It's written on my back.
On your back?
Yes. Would you like to look at it?
Yeah.
Where? Where is it!?
There's no tattoo on your back!
You can't see it right now.
It only appears when I'm feeling really good.
Is that so? In that case!
Harder... Harder... Yes... Yes...
Not yet. Not yet... not yet...
Kusanagi's Sword... is... at Katsuta Shrine!
Note: Kusanagi-no-Tsurugi (草薙の剣) is a legendary Japanese sword holding
equal status as Excalibur, and is one of three Imperial Regalia of Japan.
What about the other two!?
Didn't I tell you? What's written on my back
is only the whereabouts of the Sword.
You're still... just a child, eh.
She's so childish.
Look who's talking.
Kusanagi's Sword is at Katsuta Shrine.
Kureha, what did you just hear?
I saw it. Kusanagi's Sword is at Katsuta Shrine.
It was written on a woman's back.
Katsuta Shrine... We're going the wrong way.
Yahiro, are we gonna go to Katsuta?
No.
We have our promise to keep with Princess Sue.
We need to return to Kanmon Tower first.
On nights when the moon is red, all is beautiful.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa suteki
On nights when the moon is red, all is tragic.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa higeki
The sweet smell that climbs up from that river
ano kawa kara tachi noboru amai ka wa
Slowly, slowly travels into my eyes.
watashi no me no oku o yukkuri yukkuri to
And rots them.
kusarasete yuku
The scream of bullets, the light of the red moon,
dangan no sakebi akai tsuki no hikari
Your burning eyes.
anata no moeru hitomi
I'll take any of them.
mou dore demo ii
Destroy me with one thought, please.
hito omoi ni kowashite yo wakashi o
On nights when the moon is red, all is beautiful.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa suteki
On nights when the moon is red, all is tragic.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa higeki
On nights when the moon is red, all is beautiful.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa suteki
On nights when the moon is red, all is tragic.
tsuki ga akai yoru sonna yoru wa higeki