Miyazaki Maya Daizukan
This is...
Oh, look at him!
I'll do it when I get home.
not a dream.
Oh gosh, what's with those clothes?
Wow, he looks so lame!
I, Ishida Takehiko, have been walking without food for a full three days
I don't have any energy left.
Wait! Princess Tsubaki!
N-No!
Cliff Up Ahead.
Watch out!
The Legend
of Ooedo's
800 Holes
-Part 1-
Huh?
Where's this?
That's me from three days ago.
Listen up, Takehiko.
Holes.
Be careful of holes.
Holes?
That's right. Holes!
For example, black holes.
The universe and all of humanity are born from them and die in them
In other words, our fate is to end up in one of these holes, and there's nothing we can do about it!
Pfft.
What garbage.
Hey!
Later. I'm going home.
Ahh! Takehiko, that way is—
Manhole
Under Construction
Takehiko!
Right, I fell off the edge...
Damn!
W-What is this metal piece?
I can't seem to get it off!
That's a girl, right?
And what's more...
No matter how i think about it, her pussy is totally uncovered!
W-What the...
Oh, you've woken up?
W-W-What the? Why are you on top of me?
Sorry, I must have been heavy.
Don't move!
Anyway, I'll ask just for now, but who are you?
Who, me? I'm...
As you can see, I'm a pitiful town girl.
I work during the day, and act like a female pig at night.
You look nice.
Each and every day, I squeal and squeal!
Shake around lewdly!
I'm a poor town girl who's escaped from such a life.
Come on, squeal with an immoral voice!
Oink... oink.
No! Use more of your nose!
Oink!
That's right! I have nowhere to go.
Sob, sob.
You're so lying!
Well, whatever.
So?
Why is such a poor town girl straddling me?
W-Well, that's...
If you don't say anything, I won't take off my pants.
Sorry. I really am, but I have my own personal reasons.
Sorry, could you just let this go?
I shouldn't get anymore involved with—
I'm not letting that happen.
Sorry, but I'm a guy too, you know.
And on top of that, I've gone without eating for three full days now.
It's only natural that I'd want to eat up a treat like this.
What's with these perfect breasts? Huge yet shapely!
What are you...
Hey!
Tada!
N-No!
Digging in!
No! I don't want this!
What? You want me to stop?
Then will you me the truth? Will you tell me everything about your situation?
No!
Where's Tsubaki!?
She ran away somewhere in this area.
All right, find her! Find her!
Yes!
Huh?
I thought I heard something...
Right?
W-W-What!?
You really want to do those kinds of things with me, don't you?
With some unknown person like me?
You don't know my circumstances, but you want to do such things with me, don't you?
Father.
Mother.
You've raised me...
for a long time.
Thank you.
However, I'm at my limit now.
It seems this is a different world,
but for the first time, I will go against my principles as a person.
This pure-hearted and innocent girl, I will...
eat her all up!
There she is!
Over there, everyone! Meet up!
Sheesh.
You're a brat that hasn't even had her hair grow in yet!
It's 100 years too early for you to even try to get my pants off!
You... you really—
Don't say "you"! The name's Takehiko.
You're inside me! You're inside!
You're in my hole!
Takehiko, Takehiko, Takehiko!
Now that I think back on it, it might've been my destiny
Takehito!
I met a girl after falling into another era through a manhole three days ago.
What am I going to do?
Am I going to believe what she says?
Listen up, Takehiko.
Be careful of holes.
Tsubaki! You insolent daughter!
The Fifth
Tokugawa
Shogun:
Tsunayoshi
You escaped yet again from another marriage proposal meeting?
Are you listening to me, Princess Tsubaki!?
Princess...
Tsubaki?
Father, I shall refuse that offer!
I will make this person, Takehiko, my official husband!
The Fifth
Tokugawa
Tsunayoshi's
Third Daughter:
Tsubaki
Wha...
What!?
To Be Continued
That was on an early afternoon like most others.
Baseball
Team
Manager:
Wakameda
Chitose
The Following
Day
E-excuse me! Wakameda Chitose-san!
Who are you?
I'm the Bicycle Fairy!
This
part
is the
fairy.
This
part
is the
bicycle.
Oh my, the bicycle one?
Yes,
I'm an ever-powerful fairy of all the bicycles in the world!
Oh, I'm sorry that I didn't know that.
Oh, what? I hardly mind.
More importantly, Ojou-san...
Get on.
Get on... top of me!
I-I couldn't!
Hey! What's the point of being embarrassed now!?
I know about you!
You normally straddle your bike and pant until you orgasm!
B-But...
Then couldn't you straddle me at least once and get lost in the tingling sensation of your vagina?
O...
Okay...
If the Bicycle Fairy says so...
She took off her panties! She totally took her panties off!
H-Here I go.
What should I do!?
Bicycle Fairy, your nose and mouth are directly touching me there.
My feet... wait, my h-hips are first going to...
You mustn't! Bicycles must be pedaled by feet!
No matter what stimulation you may feel!
Pedal! Pedal forward with your left and right foot!
Don't rub me with your tongue!
How naive!
You can't handle a bicycle if you're feeling something at this level!
Oh?
What could this be?
It seems to be a mysterious protuberance with a pulse...
Ojou-san!
By the way, do you happen to know what a "wheelie" is?
Wheelie?
What is a "Wheelie"?
It's a difficult technique that involves going forward on your rear wheel while raising your front wheel.
Like this.
If you could perform this with me... if you were told to do so, would you like to try it?
How is it? This is a wheelie!
Is it supposed to be like this!?
This is the best! This is truly the most delicious situation ever!
Stop! If you tighten up that much, I'll come!
Come!? Come where!?
To the meadows!
The meadows? That sounds nice! I want to come too!
Let's come together on the bike!
Oh Manager, that's you, isn't it? What are you doing?
Bicycles are the best.
Oh, look! He's the substitute guy.
Oh, I'm just...
Still man, what's with the outfit?
He's a freaking huge pervert.
That was an early afternoon like most others.
A revolution
in turning manga into anime!?
The original drawings
have been preserved in the anime!!
Motion comic and
anime sample clip.
Miyazaki Maya Daizukan