Miyazaki Maya Daizukan
Takehiko.
I'm ready for you.
Miyazaki Maya Daizukan
W...
Why are you dressed like that!?
Where's the kimono you usually wear!?
You can...
You can do whatever you want with me.
The Legend
of Ooedo's
800 Holes
-Part 2-
Oh, right.
It's been one week now since I've set foot in this era.
I should hurry up and get used to living like this by now, but...
Takehiko, what are we doing today?
Get used to...
Shut up! It's none of your business.
Takehiko! Takehiko! Takehiko!
Takehiko!
SHUT UP!
Oh, you're my husband now,
so should I add dono to your name?
I still haven't agreed to be your husband!
But we were so passionate with each other!
Person
who
made
Takehiko
her
husband.
Person
who had
sex with
the
princess,
thinking
she was
a town
girl.
Do you want to die?
Person
who
saw it.
I-In any case,
I don't have any feelings for you at all.
Anyway,
don't you know that I'm spending everyday looking for a way to get home?
Takehiko, I need to talk to you about something.
Takehiko, do you love me?
How do you really feel about me?
What's with you all of a sudden?
What are you asking!?
There is one way you can get home.
What?
Around 400 years ago, there was a man and woman who fled from the war.
They took refuge in a canyon riddled with holes,
but ended up falling into one.
For a while, people thought they were dead,
but one day, the two of them came back alive,
claiming they had seen another world.
That's the folk tale in these parts: "The Legend of the 800 Holes."
So...
are you telling me to jump off from here?
You know,
I've still got things I'd like to do.
No one died the last time, so I'm sure you'll be fine.
I am not immortal!
Besides...
Takehiko, if you die, so will I.
W...
Everyone who's come close to me so far has only been seeking fame and fortune.
You're...
Takehiko, you're the first boy I've ever loved!
So if you go, I might as well go with you.
Oh?
Well then...
You're going to die soon anyway,
so you don't care what I do to you, right?
Then Takehiko, what are you...
Listen up, Tsubaki.
I'll tell you something about the guys from my era.
You can never tell what they're carrying around, so you'd better be careful!
No!
Stop, Takehiko!
Stop what?
Your crotch is this wet,
so what's wrong!?
Yeah, come on!
I bet you want to come so badly that you don't even care if you're going to die!
No!
There!
Suck me.
I can't!
Takehiko, it's too big for my mou...
Stop talking!
Takehiko, why?
Suck it!
Use more of your mouth!
Takehiko.
You're kind of scary.
Deeper!
This hurts.
Open your mouth up wider.
Right, like that.
That's good.
Why?
I-I'm coming!
A brat shouldn't talk about death so lightly.
Everyone has times when they hate the world they live in.
But if people ran away every time they felt that way,
our eras wouldn't come into existence.
You and I wouldn't have been born or even met.
I...
actually liked you a whole lot.
Takehiko.
Bye, Tsubaki.
I'm going to go.
I don't know whether or not "The Legend of the 800 Holes" you talked about is true, but...
No! No, Takehiko!
Wait, Takehiko!
Don't go past there!
...to.
...kehito.
Takehiko! Takehiko!
Hey Takehiko, answer me!
Are you all right?
Let's call the police in the meantime.
He definitely banged his head down there.
T...
Takehiko!
A...
Are you okay, Takehiko?
I was worried because you didn't say anything!
Hey, do you know the name of Tokugawa Tsunayoshi's daughter?
What?
What are you talking about?
Tsunayoshi doesn't have a daughter, right?
Then who was the girl I had been talking to?
I knew it. You definitely hit your head.
That must have hurt.
Who was she, exactly?
Well, whatever.
Where am I?
Afterwards, Princess Tsubaki lived here for a short while,
but we'll leave that story for some other time.
My name is Ootsuka Jinpachi.
I'm a self-proclaimed-genius science teacher.
I have zero experience with love.
For the sake of my earnest pursuit of knowledge, I have remained...
a virgin.
Ootsuka-sensei!
Matsuo-sensei.
Good morning, Ootsuka-sensei.
You're wearing the same thing again today.
It's my white coat, so of course it's the same.
There you go again!
The truth is you don't have anything else to wear, right?
Matsuo Aiko.
22 years old.
Bust, 90.
Waist, 59.
Anyway, you're the only science teacher who wears a white coat nowadays, aren't you Ootsuka-sensei?
Hip, 88.
Music teacher.
If you keep that up, the female students won't like you,
and you won't be popular with the girls.
This woman's good looks have given her a pretty crooked personality.
I guess you won't be popular even if you do wear nice clothes.
I'll take this opportunity to get it off my chest.
Don't you just want to ravage these types of women?
Science Lab
Aphrodisiac
Bifidus Yogurt Drink
Yogurt
Misumisu
Aphrodisiac
Matsuo-sensei from the music department.
Ootsuka-sensei is calling for you.
Please come to the science lab immediately.
Excuse me.
Oh?
There's nobody here.
Drink it.
I know you like that particular drink.
Drink! Drink it all down!
It feels so hot!
Why...
Why do I feel so tingly?
Looks like the drug's taking effect!
Once any woman drinks that, they lose control of the sexual urges overflowing from deep within their body.
My point is, what you drank is my creation: aphrodisiac pheromones!
W...
That's not funny, you know!
Oh, what are you talking about?
You're the one who decided to drink it, right?
But wow, this is having a rather amazing effect.
See?
Come on, take a look.
This pen is pushing into all sorts of places on you.
See? It's pushing in here too.
Please stop!
It's slowly...
It's slowly starting to feel hot!
Oh?
You don't like feeling hot?
In that case,
I'll cool you down.
How do you feel?
It's refreshing, isn't it?
Oh?
Do you still feel hot?
Well then,
Snip, snip!
Stop! Please don't cut it!
Please don't!
No, stop!
Please, I'm begging you!
What's this white liquid?
It's not juice.
What's this white liquid!?
I must harvest it!
Oh, please! Forgive me already!
I'll apologize for everything I've said to you so far!
Please!
Conscience
Curiosity
Research
Experiment
Crime
Evil
Sorry, but no matter what the situation,
my job is to collect experimental data!
I'll be using this opportunity to get lots of data.
Vaginal fluid, saliva, and breast fluid!
And now for my final goal...
That'll be to take your pussy, and...
sterilize it through heat!
How is it?
Doesn't it feel good...
to have flasks attached to you,
to have your stockings torn,
and to be raped by an ugly science teacher?
Dear Ootsuka-sensei.
I'm sorry that I normally only say mean things to you.
But to me at least, that's just an opposite form of kindness.
The truth is that I love you, Ootsuka-sensei.
I loved you, but...
Ootsuka-sensei, if you hadn't have done this,
I...
Goodbye!
You...
should have...
told me...
sooner.