Yami
Tsuki
Kage
Previously on Mizugi Kanojo.
- Previously on Mizugi Kanojo -
One-hit kill attack: Penis inferno!
Just as we were about to defeat Kuu of the Shirogane,
we were surrounded by blinding light.
Where are we?
Will we finally succeed in defeating our nemesis?
Boss, can we do her?
Wait, Kage. Our target is Kuu of the Shirogane.
She must be somewhere nearby.
We'll use this woman as a distraction.
So we can keep a low profile?
Yes.
We'll catch Kuu off guard, then finish her.
At your service, Yami-sama.
Fit .4 [Two Girls, One Swimsuit]
Mizugi Kanojo
Mizugi Kanojo: The Animation
Two Girls, One Swimsuit
Yohei Mori | Shinji Etou | Kei Nakayama | Hiro Oota
Why'd Mizuho have to tell me that scary story?
On a night like this...
Keep me safe, Suzuka-chan and Marino-chan!
Marino-chan has some nice tits...
Who?
There's nobody here.
It's just your imagination.
Nobody's home?
Shou-kun's parents are away. We're finally alone!
More or less.
Wow, it's amazing!
Why is she getting in my way again?
Your house is huge!
Big-titted ditz.
1+1 Girlfrend
Shou-kun's feeling feisty?
This is...
Let me help you with your pants.
Whoa, wait a minute!
A-Amazing?
He's rich... handsome... and hung like a skyscraper!
Dibs!
Um...
Don't worry. I'll make you... feel... good!
Sorry! It's so big, my teeth...
S-Suzuka-chan...
Now's my chance!
Suzuka-chan, you have to.be gentle.
Ow...
Look. A perfect fit!
It's as if we were meant for each other!
Do my boobs feel good?
Very good.
Bigger really is better.
Here we go.
They're huge!
Let me get it nice and wet.
Marino-chan...
You like it?
It's great.
Yay! You're a breast man, after all.
Oh yeah? Well...
Suzuka-chan?
I can do it too.
Whoa...
Suzuka-chan, I know how sensitive your nipples are.
They're not... that... sensitive...
Oh,God!
You're cute, Suzuka-chan.
Slow down, both of you!
I can't take it...
He's gonna cum!
Oh no, oh no...
Look at all that cum!
Suzuka-chan, did you cum, too?
Guess I got dibs on the semen, then.
You're still hard.
Let me pleasure you more.
Marino-chan, are you sure?
It's big, but I can take it.
Don't push yourself.
Weird. So wet, and I still can't get it in?
It's too big.
Come on... just the tip at least!
Marino-chan.
Let's switch.
Suzuka-chan?
Not to worry. I'll take it from here.
Suzuka-chan... I don't know.
I have confidence in my vagina.
It's a pretty tight fit...
...but I've got to make Shou-kun mine.
Can she really take it all?
It's filling up my insides!
Are you okay, Suzuka-chan?
No problem.
Huh? Marino?
Suzuka-chan, let me help.
Idiot.
Oh, God.
Stop that!
There, it's in!
Suzuka-chan!
No, please, wait!
I can't help it. It's so good.
It's so deep inside!
No fair, Suzuka-chan.
Let me have some fun, too.
Marino-chan?
Marino...
Let's do it together.
Yeah.
Marino!
Eat my pussy just like that!
Suzuka-chan, rub your nipples against mine.
Marino...
Your tits... they're great!
Rub my stiff nipples! It feels so good!
I didn't know a threesome could be so much fun.
My tits... my pussy! I cant.. I'm going to... cum!
Me, too.
Shou-kun, you can cum inside me.
I'm cumming!
I love you.
Amazing!
So this is the fabled Western sex craft?
A ghost!
Shit. Mizuho, don't scare me like that.
Mizuho?
I missed you so much, Mizuho!
Who clings tenaciously to my bosom?
You dressed up as... a ninja?
I'm Kuu the kunoichi. I want to ask you...
Wow, you're really getting into the sneaking thing, Mizuho.
Listen to me!
Ready?
For what?
I'll follow him. He might have valuable information.
In Surgery
Where are we?
I'll have to operate. Your illness requires deep probing.
I say! What are you-
This place will do just fine.
Awesome costume, Mizuho. You look like a real ninja.
I told you I'm not her!
Right, right. You're a kunoichi now.
You fiend!
Men! I should have known.
Did you lose weight again? You look cute.
Cute? Me?
What's wrong?
I've never been called cute before.
That reminds me...
What am I saying?
Hey!
Could you try this swimsuit on?
What's a swimsuit?
Is this the fashion here?
Yeah.
Tug up on it.
You mean like this?
How can I be falling for this man's witchcraft?
Damn, that's nice!
I'm ready to go.
What?
What's wrong, Mizuho?
You want me to eat that?
Lucky!
What is this? It doesn't feel like a normal battle.
Mizuho, your pussy is dripping.
Why are you always so loud? Nympho Mizuho.
Please... more! Lick me more!
That's my girl.
Don't tantalize me so!
Nice ninja talk. Very realistic, Mizuho.
But I'm Kuu the kunoichi!
Sure you are.
Hush! You're too loud!
Huh?
She feels different from usual, somehow..
I love it!
Oh well.
Perfect!
I'm in! Mizuho in the house!
With this disguise, I can sneak in and fuck Hiro-kun silly!
What are you doing at this hour?
Busted.
Who's this?
Find this ninja girl.
Found her!
Make her trust you.
I was just, uh...
Hi there, friend!
I'm Sayaka from Pediatrics.
I got lost during my rounds.
Surgery Ward
From Pediatrics... right!
Yes! My ticket in!
I'm not used to this place, and it's creepy
at night Can I go with you?
Um, okay...
Yay!
Excellent She has no idea!
I'm no fan of the dark.
Yeah, I'm trembling a bit myself.
I can stop your trembling.
Do it She's vulnerable!
What's with her?
Let's get it on.
I've never had it so good!
I can't.. I'm so tired...
But your pussy isn't tired, is it?
So, what are you planning?
I want to experiment on your body.
Experiment?
Lick it. Get it nice and wet.
Stop it!
No, don't...
Your nipples are hard. Were going to have a good time.
No! I'm not really into girls...
Really? Well, your body says otherwise.
Good. Now make her cum until she can't move!
Dammit! Slow down, or this won't last.
You can climax whenever you want.
What's gotten into you tonight?
I've never felt like this.
All the way into me! Your cock is so hot!
Oh, heavens!
Oh, hell!
You're rubbing too hard!
Match my rhythm. It will feel even better.
Please, no more!
But I still have to do this.
Wow, it's going in deep!
Get that thing outta my ass!
She's spoiling me for Hiro!
No...
Yes, squeeze my erect nipples!
Almost time...
I cant stand it!
Marvellous... is this real lovemaking?
Cum with me!
I'm cumming!
Oh, God!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Wow.
You've been careless, Kuu of the Shirogane!
Who's there?
What the...?
Hey!
Now we have you!
What?
Cloth storm attack!
It's them. They're close.
Someone's in trouble!
Come!
Ow!
What is this?
You've evaded us for long enough.
Huh? Who are you guys?
You must be exhausted after all that cumming.
But we're not done with you.
Tsuki, Kage!
#unrecognized text#
Yes, boss!
Transform!
Kuu! Behold our peerless ninja magic!
Huh? Ninja what now?
We'll have our way with you now!
No!
Stop it!
Look away, please!
No!
What kind of armor is that?
I've never seen such a thing.
It's not armor! It's for my boyfriend, Hiro-kun!
What a disgrace.
Now's the time to strike! Go!
No...
Gross! Stop licking me!
Fool! Don't resist us.
Just relish in the pleasure of our technique!
Tsuki, leave the other one out of this!
I can't help it. She's so tempting!
Fine. We'll do them both!
Not there!
No!
Oh no... What's happening to me?
My pussy... my nipples... I'm throbbing all over!
Filthy woman. Wallow in orgasmic stupor!
Super whirlwind attack!
What?
Boss!
Who dares to intrude?
Time for you to get some new moves.
A curse on you, Kuu!
Then, who's she?
Orgasmic... stupor...
Boss, there are two of Kuu!
A self-multiplication technique?
No, you imbeciles!
You're not Mizuho?
Very observant.
So, you're real ninjas?
Correct. We are masters of the night.
Masters of... holy crap.
Hiro-kun...
Mizuho! Wake up!
Come on!
Hiro, take her and escape.
This isn't your fight.
Who are you?
Hiro-kun...
Now, go.
Pardon me.
Not so fast!
Hiro!
I can't move!
Enough. Leave them alone!
Not until we know which of you is the real Kuu.
Shit!
Then I have no choice but to kill you.
Commence battle!
This unmistakably tight pussy...
Boss, this is definitely the real Kuu.
She'll drive us all to climax!
I've got her right where I want her.
Watch this!
Certain kill: Lightning thrust!
Dammit!
Hiro...
Kunoichi technique:
Vagina vortex!
It's no use!
Sorry, boss!
Tsuki! Kage!
Damn you!
Lightning thrust!
Lightning thrust! Lightning thrust!
Lightning thrust!!
Bind
Ow...
Mizuho!
Kuu?
Good. You're tree.
Kuu!
You finally learned my name,
Hiro.
What the...
What's happening?
Were disappearing!
Tsuki!
Kage! Nooo!***
Kuu,
you too?
I shall soon return to that from whence I came.
I don't belong in this world...
...but perhaps well meet again one day.
Thank you, Hiro...
for teaching me true affection.
Wait!
Kuu.
In another lifetime...
Huh?
What happened?
Hiro-kun?
Why are you naked?
Why are you in a swimsuit?
No sex in the hospital!
Huh?
Where are we now?
Do the lightning thrust again. Do it right this time!
Again?
Please? Pretty please?
No more! Let me rest!
Boss, I wanna go home!
Do we ever make it home?
And what of our struggle with Kuu?
That's another story altogether.