Right there!
Mizuho, shush! You're too loud.
But your dick's so big!
No, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Mizuho!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Hey, have you gained a little weight recently?
Have I?
Oh no...
Better get on the scale.
I'd rather not okay?
Maybe if you did a little exercise...
Shut up.
Oh, I know!
You could use the pool where I work part-time.
Swimming is great exercise.
But I'm not a very good swimmer. It'd be embarrassing.
There's nothing to worry about.
You could come in after-hours.
Come on, they even have swimsuits there you can use.
Fine, I'll try it.
All right!
For competitive swimwear, this is a little too revealing.
I hate it. It shows off my curves too much.
Mizugi Kanojo
Fit.1 [Get in Share, Mizuho!]
Mizugi Kanojo.
Whoa, nice swimsuit!
I don't know. Isn't it a little small for me?
It's tight.
It's supposed to be like that.
Really?
Heh, actually it is one size too small.
To start out, let's just get you used to the water.
Hiro-kun, I have to warn you. I really can't swim.
Just leave it to me.
I'm in your hands.
I'm a good teacher, you know.
Whoa! What are you doing?
Just helping you relax. You seemed tense.
Yoink!
Idiot!
Quit messing around.
Good, like that.
It looks like you're getting used to the water.
Yeah, I am.
Okay.
Call me "Coach" from now on, all right?
Got it, Coach!
Next you'll have to put your face underwater.
What?
My face?
Don't worry, you can do it.
Okay, I'll try it.
Good! Keep your eyes open, too.
Yes, Coach!
Nice job, Mizuho!
Cot to... open my eyes!
Are you all right?
Wow... your ass looks nice...
That's it, I quit!
I'm leaving!
Wait I'm sorry.
Don't have a conniption, baby.
Nope, I'm out of here!
Really, I'm sorry.
I just got a little too excited by your sexy swimsuit. Sorry.
Listen.
If I help you take care of that,
can we get on with the lesson?
Oh yeah! Totally!
Mizuho, open your legs a little wider.
Is this okay?
Nice.
Now, tug up on your swimsuit.
Pervert...
Wow... so tight!
Hiro-kun...
Looking at me really gets your dick hard, doesn't it?
I'm starting to feel strange.
Oh, so you're feeling horny, too?
But when you're close to me, my body gets hot and...
I want you so bad!
Hiro-kun, what's gotten into you?
Now I want you to turn around and show me your ass.
Okay.
Like this?
Shit, that's hot!
Don't stare at me.
If I keep this up,
Here it comes!
Let's cum together!
All done!
That hit the spot!
You couldn't have held it a few seconds more? Jeez!
Huh?
We didn't exactly finish properly.
What am I going to do with you? You little vixen...
I'm not a vixen, I just...
Pool sex... never done this before!
You want me to keep the swimsuit on?
That's part of the experience.
Wow, you're all sloppy down there!
Wanna take this fuck outside?
No...
I'm just wet from being in the water.
Really?
Mizuho, you're too loud!
Sorry.
You can't be that loud if you want to do it outdoors.
I told you,
I'm no exhibitionist...
But you kind of like getting fucked in this swimsuit right?
You're such a pervert.
You must like it. Your nipples are
hard. Way harder than usual!
Shut up, you perv!
You're pinching me!
You want to stop?
What's wrong? You seem hotter than usual.
I think I'm becoming a pervert like you.
There's nothing wrong with that.
You're going so deep!
No, I'm going to cum!
Me... too...
Please, let's cum together this time!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Look! You've lost weight.
And guess what. Today I brought a new one.
There we go!
This is becoming a strange habit...
Swimsuit sex... I love swimsuit sex!
Sayaka-san! What is it this time?
This is my upstairs neighbor, Sayaka-san.
She's older than me, but quite a cube.
Cute as she is, though, she's clumsy.
Good morning!
Oops.
You could say it's a wonder she's survived until now.
So I do my best to help her out.
Sayaka-san?
Sayaka-san, it's Takuya.
Are you okay?
Sayaka-san!
Wh-wh-whoa!
What happened in here?
Takuya-kun...
It's out of control.
Yikes!
The washer is out of control.
Yeah, urn... so's your outfit.
Sorry, it's uh... laundry day, you know?
Sayaka-san,
I'm shutting off the water.
But I think you need to visit the appliance shop.
Sorry for the trouble, Takuya-kun.
Holy-!
You're always helping me out.
I-I'm sorry!
Ouch.
Thanks, Takuya-kun. But, um...
Sorry about that!
S-Sayaka-san?
I'm sorry I'm always causing problems for you.
Don't be silly.
Takuya-kun...
Sayaka-san...
Is this... really okay?
Sorry.
I guess I sort of have a crush on you. But I don't-
Sayaka-san!
Wow, she's a hottie!
You're dripping wet down here.
Don't-!
T-Takuya-kun, you're staring...
Sorry, I just...
Haven't you seen enough?
Sayaka-san...
I want to...
Go ahead, put it in.
Sayaka-san!
You're so hot! Takuya-kun...
Sayaka-san...
Ow!
Sayaka-san, is this your first-?
Takuya-kun, if s okay. You can take my virginity.
Sayaka-san!
But gently, please!
Right.
Like this?
Sayaka-san...
This feeling...
Okay... you can in it a little harder now.
S-Sayaka-san...
I can't hold back anymore.
Takuya-kun... That's a little too hard!
Slow down!
Sorry.
I can't help it.
I can't stop.
Sayaka-san...
Well? Does it feel good?
It does... even though this is my first time...
Oh my... I feel so weird.
So good... Your dick is going so deep!
Sayaka-san... I'm gonna...
Go ahead.
Just like that... inside me!
I'm cumming, too!
I can feel your warm sperm flowing into me.
S-Sorry about that.
I...
Hey, Takuya-kun.
Y-Yeah?
I have something to show you.
Will Takuya-kun think this is too much?
It's... tight.
Am I putting weight back on?
Hi.
S-Sayaka-san! That swimsuit...
I knew it. Too much?
Good! I'll go and get us some food.
Where'd that new flab come from, anyway?
I'm not flabby!
I just overate a little.
I miss my skinny Mizuho.
But I haven't gained that much!
Then it'll be easy to lose again.
W-Wait a minute!
Wrong answer. Time for a workout.
Swimming against the tide will make
the exercise even more effective.
I'm not ready for deep water!
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
I'm really sorry, Takuya-kun.
Nah, I'm used to it by now.
But, I have to make it up to you somehow.
Don't worry about th-
S-Sayaka-san!
Keep your voice down, okay?
S-Sayaka-san?
I'm sorry for being so clumsy...
...and for being so horny.
That's all right...
I'm a bit horny myself.
Let me help you.
Sayaka-san...
Can we leave now?
We shouldn't waste this exercising opportunity.
I'm sick of the ocean!
It's not that bad.
Oh, look what I found!
Gross!
There.
This sucks. I want to go home.
All right.
But first...
How about some "nautical naughtiness?"
Hey!
Stop, we can't do it here!
Come on, no one will see us.
I think I'd prefer "nautical normalness."
Don't give me that Swimsuit sex
is your favorite, remember?
No, that's-
Speaking of wet things...
Enough. We're gonna get caught!
We'll be fine. Just try not to be your usual loud self.
Sorry!
Jeez...
You klutz!
Wait Hiro-kun, I'm gonna cum!
Jeez...
I'm cumming!
Be more careful, alright?
Okay!
Takuya-kun...
Do you like this?
Well... sure, I do.
How about if I do it faster like this?
Fuck my tits just like a pussy!
I've heard that boys like dirty talk like that.
Is it weird?
No, it's nice.
I'm glad you like it.
Wow, it's getting harder and harder.
He's really enjoying my tits and mouth.
He's really loving it!
Sayaka-san, can I-?
Of course.
Fill this hole up with your big prick.
Sayaka-san...
Aren't you done?
Impressive stamina, huh?
Not what I meant.
Liar! You know you like it!
I'm not a perv like you!
Damn... outdoor sex is a whole new world!
The danger of being seen!
But I don't want to be seen!
It's embarrassing!
You're fucking me so hard!
You're pounding me down there!
"Down there?"
You mean, your cunt?
Oh... oh, god!
Pound my cunt!
Someone's gonna see us!
Yeah... if we're lucky!
So good!
I'm cumming!
Ecw...
in my hair?
What a mess!
Hi.
Hello.
I like your tan.
Thanks!
And that's why swimsuits are the best part of summertime!
Mizugi Kanojo
Fit.1 [Get in Share, Mizuho!]