Onii-chan. Breakfast is ready.
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan, wake up.
Are you awake?
Your room's dirty again.
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing.
Okay.
Yuki, let's get going.
Okay, I'll be there in a moment.
1st Period: Yuki's Chapter
Are you okay, Yuki?
I'm okay.
Thanks, Onii-chan.
Yuki, do you want to hold hands since it's slippery outside?
Okay.
I was joking.
We aren't at the age where we should do be doing
that. We're going to graduate this spring.
You're right.
Ken-chan! Yuki-chan!
Good morning!
Morning. Hiyori
Good morning, Hiyori-oneechan.
Ouch...
Geez, you're your usual clumsy and dumb self.
That's not nice to say to a childhood friend.
Right. Yuki-chan?
Onii-chan, you should be a little nicer to her.
No. Nothing good will come by spoiling her.
Wait, Ken-chan!
Good morning, Asami-san.
Good morning, Kenji-san.
See you later, Onii-chan... Hiyori-oneechan.
Okay.
Bye, Yuki-chan
Hey, Kenji.
Hey, Minamiyama.
Give back that porno magazine soon.
I know!
Minamiyama-kun, Kiyoka-chan, good morning.
Good morning, Hiyori.
Good morning to you, too, Kenji.
Hello Ms. Small Girl with a Big Attitude.
What did you say?!
Hiyori, I can't believe you can stand being
with a guy like him in the morning.
Babysitting him is a pain, right?
Oh my, I don't babysit him.
Yeah, I'm the one who babysits her.
You never shut your mouth, do you?
Good morning, Yuki-chan.
Good morning, Shido-san.
I saw you! You're so lucky to be able to go
to school with your brother every day.
You two kind of looked like a couple, and the way you two
walk closely together made me feel kind of jealous.
A couple? You're kidding...
You two aren't related though, right? You﻿
can get married to each other, then.
That would be romantic and dramatic.
"Yuki".
"﻿Onii-chan".
Then you two will hold each other tightly.
Cut it out, Shindo-san.
Time to eat!
What is it, Hiyori?
I want to eat that. Let's trade side dishes.
No.
Pretty please?
Fine.
Wow, which should I pick.
I want to trade, too.
But this is the lunch you made, right?
You have the same stuff as me, so why?
Yeah, but...
Fine, pick whatever you want.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
It'll be Valentine's Day soon.
Yeah.
Y﻿uki... You give me chocolate every year, but
doesn't it take time if you make it yourself?
No.
Because I only make one.
That's true.
Yuki.
Look, it's a capsule machine.
This brings back memories.
Eh?
We used to use these a lot, remember, Yuki?
Onii-chan, let's go home.
Wha.. Yuki.
A while ago, I was afraid of being alone
at night in my room, so I cried.
Then Onii-chan knocked on the wall from the other room.
After that, I stopped being afraid of the dark.
Since then, I've had this feeling for him...
But I don't have the right to tell him my feelings.
Ken-chan, it's morning. Wake up.
Just a little more...
Don't say that, Ken-chan...
I've wanted to ask you two before, but why
do you two take turns in waking me up?
Because we just take turns, right?
Yup.
So why?
It's a secret.
Damn it.
Today...
I'm back.
Then this comes here.
So...
Okay.
How are you doing with your studying for tomorrow's test?
Well, it's already this late, and I don't﻿
think I can cover all the test material.
Stay over night, then.
Can I, Yuki-chan?
Okay...
Thanks, Yuki-chan.
Yuki-chan, your breasts are so soft.
Hiyori-oneechan...
That tickles.
Bear with it.
I'm washing you.
I don't think you are...
There, there.
Then it's my turn now.
Cut it out.
Why it is locked?
Come to think of it, we used to bathe together
like this when were young, right?
Do you remember your dream, Yuki-chan?
My dream?
Yeah, it's from when were elementary school kids.
My dream was to marry Ken-chan, and yours was to marry...
A prince on a white horse.
And that prince was Ken-chan, right?
Yeah.
My dream still hasn't changed, but...
She said she was going to study until morning,
but look at her... She just fell asleep.
What an useless childhood friend she is.
You must like her.
What? Me like Hiyori?
Yeah, you seem to have fun around her.
No way. She's trouble.
You're much more well-made compared
to her, so it helps a lot.
You're a nice sister to have.
A sister...
I'm done! I think I barely passed.
Thanks to me.
No way. It's because of my talent.
I taught you by sleeping overnight, you know.
You were just sleeping.
Theme Park
Oh, yeah... A new theme park opened.
I want to ride a coffee cup.
Then let's go tomorrow.
There's no school tomorrow, and we can
go as celebration that exams are over.
I second that! What time shall we go, Ken-chan?
Let's see...
We don't want to go too late, so...
So what time?
I want to go, too!
Yeah, let's go together.
Okay...
I'm sorry that I got in your way, Hiyori-oneechan.
It's water!!
Thanks, Ken-chan.
I had to cover myself too, anyway.
Are you okay, Yuki-chan?
Yeah... I screwed up there.
I thought you would be okay since
you're not as clumsy as Hiyori.
That's not true...
Ken-chan.
I was shopping since I ran out of ingredients.
Look forward to my chocolate this year.
I'm going to put a lot of effort into it
Hiyori...
You met Hiyori-oneechan?
Yeah.
She gives me chocolate every year, but
it's shaped weird and tastes like crap.
But I couldn't make fun of it this year.
I understood that she puts a lot of effort into making them.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, take this.
This?
It's chocolate.
But Valentine's Day is tomorrow.
Yeah... I won't be able to give it to you
tomorrow, since I'm going to be busy.﻿
Good night.
Yuki!
Going to be busy?
I broke the promise.
We promise to take turns doing this...
I won't be able to become his girlfriend
even if I give it to him first...
And this ring really isn't mine...
If he finds out, he'll probably hate me.
I don't want that.
Even if he looks at me as just a sister,
I want him to continue to like me.
Here you go, Ken-chan.
Thanks, Hiyori.
I can't do it. I just can't...
I can't smile seeing him like that...
What? Yuki-chan gave you chocolate yesterday?
Yeah.
Yuki-chan gave it first...
Hiyori?
Let's go home, Ken-chan. I'm sure
Yuki-chan will be waiting for you.
Okay.
Do you know how Yuki-chan feels about you?
What are you talking about?
Bye.
I know...
Yuki...
Yuki, are you crying?
I'm sorry.
Ken-chan, I have something important to talk about.
Can you go to my room?
How's Yuki-chan doing?
She doesn't seem to be doing too well, so I put her to sleep.
I see.
I hope she gets better soon.
Hiyori, what happened to the chocolate you gave...?
I took it back.
My chocolate tastes horrible, so you shouldn't eat it
I won't be making chocolates starting next year.
Why all of a sudden?
What a weird girl...
Ken-chan, will be you be sad if I suddenly disappear?
What's with you? You're acting weird today.
Answer me, Ken-chan.
I don't know what you're trying to get at.
You're right.
I'll be leaving now.
Ken-chan.
Only you can make Yuki-chan smile again.
Hiyori...
Since we were young, I've protected her as a real brother.
And that girl adores me as a man.
Then I...
Then I must have been looking at her as a woman.
But she's my sister, so I've been
restraining myself unconsciously...
Yuki, do you want to come to my room?
Eh?
Onii-chan...
That's...
It's the ring I got from you.
It's the ring that I had to give to Hiyori-oneechan.
Bu﻿t... I couldn't say it.
I was holding a prize from a capsule machine
from Hiyori-oneechon a long time ago.
Then you game me a light blue ring as
a present in exchange for the prize.
I was so happy that I forgot that
it was from Hiyori-oneechan.
So i couldn't talk to her about the ring.
She was the one who was supposed to get it...
The next day, I couldn't walk with the two of you.
I lied, saying that it would block the path for other people.
Then Hiyori-oneechan said let's take
turns walking together with you.
After that, we started to take turns for everything.
So that's how it was...
I was finally able to tell her about that yesterday.
After I apologized and told her everything, she told me...
That her prince wasn't you.
She was trying to make me feel better.
She shared the same feelings as me...
But I was still happy about it.
I'm a bad girl.
It doesn't matter.
Onii-chan, I love you.
I've liked you from before.
Me too, Yuki.
I can be besides with you, right?
It'll be troubling if you don't stay beside me
I'm happy.
I'm embarassed, Onii-chan.
Ouch...
S-Sorry...
Onii-chan...
You're...
Yuki.
I can leave everything up to you.
I'm coming in, Yuki.
Yuki.
I'm o﻿kay... So stick it in to the end...
Onii-chan...
N-No...
I don't want to get away from you anymore.
O-Onii-chan, I love you.
Onii-chan...
I got the ring back from you now.
Ken-chan.
Show me that you've made up your mind.
Or else, I...
Okay.
Yuki.
Onii-chan.
Give me that ring if you get bored with it.
Hiyori-oneechan
Don't get surprised, Kenji. Hiyori moved to another school.
She moved? Really?
She didn't even contact me, her best friend.
She could have said something.
Hiyori, did you just leave your smile behind for Yuki and me?
Hiyori...
Ken-chan.