Wanimaga Gastle
Caught you again.
Can't get enough of my cock, eh?
Only because it wasn't enough.
Boss! She's wearing a brand new body suit!
Excellent. We'll do battle...
with ninja sex tactics!
One-hit kill attack.
Penis inferno!
Where am I?
Fit.3 [Time-Traveling Kunoichi]
Mizugi Kanojo
Mizugi Каnоjo.
All right.
New suit for playing with Hiro-kun, nya nya...
Nyan!
Hello? Hiro?
This is a recording. Please leave
a message after the beep...
Dammit.
Come on, come on!
Jun, Jun!
Starring / Jun.
We're gonna be late.
Your mom already left for work!
Sweet Boing Boing Morning!!
Get out of bed already!
How can she sleep like this?
Now I've got his attention. Watch this!
Natsuki...
Talking in her sleep?
Come on, shy guy. I'm giving you a freebie!
Jun...
Come on, we're already late for first period.
Yes! He's checking out my rack!
Shit! Why's he being so rough?
S-Sorry!
Hey! They're boobs, not pizza dough!
You were pretending to be asleep.
Dummy, don't you know an invitation when you see it?
Sorry. It's just... your boobs look bigger lately.
If I seem indifferent, ifs because I'm trying not to stare.
I thought you'd been acting strange lately.
As for my boobs, they're clumsy but
I'm starting to appreciate them.
Shall we continue?
Natsuki...
I'm enjoying this. Am I a pervert?
Sorry.
You really like my titties, huh?
J-Jun...
Jun, you're getting so wet.
You dummy...
We can't top now.
Natsuki...
Put it in.
I want you inside me.
God, that's deep!
No... No, be gentler!
I can't help it. It feels so good.
So good... I've never had it like this!
Natsuki...
So nice and big...
Jun!
Natsuki... I... I love you!
I'm cumming!
Cumming!!
Yeah, baby!
Yeah...
Rewind, rewind!
Awesome! Look at those tits jiggle!
Oh, Jun!!
"Awesome," you say?
M-Mizuho...
I wish you'd have called first...
That's my phone...
You didn't answer, so what was I supposed to think?
Put your dick away.
So good! So good!
This is just... research! For us!
Research, huh?
Yeah!
Right there! Right there!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Hiro-kun, you dumb perv!
Mizu-
I'm done.
Mizuho!
Wait!
You gotta be kidding...
Ouch...
Hiro-kun? Are you okay?
Hiro-kun?
Hiro-kun!
Hey, come on...
Hiro-kun, wake up!
Hiro-kun! Hiro-kun!!
I told you, I'm not cheating!
But Okada-kun, you're so cool.
How could a boring girl like me be enough for you?
Jeez, you worry too much.
You need to lighten up.
I'm... sorry.
Why am I so pessimistic?
I want to change.
I've got to.
Enhance your look with Wani Optical
Man. Where the hell is she?
Sorry, been waiting long?
What took you so-
Who are you?
Don't recognize your own girlfriend?
M-Marina?
Come on.
Hey! Wait!
What's with you today?
New clothes... makeup...
Hey, Keisuke... isn't this hot?
Hey! People will see!
Would you enjoy taking this off me?
You mean...?
You're not undressing?
You're... different today.
You never wanted to come to a place like this before.
Off with your clothes!
Marina?
This guy seems to be waking up. What should I do with it?
Whoa, hold it!
Oh, you'd like me to "hold it," wouldn't you?
Marina...
Do I have to do all the work?
Of course not.
So good!
Marina... hey...
That was quite a load.
Am I that good?
Marina...
Well, I'm not done yet.
I'm pretty beat.
Quit your griping.
Don't you want to fuck me?
Yeah, I do.
Tonight I'm gonna make you cum a whole lot.
M-Marina!
Tight!
It's all in.
Oh my God! Your cock is so hard!
You're being rough.
If s okay. I'll let you cum as much as you want.
I'll do anything to make you feel good, Keisuke.
No!
M-Marina?
S-Sorry.
Marina, you...
Hold on. I just need my glasses.
What the hell for?
Can't you look at me unless your vision is distorted?
Just look me in the eye for once.
Okada-kun...
W-Wait Stop, it's embarrassing!
Look!
We're connected.
Let me show you how I feel.
Keisuke-kun...
We're so close now...
I feel him. I can feel Keisuke.
Keisuke!
Marina!
Don't change again.
I like you just like this.
Keisuke-kun!
Damn!
Where are we?
Boss!
What is this?
The enemy!
Tsuki! Kage!
Yes, boss!
Owie, owie, owie!
Male, unknown age. Hit by a truck while
naked. Prep the traction ward.
Wanimaga Hospital
You're lucky to be alive.
Yohei Mori | Shinji Etou | Kei Nakayama | Hiro Oota
Hiro, you dumb perv!
But this place sucks!
They say you'll be out in a month. If s like a vacation.
It's your own fault!
But a month of abstinence? They don't even have porn!
Um, Hiro-kun...
Don't make a scene.
Leave it to me.
I'm wearing my newest swimsuit.
Mi-zu-hooo!
Nobody will catch us here, right?
Not at this time of day.
And we can be as loud as we want.
Well, your wiener apparently doesn't need to be in traction.
Hey Mizuho, tit-fuck me with your suit on.
It'll feel good that way, yeah?
Really? If you say so.
Like this?
It does! Your swimsuit feels great!
Perv!
Huh? Who goes?
And what are they doing!?
Feels so awesome!
Even better than the real thing!
Don't make me jealous of my swimsuit.
It's good for you, too, right?
I see your stiff nipples.
Shut up. I expect pleasure downstairs, too.
You got it!
How's this?
Good, just like that.
I've never felt anything like this.
Good, so ifs working for both of us.
It's like I'm masturbating with your dick.
Amazing heat... and they aren't even fighting.
What kind of ninja are they?
It's making me hot!
Yes!
Hiro-kun, if somebody sees us like this...
Nobody's watching. Come on, spread 'em!
Mizuho!
Hiro-kun... your leg...
Just relax and let me do the work.
Whoa, I better hold on to something.
Grab them tight!
Shit, I'm gonna...
It's okay. You can cum inside me this time.
Oh, Mizuho!
Hiro-kun!
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
Curse my carelessness! Those three must
be somewhere nearby. But where?
Hey, Mizuho.
Sneak into the hospital tonight. We can fuck again!
What?
Come on, why not?
Well, I'd like to, but...
Don't you know the legend?
During the Feudal Period, there
was a castle on that mountain.
They say hundreds of warriors died there.
Come on, really?
And now the hospital is haunted by...
ninja ghosts!
Mizuho!
Let go of me! Keep your voice down!
Why's it always so windy when I take the night shift?
This is no job for someone scared of the dark.
Shower Room
Look at her. She's quite a beauty.
Any idea where we are, Boss?
Who cares? Today is our lucky day.