Ninjas?
Don't you Wanimaga mercenaries
ever get tired of chasing me?
You can say what you want.
Kuu of the Shirogane, we'll track
you to the ends of the Earth!
Certain kill: Air rage attack!
The pain!
My head!
Weaklings.
We won't forget this!
Nothing but an annoyance.
Still...
If I hadn't been wearing this skin-tight ninja singlet...
Yikes!
Mizugi Kanojo: The Animation
Mizugi Kanojo
Fit.2 [White Temptation]
This is a bit wild.
Then again, today is swimsuit sex day with Hiro-kun. Maybe wild is good.
Gotta pick the best one!
Julie, this one suits you!
Well, maybe... I guess I like the white color...
Julie, let's get this one. I'll buy it for you.
Control yourself, hornball!
You aren't exactly a model of modesty yourself.
But...
I know what'll happen if I wear this...
It looks great on you, Julie!
God, you can see right through it.
Wait, I should wear the support liner with this.
Bah, who needs it?
Jeez...
What? What are you doing?
Oh, baby! What a nice texture!
Pervert, get your dick of my new swimsuit!
Maybe you'd rather I did this.
No!
Wow, it's wet. That's a lot of pussy juice!
Shut up!
Let me do your tits next.
Like this?
Yeah! It's a whole new sensation!
You idiot!
Stop rubbing me like that. This is too weird.
Awesome!
Hey, that's going to stain!
Don't worry.
And that tickles!
My cockhead is so slippery... shit!
Oh, I'm gonna cum!
Ew, you got it all over me!
Not to worry.
Swimsuits are forgetting wet.
Now it looks even sexier.
This was your plan all along.
Who, me? Come on, Julie.
No, stop!
Sounds like a bag of wet eels.
Gross! Cut it out, all right?
No, stop!
What are you...
Oh, man... I might be ready to cum again soon!
But that'd be inconsiderate of me.
If s all in! Feels pretty good, huh?
It doesn't You're... such a pervert.
Don't be like that...
Check it out Your pussy is overflowing!
N-No...
Don't be such a perv!
Shit, it's like your pussy is milking me!
No, it isn't
And your nipples are harder than pencil erasers!
That's because... it feels good... so good!
Feels so good in my pussy!
I'm gonna cum, Julie!
Me too! Me too! I'm cumming!
I came a lot inside you...
Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot!
So we're getting the white one?
Get away from me, hornball!
W-Wait! Julie!
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe...
Ho, hum. I'm so bored.
What'll I do? What'll I do?
I wish something exciting would happen.
Um, hello? We're on a date here.
Onee-sama! Help me!
What'll I do?
What's the crisis, Shiori-san?
Yuki-kun asked me on a date.
Hey, good for you! I was starting to worry.
But I've never been on a date. What should I do?
We'll show you the ropes. Won't we, darling?
You mean Yuki-kun and I might become
a nice couple like you two?
Sure thing, Shiori-san.
O-Onee-sama...
So, you really think he'll like this?
Without a doubt It looks great!
But you can see... everything.
I feel so exposed.
You shouldn't hide your womanly charms.
Now you're going to practice with Hiroto.
But...
First, you must familiarize yourself with
the male body, to avoid embarrassment.
Look! Thanks to your sexy underwear, he's this happy.
Th-That's...
Go on, say hello to Mr. Penis!
All right.
Hello... Mr. Penis.
Now give him a kiss and peel back
the foreskin with your mouth.
Kiss? Foreskin?
Yes. Men love that kind of thing.
Is that true, Senpai?
Yep.
Okay.
Now peel back the skin.
All right.
Come on, Shiori. You want to learn to be refined, right?
Next, put it in your mouth!
It's so warm... I'm getting nervous.
That's the way. Take it all the way back into your throat.
What's wrong with me?
With this thing in my mouth.
I feel hot... dirty!
Looks like Hiroto's enjoying it.
Now try to swallow it all. Don't spit, if s impolite!
Okay.
Very good. Savor it carefully, like a fine wine.
Thank you, it was delicious.
It seems you've got it.
He's sucking.... sucking on my nipple! Like a baby!
This next part is very important.
Onee-sama, what's that?
It's very important... a tool of every proper lady.
N-No!
Already so wet! Did you enjoy that so much?
No...
It'll slide in easily.
No, you can't!
There. It's all the way in.
I can't believe you took my virginity with that thing!
Shiori-san, don't cry. There's nothing to worry about.
Penetration with a dildo doesn't count.
Really?
Also, your first time is likely to include anal.
Shiori-chan, let's begin.
Senpai, wait That's my butt...
Your penis is going inside my butt!
Shiori-san, how's that feel?
Feels strange... like my insides... are getting scrambled.
All right, get ready. This next part
is called double penetration.
Incredible!
Oh my god... my ass!
Your ass is so tight Shiori-chan.
Oh god...
My ass isn't... going to be the same after this.
I never knew I had such a slutty younger sister!
No!
I never knew my older sister wanted to rape me!
Dirty talk can make you feel good, too. Try it.
Pussy! Pussy! Pussy! Pussy! Wow, you're right!
Together!
Look at that. My sister's going to be a fine lady.
Um, Shiori-chan...
The answer is yes, Yuki-kun.
Shiori-chan?
I'm ready to have sex with you.
Shiori-chan!?
You are cordially invited to fuck my ass.
You sure picked a unique place to do this.
Hiro-kun, please... I need you inside me.
Horny as ever, aren't you?
You must have a real swimsuit fetish.
Hiro-kun, you taste so good!
Doing it in my swimsuit gets me so excited.
Look how wet my pussy is.
Here you go.
Good, keep quiet just like that.
How'd you get to be such a nympho?
It's like you're descended from nymphos or something.
As if!
WANIMAGA CASTLE
Your mission is the assassination
of the Wanimaga Daimyo.
He has ninja bodyguards,
but they shouldn't pose you any trouble.
Understood.
We meet again.
You again?
Sheesh.
Kuu of the Shirogane! You won't get away like last time.
Where do you want your injury this time?
Your smugness will be your end!
Is this all you've got?
Cloth storm attack.
Got you!
Curses!
Look at Kuu.
She looks good in this pose, don't you think?
Shit!
Shall we have some fan?
Let's do it, boss.
No!!
She's making a racket.
What other sounds can you make?
No, stop!
What.. I can't move! What ninja magic is this?
How about if I do this?
S-Stop!
This part of her body is reacting favorably.
Same thing over here!
Stop it!
What's wrong? Nothing witty to say all of a sudden?
You don't know who you're messing-
Kuu, you've mocked us long enough.
For that, you'll be punished.
You've been hiding some impressive equipment.
What are you doing?
I think you know.
No!
Keep your filthy... tongue out of me!
So much juice, and we're just getting started!
You filth!
I said, no more tongue!
Impossible... these dogs... making me hot?
Come on, show us your ninja moves.
Rather than suffering this indignity...
Please kill me.
This will be a plug...
for your annoying mouth.
Impudent bitch!
Now we're getting somewhere!
Your body belongs to us now.
Damn it.. I'm going to faint...
Kuu of the Shirogane... pathetic!
Well then, let's dig in.
You first, boss.
Giving us a great view, aren't you, Kuu?
No, stop...
Consider this your ultimate ninja training!
W-Wait!
I hereby promote you from "ninja girl" to "ninja woman!"
What? Speechless with ecstasy?
N-No! No!
Your pussy's hugging my dick like it can't get enough!
Let's finish her off, boys!
Yes, boss!
God, no!
She's relaxing. Feels even better!
My mouth, my ass, my pussy...
all full of cock... why do I feel like this?
Just a little more!
Almost there!
Their dicks are burning hot They're
going to blast me with semen!
Go, boys!
Yes, boss!
No more fight in you?
We'll face you again, any time.
I'm finally... satisfied.
What?
Mizuho, how much longer?
I can't... get enough swimsuit sex!
Come on, boys!
What's this tongue technique?
Oh no!
Sorry, boss!
Guys, what are you...?
More cum!
God, you're insatiable.
Now for my final attack!
Lightning thrust!
I'm cumming again!
Okay, so... are you done?
Wait? You're still going?
You guys started it.
It'll never stop!
I'm cumming!!
I'm camming!!
Can it be?
We've awakened...
...a living nightmare!
It'll never stop!
Let's do it with this one next!