Once more...
We'll see each other again...
Onii-chan, I'm coming in.
Here, I got your uniform from the cleaners.
I'm putting it in the closet, okay?
Oh, thank you.
Hmm...
There's a technique in opening it.
A technique?
Uh-huh.
There, see?
I don't think I can remember all of that.
Oh, you'll learn.
There.
Only Hiyori can open this.
Sister Hiyori...
I wonder how are you doing now...
That clumsy friend of ours is probably
happy in her new school.
So let's not worry about her anymore.
Hey Onii-chan, you can be really mean sometimes.
Later! Good night!
Good night!
Huh?
What the?
Whoa, it's dark!
It's cramped and dark in here!
Help me!
Ow, ow, ouch.
Huh?
W-What is this?
Might this be, a butt?
Whoa!
Hi-Hiyori!
The color of my sky...
Watashi no sora no iro
2nd Period: Hiyori's Chapter
I breathe once on a winter street
Hitoiki fuyu no michi
I frolicked around you all the time
Zutto soba de hashaideta
The left hand you stretched out felt really far away
Sashidashita hidari te ga sugoku toukute
I couldn't hold in my tears, and the sky I'm used to seeing was light blue
Namida koraekirezu minareta sora wa itsumo mizuiro
The wind blows through my hearts as I just stand there
Tachidomaru kokoro no naka fukinukeru kaze
The ring still shines deep in my memories
Kioku no soko hikaru ring imamo zutto
Hi-Hiyori...
What the heck are you doing here?
I don't know how I got here.
All I can remember is being inside the closet.
You suddenly transferred to another school.
Then you suddenly show up in here without telling.
Transferred?!
Huh, did I transferred to another school?
Can't you remember?
It was last month.
No, not at all.
Furthermore, Where do you live at now.
No, I don't have any clue at all.
Really.
Hi-Hiyori...
Your body...
Body?
My body is exposed!
I-I'm ashamed!!
Hiyori...
Huh?
Hmmm, my spare clothes.
Could it be?!
There.
All done!
Thanks, Ken-chan!
Onii-chan, my spare...
Floating panties!!
Ah! Yu-Yuki!
This is terrible!
Yuki-chan...
Lost consciousness!
Why did Yuki-chan passed out?
Ken-chan?
Why did you took a picture?
Just a little bit...
Hmmm...
She's on it.
Huh?
Hiyori?
She vanished.
Hiyori...
Another test again, really!
What are you doing there, Kenji?
What's that on your hand?
Good timing...
Everyone, look at this.
Huh?
What is this, a trick picture?
Boring.
Yes, it is.
I thought it was something more interesting.
I want to see something like Kenji's
nude picture or Yuki's, damn it!
That's right!
Something really perverted to help me down here!!
Kenji-san, what do you want to tell us by showing this?
If you can't see anything, never mind.
I know it, they can't see Hiyori.
Huh?
It's dark again!
Hiyori!
Whoa!
Ken-chan, please open it slowly.
Hiyori, are you a ghost?
Huh, me a ghost?
Ha, ha, that can't be.
Onii-chan, I'm coming in.
Yuki-chan!
Yahoo!
Huh?
Here are some of my clothes, Onii-chan.
Because stealing them is wrong.
Eh?
If Onii-chan has a fetish with this
sort of things, just let me know.
If you want more, I'll bring it next time...
Later!
Yu-Yuki! You misunderstood!
The clothes are for Hiyori!
Do you understand? If she saw you naked, it'll drive her nuts.
Besides, Yuki can't see you at all.
Only I can.
Huh?!
I guess I really did turn into a ghost!
Why did you turn into a ghost anyway?
I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
I'm confused.
What happened to me?
Hiyori...
Well, nothing we can do about it.
I guess I'll just enjoy being a ghost!
You worry me a little...
There.
Ken-chan, do you have a test tomorrow?
Alright, I'll tutor you.
Hey, come over here.
Hey... Hiyori!
Alright, let's begin!
This must be...
Um...
Garbage Head
I knew it. It's really fun to be with Ken-chan.
The test is finished!
We're free now.
Kenji, want to hang-out and play?
Sorry but I have to do something.
So you're really leaving me alone!
You meanie!
Later.
Onii-chan...
Why am I inside the closet again?
I can't see anything in here.
It's dark here Ken-chan!
Maybe he's still at school...
I remember I hid here when we were young.
I got trapped and Ken-chan can't open the door.
Until Ken-chan's father came home...
We were both crying.
Ken-chan really tried to open the door but failed.
He was always there knocking on the door.
He's really kind hearted.
That's why I like Ken-chan.
Aaah, my legs?!
I'm glad, was that an illusion?
What was that I just saw?
Ah!
Ken-chan, open the door!
Uh, Hiyori!
Ken-chan...
I asked you to take me out for
helping you study for your test.
Why did you took me to the park?
It's boring here!
It can't be helped.
There would be trouble if people see floating
clothes in the shopping district...
But, but...
Okay, where do you want to go?
To the amusement park and ride on the spinning coffee cups!
Impossible, there's too many people in there
Well, how about to a family restaurant?
Can we?
We'll drink a glass of orange juice with two straws together.
Romantic, huh?
Yeah, right...
So cold.
How come I don't feel so?
Is it because I'm a ghost?
Are you cold?
Thank you.
I'm sorry for taking you here.
Don't be, it's really romantic.
Eh?
It's going to be a special service today.
Thank you, Ken-chan.
Want to drink more?
No...
I don't want this to ever run out.
Aaah, it's dark!
There you go.
Ken-chan!
Are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Eh?
H﻿ere.
You opened it too fast and I was surprised.
Could it be that you waited for me after school?
Thank you, Ken-chan!
Now, now.
It's only by chance, I'd never waited for you.
Oh, Hiyori.
Is that a straw?
Uh huh, it's the straw from that time.
Why didn't you throw it away.
But...
But... But...
Okay, I understand. Do as you wish.
By the way.
Why did you became a ghost?
I don't know. I just ended up here.
Hi-Hiyori!
Your legs!
Huh?
My legs?
No, no, not again!
Again?
Yes, it happened before.
I don't understand why.
A little odd for a ghost, huh?
Could it be that you are vanishing?
P-please don't ever say that.
It stopped before. Maybe it'll stop again.
Again?
Please, stop.
Don't scare me like that, Hiyori.
I'm really glad it stopped...
This is the second time I saw it happened.
Please, no more...
Ken-chan.
Huh?
Tomorrow will be white day.
I would love to receive a present from you.
I can't remember getting any chocolates from you...
Not even a small one...
Is that so?
That's why I don't have to give anything back.
Eh? Say it ain't so.
Just for now, I'll prepare something.
Really!
What? What? What?
You'll know what, tomorrow.
Let's meet tomorrow, okay?
For sure, right?
She disappeared again...
Just like the time she transferred before...
Now that Hiyori's back, I finally understood
my true feelings for her...
How come I can't say that I love her?
No, I can't...
Hiyori...
Can't sleep...
Can't sleep but I feel I have to.
I have to take some medicine for tomorrow's operation...
The nurse had told me to do so...
An uncertain operation but I regret nothing.
However, what is this?
What is this bad feeling right now?
Wake up...
Ken-chan.
Hiyori!
Sorry, I missed to come a day.
It's okay, we'll do another white day again.
I know Hiyori likes it so let's anywhere.
Ken-chan, thank you.
OPERATION
Ken-chan, everyone's looking.
Aren't you embarrassed?
Not at all, as long as I don't lose you.
Thank you.
Ken-chan, don't let go.
If I ever disappear again, I wouldn't know what to do.
I'm afraid.
We'll stay together forever.
Uh?
Ken-chan?
Hiyori.
You're beautiful, Hiyori.
Ken-chan.
More.
I'm ashamed.
Hiyori...
It hurts!
Hiyori?
I'm okay so...
Ken-chan, Ken-chan!
Where do you want me to come, Hiyori?
In here...
More, more...
I'm together with Ken-chan...
I wish I would never go away from here.
I love you, Hiyori!
I love you too!
Together, forever...
Ken-chan?
Right now, we will never be apart.
Thank you...
I-I really did gave you a chocolate.
I really don't like going away.
I always wished I was close to Ken-chan.
OPERATION
Hiyori?
I really had a good time but I can't see you anymore.
I'm really sorry, Ken-chan.
Hiyori, what do you mean by this?
I can't remember everything.
I am not what you think I am.
Because if you see the real me, it would only make you sad.
What do you mean to see the real you, Hiyori?
Bye, Ken-chan...
Hi-Hiyori!
Sorry...
Thank you..
I'll never forget with this ring on...
Hiyori!
Hiyori!!
I'm all alone again.
A valentine's day chocolate. Hiyori must had made it.
A note is attached.
Huh?
I like you, Ken-chan.
You're too embarrassed to tell me.
Stupid Hiyori...
I need to reply to Hiyori's confession.
I wonder where you are...
Huh?
I found you at last, Hiyori.
Who are you?
Hiyori...
Sorry, I lost my memory.
I could only remember one thing. The name of the man I love.
I think his name was... Ken-chan.
I am that Ken-chan, Hiyori.
Alright!
I got it right this time!
This must be your strong subject.
The part of the amusement park that I like most is?
That will be the spinning coffee cups, right?
I embarrassed, I can't taste a thing
Kokoro no kakera sagasuyou ni
I kept looking for you...
You want to try it though, huh?
You seem to know everything about me.
I still can't remember everything yet.
Kimi no koto sagashitsuzuketeta
As if I was looking for a fragment of my heart
Hiyori, that ring...
Why I always...
Mono-chro no mainichi ga kimi ga ite kagayaki hajimeteku
My monochrome every day started to gain color as you entered my life
Why am I shedding tears?
You gave me the courage to face the fear of breaking something
Kowashite shimau kawasani tachimukau yuuki wo kuretane
The strength to open the window to the future
Mirai no mado akeru tsuyosa wo
I love you. Just that enables me to go without hesistation
Kimi ga suki tada soredakede mayowazu ikerunda
I will walk this path with you forever...
Mlzuiro no kirei na sora no shita wo itsumademo
Under the beautiful light blue sky
Kimi to aruiteku kono michi wo futari de