I'm Moe. It's nice to meet you.
It's okay... take a good look.
I'm yours anyways...
Are you feeling nervous?
Just relax.
Just relax...
Now it's time to get this dick clean.
Okay... it's all dean now.
Does it feel good?
Already this hard...
Say ahh...
Your dick is so hard...
Your just came too...
Amazing...
I don't think my pussy can stand it anymore...
Do you want to put your dick in already?
How does my pussy feel?
Does it feel good?
It's hitting me... hitting me...
hitting me deep inside...
You can as much as you want inside me...
No... that spot is...!
I'm going to cum...
Cumming...
It's okay... you don't have to hold it in.
Just squirt it out.
I like this a lot...
More...
Give it to me more...
I'm in love with your dick...
I'm there already...
I'm cumming...
Cumming...!
Please come again...
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч