This must be really hard for you.
I'm Honami, deceased Kasuga Satoshi's wife.
Thank you for coming here today even though you're busy.
Translated by SubDESU-H
Satoshi-san...
I have something important to tell you.
What is it?
Honami...
Marry me!
Eh?
How about it?
Am I really good enough?
No one else would be right, Honami.
I'm happy, thank you!
I promise that I'll build us a happy family.
Satoshi-san!
Satoshi-san, you promised that you'll make a happy family...
You bitch!
If you didn't exist...
Kayoko-san?
You're the one who killed nii-san!
What?
You ignored the objection of the people and got married,
and he had a heart attack while you two went on your honeymoon!
K-Kayoko-san...
This kid too.
I'm the one taking care of this kid since his mother died.
You took away nii-san's property and his life!
It's not like that, why are you saying such things?
Nee-san!
I won't give this kid and nii-san's property to you!
I don't need the property.
I just wanted to live happily with Satoshi-san!
I will not believe you.
Let's go, Manabu.
Ok...
What should I do?
Nee-san...
It's not yet decided that Honami-san is to be blamed.
That woman killed nii-san.
It's impossible that nii-san, who was healthy, died suddenly.
I will not give her nii-san's property.
You can think of that later.
I am your mother, Manabu.
I'm the one who's taken care of you for so long.
Yes you're right, nee-san.
Nee-san... you always call me that.
Hey, why don't we crush that woman's future?
What?
I'll take everything from her.
Manabu-san and Kayoko-san are not home yet.
Ok then, crush this bitch immediately.
What are you doing?
Stop this!
Let me go!
Rape this woman completely.
What are you saying?
Manabu-kun, no! You shouldn't do this!
No!
Stop, don't put it in!
No, no!
This woman doesn't need a meaning in her life, rape her quickly.
Stop!
Please forgive me!
No!
Here, look at yourself.
Look at how you're going to be messed up.
No, no!
Stop!
Take it out!
To make you unhappy is our only wish.
We don't care if we're reported or busted after raping you.
There's no need to hold it in, Manabu.
Release as much as you want inside her.
W-What are you saying!?
No!
Don't release it inside!
That serves you right.
"Let's make this a happy family".
Nee-san, this...
What's this?
What is that Honami thinking even when that incident happened?
I can't believe this!
She still doesn't want to go out?
Why is she still living in this house?
I don't know!
But we just need to make her understand.
The sin of deceiving nii-san and how scary we are.
Nee-san...
It's rude to meet her empty-handed so,
let's bring her a souvenir.
Welcome home.
Oh... umm...
Thank you for inviting us.
So you're not going to report or get mad at us?
I won't report you to police,
but aside from that, I have something I wanted to do.
I just wanted to fulfill the promise Satoshi-san made of making a happy family.
If you want to rape me to make you feel better then do it.
But I want you to understand that I loved Satoshi-san.
Well then, I'll feel free to rape you.
Hey, suck it properly!
What a nice facial expression you're showing.
Honami-san, don't ever try to spill Manabu's semen.
Drink it all!
No! You mustn't spit it out!
How cruel...
You're such a cruel person...
You have a nice face now.
I have a special souvenir for you today.
It's fit to your resolution.
That's...
Oh? Are you not satisfied with it's size?
Do I need to prepare a bigger one for a nasty whore like you?
Let's start!
It hurts!
I can't handle one this big!
I can't!
It hurts!
Please take it out!
That part hurts!
Yes, that face...
Honami-san's face that suffers in pain is what I wanted to see.
Please don't make it move!
No more!
You rape her too, Manabu.
Fill this whore's other hole too.
Sorry, I'm the one to be blamed, please forgive me!
Good, I like your attitude.
So you finally realize that you're the one to be blamed.
Yes, I'm the one to be blamed, it's my fault, please forgive me!
No, I won't accept your tepid resolution.
Manabu, put it in.
Hurry!
No, please don't put that in!
My butt... that part hurts!
Where is “that part”?
Say it.
That part!
It hurts!
Say what it is.
My pussy...
Yes, your pussy and anus.
Pussy and anus...
Good...
Good!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
I can't... do it anymore.
Get down faster.
Yes.
You, the chief mourner, must walk first.
Kayoko-san.
Let's not do this here.
I want nii-san to know that we're happy.
And I must tell him how the training of the nasty whore is going.
Ok them, cum in front of nii-san.
Walking the street wearing embarrassing clothes and then cuming in front of nii-san's grave...
What a horrendous bitch you are.
Satoshi-san... please forgive me, please forgive me!
I'm cumming!
Take off the panties. You know what to do after that, right?
Yes, you must lick it.
Good.
Make use of your tongue more and stimulate the clitoris.
There... good.
Lick more... stimulate the clitoris more...
Make me cum.
I... can't... hold it any longer.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Hey Manabu, what happened to you?
Why?
Yes, Honami is the one you must rape.
There's no mistake.
Nee-san!
I loved nee-san for so long.
T-That's not allowed.
Kayoko-san...
S-Stop it, Manabu...
Nee-san's pussy is beautiful.
It's so delicious.
N-No...
Nee-san,
I'll put it in.
No... no... Manabu...
But it's all wet.
This is like a dream!
I want to release inside nee-san.
No... you mustn't...
Manabu!
Nee-san, here I come!
Satoshi-san...
We've really become a family.