Sorry.
Wh-What's wrong, Senpai?
Mei.
Sorry, I'm running out of money this month,
so could we just go to a manga café for today's date?
Uh, well...
I don't really care about the place.
Really?
Thank god!
Let's
do it
Again
Let's make Love
Well, actually,
I'm happy.
Alright, let's do it here.
It's so...
intense.
Wow!
Senpai.
No Vacancy
Rooms Available
This could do.
No.
More.
Alright, wanna do it here?
Good!
It feels good!
Senp—
This is the only place that'll do.
Coming.
I'm coming.
Coming!
He's always just taking me to a hotel right off the bat.
I want a normal date for once.
karaoke
Internet & Manga Café
Welcome.
Ah, it's for two.
Um, this one.
It'll be a free-time couple sheet, right?
Yeah, that'll be good.
Take your time.
What did you choose, Senpai?
Man milk.
You're always going with that.
Mei.
H-Hey, what're you doing?!
Naughty stuff.
We can't possibly do it in a place like this.
On the contrary, this is the perfect place to do it.
Just listen to those next door.
It can't be!
Ah, this is how it goes again.
Hey, please don't strip me!
What're we going to do when the waitress comes?
Ah, that's what worries you?
Well then...
Hold your voice.
N-Not like I can help it...
H-Hey, Senpai!
No!
Aww, my voice...
Eh, what was that noise?
Isn't it a couple sheet?
Oh, I see.
So that's what it was.
Aw, I told you.
N-No, they heard it!
It's embarrassing, and yet...
Heh, you're this wet already.
I know I just have to endure it,
but when I think of it, I just end up...
Dear customers?
Huh...
I would like to show you a special offer.
S-S-Senpai!
What do we do?!
Calm down.
A blanket.
We could hide it under a blanket.
Excuse me.
Our food menu has a huge discount right now.
You may order something, if you so please.
Um...
Let's see...
Um, err...
Stupid Senpai!
Why can't you stop while she's here?!
Ask for her recommendation.
Huh?
What it is?
Anyway, just ask her yourself.
U-Um, could you recommend... something?
Yes, I can.
She'll hear my moans again!
This is a well-balanced dish with plenty of boiled seasonal vegetables in it.
She's this close, and he's still going...
S-Senpai, which one should we choose?
Huh?
Um...
Err...
Stop!
If I cum, she'll notice it.
No!
I'm on my limit.
We don't need anything.
Sorry, Onee-san.
Huh?!
I'm sorry I bothered you.
Let's see.
S-S-Senpai.
Geez.
I know:
You were twitching awfully while you were talking to her.
No.
N-No, don't.
Not here.
No.
Stop it.
Coming.
I'm coming!
Huh?
Yeah, you're right;
it's just as you said.
You can't moan so immorally here.
We're supposed to be reading manga.
Why?
I was about to...
Hmm?
Something wrong?
I can't know it unless you tell me.
I-It's embarrassing, but stopping half-way...
is just painful!
Please, finish what you started.
Well done saying it.
Be gentle, Senpai.
Hmm?
I can't hear you.
I-If you enter so suddenly, my voice will leak.
Mei, does it feel good?
It feels way too good!
P-Please don't ask me that.
I'm at my limit.
Huh?
Are we stopping?
I can't continue.
I'm coming soon like this.
Senpai.
I can't take any more.
No can do.
I'm past the point of no return.
I-I can't take this!
I-I'm coming.
I'm coming real soon.
Coming.
Shit...
Don't be so loud!
Senpai, why...
Mei, you came?
Well, I didn't come yet.
Your voice.
Bear with me.
No way.
He's still going?
I only just came...
Senpai, please, I can't go on.
They'll hear me.
It'll be soon over.
Hang in there.
No way.
It's so rough!
If you do it so roughly...
I-I think I'll come again.
No good.
I'm coming soon.
I can't hold it.
I'm at my limit.
I can't.
There's no use.
I'm coming.
Coming.
Coming again.
I'm coming again!
I'm coming soon.
Your mouth.
You're cute.
Man milk's great!
I came lots of times with loud moans.
I'm embarrassed.
Ah, you wanna drink man milk too?
No thanks.
Hmm?
How about you take it from my mouth?
No really, I'm fine.
Huh?
You're all wet, Mei.
Let's do it again.
Geez, let me read manga!