www.SubDESU-H.net
I'm sorry!
What's wrong, senpai?
Mei, I'm sorry.
I'm really tight on funds this month.
So for our next date...
Would it be okay to just hang out at a manga café?
Well...
I'm fine with any place.
Really?
I'm glad.
Wanna go for
another round?
Subdesu-H
This actually...
...makes me happy!
Alright, let's go here then.
No, it's too intense...
Oh wow...
Senpai...
Hmm... I guess this is the place.
Oh no...
More...
Well, this place might be good.
Oh yes...
It feels good...
Senpai...
This is the only spot!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
We always head straight to a love hotel!
I want a normal date!
Welcome.
A room for two, please.
This one.
A couple seat, with no time limit.
Would that be alright?
Yes, please.
Enjoy your stay.
Senpai, what did you get?
Ca*pis.
You always get Cal*is.
Mei!
H-Hey!
What are you trying to do?
Sex.
We can't do it here!
Oh yes we can.
Listen to those two in the other room.
No way...
Jeez, we still did it in the end.
Hey, don't make me strip here!
What if the employees see us?
Well, you're right.
Then...
Lower your voice.
No way, even if you say that...
W-Wait, senpai, don't...
Don't...
Oh no, my moans...
Eh? What was that moan?
These are the couples' rooms, right?
Oh, I see.
So that's what's happening.
My, that's why I told you to pipe it down.
No, no, no...
We were heard?!
This is so embarrassing...
I need to hold it in.
But when I think about it, I just feel more...
Sir, Ma'am?
It's the timed room service, and I'm here to provide suggestions.
S-Senpai, what are we going to do?
Calm down.
There's a blanket here,
so hide in here.
Excuse me.
We have quite a number of good deals at this time.
I'll be taking a few orders, if you wish.
Well, how should I decide?
Umm... well...
Senpai,, you idiot!
Why are you doing that now?
Try to ask her what she would suggest.
We're going to ask her?
Hey, please ask her yourself!
Umm... would you have any good suggestions?
Yes, indeed I do.
She's going to hear it!
Here are some seasonal salads.
You'll get more for the same price,
and it even gets cheaper before closing hours.
She's right in front of us... oh no...
Se-Senpai, what will you have?
Well... umm....
Stop it!
She'll find out if I moan...!
I'm at my limit...
Thanks, but we're good.
Sorry about that, miss.
I'll be leaving then.
Now then...
Se-se-senpai... you're such a...
I get it already.
It was twitching a lot as you were talking to her.
That's not...!
No... don't...
Not in this place...
Oh no...
No, no, don't...
Yeah, I guess you're right.
You're completely right.
I can't do something that would break the rules of conduct in this shop.
This is a place where you read manga!
Why?
Just a little more and I would have...
What's wrong?
I won't know unless you say it.
I-It's embarrassing, but...
The way it ended suddenly...
Just makes it more unbearable!
Please...
Do it, until the end.
Well said.
Senpai, do it slowly.
I can't hear you.
I'm going to lose it quickly if you push it in so quickly.
Mei, does it feel good?
It feels so good, it's making me feel weak.
P-Please don't ask things like that.
I can't hold back any longer...
So, we're done already?
I'm going to cum quickly if we keep doing it like this.
Senpai, I really can't hold back anymore.
Stop, if you say that again I might not be able to stop myself as well.
No, this is...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming already!
I'm cumming!
Why did you just let your voice out like that?
But I...
Senpai, it's just...
Mei, you came.
I haven't cum yet, though.
Hold your voice in.
No way, we're still not done?
And I just came.
Senpai, I can't take it anymore.
I can't control my moans.
It's just a little more, so hold on.
No way, this is too intense...
If you keep pushing that hard, I'll...
I'll...
I'll cum again...
Oh no, I'm going to cum...
I can't hold it in anymore...
I can't...
Oh no, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming again!
I'm about to cum.
Here I go!
Take it in your mouth.
How cute.
Cal*is tastes great!
I came lots of times.
That was so embarrassing!
Wanna drink Cal*is?
No thanks.
Should I give it to you mouth-to-mouth then?
No thanks, really.
Ah!
Mei, you're wet again.
Wanna go for another round?
Jeez, let me read my manga!
www.SubDESU-H.net