Good morning.
That outfit...
I tried my best to choose
clothes that guys would enjoy.
H-how does it look?
She's so sexy...
She really is a bit of a slut...
She looks so healthy,
and has the hips for bearing children.
A bunch of guys tried to hit on me,
but I did my best to shake them off.
So... today, can we...
She's so cute and hot!
I love her!
Her gentle personality is the best!
This smell and huggability is also the best!
I can tell that she's feeling it.
There, there, it's all good.
I-I can't anymore...
Wha...
Did you cum...?
Yes...
For some reason, I've been feeling
good in that spot since yesterday...
and it feels so good no
matter where you touch me...
I feel like I might break...
Take me somewhere...
and fuck me...
Quickly...
I-I mean, I knew we were going to fuck, but...
Who would have thought it'd be
at the beginning of the date...
There's no mistake.
This girl...
Even though she's so nice and seems so pure,
she just loves... absolutely loves sex.
Her hole feels so good no matter
how many times I fuck her.
It's just as amazing as well today.
The smell of her shampoo...
Her voice keeps coming out...
She reacts with every thrust.
She's so cute!
I-I want to make her cum more...!
It feels like it's twisting more than yesterday...
and keeps twitching...
Her entire body is so soft...!
Okada, this is too much for me to hold in...
I thought we would calm down
if we did it a couple of times,
but we just get more and more in lust.
Everyone is death staring at me...
I guess it's not the most surprising thing.
We're on a short break from having sex.
Yui must be spewing pheromones
left and right as we walk right now.
My juices overflow even if I put on underwear...
I want to get to a hotel already...
Legs... move faster please...
Yui, do you want it that much?
Uh... I'm sorry...
Do you consider yourself slutty?
I probably did a lot of masturbating...
Do you hate slutty girls?
No, I absolutely love them.
To be honest, you should probably be going out
with someone much better than me right now.
But, because of the pheromones
that just ooze out of you,
it could be that you just attracted a
bunch of bad guys for the longest time.
Just from treating her normally and cherishing her,
this girl will fall absolutely for any guy.
What a nice bed that seems so good for sex...
Over there a hard, big cock...
is going to mess me up all the way
deep inside again as we make love...
Is she imagining having sex right now?
In that case...
I'm going to fuck you so good
that you won't be able to stand.
O-okay...
My mind is fading... it's going blank...
I want to bring her to the
deep depths of pleasure...!
Such a deep kiss...
I want it...
Feel it...
Feel it more!
I just want to have good, regular ol' sex with you.
Multiple times!
With this body that has only
known rape in the past!
Her thong is a mess right now.
She's already cumming a bit again...
I want to make her body and soul all mine forever...
I love you...
Okada, I love you...
Yui...
– You're... by yourself...
– D-don't tease me...
I'm at my limit already...
I want to fuck her right this moment already,
but I want to make her feel even better.
– Yui, you cum a lot, don't you.
– I can't anymore...
– You're terrible...
– Yui, you cum a lot, don't you.
– It felt good, right?
– I-I'm cumming...
– You're making a puddle.
Okada...
Okada... I want to make you feel good too...
My pussy is doing all sorts of things right now...
I'm sure it'll feel good...
So...
I beg of you...
I want your cock...
Cum buckets inside me...
Fuck me a bunch...
I am your girlfriend, so...
It's no use...
I can't hold myself back anymore either...!
The creampies I gave her in
the net cafe are overflowing...
This feeling!
Her fucking pussy is too good!
My girlfriend's pussy feels too good!
– All the cum inside her is out now.
– Your cum...
Your seed... what a waste...
I'll give a fresh batch right now...!
So good...
How many creampies is that already...
He's cumming so much from
my pussy... I'm so happy...
I love you... I love you so much...
I want to come here everyday...
Just how many fucking times
have I creampied her already...
She's still in her teens, and her skin is so clear.
Her tits are also so huge and soft...
I want her, my beloved girlfriend,
to have my baby...
I've cum so much my eyes are twitching...
It feels so good!
Yui... Yui...!
Damn I came a lot...
I cummed 23 times.
We weren't able to go to the movies in the end.
Yeah...
But then again, you're so energetic
even though you came that much.
I have pretty good stamina.
I rarely even catch colds.
Yeah, I can see that.
Oh, can I go to the toilet for a sec?
Of course.
I didn't mean it that way...
Yay, we're having sex again...
How many times are we gonna have sex today?!
But, I end up having sex with my
girlfriend wherever it seems like we can!
So... so good...
We're having such good sex
in a public toilet stand...!
It feels so good...!
It feels so much different than when I
was a plaything for those delinquents...
So deep...
He doesn't dry up and he doesn't
force it into my ass either...
He just has regular sex with me...
Okada, I love you...!
How many times did he make me cum today...
I can't even count how many times...
I love you... I love you so much...
I want to make him feel even better...
I'm going to piss myself!
Gotta take a piss!
Hold it in a bit more dude.
Someone's here...!
– Did you see the video of that 16-year old gravure idol?
– We should be quiet for the time being...
– Oh, that one?
– E-eh...
That girl's body is so god damn hot...
I'll bet she's at least a G.
Damn, she's so freaking huge.
Right?!
If she sucked me off with that face, I'll bet
I cum inside her mouth within 5 seconds.
My girlfriend with a better
body than that gravure idol,
is letting me fuck her mouth right now...
Yui... I'm cumming...
My mouth is so full of Okada's cum...
Let out more...
Give me more...
Can't you wait just a bit?
I-it's because you made me feel so good...
I still have to repay you back...
I want you to feel good as well.
What a nice kid she is...
She makes me love her more and more.
Um... so...
Pl-please let me have your baby.
I think I'm already pregnant from
getting creampied this much already.
Is it ok for me to have your child?
I'll quit school and go to work.
I'll even do the talking with my parents.
I won't cause you any trouble.
So let me have your child, please!
Marry me and raise it with me together...
I love you...
Okada, I love you...
Sex...
More sex...
I'm still young so I can give birth to a lot of kids!
There's no way anyone could be better than Yui!
This is mating for real now...
I'm going to pour it into the
deepest spot I haven't reached yet...
The guy in his 30s had nothing in
his head but to impregnate her.
The female high school student had nothing in her
head but wanting to give birth to the man's child.
The raw animal sex of a couple
who are determined to have a kid.
Out of lusting for each other too much,
they bump into each other
with such force as they sweat.
A perfect grip on the penis
that spews sperm like a fountain...
Sex where they give and take!
Having sex till the morning in
a toilet was a bit excessive...
You're too freaking erotic...
To be honest, I can still keep going plenty.
Where will you fuck me next?
Let's see...
Maybe at your place.
Or a movie theater with no one in it.
Or inside a bathtub.
Oh, I want to do some role-playing too.
Gosh... you're such a perv...
Let's do all of it.
Geez...
Okada, you already touched it so much already...
Your ass is so full... I can grope it for days...
I'm so happy...
The light turned gr-green...
Yeah...
There still isn't enough cum to make a baby yet.
I want to make sure I can have your baby.
So let's hurry back home so that
we can go one more round...
G-god damn...
She's so hot and cute!
My girlfriend is too hot and cute!
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч