I didn't intend for it to happen in the beginning...
The rush hour after work...
The girl that rides this train
at this hour all the time,
is cute.
But,
she is also sexy as hell, in the
middle of puberty as a student.
Damn her boobs are big.
God I want to fuck her from behind...
If a girl like this became my wife, I could
never wait to get home from work.
I would go home immediately and
make her moan every single night.
I go to a job that I don't even like and go home tired, but
this time of the day gives me the rejuvenation I need.
Woa... Crap, it's touching...!
The train is moving...
I have to move away...!
What am I saying!? That's impossible...
How could such a tight ass be this soft!?
I'm being molested again...
How far are they going to take it this time...?
I have to hurry and prepare dinner...
I wonder if they'll make it quick...
It's no use, my hand just won't...
God damn!
It feels like mochi!
Wait... Wha...
She's not resisting?
Could it be she's a slut?
No, no, no. There's no way.
How could such a cute innocent-looking...
But... but...
Her ass is too soft...
and smells so good...
It's no use... I can't hold myself...!
I'm touching her tits!
I'm grabbing them...
A complete white-collar stranger
like me is doing this inside a train...
To a student...
I can't make excuses at this point anymore...
So big...
Her tits are so big!
So much of it between my fingers...
The growth of some kids
these days is just ridiculous...
This... wait a sec...
She's probably at least a J cup!
Why does someone in their teens
have such weapons on her already...
Wh-what's with her...?
Why is this girl not making any commotion...?
It's not rough today...
This person isn't hurting me...
Below her waist...
Her bare ass is so smooth, and soft!
This is... she's wet as hell...
Wha...
Did she just moan...?
I feel weird today...
It's wetter than usual...
It even feels a bit... nice...
I'm having sex right now...
With the girl that I was always
molesting on the train...
With a girl that is almost a
decade younger than me...
Rape...
But she was wet,
so it's fine, right?
I mean, at this point I can't stop!
This feels too good!
I'm doing it bare, and she's
letting out so much lube!
Who knew there were pussies
that felt better than a onahole.
What a pussy she has,
even though she looks so cute.
This fucking slut!
I'm going to cu...
Inside... Cra...
Wh-what's with this girl...
It's her first time with me and yet...
She looks so...
sexy and cute!
So hot!
I'm so sorry!
This is really bad.
What the hell was I doing?
This is just rape!
A crime... Rape... With a student...!
And bare...!
I'll be screwed if she's pregnant, freaking screwed!
It's fine.
What?!
Oh, by "it's fine" I mean that
it's not okay to assault a girl,
but with me...
it's as if I was born to be raped, or rather...
This has happened many times before.
I've had some terrible things done to me before,
such as being filmed while being assaulted...
I don't report any of them usually,
so the same goes for today's as well.
Rather, today's actually felt really good...
All I did was fuck her in a way that anyone has sex...
What has she been subjected to for all this time...?
I raped you.
You're going to forgive me?!
The truth is you really shouldn't do stuff...
What a nice kid
with such big breasts,
soft skin,
and plump body!
She's still a student too...
She's going to make me like her even more...
I can have sex with her...
I get to have sex with such a nice bitch!
She's so cute!
Her voice is so sweet...
She's cumming again.
It's squeezing me...
It's pulling on me even though
there's so much juice...
I can feel her walls...
Is this what they call a clamper?
Her ass is the bomb!
There's so much of it that I can...
use it to jerk off!
I never thought that I would
end up assaulting a student...
It's true that she does seem
like she was born to be raped,
but both her appearances and
personality are too bewitching...
Who would have though that I would
bring a student to a hotel and go this far...
But this isn't something that is allowed.
It's rape...
This will be the last time...
I should be satisfied already...
The guys that usually get girls like
that usually work at a big company,
or are good looking.
Is what I thought...
Oh, hello.
Hey...
Did she just greet me...?
Wai... Why?
I raped you!
Do you make it yourself?
I'm good at cooking...
Um, hey...
Do you want to continue last time?
I'll be gentle.
What the hell am I saying?!
In that case...
God damn her lips are soft...
Her entire body is so soft...
It's my fi-first time having a regular kiss...
Amazing... I feel like I'm going to melt...
I didn't know a kiss could
be such an amazing thing...
She's too damn cute!
It feels like my body got struck by lightning...
I can barely stand...
She's already so...
It feels different...
It feels so much different than when
those other random guys do it...
It feels good...
It feels so good...
It feels so much better than doing it by myself...
Did she just cum?
Already?
Just by this?
I-I have to return the favor...
and make him feel good as well...
Can I give you a blowjob?
Ye-yeah...
Seriously!?
She's going to do it without me asking?
Oh yeah... the ice cream I bought is going to melt...
But this man's... my body...
It was so scared of penis, now it wants it so bad...
What is this...
It's so tight, all the way to the base...
She's so young, so why...
Was she forced to do it?
I was trained in fellatio...
This is bad... her tongue is
also wrapping all around me...
I'm going to cum...
Should I do it in her mouth...?
You idiot!
How could you do that already from the first time...
But... I want to...!
So goo...
My legs feel like they're going to give out...
Sorry!
If I remember correctly, now I go like this...
and show it to him...
I want to feel even better with this girl...
What is this?!
What is this body?!
My dick feels so good...!
It feels good...
It really is different from all the other times...
His sex feels good...
and gentle...
Deep... it feels so good deep...
What is this...
No... no...!
I'm going to...!
Crap! I'm going to...!
Deep... deep inside...!
It's spewing inside me...
If it's ok with you, we might
as well just become a couple.
That way, we can have sex as much
as we want without any trouble...
I'm falling for this guy...
I didn't know sex could be such a nice thing...
I... I might get addicted...
I want her more...
I want to indulge in her more.
I want to make her moan more.
I want to put his dick in me more...
I want him to fuck me more...
He's cumming inside me...
I didn't know sex could feel
so good and satisfying...
This is bad...
What should I do? I can't stop!
Are you going from behind next?
I can't stop fucking her!
I can't believe I brought a
student to my place to do this...
Is it fine that we're lovers now?
Is it?
I mean, it feels too damn good!
There's no way I could stop this!
It feels so good...
I'm so happy right now...
I can't believe someone like this is my boyfriend...
I feel like I'm going to cum again...
Cumming... I'm cumming...!
She cums so easily...
It makes me want to make her cum even more...
And her body is so honest in its reactions...
I'm going to make her pregnant
with all these creampies...
I feel that I actually want her to have my baby too...
What the hell am I thinking,
when we've only been dating for a few hours...
I see.
So you live by yourself.
Yeah.
Yeah, I work at a company nearby.
I'll fold these for you.
O-okay...
Sorry for the trouble.
What a nice kid.
She's the family type.
Her name is Yui, if I'm correct.
So nice and sexy...
and erotic...
I-I'll fold these for you...
That's if you can.
The penis of the person I love...
He's feeling good using my body again...
I'm so happy...
Use it as much as you want!
I love you!
Alright, so we're going to the movies tomorrow.
But why are we meeting at 5 AM?
Because I want to be with you as much as I can.
Okay, I really do have to get going...
My father is going to get worried...
Before I leave though, just give me a kiss...
So cute...
I don't want to let her go home...
We had that much sex and yet I'm still this hard...
There's no way I can wait for
this body until tomorrow...
God damn her tits are huge!
I can't control myself!
Ah, my curfew... Papa's going to get worried...
But just a bit longer... just a bit longer...
More... more...!
Sorry, but I do really have to go now...
You-you're right...
It is pretty late too.
Let's definitely go on a date, okay?
Tomorrow, no matter what!
I feel like I'll end up fucking
her just by getting close...
I hope it's tomorrow already
so that I can hold her again.
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч