Good morning.
I found you, Kazuto!
No, Kazuto, please don't look.
Please don't look!
It's you, Ayane.
Kazuto, you've remembered my name.
I'm so happy!
She's Ayane. She's in
the same grade I am.
I think Ayane is love with Kazuto.
Although, I'm not very good
at detecting this sort of thing.
Kazuto, I'm a bit upset.
Don't keep ignoring me,
I'm always there for you.
What do you want?
I don't have anything specific in mind...
can't I talk to you even when
there's nothing to talk about?
I'm busy! Let's go, Momiji.
Yes.
Ayane seems to be jealous of me.
Doesn't she know...
Kazuto treats me badly.
In fact, I'm jealous of Ayane.
Rather be in her shoes.
Hey there, Momiji.
I am not going to let you
monopolize Kazuto.
Kazuto?
Stay there and don't move.
Even though you're in
your school uniform...
can you still feel it?
Not there. Please don't, not there.
No one's going to come in.
You're getting wet, Momiji.
All right, you're ready.
You're soaking wet. You little slut!
I like it.
No, that's not...
What a drama queen,
you like it that much?
How is it Momiji?
Don't! No!
No!
Your hot body wants it.
No matter what you think,
your body likes it a whole lot.
Looks like you won't release me
before I come.
I'm about to come,
I'll spurt out on you to finish.
- On me?
- That's right.
No!
Momiji!
- I can't! I can't!
- Come on, Momiji, come on!
Momiji!
My uniform's dirty.
You have the gym clothes
you just took off.
You can always go to class
the way you are.
- It's cold.
- Don't skip your classes.
Momiji: I'm not a doll.
Episode 2: Young Leaves
Change Their Colors
Kazuto!
Kazuto, funny meeting you again.
Don't you think it's fate?
I really believe in stuff like that.
Don't you think so?
I don't know. To me, it kind of feels like
you're ambushing me.
No way! You're imagining it!
Hey, wait! Where are you going, Kazuto?
Where are you going?
Don't you know, I'm going home.
- Why don't we walk home together?
- No thanks, I have a chauffeur.
- Then, will you give me a ride home?
- No way.
You're not nice.
- I don't really care.
- Hey, wait!
Can't you spare a minute to talk?
I think we'd get along great.
I just don't have anything
to talk to you about.
Well even if you don't, I do.
You know?
Why don't you talk to yourself, then?
I don't think it's a good idea.
I think you'll benefit
if you'll listen to me, Kazuto.
It's never too late to learn new things.
Wait a second, what do you mean?
You know what I'm talking about.
It's about you and Momiji.
But I can't talk about it here
where anyone can hear us.
So Ayane, what is it
you want to tell me?
Kazuto, will you loosen up a bit?
Don't tell me what to do.
I didn't come here for this.
Would you just tell me already?
I care. If you'll change
your tone I'll tell you.
- I'm out of here.
- No, please wait, Kazuto.
I'll tell you.
Just listen: I, Ayane...
am in love with you, Kazuto.
What?
So, I think it's a good idea
if you go out with me, Kazuto.
No thanks.
Kazuto, I mean it. I really am
in love with you. I'm serious.
Just give it up. You and I
are not a good match, you know?
I wouldn't say that if I were you.
Wouldn't it be a great big scandal
if people found out that...
the heir of Mikato Zaibatsu
is having wild sex...
like an animal at school?
Are you talking about Momiji? Ridiculous.
No one's ever going to believe that lie.
But I took pictures of you
having sex with her.
What!
It was the pictures of me
having sex with Kazuto at school.
I didn't know she was taking
these pictures when we were...
I'm so embarrassed.
Are you trying to threaten me?
You know it won't work.
Tell me, what about Momiji?
I mean, if it's okay with you,
what about her?
No!
Let me teach you what happens to people
that try to threaten me.
Kazuto, please stop it!
Kazuto, please don't be rough,
I don't like it!
So if I'm rough, it's okay then?
No, that's not what I meant.
Just give in. I won't stop once I've started.
I think you know what I mean.
No.
It hurts.
It hurts. Kazuto!
Just relax. The more you resist,
them more painful it's going to be.
Give in.
I can't relax. Please stop.
Kazuto, why does...
No!
Too rough.
All right, I guess I'm ready
to look down there.
No, please don't.
What do you mean?
It hasn't even started.
No!
Looks like you take
good care of yourself.
No, please don't say that. No.
Look, your excited
despite my rough housing.
That's not true, no.
Come on, let me see.
It's hard, not tight.
Are you a virgin?
If that's the case,
I need to loosen you up a lot.
You're getting pretty slimy.
I'd say you're ready.
- Here comes.
- No, don't!
It hurts, please pull it out!
You're tight.
No it hurts, no, don't move like that.
Yeah.
It hurts.
Your usually little giggly face
is distorted with tears...
I like it, it excites me.
Kazuto, you're excited by me?
Ayane!
What? Something is coming out.
It's hot. Hot.
No Kazuto, don't look.
Ayane, I like it.
Let's do this more often.
I want to see you in tears a lot more.
Kazuto, what do you...
How stupid are you to think that you
could threaten me, Ayane?
Stupid.
That's how Kazuto
had an affair with Ayane.
Just like me.
Recently, I get tired
whenever I go to school.
I bet its because I have Momiji
there to take care of me.
Kazuto! Kazuto!
Did you call me?
I shouldn't, but my fingers just won't stop.
Sorry about that.
Guess I forgot that you're woman, too.
Kazuto...
I must punish a maid
that would do that on her master's bed.
Kazuto, please don't.
You're really pretty, Mari.
No, I'm not.
I'm embarrassed.
With a body like yours,
you shouldn't be embarrassed. It's hot.
It's incredible.
Kazuto, please don't be rough with me.
You're a maid and aren't in a position
to give orders to me.
Please, pardon me.
Look at these huge tits.
No comparison with Momiji.
Please don't compare me with Momiji.
All I'm saying is that, Mari,
you're a lot better with bigger breasts.
With the breasts this big,
it's fun just to suck on.
No, please don't suck them.
Don't you like it?
But your tits are poking out.
Because it feels good.
This is a punishment,
so it's a problem if you feel good.
It's about time I check down below.
No, Kazuto there's no...
That's what?
Just like your personality,
your hair looks tough.
No, please don't look.
Mari, so you're aware
you've got loads of hair?
Because you've masturbated,
you're totally soaked.
It's embarrassing. Please stop.
Smells really good, Mari.
Seductive, female smell.
You're spreading me.
No, please don't look.
Kazuto.
It feels good, Kazuto.
Kazuto...
I love you.
You love me? You mean it?
Yes, I can't deny it.
I know that our social status is
far apart, but I love you, I do.
A dick of a lover won't do
as a punishment...
I'll think of something else.
What? Kazuto, what do you mean?
Someone like you...
who forget your own position,
deserves this one.
No!
It's weird. Despite she's soaking wet.
Mari, are you virgin?
Yes.
Yes, it's my first time so, please...
Kazuto, forgive me.
I don't want it. Kazuto, I want yours.
Please give it to me, please!
You don't want the vibrator? Too bad.
You're sacrificing your virginity
you've kept for so long...
to a vibrator!
No! Kazuto, pull it out, it hurts!
Having been carefully guarded,
it's pretty hard to crack.
You're horrible, Kazuto!
If you want it so bad, I'll take your
second virginity with mine.
You're in for a big surprise.
Your hair over here is cleanly trimmed.
How neat are you.
Kazuto, that's, no...
Let me give you what you dreamed of
as you masturbated.
You wanted this, didn't you?
You're asshole's really tight.
Does this hurt? Really painful?
How is it?
Have you learned your lesson, Mari?
If you want to be fucked,
just tell me so. Anytime.
So long as your asshole's ready,
I'll be happy to fuck you anytime.
Don't you ever tell me
you love me, again!
I don't want anyone's love. Got that?
Even that harsh and uptight Mari
submitted to Kazuto.
Momiji, I know you're there.
It's your turn. Come in. You hear me?
Isn't there anything that can be done?
It's like living in hell.
Be it school, or home.
Kazuto, they're ready.
All right.
Kazuto, I can't stand it!
Please, comfort me.
Kazuto, please!
I'm the first.
Please, me first.
Let's see. Who's going to be first?
- Me!
- Me! I want you, too.
Kazuto, do me.
Yes, me Kazuto.
So, Momiji, you finally learned
how to speak your mind.
Never thought I'd see the day.
It's all because of you,
Kazuto, thank you.
All right. Today, you're the first, Momiji.
No way!
You always favor Momiji over us.
Not fair!
I will not let you complain
about Kazuto's decision, understand?
Now, go for it, as usual.
- No, don't!
- No!
That's right. Good girl.
Momiji!
I tremble with pleasure
to serve Kazuto every day, like this.
And my private part drips
with my passionate fluid.