Are you aware
of what I'm about to do to you?
Then why don't you resist a little?
I'm used to it. Please, go ahead.
You're used to it?
You mean, having sex with a man?
You mean, you're used to giving up...
doing things against your own will?
If you have no intention of resisting me,
I take it you're consenting.
Yes.
Please do as you wish.
I'll do whatever you want
to do to me, I don't care.
Fine.
Momiji, you're very excitable.
No!
After all, even you feel embarrassed...
Why're you doing this? Stop it!
You already feel that much?
I touched only a little.
Like that?
No.
No, don't!
No! Not there, please!
I'm surprised. You're already wet.
Let me take a good look.
No, don't look!
What's wrong? I thought
you would obey my words...
so I can do anything I want.
You'd better give up now.
You're good at giving up,
anyway, aren't you?
Your hair is pretty thin.
I guess you're not even fully developed.
What...
Pretty tight, as I thought.
Yeah, you're wet enough.
You'll be fine.
Ready?
No!
It hurts. Don't. It hurts!
Are you crying, Momiji?
Even you can cry.
Are you angry?
About your virginity being stolen like this?
It hurts, don't! Please!
I see, you're crying like a baby
because it hurts.
You're like a baby!
It hurts, please stop!
So do feel it?
You're giving me a lot of pleasure, Momiji.
I don't feel it!
You can feel it the first time around.
That's good, Momiji.
We'll have fun together,
a lot more fun.
Please, I beg you, this will be, our last...
Please stop it!
Momiji, I'm almost there.
I'll let you soak in mine
until it becomes a part of you.
No! Please!
I'm coming!
- Momiji!
- No!
That was the first night Kazuto had me.
Yes, that was the day it all started.
Momiji: I'm not a doll.
Episode 1: Fallen Leaves Off Season
Sorry! Will you take that back
to the warehouse too?
He says it was how he first noticed me.
And then...
What's wrong, Momiji?
That won't make me come.
Hurry up, otherwise,
we'll be late for school.
I had to go to great lengths to get you...
so you'd better let me have fun,
enough to make it up for it.
It's good, Momiji.
Momiji, you're getting better
with your tongue.
Momiji, harder! Harder!
That's not enough!
Yeah, this is how you do it!
Good, it's much better.
Momiji, I'll spray it on your face,
all right?
No!
There!
It's not nice, Kazuto.
What do you think?
Why do you think I got you?
I told you I hate girls like you.
I'll see you later.
That's right. Kazuto hates me.
I am the type Kazuto loathes the most.
A girl without her own mind.
That's why Kazuto took notice of me.
Kazuto.
What do you want, Shizuru?
Please, will you please stop hurting Momiji?
I'm free to hurt her in any way I choose,
don't you think?
No. It's you, yourself, Kazuto,
who's hurt by hurting Momiji.
You did it by yourself.
Don't be ridiculous.
Just because you've been
around for a while...
doesn't mean you know anything
about me, so shut up.
You're just a housemaid.
Kazuto...
I'm sorry for you.
Momiji.
Kazuto.
It's lunch time already.
Where're the others?
Why are you the only one cleaning up?
Not again!
Momiji, who gave you
permission to do this?
Remember, I'm the only one
who can give you orders.
All you have to do is to obey my words
and not anyone else's. Understand?
- Yes.
- All right.
Your tits are poking out.
You getting excited
in a place like this?
That's not it...
I just got cold. Because of the pool.
Don't lie to me.
That won't make them poke out that much.
Look, they're obvious,
even through your bathing suit.
Here, take a good look.
It hurts!
Momiji, tell me why
your tits are poking out.
It's because it feels...
it's good.
I knew it.
You've gotten chilled, Momiji.
It's burning hot down here,
and, soaking wet too.
Momiji, open your legs wide.
But what if someone comes by?
Don't worry, no one will come by.
All you have to do is do what I tell you.
If you do that,
I'll make you feel good.
It'll feel so good that you'll forget
we're here at school.
Now, get yourself prepared.
Hurry up!
That's good. Now, ready?
Please don't move so hard.
The way yours tightens...
I bet you're enjoying it too,
so don't tell me what to do.
But, no!
Looks like you're really enjoying this.
Don't!
Your juice is pouring out.
But, that's...
I'm so hot, Momiji.
I'm not.
That's right.
It's as if yours is melting mine.
I'm hot, too.
Momiji, it's good.
Good. Go, just go!
I'm ordering you to come. Just come!
Yes, I'm coming!
I'm coming too.
Welcome home, Kazuto.
Thanks, Mari.
Momiji.
I can smell it on you.
Before you go back to your room,
take a bath please.
Yes.
I'll take a bath with her then.
- What?
- Kazuto!
Just kidding.
Mari, you're so uptight.
Kazuto, you fool around
a bit too much.
Shut up and cut it out.
Mind your own business.
Is that you, Momiji?
It's me, Kazuto.
Are you disappointed that I'm not Momiji?
Let me help you wash.
It's been a while since last.
There, why don't you come out
so that I can wash you?
Lt'll be really nice.
Are you ready?
There, there you go.
Shizuru, what are you doing?
You could feel it? Don't you like it?
Shizuru, be serious.
Well, I am serious.
Stop it, Shizuru.
You sure you want me to stop?
You are already this big.
Hey, stop it.
You always take the bath alone, Kazuto.
You must find it lonesome.
Don't be crazy.
Baths are what people
take alone, dumb ass!
Stop pretending that I don't know.
So, how about it, Kazuto?
Fuck!
Good. You feel like it now.
If you hold them so hard it hurts.
Please be more gentle.
Since Momiji came, I left you alone.
Now, I'll make it up to you.
That's not what I meant.
Looks like you're ready.
No!
Looks like your ready.
Shizuru, you're so hot.
It's as if I'm inside a sauna.
Shizuru, do you like it?
I feel dazed. And, very good.
You must be overheated.
You're probably right.
But, I feel good.
I feel really good, too.
All right! Harder then, as you want!
Shizuru, I'm coming!
Yes, come! Please come!
A lot of yours came.
Will you let yours come
with me from now on?
Shizuru, who do you think you are?
You're acting out of bounds.
I didn't mean that.
I fuck whenever I want
with whomever I want.
Remember that.
If you obey my words,
I may have you once a month.
That's the extent of our relationship.
Don't imagine it's more than that.
Kazuto.
I learned much later that Kazuto...
and Shizuru had that
type of relationship.
To Kazuto, are we, Shizuru and I...
simple toys to play with?
But, I...
Come in.
Excuse me.