Are you ready?
Yes.
Good. As of today, you've become
one of the honorable maids...
of Mikado Zaibatsu.
Under the normal circumstances,
you would've had to go through...
a strict examination
of not only your looks...
but also the position and the stature
of your family.
Yes, I am aware of that.
Your case is very special.
Remember that and serve your master
well, All right?
Yes.
Very well. First things first.
Go and greet the master of this house.
That's your first task.
I understand.
You may go now.
Momiji: I'm not a doll
Episode 3: Young Leaves Awakened
Kazuto?
It's the morning. Time to get up.
Momiji?
It's you.
Kazuto.
So, it's you? The new maid,
who's just started work here?
Yes, I wanted to be near you
every second of my life...
so I became a maid.
Get out of my bed then, quickly!
No way, Kazuto,
it was you who pulled me up...
Looks like Mari hasn't
taught you the rules.
In this house, I am the master!
Who's there?
It's me, Momiji.
You're late.
I'm sorry.
Ayane?
She's the new maid.
Can you believe it?
Is that so, Kazuto?
It doesn't have to be me
then who wakes him up.
- Hey, Momiji, are you listening?
- Yes.
Why are you standing there
as if you're dazed?
Hurry up and get over here!
Momiji, give me your
regular morning service.
Is it okay for me to do it?
Are you sure, Kazuto?
Stop jabbering!
Just get on with it as usual, understand?
Yes.
That's not fair! No way!
Let me serve you too.
Listen, you just wait there and watch.
Understand me?
But...
I understand, Kazuto.
You're not getting better at it.
I'm sorry.
That's right. Do it with care.
Kazuto, why can't I do it?
Why do you choose her instead of me?
If it were me,
I'd be much better at it.
No, I'm getting wet. What about his...
Take it like a good girl.
Yes.
- Make sure you drink it all.
- Yes.
What?
Please, let me serve you too.
No way.
Please let me, master.
You want it that bad?
Yes.
What do I do? Let me see.
I'll do it with the one
who makes the other come first.
No, don't!
Momiji, you've got to attack Ayane.
Yes!
No, not there.
With the breasts alone.
What a slut!
No, I can't.
Kazuto.
What are you watching?
Nothing at all.
Momiji, look.
Here, get it over there!
Keep it moving!
Should have blocked that.
Can you see those
who are wasting their lives away?
Yes.
Listen, I'm telling you this because
you don't seem to get it.
You're different from all of them.
First of all, you're mine,
and that fact alone makes you...
a couple of levels above them.
So become stronger,
not just your body but also your soul.
Strengthen your entire being. Understand?
Yes, I understand.
Show me your body now.
Right here? Now?
That's right. Take off your top, first.
Hurry up. Once the sun sets,
the light over there will turn on...
and everyone will know
who's up on top of the building.
Is that what you want?
Tell me, is it?
You look like you're cold.
Let me warm you up.
Don't!
What don't you want?
I'm making you warm.
Besides, your tits are hardening.
That's not it.
You're getting excited
by my kindness.
That calls for punishment.
No! Kazuto, don't, Kazuto!
We're too far, no one can see us.
No, it's embarrassing!
You're dripping wet.
People might hear you.
No, please, stop!
It's you who's making the noise, Momiji.
Stop, please stop it!
I'm burning hot!
Why did I do that?
Why didn't I have to visit
his room today?
I don't understand.
I shouldn't, but...
That sensation warm and numbing.
No. Why am I...
If my fingers were his.
No, not like this, no.
Kazuto!
Yes? Come in.
- I'm sorry. Did I wake you up?
- No.
That's good.
Kazuto is out tonight
at an industry party.
A party?
That's right. "Just go to bed
without staying up."
"Don't wait for me."
That's what he said.
I got it. Thank you.
Sometimes, sleeping alone
can help you sleep better.
Yes.
Okay, sleep well then, Momiji.
Mari, what's my schedule today?
There's nothing booked at the moment.
Is that right? How unusual.
Momiji, how about doing
what we talked about yesterday?
So, you've never been
to an amusement park?
Yes. How about you, Kazuto?
I don't have a time for such things.
I'm sorry.
It's not a bad idea to be entertained
by such plebeian forms of amusement.
Kazuto, it is fun.
All right, we'll go
to the amusement park tomorrow.
Are you sure, Kazuto?
That's right. Okay?
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Boring!
The haunted house and
roller coaster rides and all.
I don't understand
what's so entertaining about them.
Momiji, what about you?
Did you have any fun today?
Did you?
Not much.
Right.
That's what they call
a Ferris wheel, I think.
All right, let's try that one.
It looks a little large.
Interesting, rather than looking up
at it from below...
we're looking at everything
from up above in the gondola.
- You like it?
- Yes.
Momiji.
Kazuto.
Not in a place like this.
We've come to the amusement park,
so we'd better amuse ourselves.
No, don't please, don't!
Please don't!
You're getting wet.
Does this feel good?
No. You're not nice.
Does this feel good or bad?
You shook your head
when I asked if it's bad...
so you must like it.
No, that's not true.
Even if you try to hide it,
it's obvious.
No!
You're wetter than usual.
This change of scenery
has got you excited.
No, I'm not.
It's more convenient that way.
After all, we don't have much time.
Momiji, you don't like getting
come inside you, right?
Yes.
All right, I'll come outside.
But, don't soil the dress
Shizuru made for you.
But how?
- Take it all in your mouth!
- Yes!
Momiji, I'm coming!
- Welcome home.
- You're home, Kazuto.
How was the date?
It wasn't a date.
You should be honest with yourself.
Scary.
Both the dinner and the bath
are ready for you.
What would you like first?
Let me rest in my room for a while.
I understand.
The ticket for the Ferris wheel,
I bought that for...