What's wrong?
You don't look happy.
It's nothing.
Kazuto, it's not good to lie.
Just get out of here!
Scary.
Momiji: I'm not a doll
Episode 4: Momiji That Never Falls.
There you are.
I'm sorry for being late.
I didn't expect to be called.
Let me wash your front, too.
Let me wash you down there, please.
Leave it alone.
- Don't say that. Let me...
- No.
If I let you, you'll enjoy it.
No, that's not true.
That's enough. Stop it.
But, I'm not done washing you.
You want it that bad?
Yes.
What's wrong?
Hurry up and wash me!
Yes.
You said you'd wash me,
but you can't even do a good job.
What's wrong with you?
So sorry.
You deserve to be punished.
You've developed a real sensitivity
right there, little girl.
Please stop.
Ready? I'm coming.
I'm coming!
Is that what happened later on?
Mari, it's not fair.
I tell you, he was more
passionate than usual.
Kazuto doesn't even look at me.
It's not fair at all!
Yes, this is Ayane.
Well, I'm on my way right now. Okay.
Well, it's Ayane's turn, then.
But, you know...
Just get out of here, would you!
He doesn't look happy.
Kazuto?
Yeah.
When something bothers him,
he's likely to resort to...
Please do it to me, too.
Kazuto.
I hear he was acting like that before.
Kazuto!
No, not the please not my ass. No!
No, don't!
Momiji's absence is affecting him.
She's at the physical exam, right?
This is really terrible.
I can't wait for Momiji to return soon.
Welcome home.
- So, you're back.
- Yes.
Good.
Kazuto, you don't have much time.
We must get going.
I got it.
You, let's stop by somewhere
on the way home tomorrow.
You sleep in your room tonight.
Yes, Kazuto.
Finally, we can take a break.
So, how did your exam turn out?
They found no problem.
- Kazuto?
- What's wrong?
Please, I can't...
It was fun at school, wasn't it?
That's not...
What a slut you are,
wetting your underwear all day long.
It's because since this morning, I...
Hey, what's that?
Yes, that's a popular fast food restaurant.
- Commoner food.
- I hear it's surprisingly tasty.
I guess it won't hurt
to see what it tastes like.
Welcome!
Hamburgers.
Excuse me, young lady,
would you mind terribly...
repeating your entire order?
Hamburgers, please. Thank you.
Hamburgers? How many?
Excuse me, Miss.
Two hamburgers, please.
Two hamburgers.
Yes.
Are you going to eat at the restaurant
or is this take-out?
It's take out.
Yes, it's take out!
Please, please...
Don't...
Excuse me Miss, are you
in trouble? Do you need help?
It's not good. Don't worry.
She's always like this.
Okay then, sir.
Yeah!
So uncool!
Game over.
This commoner food sucks.
You woke up?
Where are we?
This place is called a game center.
Do you know why I brought you here?
It's because...
Keep it down, otherwise people
can hear you.
Stop it, please not there.
We're doing it because we're here.
It's your punishment.
Now, stop grimacing.
Please forgive me,
someone please come.
Don't worry, no one will
know so long as you keep quiet.
Hey, let's try that one.
That one over there?
- Why not?
- All right, then.
It's kind of weird for two girls.
- What's wrong with that?
- Okay, then.
- Someone else's using it.
- You're right.
- Let's go try that one over there.
- Okay.
It's good Momiji,
you're tightening it up much better.
It's about time we take a photo.
No, please don't!
No photograph!
I'll show it to Mari and Shizuru.
Hey, stop frowning.
If you do, I won't show it to anyone.
We're not done yet.
I haven't come, all right?
Next one will show you covered
in my sperm, you little whore!
Come on, take it!
No, don't!
There's nothing in the world
to match these. Nothing at all.
It was a lot of fun today.
Hey, take a look.
Listen, Momiji, stop covering up
your emotions.
The dead look on your face
annoys a hell out of me.
I'm sorry.
That's it. That's the look.
I forbid you to hide
how you feel from now on.
No, don't!
You already feel it?
As usual, your body's very sensitive
to sexual pleasure.
Don't!
Don't! It's hot!
Don't! Don't! Don't!
I can't!
I'm sorry. Did it sting you?
It's all right. I'm okay.
Don't make that face.
While you were away,
Kazuto was a lot worse.
His personality doesn't let him
show his feelings.
Really? Is that so?
Yeah. He used to look disinterested
all the time, it was very bad.
As if he'd given up on everything.
Everything?
That's right.
But you know, since you arrived,
everything's changed so much.
So, don't let it bother you too much.
Shizuru.
This works the best for the burns
all over your body.
No. Why does this feel so good?
Shizuru's doing this just to help me.
My body's reacting against my will.
What's wrong?
Did I make you excited?
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
Momiji, you're the one
who's getting the brunt of it.
Shizuru!
Let me help you heal.
What? No!
Everything will be all right.
It's warm.
No.
Touch me, Momiji.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Momiji.
I mean, please.
Momiji, you're really good.
I'm not, really.
You're always so humble.
Momiji, will you do it to me too?
Momiji, I can't!
No!
Shizuru!
It's good!
I'm coming!
Perhaps, this girl can change Kazuto.
As if he'd given up on everything.
Someone so horrible like him...
is same with me.
But he needs me
and he can't leave me alone.
He cares about me.
Kazuto, you're my very first.
No, don't do this. Not like this.
Don't tell me what to do. You're mine!
But...
What's wrong?
I see. It's too lonely to sleep alone?
Yes.
What a pain in the ass. Here.
Come here.
Good morning, Kazuto.
Good morning.