Mmm...?
Ah!
Tagami-san, are you awake?
How does your body feel?
That's the daughter of our landlord, Sanae-chan, right?
What is she doing here?
BEWARE OF THE FLU!!
I heard you were down with a fever.
I thought I might be sticking
my nose where it doesn't belong, but...
I've brought a few things like flu meds for you.
Th-Thanks, that'll be a big help.
I brought some groceries as well,
I'll make something nutritious for
dinner so, just rest up, ok?
Eh?
No, umm...
I kind of remember something like that happening.
Dinner will be ready soon, ok?
Eh? No... I'm fine, so...
Your parents will be getting worried,
so you should go home soon.
I already told my mother that
I would be taking care of you.
My house is next door, so it's fine even if gets late.
No no no, I'm not worried about that.
Even if it's near, you're still alone
with a guy in his house, right?
I'm afraid of doing something on impulse.
Anyway, it's dangerous, so go home.
Dangerous? What is?
Ahh! Oh no! The stew is...
Tomoka-kun, it'll be ready in a minute,
so just wait a little more, okay?
Yep, good. Now all that's left is...
Men are dangerous.
Something like this could happen, you know.
U-um, It's fine. Something like this
happens all the time, so...
All the time?!
Students these days are so...
Or more like, hmm?
And here I thought you were innocent.
I used to be me until I turned six. When my brother was
born, everyone started paying him all the attention
I was very spoiled though.
Is that so?
If you're really that used to it,
then I can feel you a bit more, right?
Eh?!
They're quite big, aren't they? I wonder if
it's because they're always being fondled.
Something like that is...
So rough! Don't!
Your body is so soft and cold.
It feels real good.
Don't! You're being so... rough.
You have a fever, so you should
rest and keep yourself warm.
That's right, isn't it?
Ahh! Th-The skirt is...
It's... coming in...
Thi-This is... a penis!
Sanae-chan, you feel warm huh?
No... Don't move!
You've gotten pretty wet.
So you're feeling good?
You must be warmer inside, I'm sure.
Inside? No, please don't...
No way! That's just too rough!
Suddenly thrusting your dick all the way in...
Even though it was my first time!
It feels like my fever is going down.
Warm me up some more.
My stomach, it hurts!
It's slippery and feels good.
It's so warm!
Sorry, I'm cummmg!
My bad, it felt so good I just had to let it out inside.
Its going to spill on the floor.
It's alright, I'll clean it up later.
Let's continue on the bed, shall we?
Ye-Yes...
That's right... that's right. Just like that.
But I'd like it if you thrust it in deeper.
Yes...
Doing it so hard.
You must really like these perverted things.
Yo-you're wrong!
What I like isn't perverted stuff.
It's Tagami-san!
Yeah, yeah.
This time I'll pour my load deeper
inside you, alright?
If you do that... I might have a baby.
It's alright.
Unlike a student, I'm an adult who can take responsibility.
I-Isn't that... a proposa... Ahh!!
I'm cumming!
My insides are so hot.
A little more... Just stay like this a little more.
The ceiling?
Was that a dream just now?
Good morning, Tagami-san.
How is your fever?
It wasn't a dream!
Even if I was semi-conscious 'cause of my fever,
I did it with the landlord's daughter!
U-Um, Tagami-san.
That made me really happy!
To think that I would be proposed to by my crush!
It's like a dream come true!
Eh?
I also calked my mother a little while ago and
received her blessings.
EHHH?!
Take responsibility, okay?
Y-Yes!
I'm home.
Welcome back, Sou-chan.
I'm Koishigawa Seita, and this is my other
older sister, Koishigawa Maho.
Our parents remarried three years ago.
– I've been waiting, I've got something good to show you!
– For the first time in my life, I had another name attached to mine.
– I have always been a single child so
I was worried about what would happen but,
– Boo! Good morning. I have been trying to wake you up for a while, you know?
– Yeah!
– You were in my bed?
Maho-nee was a real bubbly person.
– I'll wash your back for you!
– She's a little too bubbly sometimes so it becomes
rather problematic, but...
– Wai...! Why did you just come in?
– I'll make it sparkly clean.
– But now, I think of us as very close siblings.
– Eh?!
But I am in love with Maho-nee.
Traveling for couples
Recommended date spots
Couples, huh.
It'd be great if I could go to places like these with Maho-nee.
Sou-chan, I borrowed the DVD I wanted to watch!
Let's watch it together!
Don't surprise me like that Maho-nee!
Ahh, what did you hide?
Is it a porno mag?
It's not!
Come on, let's go to the living room!
Boo boo!
– It's a given, but Maho-nee treats me
just like any other little brother.
– Can't wait, right?
– I wonder if it's alright like this...
– I'm getting so excited.
I couldn't ask her on a date today either.
Let's try a little harder tomorrow.
Huh? Maho-nee?
Sou-chan, look at this.
I got a sea cucumber!
OUCH!!
Huh? U-Um, I'm sorry!
I couldn't see it because it's dark.
Eh?
M-Maho-nee?
What are you doing?
Ni-Night crawling?
Huh?
Sou-chan should just keep quiet.
Whoa! Maho-nee is actually sucking my dick!
Is this a dream?
It feels a little too real for a dream.
Maho-nee's blowjob, it's surreal!
Maho-nee's pussy.
She's wet?
This is her taste.
Sou-chan...
Her tongue is twirling around, it feels so good!
I'm about to cum!
I wonder if it's alright now.
Maho-nee?!
I can't do it well!
Don't push yourself, it's fine...
NO!!
Sou-chan, don't you wanna do it with me?
Do you love doing it with your girlfriend?
Eh? Girlfriend?
Even though I'm the one who loves Sou-chan the most.
Maho-nee...
Sou-chan?
I love you, Maho-nee.
Sou-chan...
R-R... Really?
Really! I don't have a girlfriend either.
Huh?!
Why did you have that misconception?
But... there were a lot of love hotels in that
date-guide you were reading today
I thought maybe you wanted to
go there with our girlfriend.
I...
Maho-nee...
It looks like it was just a misunderstanding.
I'm so glad!
Yeah, I love you a lot, Maho-nee.
I love you so much, Sou-chan!
Maho-nee, there's blood!
It's alright.
I'm happy that Sou-chan's my first time!
Sou-chan.
Y-Yeah.
Maho-nee's insides are so hot, it feels great!
Sou-chan!
You and I are connected!
I'm so happy!
Maho-nee!
I'm so happy to be together with you too!
Sou-chan, I love you!
Let out a lot.
Inside me!
Maho-nee!
– Sou-chan, lets go on a date!
– Eh?
But, I-I haven't decided where to go yet.
If it's with Sou-chan, then anywhere is fine.
You know, as your lover, I want to
walk around town with you.
Maho-nee...
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's going inside!
Maho-nee is the person I love.
She is beautiful, cute, and good at cooking.
Even though she's older than me, she acts a little spoiled.
Sou-chan!
Maho-nee!
It's so... thick...
I love everything about her!
I actually like her perverted places a lot.
I have a feeling Maho-nee initiates
this more than me though.
Sou-chan's penis feels so good!
I want it deeper inside me!
Cum in me a lot!
And then, the part that I secretly like are these boobs.
Mmm, you love boobs after all.
They are squishy, soft, and bouncy.
Maho-nee actually has a soft spot for boobs huh?
Your face gets like this just from me
sucking on them a little.
My boobs turn me on a lot!
You're like a baby, Sou-chan!
Now that you mention it, milk comes from boobs, right?
I wonder what sort of taste it has.
I want to drink some of that breast milk!
Eh? Was I speaking out loud?
What should I do! She must've heard it!
I-I'm sorr...
I'm sorry!
Huh?!
I can't produce milk from my boobs.
Please wait a little, I'm sure something will happen!
Please don't hate me!
Are you asking me to make a baby, by any chance?
Th-That's not what I meant!
But I want to have Sou-chan's kids!
I also like this silly side of her.
I don't think I can pick out a single thing to call my favorite.
I love all of you!
Translator: Maq-kun
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4real & Hikarucon