I'm sorry.
D-Do you have someone you like...?
Um, maybe... I'm not sure.
Adolescence is filled with bittersweet experiences.
Someone I like...?
The Pink Telescope
Momoiro Bouenkyou
Whoa, that's amazing!
Again? You heart-breaker...
No, it's not like that!
Jeez, Natsumi...
You say that, but how many has it been?
Y-Yeah, maybe I'm bad for turning them down...
By the way, you've got nice body, don't you Emma?
I know, right! I wish you'd share me some...
Hey, it's embarrassing if you stare that much!
Eh? It's no big deal, is it?
Right?
Jeez! If you two keep at it, it's going to be!
We don't look the same age, do we?
She's very adult-like.
Do boys like that kind of thing?
Oh, I remember what Onee-chan said.
Apparently if you have someone rub your chest, it'll get bigger!
Oh really...?
Right...?
Jeez, I haven't had that  done to me!
Yeah... Nothing like that...
Yeah, no way!
Totally!
Welcome back.
Oh, it's dad!
I came to pick you up.
Hello!
Your dad sure looks cool!
Eh? R-Really?
Definitely a cool guy!
You sure have made some good friends that can give a cheerful greeting!
Oh my...
Right...?
If you have a dad like that...
The boys in the class are brats compared to him!
Catch you later!
Emma-chan, bye bye!
See you later!
Dad is actually the man who took the place of my real dad.
Yes... A really important person to me.
Shall we go?
Yep!
I'm home!
The house we live in is large for just the two of us.
Right, welcome home.
You're being weird, dad!
Although I hear it housed a family in the past.
Is that so?
Welcome home to you too, dad!
Looks like we've worked up a sweat.
Do you want to take a bath together?
Yeah!
I'll wash you today, dad!
You're such a nice girl, Emma.
It's because you're always looking after me.
Like this, right...?
Yes, that's it.
I'm glad.
You're good at this, Emma!
Oh, it's gotten big!
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels really good.
I'm happy that he's liking it...
When did I start to feel like this?
That's right, something like this happened.
It was soon after I came to live here...
Now I've done it...
I had wet myself.
I was so embarrassed...
I tried to do something about it, but...
Emma! Is something wrong?
I couldn't do anything.
I, um... I'm sorry...
It's fine.
I wonder if he's mad...?
Let's get you in the bath to wash up.
With that, dad brought me along to the bathroom.
I'm going to get scolded... Aren't I...?
Aren't you going to scold me?
It's fine, don't worry about it.
You're a good girl apologizing.
But...
If you need to go, it would be great if you could tell us beforehand.
Okay!
What's this feeling?
Whenever the hot water splashed between my legs, it felt a little ticklish.
Just say so if you've wet yourself again, okay?
Then I'd wash you throughly, like this.
You're squeaky clean!
How about some ice cream?
Y-Yeah!
I wanna eat the ice cream...
Maybe that's when it started...?
Did I use to wet myself so he'd wash me again?
Did that really happen?
You've sure grown up since then, Emma.
Dad!
When children get praise, they want to be praised again,
so they try and become better at it, or so I hear...
She's definitely still a child, no matter the age.
Dad!
Um...
What is it?
I wanna go for a pee...
Saying it so boldly, you sure are a good girl, Emma!
Really?
I'll keep watch, so let it all out.
That's a good girl! You let out a lot!
I better wash you squeaky clean!
Like from many years ago,
she leaves her body up to me, with the same trusting demeanor.
I adjust the temperature to a comfortable level,
and I wash Emma's sensitive area.
Gently and thoroughly.
You seem particularly dirty here... See?
As I continue to wash her, her hips start to shake erratically.
Does it feel a bit ticklish?
What a naughty girl... You're all dirty again.
Dad... Um, please do it to me...
Hm? What is it?
Do you want to feel even better?
Although I haven't taught her that it's a bad thing,
she's a girl coming of age... It's probably embarrassed.
Can you do it, like we usually do?
Yes...
Okay, here we go!
Emma, I'm going to thrust.
That's a good girl... This feels great!
Um, today...
I was confessed to today...
Is that so?
How did it go?
It was a boy from my class...
I... It's nothing...
My mind, it's feeling weird!
No-!
It feels too good...!
I'm the only one for you, Emma.
Got that?
Yeah... You're my one and only, dad!
This feels great...
Emma, make me... Please make me feel good.
That's it, Emma...! It feels wonderful!
Dad...!
Sorry, I was a little rough.
I'll make you feel better, okay?
Emma's grown up to be a really good girl.
She's grown up to be a good girl that can accepted all of my lust.
Emma, I love you.
I really do.
I love you more than anything in the world.
I won't give you up.
You're only for me.
I'm going to cum inside!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
Is it getting late? Let's have some dinner.
Okay...
Um, before...
About the confession...
Oh, right.
I was asked if I had someone I liked.
Oh really?
Is there someone you like?
You meanie, dad!
I'll be the one to comfort you dad, okay?
Surely it's only trollsubs that put memes in releases... Right? - Shikkaku fansubs