Momoiro Maniac 2
Araiguma's MOMOIRO MILK
So you use this equation here...
Oh?
By the way...
Your boobs are pretty big,
aren't they, Yoshikawa?
Do you know why I'm here, Hibiya-kun?
– Yeah. The teacher asked you to tutor me because I'm a bad student.
– Please, help him out.
If you know that, then take this seriously!
Then let's get back on track.
Okay...
I can't stand it
So what's your cup size? Can I touch them?
This guy...
Come on, Hibiya-kun!
Well, when I'm curious about something, I can't focus.
I lose my motivation.
Ugh, fine, I get it already. I'm an F cup.
Satisfied?
Whoa, F? Isn't that the perfect size for tit fucks?
They're so big!
H-Hey!
I never said you could touch them!
Just a little. Just a little, okay?
After I'm done, I'll go back to studying.
F-Fine then. Just a little, okay?
Sure!
Hey, wait, what do you think you're doing?
You said I could touch them, didn't you?
I didn't say you could touch them directly!
No!
They feel so good! They're so smooth and soft!
Not there!
Don't play with them like that!
No, Hibiya-kun! The way you're
touching them is kinda erotic...
Well that's because I am touching them erotically.
No, don't lick them!
My lower half is tingling.
Sorry, I can't hold back anymore.
Huh?
No way!
I've never seen this before!
Wow, your breasts are amazing!
So squishy!
His dick is so hot!
What is this? This wriggly thing feels so good.
It's slipping and sliding through my breasts.
Oh no, I-I'm gonna cum.
Yoshikawa-san, Hibiya-kun?
How's studying going?
H-Huh?
Where could they have gone?
Th-That was close!
Hurry up and leave!
Their bags are still here, so I guess I'll wait around.
What?!
What are we going to do?
Yoshikawa...
Hibiya-kun, what are you doing?
Just continuing where we left off.
We can't, the teacher is right there!
No, you can't!
Your insides are so tight!
I'm going to move.
No, you can't!
No!
You're being too rough. She's going to hear us!
Hibiya-kun...
What should I do?
It feels so good I can't think straight!
It feels so good!
Hm? Is someone there?
Yoshikawa, I'm gonna cum.
No... I'm going to cum!
The teacher's going to see me cum!
I forgot that the teachers are having
a meeting to discuss the culture festival!
I need to go!
Are you mad, Yoshikawa?
Of course I am!
What would we have done if we were caught?
Sorry!
Hm?
You're not mad that we were having sex?
Come on, let's study!
Yoshikawa-san...
I-If you study, I wouldn't mind doing it as a reward.
Really?!
Even among the Four Heavenly Kings, I am the most evil.
This is your last chance to realize
the futility of even trying to defeat me.
Who are you?
My name is Leyritt and I am a queen.
I will definitely make you into my slave.
WATCH ME!!
Her name is Hoshikawa Yuna.
She's a gravure idol who
was cast as a villain in a show.
I've been her fan since she debuted
so I'm thrilled to be able to oversee this.
Hoshikawa Yuna's really great isn't she, Hiraoka-san?
Hearing that makes me as happy,
as if he was actually complimenting me.
It's great that she has big boobs,
even though she's a loli.
What'd you say?!
Actually, I just accidentally touched her boobs.
This guy's dangerous,
I have to keep him away from Yuna-chan.
Well, I think Maho-chan is better.
Yeah, Maho-chan is good too.
Her boobs are kinda small though.
I think the size is fine. They're small, but delicate.
Well, big boobs do tend to sag, right?
Serial drama: The Hero and the Witch
Hoshikawa Yuna
Come in.
Excuse me, you called?
Ah, yes, over here.
What's the matter?
U-Um...
I was thinking that I should
thank you for your hard work.
My boobs are soft and feel good, you see?
Wh-What?!
Th-They're so soft.
See?
Th-They're so squishy.
I could give you a titfuck if you want.
Do you want to cover me in sperm?
Knock it off!
I've been your fan ever since you debuted...
I've been cheering you on all this time,
so I was so happy that after all your hard work,
you finally became popular!
B-But did you actually get your job
by doing something like this?!
N-No way!
This is the first time I've done something like this.
So why me?
I'm nobody special, just an AD.
Hoshikawa Yuna
You were the first person to come to
my first ever handshake event, weren't you?
You remember that?
Of course!
I would always wonder if you were coming or not.
But then, you started coming less often...
So when we were reunited here, I was really happy.
But then I heard you saying
that you thought Maho-chan was better.
That was a big shock...
I couldn't stand it.
I wanted you to look at me more than her.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry! You've got it all wrong though!
I still like you the most.
Back there, my colleague was praising
you so much that I got over-excited
and ended up saying the opposite
of what I was thinking to cover it up.
Really?
You really like me?
O-Of course!
I like you the most!
I'm so happy!
I like you the most too!
Hiraoka-san...
U-Um... something hard is hitting me.
S-Sorry. It, um... It just acts on its own...
If we wait, it'll go down eventually.
Why wait?
W-Well...
Let's do something romantic to celebrate today.
You don't have to force yourself.
See, I'm like this anyway.
I just lost my virginity.
I'm so happy that you're my first.
Y-Yuna-chan...
I'm so happy! Being connected with
you like this... it's like a dream come true!
I like you! I love you!
Me too, Yuna-chan.
Hiraoka-san!
That feels so good!
It feels so good right there!
I'm so happy! Yuna-chan is expressing
how much she loves me with her entire body.
I'm so happy!
I'm cumming!
Sheesh, you're horrible.
Sorry, I didn't think cummmg inside was
a good idea, but I didn't mean to cover you with it.
No, that's not what I meant.
I don't want you cumming anywhere but inside.
Yuna-chan?
Her tongue is wrapped around me...
Yuna-chan's mouth feels so good!
I'm fine, okay?
So go deeper!
Yuna-chan!
I love you... I love you!
That's not fair.
I love you. I love you so much!
Watch me carefully, okay?
You can't look at other girls, okay?
You've always been the only one,
Yuna-chan. Then and now!
From now on too.
Of course!
Here I go!
This time you let out a lot inside.
By the way, there's something that's been bothering me...
What is it?
Do you like big or small breasts more?
Um, well...
Come on, tell me.
I'd love you no matter what size you were.
Okay. Good answer.
Ryou... suke...
I can't believe this is happening.
Your boobs are something else!
They're so squishy and nice!
They're not gross?
As if they'd ever be.
I'm so happy!
Wow...
It's so wet and hot down there.
How is it?
It feels good.
Ryousuke!
I can't hold back anymore.
Please...
I never thought I'd see Honoka like this.
That's because
I love you
Stare...
Ho-Honoka-chan, what's the matter?
Scared...
I'm jealous.
Small Boobs
Big Boobs
What?!
Did you really just say that?
Geez, did something happen with Ryousuke-kun?
What a great view. Bloomers are amazing, aren't they?
Honoka-chan?
Huh? Why are you bringing her up?
You two are always so friendly, so I thought
you might be interested in her or something.
We've been with each other since we were little
but I don't like her like that or anything.
She's cute and has big boobs,
but you have no interest in her?
No way I'd like someone with cow tits like hers.
I, uh... I like small breasts!
So that's what happened?
What should I do?
I never knew he liked small breasts.
I wonder if there's a way to make them smaller.
Hey, Honoka-chan.
If he doesn't understand the beauty of big breasts,
all you have to do is make him understand it.
How?
I-I-I can't do that!
Of course you can. Are you okay with Ryousuke-kun
being taken by some flat chested bimbo?
No, I'm not...
Then do your best!
Yeah... I'll do my best.
Huh? Why am I in the nurse's office?
G-Good morning...
What are you doing?
Giving you a titfuck.
No, I can see that...
Your dick is getting really hard and stiff.
So this feels good, huh?
Well, yeah...
Good.
I'm glad.
Crap, if she keeps going like that, I'm gonna...
Wow, you came so much.
So, big breasts are good, right?
Seriously... What are you playing at?
I was trying to get you to understand
how awesome big breasts are.
Huh, why?
You're a complete idiot, aren't you?
Wh-What? I'm not an idiot.
You are.
Do you do this to just anyone?
A-As if I'd do this with anyone but you.
Wh-Why?
Because...
Because I love you, Ryousuke!
I heard you saying that you like small
breasts... but I have big breasts!
I tried thinking of ways to
make you come to like them, but...
Yeah, you're an idiot all right.
I was just saying that to get him off my back...
Ryou... suke?
I love your boobs.
R-Really?
Ryousuke...
I can't hold back any longer.
Please...
I won't be able to stop until I'm done, okay?
Ryousuke's going inside!
Wow, this feels like a dream!
I'm so happy!
They're really amazing.
Your boobs are bouncing like crazy!
S-Sorry!
Why are you apologizing?
I told you I loved your boobs, didn't I?
Ryousuke, I love you. I love you so much!
Ryou... suke...
By the way, how'd I get to the nurse's office?
I think I feel a bump on my head...
Eh?
No idea...
HentaiHaven.org
Translation: Hikarucon
Timing: V1touch
Typesetting: Hybrio21
Editor: Punk4real
Quality control: Fyurie