I'm sorry.
So, you like someone else?
Well.
The answer is yes.
Youth is such a bittersweet thing.
Someone... I like, huh?
That was amazing.
So you're at it again, eh.
Oh you.
That's not really it.
Jeez, Natsumi.
Not really it, huh...? So how many so far?
I must have done something bad.
By the way, you do look kind of nice, Ema.
She sure does.
So envious. Gimme some of those breasts, too!
Hey!
It feels embarrassing when you two look at them.
What? You've got nothing to lose from us staring, anyway.
I know, right?
Oh come on. Of course I have something to lose!
She definitely doesn't look our age.
So mature.
Is that what boys notice about me?
Oh yeah, onee-chan told me,
that breasts can grow bigger when fondled.
Ohh.
Indeed.
Jeez, nobody's doing that!
Yeah, that's actually false.
I guess you're right.
Really?
Welcome back.
Oh, Dad!
I came to fetch you.
Hello.
Your dad looks cool.
Really?
He definitely is!
Your friends sure are courteous.
Oh my.
Indeed.
With that kind of dad,
our boys don't even stand a chance.
See you then!
Bye, Ema-chan!
See ya!
He's pretty much my dad at this point.
I really cherish him.
Shall we head home as well?
'Kay!
I'm home!
The house is kinda big for just the two of us.
The entire family lived here before.
We've gotten quite sweaty.
Shall we take a bath together, then?
Okay!
I'll be the one to clean you today, Dad.
Of course. You're such a good girl, Ema.
You've always taken care of me.
It's like this, right?
Yes, you've got it.
Good then.
You're doing well, Ema.
It's getting bigger.
Does this feel good?
It does. It feels amazing.
I'm glad he's enjoying it.
I wonder when I first felt like this.
Oh yeah, it reminds me of that incident before.
It was back when I first stepped foot inside this house.
I did it again.
I peed on the bed.
I felt so embarrassed,
that I tried to hide it, but.
Ema, is something wrong?
It was no use.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
Is he mad at me?
I'll wash it for you, so let's take a bath.
He then took me to the bathroom.
I guess he's mad at me.
I'm sure of it.
You're not mad?
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
It's good that you apologized properly.
But you see,
you'll have to properly tell me if it's about to leak from now on.
'Kay.
What's this?
I feel a bit ticklish as the water flows down between my legs.
Tell me when you're about to pee next time,
so that I can properly clean it like this.
It's clean now.
Alright, shall we go for some ice cream?
'Kay!
I wanna eat ice cream now.
I think that might've triggered it.
I've been pleasuring him, so that he could return the favor.
The seasons have passed us by,
but I see you've grown quite well, Ema.
Dad.
Children often try even harder whenever they're praised.
But in the end, they're still children.
Dad,
well...
What is it?
I want to... pee.
Letting me know in advance,
you sure are a good girl, Ema.
Really?
I'll be watching closely, so just let it out.
Good girl. You peed quite a lot.
Now we'll just need to wash it clean.
As always,
she entrusts herself to me by leaning on me.
The water warms up our already hot bodies.
All the while, I stimulate her sensitive spots.
Properly.
Thoroughly.
Looks like this particular spot is soiled.
Here.
Her hips soon start to unconsciously
move as I continue washing her.
Feeling tingly? My, such a naughty girl.
It became soiled again.
Dad, umm.
Please.
Oh? What was that?
Ah, so you want to feel even better?
I did teach her that it wasn't technically wrong,
but she's still a growing maiden.
She's probably embarrassed to say it.
Will you do the usual, then?
'Kay.
Alright, good.
I'm going to move, Ema.
Good girl. That feels great.
Umm.
I was... confessed to today.
I see. So what happened?
It was
a boy from our class.
Forget about it.
My mind's going blank.
Oh no!
It feels too good.
You belong only to me, Ema.
Do you understand?
I'm completely yours right now.
That's good.
Ema,
please, make me feel even better.
That's good, Ema.
This is the best.
Dad!
I'm sorry. That was a bit too rough.
I'll make it feel better for you.
She really grew up well.
Indeed, she has become a good girl, able to accept my desires.
I love you, Ema.
You are the apple of my eye.
My heart throbs only for you, and my love
transcends this world's splendor.
I alone lay claim upon you
and my dominion shall last an eternity.
I'm cumming inside.
Me too, I'm about to cum!
It's already this late, huh?
Shall we go for dinner, then?
'Kay.
About earlier,
the confession.
Oh, yes.
He asked me if I already like someone.
Is that so?
Do you?
Dad's such a meanie.
I'll be the one to properly comfort you, Dad.