Tagami-san, you're awake.
How are you feeling?
That's the landlady's daughter, Sanae-chan, right?
Why is she here?
BEWARE THE FEVER!!
I heard that you had a fever and were bedridden,
and I was worried about you.
So I brought cough medicine, among other tings.
Th-Thanks, you're a lifesaver.
I brought food, too.
I'll make you a healthy meal from this, so please take it easy.
You don't have to...
I'm pretty sure that's what happened.
The food will be ready soon.
I'm okay, really! The landlady will get worried,
so you should hurry up and head home...
I told my mom that I'd be nursing you, Tagami-san.
Besides, we live right next door, so it doesn't
matter if I go home late at night.
No, no, no, that's not the sort of concern I'm talking about.
She’d be worried about you being in the dwelling
of a single bachelor, even if he is ill.
I'm afraid of inadvertently laying hands on her.
Listen, it's just not safe, so go home.
What's not safe?
Oh no, the pot!
At any rate, I'm almost done here, so please wait.
Okay!
Now we just need to...
Men are dangerous.
They'll do things like this to you.
Um, I don't mind.
This sort of thing always happens to me.
Always? Students nowadays...
Wait a minute... Hmm? I thought you were more innocent.
They are six years younger than me,
but my little brother was the center of attention.
And he clung all over me as well.
I see.
If you're so used to it, then that means
I can touch them some more, right?
They sure are big.
It must be because they're always getting touched.
That's... not...
Don't... squeeze my nipples!
Your skin is smooth, cool, and feels good, Sanae-chan.
Stop... this...
Tagami-san...
You still have a fever, so you need to keep warm and go to bed.
You're right.
M-My skirt!
Ow!
So this is a penis...
You're so warm, Sanae-chan.
No! Don't rub against me!
You got wet.
It feels so good.
You're probably warmer on the inside.
Inside? No, stop!
You're moving too fast! You jammed your
penis all the way in right from the start!
This... is my first... time...
The heat is sort of relieving.
Now look!
Let's get warmer!
It hurts!
You're so wet, it feels good. It's so warm.
I'm going to cum!
Sorry! It felt so good that I came inside.
It's leaking out onto the floor.
It's fine, I'll wipe it up later.
Before that, let's continue in bed.
Okay.
There you go, that's nice!
But I want you to take it in deeper and harder.
I didn't think you would fuck me so boldly. You must love sex.
N-No! Sex isn't what I love, Tagami-san!
Yeah, whatever!
This time I'm going to pour my cum deeper inside you, okay?
But then I'll get pregnant!
Don't worry! I'm an adult who can take
responsibility, unlike a student!
I-Is that a propos...?
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm so hot on the inside.
Just a bit longer... Let's stay like this for a little while longer...
The ceiling? Was that a dream just now?
Good morning, Tagami-san! How is your fever?
It wasn't a dream!
This is bad! Even if I was half out of it with
a fever, I fucked the landlady's daughter!
U-Um, Tagami-san...
I was so happy! The guy I had been
crushing on proposed to me...
My mom gave her approval when I contacted
her a just a moment ago.
Take responsibility for this, please.
O-Okay!
I'm home!
Welcome home, Sou-chan!
I'm Souta Koishigawa.
This is my big sister who is two years
older than me, Maho Koishigawa.
Our parents got married two years ago...
...and I got my first step-sister.
Hello! I'm your new sister!
I'd always been the only child, so I had no idea what to do.
Hey, Tou-chan. Hey, listen to me!
But Maho-nee was an extremely friendly person.
Even a little too friendly at times.
But we've grown very dose, and get along too well now.
Why are you in here?!
But I...
...am in love with Maho-nee.
Let's go as a couple.
Recommended dating spots
It'd be great if I could go to a place like this with Maho-nee.
Sou-chan, I rented the DVD you've been dying to watch!
Let's watch it together!
D-Don't scare me like that, Maho-nee!
Ah, what are you hiding? A dirty magazine?
Nope! Come on, let's go to the living room!
I'm really looking forward to this!
Of course it was to be expected, but...
...Maho-nee only saw me as a little brother.
Maybe it's better this way.
I couldn't ask her out on a date again today.
I'll try again tomorrow.
Maho-nee is reckless
Huh? Maho-nee?
Sou-chan, check it out!
I caught a sea cucumber!
Owwwww!
I'm sorry! I don't know my own strength.
Ma-Maho-nee...? What are you doing?
S-Sneaking into your bed?
Just do as you're told, Sou-chan!
Woah, Maho-nee is really sucking my dick!
Is this dream?
It's too real to be a dream.
Maho-nee's mouth is so hot.
Maho-nee's pussy!
Maho-nee is wet.
This is Maho-nee's flavor.
Sou-chan!
Maho-nee's tongue is wrapped around my cock!
It feels so good! It feels like I'm going to cum already!
I think it's good to go.
Maho-nee!
It won't go in!
You don't have to force it!
Oh no! You don't want me, Sou-chan?
Do you love your girlfriend more than me?
Uh, girlfriend?
I'm the one who loves you the most, Sou-chan!
Maho-nee...
Sou-chan...
I... love ou Maho-nee.
Do you mean it?
Of course I do! I don't even have a girlfriend.
What gave you that idea?
B-But... you were looking at a dating magazine,
and you had a bunch of bookmarks in it.
So I figured you had a girlfriend and were
going to go to those places with her.
Maho-nee...
Oh, so it was all just a misunderstanding. Thank goodness!
I love you too, Maho-nee.
I love you, Sou-chan!
Maho-nee, you're bleeding!
It's okay! I'm happy that you're my first, Sou-chan.
Fuck me, Sou-chan!
Your insides are warm and feel so good, Maho-nee!
Sou-chan!
I've become one with you, Sou-chan!
I'm so happy!
Maho-nee!
I'm... happy that we became one as well, Maho-nee!
I love you, Sou-chan!
Fill me up with your cum!
Maho-nee!
Sou-chan, let's go on a date!
But I haven't decided where to go yet!
I don't mind as long as I am with you, Sou-chan!
You see...
I want to walk around town as lovers!
Maho-nee!
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's all the way in!
The things I love about Maho-nee...
are that she is cute and beautiful, good at cooking...
...and that she likes me to pamper her
despite her being older than me.
Sou-chan!
Maho-nee...
I love you!
I also love that she loves me so much!
Also... I may like the fact that she is rather erotic.
I feel that she propositions me for sex more than I do her.
Sou-chan, your cock...
...feels so good!
I want it deeper inside me!
Stick it all the way in!
And as for the part that I especially like...
It's gotta be her boobs.
You sure like boobs.
They are so plump, juicy, and bouncy!
It turns out that Maho-nee's boobs are actually quite sensitive.
I can send her into fits of ecstasy simply by sucking on them.
Don't suck on the tips like they're cocks!
You're like a baby, Sou-chan!
Speaking of which, milk comes from boobs, right?
I wonder what it tastes like.
I sure would like to drink breast milk.
Wait...
Did I say that out loud?
What should I dot!? She might have heard me!
I-I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
My boobs can't produce milk!
Just wait, please!
I'll make them produce milk!
Don't hate me!
Um... does that mean you're trying to make a baby?
Th-That's not what I meant!
But I do want your kids, Sou-chan!
I also find her silliness charming.
I can't choose just one thing I love about her.
I love everything about her!