Monsters and humans...
Aiming for a world where they can coexist peacefully...
The legendary hero Luka and Alipheese...
Continue their journey...
At that coastal village...
Within the succubus illusory world of temptation...
The monsters continue to milk the hero dry.
Hero Luka, do you realize that you're giving us more power each time you ejaculate?
Well, let's see just how long you can keep going!
Monster Girl Quest ~ Lose and get raped by enchanting women ~
Minagi: The Great Whore of Babylon
Where am I? Am I...dead?
I'm sorry, Alice. It looks like I wasn't strong enough.
You can't fight back this time, can you?
Now I can do whatever I want to you, hehe.
No, no more...
I'll make your penis nice and clean with my washing technique.
It, it feels so slippery... and g-good!
I'll carefully wash every inch from the tip to the base.
Aaaah, stop it...
Hahaha, you're totally entranced.
Does my washing technique feel that good?
In that case, let me make it even more intense.
Stop! Not there!
Not where?
Here? Yep, here.
Hahaha, you came!
You're shooting out so much.
Now that you're dirty, I have to wash you all over again.
Please...don't stroke me...
Oh? What's wrong?
Are you about to come again?
You must really want me to keep washing you.
All right then, just for you, I'll clean you out completely.
No, that's not what I want. Please don't!
You're totally writhing in pleasure. I'm way too good for you.
Hora, hurry up and come!
I'm going to wring every last drop out of you!
How does it feel to be embraced by a spider queen?
I'm going to squeeze out lots of your semen and give you a taste of heaven.
Weird. Her insides are so slick and moving around me.
It feels so goooood...
I can't stop... I'm going to come inside her.
I'll suck all the semen out of you, hero.
Just relax and come.
C-coming!
Your semen is delicious and such high quality.
Fill my pussy up until it can't hold another drop!
Stop...no more...
Feeling good? The more turned on I get, the better it'll feel inside me.
I'm so sensitive from coming just now, but, but...
This feels amazing! She's so wet and squeezing me tight.
I'm loving this. I bet you can't resist it either.
Just wait until I squeeze you out deep inside my pussy!
This is paradise, isn't it?
Stop! If you squeeze any more...
What, what is this!?
I can't take any more! I'm going to come!
How does it feel to come inside me?
Hora, let me suck on you until your semen is all dried up.
Cut it out! Stop tightening around me! Coming again!
Haha! Look what I managed to catch in my tentacles! Lucky!
The way you look right now is super pa-the-tic.
I'm barely squeezing you at all and you're screaming like a girl.
I thought you were supposed to be a hero, but your cock is twitching for me.
Stop, no more! It's too tight!
Aaaah, you came already?
Your cock erupted so fast. Is it defective?
So pitiful!
Come on!
Hora! Hora hora, Emily's pleasure massage is only just beginning!
This is bad. It feels so good that my waist is moving on its own.
Look at you twitching. Do you think you're having sex or something?
Nope. I'm just playing with your cock.
It's coming ouuuuuut!
What am I doing?
I'm supposed to be a hero!
Luka.
You're the hero who saved the world.
There's no need to fight anymore.
Just indulge in pleasure here with me.
Forever...
No, Alice. Come on...
Don't hold back. We're together now, aren't we?
Let me see you cry tears of pleasure.
H-hang on, Alice. No means no!
I'll let you have the special honor of shooting your dirty semen all over my fingers.
I know how much you like my breasts. You're always stealing glances at them.
Th-that's not true...
How long are you going to keep up that fiction?
Just admit it. My breasts are always on your mind.
You want to know what it'd be like to spew your seed between them.
Alice, your breasts are so soft and warm...
Hora, how much longer can you resist me?
I bet you're about to blow your load.
I can't... If you keep this up, I'm gonna...
You're the only one who gets to experience my mouth.
Yeah, but...
I keep getting hotter the more she sucks on it.
The saliva is making her breasts nice and slick too...
Alice is so much more lewd today than usual.
Can't hold on... I'm going to come again!
This feels good, right? I bet you're at your limit.
Shoot it all out into my mouth!
Alice, hold on. What's gotten into you...
Hora, here's the Monster Lord vagina that took your virginity.
I'll lead you to paradise inside my pussy.
Wait, Alice!
Does this remind you of our first time?
Oh dear. You came right after I put you in, just like when you were a virgin.
That's not fair!
Amazing! Her insides are so wet and squeezing me tight!
Hora, you're feeling great, aren't you? I'll give you the greatest pleasure.
Melt in bliss inside my pussy!
Cut it out, Alice! If you keep this up, I'm going to go mad!
Don't sound so pained, Luka.
You're the man chosen by the Monster Lord.
Aaah, here we go. Pour all your semen deep into my womb!
Hora, hora! You're nearly there, don't hold back!
Alice, please! No more!
I know how much your dick is loving this.
Satiate your lustful desires inside me as much as you want!
I'm never letting you go.
You can stay in this world and keep having sex with me.
Just the two of us. Forever and ever.
Something's not right here.
There are still things I should be doing as a hero.
So I can't even tempt you with the one you love the most.
Huh? What the?
It looks like I'll have to defile you personally.
Wh-who are you?
I am Minagi, one of the Six Ancestors sealed by Ilias.
I see. So you're the one behind all of this?!
I'm going to take the fight out of you and make you my puppet.
I don't think so!
Jaws of the Rakshasa, come and drive out evil!
She, she disappeared?
Now, just drown in pleasure.
Is that all the energy you've got?
What is this?
I can see all of your life through my bindings.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
It looks like you're feeling plenty good wrapped up.
Oh? Are you suffering? I know you'll like this, though.
Enjoy the taste of my juices all you want.
I'm struggling to breathe, but my penis is getting so hot.
You're already turned on. I knew you were a perverted masochist.
Let me give you exactly what you've been hoping for.
She's stroking me so hard it's sending waves through my whole body.
Crap, she's sucking me dry!
I can't resist! I'm going to come as she milks me!
Tastes pretty good., as expected from a hero.
A lowly human like you gets to have sex with me...
...for the first time.
Ascend to heaven! My exquisite pussy will drink you dry!
She's so tight, and getting tighter around me!
Stop, please!
Finished already? Your cum is truly thick and delicious.
Now to make you finish over and over inside me!
No, please let me go. I'm gonna die if you don't stop.
Who cares? You'll just come back to life if you die.
This is an endless world I created...
...where you can come forever! Enjoy it to your heart's content!
Over and over and over and over!
Stop... no more...
It hurts, doesn't it, Luka? Give yourself body and soul to me and this hell will end.
Then you can enjoy an eternity of pleasure...
...in this endless world!
It's over.
Hey, Luka!
Huh, Alice?
Were you planning on sleeping all day?
I cleaned up all the succubi while you were asleep.
You're safe now.
You've been ejaculating nonstop thanks to those succubus skills that hit you.
Eh? Oh...
It's way too late to cover yourself up now.
I've been drinking almost all of your semen while you were passed out.
You were doing what?!
Hero Luka, now I want you even more.
See you at the next feast...