Monsters...
In the process of creating humanity...
The Goddess also gave birth to the monsters.
They were a total failure.
Not long ago, a legendary hero saved the world.
That hero, Luka, strives for coexistence between man and monster.
Together with the Monster Lord Alipheese, they travel the world...
You're going to die if you keep coming, you know.
Succubi like us suck the life right out of you as you ejaculate.
No! I don't wanna die!
Amazing! You just keep pouring out more and more semen!
If you keep sucking on me, I'm gonna die.
I'll make you feel like you're in heaven until you're all dried up.
Argh!
Succubus pussy is amazing, isn't it?
You get to taste the finest pleasure in exchange for your life.
I'll take good care of you in your final moments.
This feels so good... But any more and I'm a goner!
Keep coming! I'm going to drain your semen until you're completely dry!
Get off me!
Aaah, you're pouring your life itself into my pussy.
Isn't being sucked dry by me the greatest?
Your life is now mine. Thanks for the treat.
Jaws of the Rakshasa, come and drive out evil!
Monster Girl Quest ~ Lose and get raped by enchanting women ~ Side Story: Succubus Illusions
Why would succubi attack a remote mountain village like this?
Let's beat them up first and ask questions later.
The great Luka, hero who saved the world.
Still traveling around trying to promote coexistence between man and monster?
Monster Lord Alipheese, ruler of all monsters.
Currently accompanying the hero to deal with any monsters who harm humans.
Hardly a fair fight for my daughters, is it?
Well then, let me introduce you to the world of lust and temptation!
What the? I feel so weak...
Luka! Look over there!
So many parfaits! There are too many to even eat!
What are you talking about? I don't see any parfaits.
Hey, Alice.
Alice, where'd you go?
Welcome to the world of lust and temptation, hero.
S-succubus!
I can't move my body...
Waaaah!
It's time for us to indulge in an orgy of pleasure.
Just leave everything to us, okay?
Let me go!
You ought to be ashamed of yourself for being this erect already, hero.
Your cock is delicious.
This thick precum is just begging me to clean it off.
Aren't you supposed to be a hero?
This isn't good. I can't hold on much longer!
About to come already?
If you come in a succubus's mouth, she's going to suck out more than just your semen, though.
Hora, come! Let it all out!
Crap! It's too much! Aaaaah!
How embarrassing, hero. Look how much you poured out into a succubus's mouth.
No more. Don't suck out any more...
Don't you want to feel this sweet pleasure forever, hero?
You can stay in this world and have fun with us from now on.
No please, anywhere but there!
You're inside me now. My succubus pussy is going to milk the semen right out of you.
Let me go!
Feels great, doesn't it, hero?
Enjoy having your life itself sucked out.
Amazing, you're so big!
Let me suck on your cock even more for you!
I can't hold it in...
It's no use, I'm gonna come...
Can't resist...
Let me tighten up inside and suck even harder...
Stop! You're draining me dry!
Aaaaah!
I'm losing... consciousness...
Luka, Luka.
Wake up, Luka.
E-Erubetie?
Oh, did you come and save me?
Save you?
Sure, that's one way of putting it.
What a relief. My body is so heavy I can't even move.
Luka, you've fought enough.
You can just relax now.
Huh?
Clear your mind and let me take care of your body.
You always get hard so fast, Luka.
You sound so pitiful, you know.
That's fine. I'll make you into my slave.
This isn't fine!
What isn't? You're obviously enjoying it.
Having your cock sucked makes you happy, doesn't it?
Nooo! Please, you're sucking too hard!
Aaah, I'm going to come! Stop!
Like I said, that's just fine.
I want you to come.
I'm here to milk all your semen out for you.
Let it out!
Commmming!
Heheh...
All you have to do is surrender to your desires and embrace the depravity...
..and eternal pleasure is yours.
Please no. Don't force me inside.
I'm still really sensitive!
Aaaaaah!
The hero's cock is inside me!
Luka, how does my pussy taste?
How does it feel to have your cock inside me?
Tell me. I'm dying to know.
That's all you're concerned about?!
Her insides are rubbing against me and stirring me up.
I'm gonna go mad!
Not yet. I haven't had enough yet.
Forget about everything else and just think about coming.
Aaah! This is bad, really bad.
There's gotta still be something I can do.
Don't waste your breath.
Just stick your tongue in deeper and get a better taste instead!
Oh man...
There we go! Like that!
It's no use. She's going to milk me dry.
I, I don't want to come...
...but my dick won't stop twitching.
I can't hold it in. So much cum is waiting to pour out!
Now! Come with everything you've got!
Commmmming!
Amazing!
So wonderful...
Your torrent of semen is exploding into my womb.
There's so much of it!
This time I'll be the one to send you to heaven.
Look how hard you still are.
While you experience the final throes of pleasure...
I'll finally break you.
Time to put your cum-covered cock in me.
It's so tight!
I'm gonna come in no time like this!
It really is going to be the last time I ever do!
Yes, I'm going to wring out you for the last time!
Feels wonderful, doesn't it?
Come whenever you desire.
Come until you don't have a drop left in you!
C-coming! I'm commmming!
Huh?
Now it's my turn to play with you.
Alma Elma? Wh-what are you doing?
There's no reason for you to attack humans anymore.
You've been helping me promote coexistence between humans and monsters!
Alma Elma?
Luka-chan, you know what this means, right?
I only get naked when it's time to get serious.
There's no need to worry your pretty little head.
Just let me send you to heaven between my breasts.
I came so many times already. So why does this feel so good?
You don't have to hold back.
You shouldn't be doing this though...
But you're so hard already.
Spray all over my breasts whenever you feel like coming.
Sorry Alma Elma, I can't... I can't...
Hold baaaaaaack!
Just once isn't enough.
I'm going to make you drown in my breasts!
No, stop! If you keep this up...
Keep coming and make my breasts sloppy with your semen.
Let it all out and I'll be sure to reward you!
Your mind still isn't broken?
Guess I better rape you then!
You know what's next, right?
Once my pussy swallows you up, it's going to drain every last drop out of you.
Please don't!
It's your fault for being this stubborn, Luka.
Now, ascend to heaven inside my pussy!
Hehe, you came already?
Aren't you embarrassed to come so easily, Luka-chan?
I don't want to come...
...but my body keeps doing it on its own!
That's a shame, Luka-chan.
If you were honest, I'd give you a taste of the sweetest pleasure...
But since you keep being stubborn, I have to squeeze you to death!
Offer up all your semen to me!
Every last drop of it!
Hora! Ascend to heaven inside my pussy!
The next one is going to be your last.
I'm going to drain it all and send you to heaven.
Alma Elma, were those succubi attacking the village earlier your friends?
There's no need to worry about that.
You're about to die here, after all.
See you, Luka.
Thanks for the treat, Luka-chan.
But this torture doesn't end here.
Not until you succumb to temptation. Got it?
This isn't right... Erubetie and Alma Elma wouldn't do this.
Someone else is responsible...
As expected from the hero who defeated the Goddess Ilias.
No matter how many times you're about to die, it isn't so easy to break your mind.
Very well. Then I'll have to show you even more fun.
Until you're a slave to pleasure...
Heh heh... Hahaha...