"Demons and Humans".
"In order to bring peace to the world."
"Legendary Warrior Luca and Alicefeeze"
"continue to travel together..."
"In the village by the seashore."
"Trapped in the illusion made by succubi."
"Their souls keep getting sucked out..."
Warrior Luca, are you aware your semen is
giving us more power?
I am determined to see you die.
Monmusu Quest!
Where am I? Am I dead?
I'm sorry Alice, I couldn't stay strong.
You can't fight anymore, can you?
You just let me do whatever I wanted.
Ah... please stop!
Let me wash your penis using my hand-job skills.
It's so slippery... it feels so good.
Making sure to clean from the tip to the bottom.
S... stop please!
Look at you... you're loving it, aren't you?
Very well, I'm gonna play much harder now.
No... not there please!
What do you mean by there?
Do you mean right here? Or here?
Yay, you came!
So much sperm... you made it dirty again.
I gotta wash it again.
Please... stop moving your hands.
What's going on? Coming again so soon?
You really want me to wash you huh?
Then I'll give you something special.
No, that's not it... please stop.
You're moaning so much.
You can't last any longer huh?
Come on, come for me now!
I'm gonna squeeze till your last drop comes out.
I'm coming!
How do you like fucking a spider queen?
Enjoy giving me your semen before going to heaven.
What is this... you're moving so much inside of me.
It feels so good.
I'm about to come.
I want all the semen from you, Warrior.
Stop worrying and come inside of me.
I'm coming!
What a tasty semen.
I won't finish till I have all of it in my pussy.
Please stop...
Can you feel my pussy getting tighter?
It's too good... your pussy is
squeezing my penis so tight.
I can feel it getting much tighter.
That's it... you love it too, don't you?
No matter what, I want all your semen in me.
This feels like heaven.
Wait, don't get any tighter please.
What's going on...
I can't hold it any longer... I'm coming.
I'm coming.
How do you like coming inside my pussy?
See? Squeezing all of you... your soul too.
Please stop... stop squeezing me.
I can't stop coming!
Look, my tentacles are hugging you.
You look so pathetic right now boy!
You're moaning from such a light squeeze.
Are you really a warrior?
Your penis is shaking.
No, please stop... they're moving so hard.
You came already?
Is your penis defective?
How pathetic.
No...
Come on, your massage has just started!
No... my hips are moving cuz it feels so good.
Look at your penis shaking so much.
You pretending to have sex?
I'm just playing with your penis.
I'm coming!
This is bad... really bad.
I need to act like a Warrior!
Luca... Luca?
You once saved the world.
You don't need to fight anymore.
You can now drown in the pleasure.
Forever.
N-No, Alice.
Don't hold back, it's me.
I wanna see you drown in pleasure.
Alice, no... we can't.
I'll give you a special permission,
to put your dirty semen on my hands.
I know you love my boobs too.
I caught you staring at them all the time.
No, that's not true!
How long can you stay this stubborn?
Give in already.
Just say you've been wanting my boobs
and wanted to put semen all over them.
Your boobs are so soft and warm.
Let's see how long you can last.
I can tell you're about to come.
No, stop... I can't hold it any longer.
Your penis is the only one to touch my mouth.
It's so...
Stop sucking so hard.
It's getting so hot again.
Her boobs are so wet from her saliva.
Today's Alice is so naughty.
Ah I can't hold it any longer... I'm coming!
Your penis is shaking so much.
You're at your limits, aren't you?
Go ahead and come in my mouth.
Alice, please wait...
See? This is the pussy that took your virginity.
Let me show you heaven with this pussy again.
Wait, Alice!
Do you remember our first time?
Well well, you came just by putting it in my pussy.
Just like when you were a virgin.
Because.
Wow, her pussy is so soft and tight!
Don't you love it?
My pussy gives you the best pleasure.
Come inside my pussy!
No, Alice... please stop or else.
I'm gonna go crazy...
Don't say such pathetic things.
You're chosen by me, the Devil Queen!
That's it, put your semen straight into my uterus.
Come on, fuck me harder! Don't hold back!
Alice, please, can't hold anymore.
I can feel your penis enjoying my pussy.
Come as much as you want into my uterus!
I won't let you go anymore.
We'll have sex in this world forever.
Together in this world forever and ever.
There's something strange.
There's more I need to do as a warrior.
I can't believe you won't even give into her.
What... what's going on?
It seems I have to be the one to drown you.
W-Who are you?
My name is Minagi.
I'm one of the ancestors sealed by illias.
I see... it was you this whole time!
I'm going to control you after drowning you in pleasure.
I won't let you!
Minagi, I now end you from this world!
She disappeared...?
Let's see you drown in pleasure now.
So this is your vitality.
W-What's this?
My power let me see all your vitality.
It... it hurts!
I see you get more excited with torture.
How's this? Too tight?
Or you're getting more turned on?
Taste my pussy as much as you want.
Why... I can't breathe but my penis is getting so hard.
Look how hard it is... I knew you'd love it.
You want me so badly? As you wish.
So hot... and my penis feels so tingly.
No, I can't let her take my semen!
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm coming again, but I shouldn't...!
Pretty delicious... you're a warrior after all.
You are the first human ever,
to have sex with me.
Come on, come inside me.
My perfect pussy will suck up all your semen.
Her pussy's getting tighter...!
Please stop... please!
You came already?
Give me more of your thick delicious semen in me!
Please forgive me...
If you keep going, I'm going to die!
I don't care, you'll be revived anyways!
This is a world created by me.
There's no death so we can keep going.
Enjoy to the fullest!
Again and again and again!
I don't want to.
I love seeing you suffer.
The torture will end after you give me everything,
in this endless world.
You'll be able to enjoy this pleasure forever!
You're finished!
Hey, Luca!
Alice...?
Wake up, I killed all the succubi while you were sleeping.
Are you okay now?
You kept ejaculating under their spell.
Too late to hide it now.
With my power, I can easily
drink all of your semen... no problem.
Wait... you did what?
Warrior Luca, I want you more than ever now.
We'll meet at my next party.
перевод Hentaisun
хард в этот раз уже не захентаился выдирать торрент иваниваныч...