What is a "Monster?"
"Due to the surplus of humans that the goddes created..."
"They were born."
"Failures."
"As a legendary hero who once saved the world,"
"Luca aimed to make a world where both
monsters and humans could coexist."
"To that end he and the Demon King Arisphese worked together..."
If you cum any more than that, you're gonna die.
We succubi make males cum to steal their life energy.
N-No!
Don't!
That's amazing.
Your cum is still gushing out.
If you keep sucking that hard, I'm gonna die!
I'll make you cum until there's nothing left.
The succubi pussy is amazing isn't it?
It's a pleasure that you can only gain
by exchanging your life force for.
I'll make sure you enjoy every last second until your end.
I-It feels so good!
But this can't go on!
It's coming out!
I'll make sure to keep squeezing
you until there's nothing left!
No!
It's okay. Your life force is pouring out into my pussy.
Doesn't it feel good to be sucked dry by me?
Your life is mine now.
It was delicious.
Man-eater Agito.
Heed my call and taste my blade!
~Losing Means Getting Raped by a Demon~
Story: Succubus Fantasy
Monster Girls Quest!
I can't believe that the succubi are
attacking a remote village like this.
Just...
We can talk later. Let's rip them all to shreds.
Yeah!
Luca the Hero.
The hero who once saved the world.
He's still continuing his journey to unite
the monsters and the humans.
Arisphese, the one who stands above
all other monster as their king,
is currently assisting the hero on his
quest and helping him kill monsters.
It seems that they have quite the
grudge towards my subordinates.
Very well then.
I'll gladly show you the door to the world of temptation!
Wh-What's going on?
My strength is leaving my body.
Luca look at that!
Parfaits!!
I don't think I can finish this all!
What are you talking about?
There's no parfait... anywhere...
Hey, Aris?
Aris?!
Wh-Where are you?
Welcome to the world of temptation, Lord Hero.
A-A succubus?
What?
I can't move my body!
I'm going to drown you in pleasure.
Now, leave your body to us, okay?
Let go!
Lord Hero, your dick has gotten so big. How shameful.
This dick is so tasty.
It's so hard, it must really want me to suck it.
How shameful for a supposed hero.
S-Stop this...
I-I'm gonna cum!
Are you gonna cum already?
Don't you know that your life force is taken
when a succubus drinks your cum?
Come on, cum! Make a mess!
Stop!
Don't suck it!
How embarrassing, Lord Hero.
You just came so much in the mouth of a succubus.
Stop this! Don't suck it anymore!
But don't you want to experience eternal pleasure?
Don't you want to have fun with us in this world forever?
Stop! A-Anything but that!
It went inside!
It's ready to be sucked dry by my succubus pussy.
Let go of me!
Feel free to move more. This is pleasure in exchange for
your life force, you should try to enjoy it to its fullest!!
Wow, you're so big!
I'll suck your dick more for you!
It's getting tighter!
N-No!
I-I'm gonna cum!
I-I can't...
Look at how tight it's getting. I'm
gonna squeeze it all out for you.
S-Stop! I-It's squeezing it out of me!
I-I'm fading...
Luca? Luca?
Wake up. Luca!
Elvetti?
Did you come to save me?
Save you?
I guess. That might be it.
Thank goodness.
My body feels so heavy, I can't move a muscle.
Luca, you've fought enough.
You can relax now.
Don't think about anything.
Just entrust your body to pleasure.
Luca, you seriously got this hard in just a second?
And now you're making these pitiful sounds. How shameful.
It's fine though, just stay like that and become my slave.
No!
What are you saying no to when you're
feeling this much pleasure?
You like having your dick sucked like this, don't you?
I-It's being sucked! Stop! Don't be rough!
I'm cumming! No!
Good. Just like that.
Come on, shoot it out.
I'll squeeze all of your cum out of you, so cum!
I... I'm cumming!
Just let your body indulge its desires and fall into pleasure.
If you do that, you'll obtain eternal pleasure.
D-Don't!
Don't put it in!
I'm still really sensitive...
The hero's dick is inside me!
Luca, how does my pussy taste?
Why don't you tell me what your dick is feeling right now?
I-I can't do that!
It's rubbing her insides!
I can feel myself stirring her up!
I'm gonna lose my mind!
Not yet. This isn't nearly enough.
You need to forget everything and only focus on cumming.
I can't! I still have things I need to do!
Enough with that.
Stick your tongue deep in me!
Taste my pussy!
Yes! Yes, that's it!
N-No. She's going to squeeze the cum out from me again.
I-I don't even want to cum anymore.
But I can't stop my erection!
It's gonna overflow! My dick is gonna explode!
Now! Cum with everything you have!
I'm cumming!!
Amazing!
Wow, your cum is shooting into my womb.
There's so much!
How about I service you next?
You're still rock hard.
I'll let you experience your final moment
of pleasure before I bring this to an end.
I'm gonna put your cum covered dick inside me now.
It's so tight!
I-If this keeps up, I'm gonna cum again!
I'm really gonna be empty after this!
This is the final tightening!
It feels good, doesn't it?
Just cum whenever you want.
Cum until there's nothing left!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
Okay then, it's my turn now.
Allmairma?! Wh-Why are you...
There isn't any need for us to fight anymore.
You said that you'd help to unite the monsters and humans.
Allmairma?
You know already, don't you, Luca-chan?
I only get naked when I'm serious.
You don't need to think about anything difficult.
I'll take you to heaven with my boobs.
H-How am I still feeling this good
after cumming so much already?!
You don't have to hold back.
Th-This shouldn't be happening, but...
You're already this hard. Just cum whenever
you want onto my boobs.
S-Sorry! Allmairma, I'm gonna... I...
No!!
We're not done yet.
I'm gonna coat my boobs with your cum.
S-Stop. I-If this keeps going on...
Just keep cumming and make my boobs drip with your cum.
I'll give you a reward for cumming so much!
Your spirit still won't break, huh?
Okay then, let me rape you.
You know this already, right? Once your dick goes inside
me, it won't let go until it gets every last drop.
S-Stop!
It's your fault for being this stubborn, Luca-chan.
Now ascend from my insides!
Did you come already?
That's gotta be embarrassing to
cum that quickly, Luca-chan.
I just came, but my body is moving on its own!
See, Luca-chan,
if you were just more obedient, you could
experience something a little nicer, but
since you're so stubborn, you're going to
be sucked dry and then killed by me!
Come on, give me all your semen!
Give me every last drop!
Come on! Ascend with my pussy!
One more and then that's it for you.
Just one more time and you'll ascend to heaven.
Allmairma, are those succubi your allies?
You don't need to worry about that anymore.
You're going to die after all.
Goodbye, Luca!
Thanks for the treat, Luca-chan.
But this isn't over yet. It won't be over until you break.
This isn't right. Both Elvetti and Allmairma aren't like
this. There has to be someone pulling the strings.
As expected of the hero who overthrew illias the goddess.
No matter how many times he's brought to the brink of
death, it doesn't seem a simple feat to steal his heart.
Very well then.
I'll just have to entertain myself even more with this.
Until you crumble and fall to pleasure that is.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч