Humans and monsters.
Aimed for a world where they could coexist.
Both the legendary heroes, "Luca" and "Arisphese".
Continued their quest today as well.
Save me!
At a certain village that lay next to the coastline.
Stood a space that succubi had created to
drown those who entered in pleasure.
In that space, the monsters sucked the life force of those within it.
Luca the hero, do you know that every
time you cum, you strengthen us?
Well, let me see just how long you'll last.
~Losing Means Getting Raped by a Demon~
Bewitching/Whore of Babylon
Monster Girl Quest!
W-Where am I? Am I dead?
I'm sorry, Arisa. This is as far as I can go.
He can't struggle or resist like this, right?
You'll just have to sit there and take whatever I do to you.
S-Stop!
I'll wash your dick with my technique.
I-It's getting so wet... It feels so good!
I'll make sure that every last inch
of your dick gets some loving.
S-Stop!
You really seem to be into this.
Is my technique really that good?
Then how about I make this even more intense for you?
No, stop! That's...
What? Be more specific.
Are you talking about this? Or maybe this?
You came!
Look at how much is coming out!
You made such a mess. I guess I have to clean you up again.
Please, don't rub it anymore!
Huh? What's the matter? Are you gonna cum again?
You must really want me to wash you, huh?
Okay then, I'll use my secret technique, just for you.
N-No, don't! Stop!
Are you worried? Is it because you're about to cum again?
Come on, just hurry up and cum already!
I'm gonna squeeze out every last drop!
I-I'm cumming!
How does it feel to make love to the Queen of Spiders?
I'll suck your life force out and let you
have a glimpse of the gates of heaven.
What's happening? Your insides are moving around.
It feels so good!
N-No, I'm gonna cum inside!
I'll suck every last drop out from you, hero.
Just sit back and relax.
I'm cumming!
What high quality life force you have.
What strong seeds you're sowing within me.
I'm going to suck all I can until my womb is full.
Stop... I...
What's wrong? Don't you know that the more pleasure
I feel, the more pleasurable my insides feel to you?
W-Wait, I just came, so I'm still really sensitive...
It feels so good!
It's so wet and it's wrapping around me so tightly!
It feels so good. It feels good for you too, doesn't it?
Just wait. I'll take everything you have into my womb.
I've never felt such great pleasure!
Wait! If you get any tighter, I...
What... What's going on?!
I'm reaching my limit. I won't last much
longer. I'm going to cum. I'm cumming!
How does it feel inside me after I came?
Now it's time for me to wring the
last bit of your life force out of you.
S-Stop! Don't get any tighter!
I... I'm cumming again!!
You're one lucky guy to be between my tentacles!
You look so pitiful right now.
I'm barely even squeezing you, but
you're already moaning like that?
I can't believe a guy like you is a hero.
Your dick's even twitching.
Stop! Don't! This is too intense!
You came already?
Is your dick a piece of crap that just cums immediately?
That's pathetic.
T-That's...
Come on, I'm not done yet. My tentacle massage isn't over!
No! It feels so good, my hips are just moving on their own.
Look at your dick quivering. Does it think
we're gonna have sex or something?
I'm just playing with it a little though.
I-It's gonna come out!
No. This isn't good.
I'm supposed to be a hero!
Luca? Luca?!
You're the hero that saved the world.
There's no more reason for you to fight.
It's over. You should just let yourself
fall to the pleasure in this world.
Forever.
I... I can't, Aris.
Don't hold back. Aren't we close?
I want you to show me what you
look like when you're lost in pleasure.
Wait, Aris... Don't!
I give you special permission. You
may sully my hands with your cum.
You've always liked these breasts of mine too, right?
I could always see you taking a glance
at them at any opportunity you got.
Th-That's not true...
Just how long will you be able to put up that strong front?
Just admit it.
Just say that you've always been fond of my breasts.
Say that you want to try coating them with your cum!
Aris, your boobs are so warm and soft...
Now then, how long will you be able to last?
I know that you're already about to cum.
No. Stop!
If you go any longer, I...
You're the only one I'd use my mouth for.
Th-That's...
If you keep sucking on it like that, I'm gonna get hot again!
Your boobs are getting wet with your saliva.
You're so much more erotic than usual, Aris.
N-No, I'm gonna cum again!
It's starting to twitch and it's getting
bigger! You're about to cum, aren't you?
Cum in my mouth!
A-Aris, wait! What's...
Look, it's the monster queen's
pussy that stole your virginity.
Allow me to show you a good view of heaven
once more with this fleshy hole of mine.
Wait, Aris...
Have you remembered your first time?
Oh my, you came just by putting it in? You're
no different from when you were a virgin.
B-But...
This is amazing. Her insides are so
squishy and they're wrapping around me!
It feels good, doesn't it? I'll show you
the greatest pleasure you've ever had!
Melt within my pussy!
No, Aris! If you're so rough, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna break!
Keep that pathetic voice to yourself.
You're the man that the queen of monsters has chosen.
That's good! Just like that, shoot
your seed inside my womb!
Do it! Come on! Impregnate me!
Come on, don't hold back!
Aris, please, I can't hold back!
I can tell how pleased your dick is!
Fill my womb with your desires to your heart's content!
I'm never letting you go. You're to
stay with me in this world forever.
It'll just be the two of us until the end of time.
Something's... something's not right.
There should still be something
left that I need to do as a hero.
Your spirit won't break even in
the face of your greatest lover?
Huh? Wait, what?
It seems I'm left with no choice but
to take matters into my own hands.
Who's there?
My name is Minagi.
I'm one of the six monsters once sealed by illias.
I get it. You're the mastermind behind all this!
I'll pick you to the bone and make you my puppet.
That's not happening!
Man-eating Agito! Lay waste to the evil before me!
S-She disappeared?
Now, drown in pleasure.
So this is your life force, huh?
What is this?!
I can see your very life with my garment.
It hurts! It hurts! It really hurts!
You get turned on through pain, huh?
So, does it hurt?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Get your fill of my juices.
W-Why? I can't breathe and it hurts so
much, but my dick is getting so hot!
Hurting you more gets you more aroused?
You really are a very perverted masochist.
If you want to become my puppet
that badly, I'll grant your wish!
Th-The pleasure's so intense, I'm getting tingly all over!
No, she's gonna suck everything from me!
I can't resist!
I'm gonna cum again! She's gonna squeeze it out of me!
Quite the taste. Nothing less from a hero, I suppose.
You're the first human to ever make love to me.
Now focus. I'm going to wring
you dry of all of your life force!
It's getting tight! It's getting so tight!
Stop! Please!
You already reached your limit?
Your cum really has a raw but refined taste to it.
Now then, I'm going to have you do that many more times!
P-Please let me go! If you do this anymore, I-I'm gonna die!
That matters not.
I'll just resurrect you once you die!
This is a special world I created that has no end.
A nightmare of pleasure where
you'll be cumming for all eternity.
Now, get a good taste of it!
Over and over and over again!
N-No, stop!
It hurts, doesn't it, Luca?
If you offer both your soul and
body to me, this hell will end.
You'll be rescued from this world without end.
You'll be able to enjoy your
desires as well as endless pleasure!
It's over.
Hey, Luca!
A-Aris?
What are you asleep for?
I took care of the rest of the succubi while you slept.
Are you okay now?
While you were under the succubus's spell,
you just kept cumming over and over again.
It's a bit too late to hide it now.
Well for someone of my power, taking
in all of your cum was an easy feat.
Huh?! You did that?!
Luca, the hero. I've come to want you even more now.
Be ready for the next party.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч