Demons...
They are born...
as failed creatures by a Goddess
in the process of creating humans.
Luca, the warrior who once saved the world.
Traweled together with a Satan, Alicefeeze,
to make a peaceful world.
For both humans and demons.
You're going to die if you come anymore.
We steal your souls by making you come, you know?
No, no way! Stop it!
Wow, you are coming so much.
If you suck any harder, I'm going to die...
I'm going to send you to heaven...
Don't you just love our pussies?
You get to have sex with us in return for your souls.
I'm going to let you enjoy till you die.
It feels so good... but, I cah't hold it any longer.
Wow, I can feel you coming so much!
I'm gonna keep on going till I suck your soul too!
That's it. Your soul is filling my pussy.
You love it, don't you?
Thank you for your soul... it was delicious.
Hey you, Agito!
I'm here to send you back to hell!
Monmusu Quest!
I can't believe Succubuses are here in the mountains.
We gotta kill them before we discuss that.
Yeah!
Warrior Luca, you once saved the world.
I hear you are travelling to make this world a safe place.
And Alicefeeze... the top of all the satans...
You are traveling with Luca to beat all the demons.
I guess you two are too strong for my disciples.
Fine... I will personally invite you to
the world of desire and temptation.
Wh... what is going on?
I'm starting to lose my powers...
Luca! Look at that!
Look at all these parfaits!
Wow... Look I want to eat them all.
What are you talking about?
I don't see any parfaits anywhere... hm?
Hey, Alice?
Alice? Where did you go?
Welcome to the world of desire and temptation.
My dear Warrior.
Su... Succubus?
Wh... what?
I can't move my body.
Nooooo!
You are about to drown in pleasure.
Now, let yourself go, ok?
Let me go! Ah...
Mr. Warrior, your penis is getting so big.
Do you like it?
It's so hard...
Come on, you are a warrior for goodness sake!
No, I can't hold it any longer.
Already? You know we will suck your soul too...
Come in her mouth now!
Nooo!
Stop sucking on my penis please.
Shame on you, Mr. Warrior... you
let a Succubus suck your penis.
Ah, please stop... don't suck it anymore.
Mr. Warrior? Don't you want to feel the pleasure forever?
You want to keep having fun with us, don't you?
No... please stop.
You are inside of me now... I will dry your semen out.
Let me go!
Mr. Warrior, enjoy this till we take your soul.
Wow, it's so big.
Let me feel your penis more.
Ah, you're so tight.
No, don't move... you'll make me come.
Can you feel how tight my pussy is? Keep going...
I'm begging you to stop!
Ahh!
I'm starting to black out...
Luca... Luca!
Wake up, Luca.
E-Erubetie... you came to rescue me?
Help you? Maybe I did.
Thank goodness. Help me, I can't move my body.
Luca, you fought so much.
You need to relax.
What?
Stop thinking and give yourself to pleasure.
Luca, you got hard so fast.
Such a pity... making sounds like that.
That's it, you'll be mine soon.
No... Ahh...
What are you trying to stop... it's too late!
You love getting your penis sucked, don't you?
Stop, please don't suck any harder!
You're gonna make me come. No!
That's it. It's okay... you can come in my mouth.
We are going to swallow all your sperm... just let go.
I'm coming!
You'll drown in your pleasure forever... let's keep going.
Ah... no! Please don't put me in.
I'm still very sensitive.
I love Warrior penis. It feels so good!
Luca, can you taste my pussy?
Tell me how your penis feels in my pussy.
I can't do such a thing...
Your penis is fucking me so deep inside.
You're making me go crazy.
We aren't finished yet. I need more.
Forget everything and just think about coming inside.
No, I can't die yet.
Shut up and put your tongue inside my pussy.
Taste my pussy!
Yes, that's it.
Oh no... she's gonna take all of my sperm.
I don't wanna cum but my penis feels so good.
I can't take it anymore... I'm coming!
Come on, come inside my pussy!
I'm coming, I'm coming...
Ah, it's so much!
I can feel your semen coming in my uterus.
It's so much.
It's my turn to give you the pleasure now.
Look, you're still so hard.
This will be your last pleasure before you go to heaven.
Are you ready to go inside my pussy?
Ah you're so tight...
So tight... you are gonna make me come again.
Come on, this will be the last pleasure.
Don't you love it? I'm ready for you whenever.
I want all of it... every drop of your semen in my pussy!
I'm gonna come. I'm coming!
Wh... what?
It's my turn to enjoy you now.
A... Alma Elma! What are you doing here?
There's no need for us to fight anymore.
You said you'll help me build a peaceful world...
Humans and demons.
Alma Elma?
Luca, you already know...
that I only get naked when I'm serious!
No need to think about anything...
I'll take you to heaven with my boobs.
I came so hard... but my penis got so big already.
You don't need to hold it in.
This isn't right...
You are so big and hard already.
You can come on my boobs any time you're ready.
Sorry, but I can't hold it any longer.
Nooo!
Once isn't enough.
My boobs are gonna make you come so much more.
Stop... if you keep on going...
Give me more... I want your semen to cover my boobs.
The more you come, the more pleasure you'll get from me.
You haven't given up yet, huh?
Then I'm gonna fuck you hard.
I hope you know my pussy will take every drop of your semen.
Please stop it!
It's your fault for being stubborn.
Come fuck my pussy!
You came already? You didn't even last for a minute, Luca.
I'm not allowed to come anymore but my body won't stop...
Too bad, Luca. You should've listened to me from the beginning.
But you didn't and now you'll die.
Now, give me your semen... I want all of it.
Come on. Come inside my pussy!
Let's do one more... next time will be your last.
Once I take all your cum, you'll go to heaven.
Does that mean those Succubuses are your allies?
It doesn't matter anymore because you'll die soon.
Time to say good bye, Luca.
Thank you, Luca.
But I won't stop my attack till everything is finished.
Strange... Erubetie or Alma Elma would never do this to me.
Who's behind all of this?
I knew that warrior wouldn't give up too easily...
Hm... impressive that he hasnt' given up even with these girls.
Fine, I shall give him more pleasure...
til he dies from drowning in his own pleasure.
перевод Hentaisun
хард захентаился выдирать торрент иваниваныч...