ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Mother Knows Breast
Vol. 2
Fumi-nee, why did you return?
Can't you tell by what took place at the river?
Are you blind or something?
Sorry.
Hey.
Yes, what is it?
How is Shinobu?
Shinobu is doing fine.
You gotta be kidding me!
No, but that's...
I'll say it again. You're blind as a bat.
Let me tell you something.
She's acting odd intentionally or she's feeling very uneasy inside.
Well, I...
Shinobu, I bumped into Fumi-nee.
I think I'm gonna be home late.
Okay.
Here's your special. Octopus with hot radish sauce!
Take-chan...
Take-chan...Take-chan...
I know I shouldn't be the one saying this but...
Why can't you look at Shinobu as a girl?
I really don't know.
So that's the way you talk now.
But there's something I need to say.
Especially to you.
You don't have to tell me. I know what you're about to say.
Anyway, you want to come to my place?
I think I'm a little drunk. Take me to my room.
Are you sure?
Hey, you're thinking about something erotic.
No Takeshi.
Don't just play with my tits.
But it seemed like you wanted me to play with them.
You're so mean.
Then I'll play with this.
Don't touch that spot.
Your cunt is all sticky and wet.
No, don't say that.
It's amazing. You're all wet.
Your clit is hard too.
You're good Takeshi, I love it!
Your nipples are hard too.
Takeshi, stop saying that I'm getting hard.
I'm a girl you know.
Now what about here?
Stop.
I haven't been screwed there yet.
Don't play with it too much. Be gentle.
Takeshi.
It's amazing Takeshi.
It's such a waste to keep treating you like a brother.
Well, it seemed like you wanted me.
So I have to try my best to meet your demands.
Don't lick me like a dog.
It's embarrassing.
I'm embarrassed.
I have my legs spread open like a frog.
I'll pee. You're gonna make me pee!
Don't make such disgusting noises...
No Takeshi. Not there.
Not there.
But don't stop.
Please. Just keep on licking it.
More. Do it more.
Lick it in a dirty way.
Don't keep licking the same spot.
If you keep doing that, my clit will get bigger. I'm embarrassed.
I'm coming!
Here I come, Fumi-nee.
Do it, Takeshi.
It's amazing Takeshi.
If you thrust me that hard, I'll pee.
My pee will come shooting out.
No Takeshi. Don't...
No, stop looking at my ass.
It's embarrassing.
I'm coming!
You're finally mine Takeshi.
I'm not letting you go.
Now let's continue.
Okay, Takeshi?
You're rubbing my nipples.
Squeeze my tits too.
Let me see your face.
Don't be mean.
Just let me see your face.
No.
If you look at me, I'll pee in embarrassment.
You're usually very aggressive.
It's just that I like you so much it's embarrassing.
lt feels so hot down there...
I won't be able to hold it in.
I'll pee if you keep doing this.
It's okay Fumi. You can release it.
It feels that good right?
It's embarrassing if I release it right here.
I don't want to pee.
I feel like I'm gonna pee.
I can't hold it. I can't hold it.
I'm peeing!
I'm sorry Takeshi.
I peed all over. I'm sorry...
I know I've never been good to you, but I want you to only love me 'til you die.
Where am I?
Oh yeah, I went to Fumi-nee's place and she forced me to drink a lot.
I see, I see.
What the hell? Was that a dream?
What? This can't be!
You stupid slut.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
I'm gonna mess up your so-called life.
She's getting wet even though we're violating her.
You really enjoy this don't you?
Maybe it's her lecherous bloodline.
You're enjoying this too.
You stupid slut. Bringing home a new man, huh?
Let me get some action.
You slut.
How do you like that?
Does it feel good?
I'm coming!
Hey, how does my cock feel?
Suck it more.
Feels good right?
Looking good there.
No! Stop it!
Fumi-nee!
Fujino-san! Fumi-nee's condition is really bad.
Why can't you be there for her?
You're her real mother, right?
She may be my real daughter but if she can't accept me as her mother...
...I don't want to see her!
Hello? Fujino-san?
Fujino-san? Fujino-san?
It's no use.
Damn it!
What the hell?
Fumi-nee's condition is bad and she has to act like this?
Can't we start over as one happy family?
She doesn't care about me either.
Fumi-chan left the house all of a sudden...
Why is nobody paying any attention to me?
Why is that?
Tell me why.
But you won't leave me, right, Take-chan?
What is it that you want to talk to me about?
Shinobu feels you abandoned her.
And I feel that Fumi-nee left this house because of you.
Fujino-san, if you want to keep bossing us around...
Then I want you to leave this house immediately.
That's all I have to say.
What did you put in my mouth?
Oshino
You can't move right?
It's a special drug.
But your cock still works fine.
On top of that, you'll be a million times more sensitive.
Your stuff is the best. It's so thick and delicious.
Take a look Take-san.
Isn't mine better than Fumino's?
I won't let Shinobu have your cock.
Now here I come...
I'm lowering my hips.
Yes, it's great.
Your huge special cock is moving inside me.
I want you to move some more.
I can't help it.
More.
I want you to use your huge cock and stir me up inside.
I want you to thrust me harder.
Thrust me inside.
Look Take-san.
It's soft right?
My tits are soft like marshmallows right?
But it's actually packed with lots of meat, like a tasty beef steak.
My nipples are hard and tasty too.
I wanted you to taste them with your tongue.
I'm inviting you over for the night.
Now enjoy the food.
Make sure to lick everything.
It's getting good.
My body feels hotter.
Your cock makes me get tighter.
When I move like this, my crotch gets tighter.
My god, It won't stop.
I can't keep going like this, I'll climax.
I'll go crazy.
I can't take it.
My body is rubbing against yours.
It feels so good.
I think I'm losing my mind.
But I don't care.
I don't mind at all.
Your cock...
I feel like...
Hey Takeshi...
Release it inside me.
It feels so good.
It's coming inside. I can feel you coming inside me!
Fujino-san, please stop.
No. I'm going to keep enjoying this.
Drink it Take-san.
I'll give you some of my stuff.
That was a nice hot bath.
Let's keep going Take-san.
You're kidding. That drug should still be in effect.
Thanks for everything. - Takeshi
Why does it have to be like this?
I don't want this.
I don't want to lose any of the ones I love.
What did I do wrong?
I first married the wrong man, then I married the right man after that.
But I lost everything in an instant.
I tried looking for a new partner but it didn't work.
And then I found you, the one who had his bloodline.
You should've been my husband.
I mean, you're his son right?
You're his one and only son.
But why? Tell me, please...
I'm begging you.
Don't leave me.
Fujino-san, are you satisfied?
Thank you for everything you did for me.
I'm leaving this house.
It's too late to say this but, I should leave since I'm not your son.
Fujino-san, don't you think you should love your real daughter more than me?
Until we can live happily together as a family...
I won't be coming back to this house.
Take-chan...
What do you want to talk to me about?
Shinobu, I'm thinking of leaving this house.
Everything will work out fine.
Why do you say that?
You know you're the only one for me.
You promised me at the hospital.
I'm serious. If I have you, I don't need anyone else.
You were just confused, that's all.
No.
I knew you were doing it with my mother every night.
Do you know how hard it was for me?
But I can't take it anymore.
I really love you, Take-chan.
Shinobu, I understand.
But after I leave, you'll soon forget about all this.
I'm not as foolish as you might think, I'll show you.
Wow, it's so big.
Shinobu, just take it easy.
It's so hot.
Your stuff is pouring inside.
I think I'm gonna melt.
Are you okay, Shinobu?
I'm fine.
Sorry about that.
It's amazing. It feels like jello.
This is more that what I expected.
Even after you released your milk your cock is still rock hard.
Your cock is a ferocious monster.
Stop it, Take-chan.
It hurts.
It won't fit.
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts.
It hurts!
Stop it! It hurts!
It hurts.
No, it hurts!
It hurts. It hurts.
No, not there.
It's the wrong hole.
It hurts. It hurts.
It hurts.
Hey wait.
Take-chan, it hurts.
It hurts, it hurts.
No, it hurts. No!
I'm sorry Shinobu.
I tried to forget about Fumi-nee, Fujino-san, and everything...
...by tolerating it and acting like a grown-up.
But when I was doing it with you, something exploded inside me.
And I took it all out on your body .
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm fine.
I understand your feelings.
I cried because I was a bit surprised.
But I always wanted you to do me like this.
Plus my pussy is now ready to accept you.
So please let me be your wife.
I want you to release lots of your stuff inside me.
Are you okay Shinobu?
I always wanted you to do this, so it's nothing.
Does it feel good now?
That's because I was fingering myself before.
You can do it faster.
Do it as fast as you like.
You can thrust me harder, make me into a real woman.
It's starting to feel good.
It feels good, Take-chan.
I love your cock.
I'm gonna release it.
Release it inside me, Take-chan.
I love you Take-chan.
One year later
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Welcome back Take-chan.
Takeshi, welcome home.
Welcome back Fumi-nee.
The four of us are living happily together as a family.
Family members need each other!