ENCODED BY KHMER|YIN
#KHMER@IRC.RIZON.NET
Mother Knows Breast
Vol. 1
Shinobu.
You're here again?
Why is Shinobu always like that?
Are you okay, Shinobu?
Yeah, I'm ok.
I don't need you to help me, I'm really fine...
Hey, give me your hand.
Use this.
Thanks.
I'm a nice guy, you know.
Let's get on the swing or do you want to play on the slide?
You wanna play by taking turns?
Climbing the pole is fun too.
You're a meanie.
Teasing your sister who got all dirty.
I'll give you a hand. Come on.
Alright then, I'll forgive you.
But now I don't owe you any favors.
Shinobu...
We'll be home soon, so can I keep holding your hand?
The things she says surprise me at times.
Oshino
Man, that stings!
Take-chan, where's the bandaid?
Go take a bath.
l'll get a bandaid.
Okay.
Why won't Take-chan understand me?
Shinobu, go sleep in your own bed.
Don't worry.
I'll stay up until mother gets home...
Welcome home Fujino-san.
When will you start calling me mother?
You can call me mama if you want.
I'm just kidding.
Anyway, where's Shinobu?
She just went to sleep.
She said she'll stay up until you get home but...
I see.
Now hurry up and take yours off.
Fujino-san, let's not do this anymore.
Don't worry about it.
Let's just do this while Shinobu is sleeping.
Don't get hard. Don't get big.
I got it, I'll think of something disgusting.
Corpse of a frog, decomposed body of an elephant...
It's not working.
It got bigger.
I don't want to sleep with you.
Shit, it just gets hard on its own.
I can't help it.
Fujino-san, please stop this.
Stop what?
Stop toying with my body.
It's okay, we live together, after all.
Come on, release your stuff.
I'm coming.
Delicious.
It's so fresh.
It's still hard? You're a ferocious monster.
But you might be a bit hyper.
My cock isn't a sign of braveness, it's a symbol of shame!
Delicious.
This is just...
Great.
I want to see you enjoying this.
It's good, it's good.
Your cock is getting so big.
You're coming?
Give it to me.
I'm coming too.
It's coming.
I'm coming!
How much longer do I have to do this?
Should I become a eunuch or get castrated?
Mother's mean.
Don't you think she should at least be up when we go to school?
I don't know. I guess she's tired.
Besides, you're way too old for that.
Try to understand that she can't always be there for you.
Yeah, but...
Shinobu still doesn't know.
Your mother and I are screwing each other. We're scumbags.
It would be best if Shinobu never finds out about this.
But I don't really care about that today.
Do you know why?
I don't know.
You have to think a bit harder, okay?
You're in love?
They say if you're in love, you can see the world in a different way.
What are you saying?
I can't believe you said that.
I'll tell you since you're so stupid.
Hey, stop looking at my cell phone!
I'm coming back! - Fumino
She really hated Fujino-san.
Why does Fumi-nee hate her real mother?
Oh, I get it now.
Do you wanna release it?
I can keep going.
Then hang in there.
You're hanging in there pretty well.
You're doing too much.
Then should we climax together?
Not yet.
You can't do me with a shriveled up cock.
I'll make it rock hard so you can drive a nail with it.
It's getting hard.
Your cock is bulging out of my tits.
Now I'll suck on your balls.
Release your stuff.
Release plenty of it.
Your stuff smells very masculine. It makes me wild.
Yes, that's it. Do it harder.
Yes, there.
Bang, bang, bang.
Bang me.
Yes.
Yes, more.
More, more.
Bang me.
Bang me so that my pubic hair wears out.
Yes. That's it.
That's it...
I'm coming.
Yes, release it.
Give it to me.
Release that milk from your cock.
Aren't you happy that Fumi-chan is coming back?
Of course I'm happy.
You look very confused, so...
Sorry, you go home without me.
I forgot to do something.
What are you gonna do about dinner?
I'm coming back! - Fumino
This is bad.
This is definitely bad.
The reason Fumi-nee left is because she hates Fujino-san.
And the reason for her leaving is what happened that day in summer.
Even if she does come back, things aren't gonna work out.
Besides, Fujino-san has gotten more sexually active since she left.
But what's more troubling is...
The fact that Fujino-san and I are screwing each other.
If she finds out about us, it'll be terrible.
Why does she use me to have sex?
Could it be...
It looks like Fujino-san isn't having much sex these days...
Shinobu has been accepted to a new school...
I hope Fumi-nee can come back.
Who's there?
It's me.
Fujino-san, please stop.
Oh come on, I'll be nice and teach you a lot of things.
It'll be fun.
I see that a virgin climaxes quickly.
Plus it's thick like jello.
You're still rock hard.
I think I can enjoy some more.
I should've said no at that point.
Yeah, I should have.
Both Shinobu and I are gonna leave that house someday.
Even though Fujino-san's a nymphomaniac...
...I should've just refused to do it with her...
But if we keep going like this, things will get worse.
I'm sure of it.
This is where you stick it in.
Hurry up and do it.
Stick it deep inside.
That's right. Shove it in there at once.
Don't be scared.
I won't bite.
It's inside me! It's coming inside!
Your cock is inside me.
I don't have to tell you what to do from here on, right?
Yes, that's it.
In and out.
Keep it consistent.
More.
Do me harder.
I want you to mess me up.
There. Yes, yes.
Bang that area.
You're good.
Don't pull it out.
Your cock felt good.
Don't pull your cock out.
I liked it nice and slow but stick it in all at once this time.
Yes. Your cock feels good.
Yes.
Feels good. Amazing.
Feels good.
Yes.
Take-san.
Take-chan, you're in there for so long.
Hurry up and get out.
Just answer her like you normally do.
I'll be out as soon as I can.
Fine. Try to make it quick.
I know we're in an awkward situation but let's just stop.
This is some kind of a mistake right?
You're right.
It seems that the cock inside me has become a bit soft.
Fujino-san!
I was just kidding.
Now let's continue.
See? Your cock is hard again.
Yes.
It's deep inside my uterus.
Your cock is getting harder.
You recover faster since you're young.
Wonderful.
What? Are you going to climax?
Then we'll climax together.
Watch my face as I climax.
I'm coming!
I can't believe I was in love with a man like you.
What's that?
A lovers' quarrel, huh?
How nice.
Compared to them I'm...
Let me do you one last time.
Stop it.
Hey, wait a minute.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Takeshi!
Fumi-nee?