Wh-What is this? Why am I here?
Amano-san.
Sugiuchi-Kun!
So many...
So many so suddenly!
I guess that can't be helped...
You can use my body as much as you want!
You can't slide it around like that!
Hurry and put it inside!
Sugiuchi-kun's cock is inside!
Even though he's just putting it in I'm cumming!
So... good... rub it... more...
Yes...
Sugiuchi-kun's penis... so many...
Yes... penis feels good...
Sugiuchi-kun's penis... it's tasty...
Make my whole body sticky and
wet with Sugiuchi-kun's sperm!
Oh, did you wake up?
I tried modifying your dreams a little, was it good?
I wish the test tomorrow will be cancelled because
of a mysterious fire of unknown cause.
And, that the P.E. the teacher would get into some
kind of accident so there would be no class.
And also that all the people who aren't
geeks or otaku would perish.
And... that I'd look more attractive in general...
Especially my chest and stuff...
What?
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
I just can't stand not getting between them!
Phew, a dream...
Huh? My chest is heavy...
What is this? Could it be that my wish came true?
But... wasn't that a dream?
I apologize in advance. Sorry.
I'm Hailey, from Planet Hakurei.
I'm what you guys would call an "alien".
To be honest, I had a collision with you yesterday.
During which, the body of you, Amano
Inori, was greatly damaged,
and your life activity had once stopped.
Huh?
In other words, you died.
I died!?
Don't worry. With our technology, I
repaired your body and revived you.
Wait, what do you mean? What's going on?
What are you trying to do to make me do?
Become a hero and protect Earth or something?
No, I don't mean that.
I think I've revived you properly, but since it's
my first time repairing life on this planet.
Please let me follow up on your
body for a while just in case.
Woah! It's already this late, and I have school!
What was that?
I was taking off my pajamas and it echoed in my body...
Well, since it was just recently regenerated,
your sensation of touch is probably very sensitive.
Geez, I can't get my bra on...
It's like an electric shock inside...
It seems like I've made a little mistake on the size,
I'm sorry.
Good morning!
Hey, who's that?
Huh? Amano-san?
Amano is that girl, right?
She's always looming darkly in
the corner of the classroom.
Did she get plastic surgery!?
So... So easy! I can solve these...
Here I go!
I can jump!
Amazing!
It’s so soft and slippery!
My skin is nice and shiny, school feels
easier, and I can do sports, too!
Victory! I've just won at life!
Could it be all thanks to being revived?
Thank you, something-san from Planet Something!
I'm Hailey from Planet Hakurei.
I tried regenerating you according
to your original existence,
could it be that it was different from who you were?
Is there some way to fix this sizzling?
Well, I guess it’s okay since I can still bear it...
Don't worry, you'll get used to it after a while.
By the way, why did Mr. Alien become a comet?
Could it be that It’s your hobby?
No, err, I slipped and fell off my ship...
Haha, what's with that?
Su-su-su-sugiuchi-kun!?
Oh, Amano-san.
Who is this?
The only guy who would talk to me normally in class...
I see...
Amano-san, you somehow look quite
different from usual today.
Like, more bright and cheerful than usual...
Or like... shining... or something...
You really think so?
Hmm, your heart rate has increased and
you're secreting a lot of E.R.O. hormones.
Could this be that? What they call, going into rut?
Ru-rut?
Rut?
This is perfect.
Wait, what are you...
I came to research the life forms of this start.
Stop...
You can't Sugiuchi-kun is here...
My nipples...
Wait, Amano-san, what are you doing!?
No... This isn't me...
My hands... on their own...
You can't... move around so much...
I’m being watched by Sugiuchi-kun...
I'm really embarrassed... but it's still getting... so...
You guys perform sexual intercourse between
male and female to reproduce, right?
It's a mechanism that we can't understand.
It’s extremely intriguing.
Please allow me to observe the reproductive activity of life on this planet.
You can't do it somewhere like this!
Someone will come!
Oh I see! Then let's go somewhere
nearby where not many are around.
Ow... Huh? Why am I in the girl's washroom?
Amano-san's wet?
Sugiuchi-kun's pants are bulging!
So the reproductive organ of the male is hidden here.
A-Amano-san, what are you...
Uh... um... this isn't actually me...
Hmm, this is much larger than what
I read from previous data.
Sugiuchi-kun's penis is amazing...
I think data collected from so called AV's
showed doing something like-this...
Wait...
Amano-san, what's wrong?
But, your mouth isn't a reproductive organ, right?
What is the purpose of this action?
Sugiuchi-kun’s penis... it's getting larger
and larger inside my mouth...
He can get this hard from being inside me!
Sugiuchi-kun... and I...
Sugiuchi-kun's penis... it's so big and hard!
Amano-san... if you do it so much...
Then... me, too...
Don't...Sugiuchi-kun... if you
tease my pussy that much...
Sugiuchi-kun's... penis... it's rock hard...
It's like It'll explode...
I’ll make you feel really good, okay?
Amano-san...
Amano-san's boobs... so soft...
Amano-san?
Does this feel good?
Wow! Something is flowing out!
Don't, that's too much, Amano-san!
Sugiuchi-kun's penis is wet.
Amano-san... if you rub it so much like that...
I said I'd make you feel good, right?
B-But if you do it that much... I’ll cum!
Not yet.
I'm trapping Sugiuchi-kun's penis inside my boobs...
Your penis is hot and twitching...
Wait... if you do that, I'll cum from the
pressure of the boobs squeezing!
Does it feel good?
More and more wet stuff is coming
out of Sugiuchi-kun's penis...
It's good...
Amano-san, I’m cumming!
Amazing! Sugiuchi-kun, so much...
Sugiuchi-kun's penis... it's tasty!
Amazing...
My mouth is so full with Sugiuchi-kun!
Does this... feel good?
My tip is hitting Amano-san's throat...
Wow... his penis is going crazy inside my mouth...
Amano-san...
Sugiuchi-kun, feels really good from the tip, right?
My whole body is sensitive... so even just his hot penis
rubbing between my boobs is turning me on!
I can't... hold back anymore!
Amano-san, I’m cumming...
It's fine, don't hold back...
Spray lots on me!
Amano-san!
Amano-san, I'm so sorry!
Sugiuchi-kun's... penis.. semen... tastes good...
Amano-san, what are you...
Hey, Sugiuchi-kun... this time...
Feel good from here, okay?
Amano-san, that's...
But Sugiuchi-kun's penis... is already so hard and erect...
It looks like it feels really painful...
I'll help you immediately, alright?
I'm scared that it’s my first time...
But with this body I can make him feel really good...
Your penis... is twitching...
It's my first time, but... it hurts, but... it feels good!
Amano... san...
Sugiuchi-kun!
Sugiuchi-kun's penis... feels really good!
Sugiuchi-kun! Sugiuchi-kun!
Just touching Sugiuchi-kun is making
my whole body aroused!
Hey, look... my nipples are this hard, too...
it's all...Sugiuchi-kun's fault...
Your penis... feels good!
Sugiuchi-kun's... big... and hard... penis...
It feels good...
Ama... no...-san...
Amazing...
So good...
This position... wow...
Your penis is going... all the way inside...
My pussy can’t stop squeezing...
Inori's new pussy... is getting Sugiuchi-kurn's
penis shoved inside...
My clitoris...
Amano-san... I can see... where we’re connect...
No... don't say that...
Just touching is already making me...
You’re hitting my womb so hard...
it feels so good I could go crazy...
I feel really good, too... Amano-san...
Sugiuchi-kun...
Here I go, Amano-san...
Sugiuchi-kun! More, thrust more!
Amazing... even more than before...
you're going deep inside...
It feels so good... thrust your penis more...
It's even bigger... than before...
Sugiuchi-kun's penis is rubbing inside...
You can't be so rough...
I'll lose myself!
Don't touch my nipples...
Amano-san's pussy is squeezing tight...
No... when Sugiuchi-kun touches...
my boobs and my nipples...
My pussy, too... it feels too good!
Amano-san's pussy... is really wet... and hot...
My pussy... inside my pussy... Sugiuchi-kun
is thrusting so wildly...
I... it's my first time... but I’m going to cum!
Amano-san... I can't...
It's fine, let it out!
Let out lots of Sugiuchi-kun's semen
inside! Make me pregnant!
My womb is cumming from semen!
Semen is flowing inside my pussy...
I'm so sorry, Amano-san! I got too full of myself and...
What, what do we do!? What if you get a baby!?
I'm sorry! Apologizing won't do any good, but sorry!
Hmm, so a baby means the next generation.
When will it form?
Shut up!
Sorry, I'm really sorry!
That's not it! I wasn't talking about Sugiuchi-kun...
But, if you take responsibility and date
me some other time, I'll forgive you.
Huh?
it seems like the female is the superior sex on this planet.