www.SubDESU-H.net
Honestly...
That raccoon brat and her gang are late.
Their job was simply to exterminate a few youkai  in that abandoned school.
Just how long has it been already?
They haven't even made a single call.
It's all because of that animal's obliviousness to modern society.
Sorry about that.
Hurry up and get back already.
You idiot raccoon...
Mouryou's Sacrifice
Person #2
Suzuna and Reika's BAD END Impregnation Hell
Wait, Hayato-kun!
Hayato-kun!
Suzuna.
Hayato-kun?
Suzuna...
This place is...
Hayato-kun?
Ouch!
Could this be...
No way...
Why?
Suzushiro?
Where are you Suzushiro?
Where are you?
Please come out!
What in the world happened?
Did I just lose my virginity?
Hayato-kun
Hayato-kun...
Hayato-kun!
Suzuna.
Hayato-kun
Suzuna...
Suzuna!
Stop!
No, don't do something that perverted.
You bear the smell of a man.
So you've become a bitch, Suzuna.
So even if I do it with you, you wouldn't care at all.
No...!
I just kissed Hayato-kun.
My first kiss was with Hayato-kun...
Suzuna.
You taste good despite being a bitch.
Let me taste you more.
So these are Suzuna's breasts...
They're small, but tender.
No...
Not here...
Being forced...
Oh? You don't want to have sex with me?
That, shouldn't be done... until after we're married...
Getting your nipples stiff like this...
You're aroused, right?
No, I'm not...
There's no need to be shy, right?
This is between you and me.
But, we're still just...
We're still just friends...
We're not anymore.
We can't do this, Hayato-kun!
Now, this is where the real thing begins.
Anything but that...!
I'll let you do anything but that!
It's a lovely pussy, even though it's no longer a virgin one.
No... please don't look!
No...
If you do it that intensely, it will come out...
Don't look!
Peeing like that at your age, eh?
I'm sorry...
I won't get angry just because of that.
Suzuna.
Well then, why don't we become one already?
Is that what you intend to do?
You've already done it with another guy and yet you don't want to do it with me?
That's not it.
I really don't know anything about that!
I haven't had sex with anyone before!
It hurts, stop!
So it still hurts after it was just opened.
It hurts! It hurts!
Pull it out!
I see.
So you want me to pull it out, then push it back in, eh?
No...!
Your inside is warm and wet.
It hurts...
Don't move inside me.
Don't stir my insides with your cock.
I'm going to die! I'm dying!
It's going to break!
Your pussy feels so good that I feel like cumming inside.
No way, you're going to release it inside...
Stop, no...!
If you cum inside, I'll get pregnant!
I definitely don't want that!
I'm cumming now, Suzuna.
No, you really came inside...
I'm not married, and yet I'm going to be pregnant...
Bear my children, Suzuna.
I'm going to rape you non-stop, to ensure that you become pregnant.
I'll transform your body into a motherly vessel.
Now it's time to inject my seed into you.
This tightness, it's superb.
I guess this is what the humans call, a top class tool.
Well then, next up...
How does it feel to be able to do a titty fuck?
No, no...!
Oh, it seems like it's time to cum already.
I'm also impregnating your butthole.
Suzuna.
Suzuna!
Hayato-kun...
Suzuna...
There are a lot of Hayato-kuns...
There, that's good Suzuna.
Your butt and pussy are both the best.
I'd also like to try a nipple fuck.
I'm going here.
And I'm going here.
Suzuna...
This is the best.
This feels great Suzuna.
You're the best Suzuna.
Why...?
I'm going to cum...
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
www.SubDESU-H.net
For a low level youkai  like her to make a high level demon like me wait...
How impertinent.
I wonder what I should do to her after she returns.
It wasn't like I was waiting for you all to come back.
That's right, I just had something I needed to do.
Oh, what about the brat raccoon and the others?
This is, a youma field!
Just what are you...
I can't believe I lowered my guard like this.
This hurts you know, let me go!
You've got some energy there.
Though, it seems that your spiritual energy is also equally strong.
Ouch, that hurts!
Stop this!
My thighs...
My thighs are going to break!
So this lady has also taken a leak.
I'm really excited.
Stop that, you perverted youma!
So your part down here is also stinky despite you being a fine lady.
These have grown quite well.
It also feels good to touch.
Stop this.
My breasts are not meant to be touched by the likes of a youma.
This humiliation...
No one even has....
Stop fondling it!
I'm going to give you pleasure that's not even imaginable for a lowly human.
Pleasure...
and pain!
Ouch!
What are you injecting in me?
Stop!
No... my beautiful breasts, are swelling horribly.
I'm going to transform your insides into something more fitting of me.
I don't want that...! Somebody please help!!
Your screams are futile.
No one's coming to help you.
Don't tell me... Kodanuki and the others...
Curse the fact that you decided to side with the humans.
No, not there!
The only ones that can see my pussy are the ones who are at my level...
It hurts!
I'm sensitive down there!
So do it more gently.
Doesn't it feel better when it's done violently?
Don't say such foolish things!
It hurts!
Stop!
That part's going to get numb and wear out.
As expected of a demon class I guess.
But, how about I pierce through your virginity veil,
would it heal that quickly then?
Are you planning to...
...drive that inside me...?
Stop!
My purity is my treasure as a member of my family.
It's something that is only mine...
It hurts.
Pull out that filthy thing immediately!
It's still not too late.
It's already too late!
It hurts.
It really hurts!
Pull it out, right now!
What a spoiled lady we have here.
If you think everything will always go your way,
then you're absolutely wrong!
No...
My breasts...
My breasts are going to fall off!
Why don't we see if they're really going to fall off?
It's cumming inside...
It hurts!
My butt will break!
It's a precious body meant for giving birth.
It won't break as long as I can still use it.
It's really wrapping me tight.
Are you letting it constrict like this because it's painful?
Even if you try to bear with it,
it will only become tighter,
and will only serve to make me feel better.
No...!
I'm going to open up this one too!
Now, I'm going to rape your bladder too and impregnate it as well.
No, stop that!
That can't fit into where I pee from.
It's impossible.
Let me be already!
How unsightly for someone who used to have the air of a fine lady!
Serves you right!
Get pregnant...
www.SubDESU-H.net
My babies...