www.SubDESU-H.net
If I could just find a specific weakness...
This happened several centuries ago.
A catastrophe befell upon the world, that was chosen to be struck off from the records of history.
A calamity that was brought about by just one monster.
Armed with wickedly great powers, this terrible monster
wrecked havoc upon villages and towns
and devoured every living being in it's path.
The only things that it left behind
were violent chaos and massacres.
Be it humans or beasts...
... even other monsters like ghosts and specters weren't spared.
They were all indiscriminately devoured by it
as if it was trying to consume the entire world.
Only corpses laid in the wake of its destruction.
If it wasn't destroyed soon enough, it would devour everything into nothingness.
The specters, ghosts and humans
who had been keeping their distance from each other,
allied, and combined their strengths.
They sought to bury the monster.
However, the monster was overwhelmingly powerful.
90% of the entire frontline attack force was obliterated.
Finally...
After a long struggle, the alliance was able to seal the monster.
Centuries passed after that incident.
Mankind walks in the light,
while the specters and the ghosts tread the dark.
They aimed to coexist,
and hence established an agreement
to guard the seal of that monster.
However,
that monster vowed to regain its powers,
and even now it secretly attempts to resurrect itself.
The name of that abominable monster is
Mouryou.
Mouryou's Sacrifice
Person #1
Bad Ending Impregnation Hell: Chihiro and Suzushiro
Hayato,
do it quickly.
Just a little more.
I need a little more time to max out my spiritual energy.
Okay, done!
No fair, Chihiro!
It's all because you're so slow!
This is my childhood friend, Kasugai Chihiro.
She's a monster that allied herself with humans.
Even though she's descended from spirit raccoons,
she can't use her demonic power and only acts as a flesh cannon.
Hayato,
you again weren't able to finish the job.
You're really useless.
It's okay!
I'll protect you.
I'll be retiring for now.
I need to save my spiritual energy.
Getting tired, Suzuna?
Your face is too close!
Your face is too close, Hayato-kun!
Wakatsuki Suzuna is human,
but she was possessed by a holy higher being called Suzushiro.
Hence, she is able to use spiritual energy.
Or should I say,
it's Suzushiro that fights in battle.
I'm totally fine, Hayato-kun.
Don't push yourself.
Okay!
Hayato-kun's warmth...
Just a bit more like this...
And I'm Kobayakawa Hayato.
I'm the descendant of a ghost
but except for a bit more strength, longevity,
and demonic energy of a ghost...
I'm no different from a regular human being.
It's almost a waste.
Hayato,
I'm hungry.
You just ate my rice balls earlier, didn't you?
But that wasn't enough!
Hayato,
please give me more!
No.
We won't have enough dinner for everyone.
Hayato, you cheapskate!
Chihiro-chan,
if it's good enough, you can eat this.
Wow, candies!
I love candies!
It's delicious!
You shouldn't chew them!
While three of us are students,
we are also employed at a company run by ghosts
that specializes in exterminating other monsters who break
the antebellum non-aggression pact.
There are monsters still who try to hurt and kill humans.
We, who are still inexperienced exterminators,
also take guidance from our seniors
while carrying out our work.
When will you stop playing around?
Come on, if we don't clean up this mess soon,
dawn will be upon on us.
Okay, then.
Hey, you two.
We'll investigate the third floor next.
Just wait up!
I feel like peeing.
You can't do that, Chihiro-chan!
You can't just pee in front of a guy!
Then do it in the toilet!
That's too bothersome.
This is not the mountains where we live.
You must follow human rules.
Fine, fine.
We'll be going ahead then.
Just catch up with us later.
Okay!
Toilet, toilet.
Huh?
No toilet paper...
How inconvenient.
If this were the mountains,
there'd be leaves to use everywhere.
M-Monster?!
No...!
Don't...!
Let me go!
You...!
Full power!!
Easy, easy!
Break apart, you gross thing!
I'm all slimy.
I don't want this...
You're persistent...!
Oh, no!
Let me go!
Pervert...
Why?
I can't break through even at full power.
Stop!
It tickles.
No...
Don't tease my breasts!
I-It hurts!
What's this?
Something's entering my breasts.
Stop!
No...!
What?
Not there...!
It's getting tingly there.
Wh-What's this?
What happened to my breasts?
Don't!
Don't fondle them strongly like that!
Save me, Hayato!
Save me!
If you don't,
my breasts will break!
I'm cumming!
This intense fondling of my breasts
is making me cum!
What?
Don't...
Anything but that!
Hayato, save me!
It won't fit.
It won't fit in!
It hurts!
You can't...!
No!!
It hurts.
It hurts...
Pull it out!
It hurts.
Don't move!
Please stop this!
I'll break.
I'll break!
Hayato...
Hayato!
The tentacle
is hitting me so deep inside!
It hurts!
Please, don't do it so intensely!
And it's even my first time!
Save me!
Don't stir up my insides!
My pussy can no longer stretch like that!
It hurts.
My belly's about to burst!
I'm going to get pregnant!
It's coming out...
Something hot is coming out...
Something hot is filling me...
Pull it out!
It can't go in further...
My womb is going to break!
What?
Something weird is entering my pussy...!
My insides are going to burst!
There's something also entering my butt!
Don't put it in anymore!
It will break!
So a low leveler can be simply squeezed in like that.
But in terms of quality, your body is good.
You can do anything with her now.
Impregnate her to your heart's content.
Rape her hole by hole.
Release cum into her until it overflows.
What are they doing?
No, save me!
Hayato!
Suzuna!
Save me quickly!
If they don't...
I'll...
... go crazy!
Even though it hurts and I don't like it,
it still feels good.
This hot thing's being poured into me.
My breasts are being played with till they hurt,
and my womb's even getting mixed up.
Every time they pour it into me,
I lose it.
Save me...
No more!
Don't put it in!
My head's going blank again,
as it's getting poured in.
I'm going blank!
Lots of it is coming out!
Hayato, save me!
I'll be your wife...
I'll be a good girl...
I don't want it,
and it feels gross...
More...
So save me...!
Stop that!
You monster!
Oops, so you don’t care what happens to him, eh?
How careless of me...
I underestimated it and lowered my guard.
Suzushiro, look out!
Hayato!
What are you doing?!
How shameless!
If you stay still,
it won't hurt and your end will be quick.
It will even feel good.
This is bad.
My energy is being sucked out.
If this continues...
Even if it's just possessing a human, the spiritual energy of a holy beast is still quite different.
If I give this to Mouryou,
its resurrection will be hastened.
Mouryou, you say?!
Are you out of your mind?
If you resurrect that thing,
another age of chaos and massacre would begin!
That's our real body.
Don't touch me with your filthy tentacles!
That's Suzuna's important part!
That's good.
Fall into further despair!
Struggle and suffer all the more!
That's good.
This is a wonderful spiritual energy
that's mixed with wisdom and pain.
Let me suck more of it!
It's painful!
Being raped in the mouth by a a disgusting monsters...
This is humiliating!
If this continues, I'll suffocate!
For me, a god of dawn,
to be defiled
by this lowly pawn of a monster...
Damn, where's the real body?
Even if I kill its double,
it'll probably just resurrect again.
You will stop this!
Suzuna's breasts will break!
Now, we're going for the main course.
Stop!
You will not hurt Suzuna's body any further!
No...
No, stop that!
This is still an untainted girl's body.
Stop!
I'm sorry, Suzuna.
I wasn't able to
protect your purity.
The fact that I'm possessing her
while her consciousness is asleep,
may be her only solace.
For me to have her experience her first time like this...
I won't forgive this, Suzuna.
If you thrust it in so intensely,
even if it's just my first time,
I'll break!
It's going to rip apart!
Oh, no!
If my consciousness gets interrupted, and I lose my control over her body,
Suzuna won't be able to bear this pain!
How is it?
Sex with a monster sure feels different, doesn't it?
You...
I definitely
won't forgive you...
I won't forgive you...
Still not enough?
Then how about this?
If I bear this...
If I at least protect Suzuna's soul...
I'm about to cum!
Damn you!
If you do that, I'll...
That's exactly why I'm raping you.
In order to impregnate you with a healthy child...
What are you saying?
Why do you think I'm raping and keeping you alive?
You'll become the nursery of Mouryou's food!
You'll be a nursery that will give birth to tens, hundreds of fresh little monsters!
Stop!
A monster's seed is being poured
into Suzuna's womb...
Even if you're a god,
if you can't use spiritual energy,
you're just a breeding female.
Are you satisfied now?
Then release Hayato now!
What are you saying?
This one will serve as a sacrifice for Mouryou.
We have no use for males who can't be impregnated.
You bastard...
You're going to break your word?
What's that?
Stop...
Not any further...
There's no way a human female can stay sane
after taking the semen of a monster.
You...
No way...
The tentacle is entering the womb.
Please stop...
If you hurt the womb,
it won't be able to bear children.
If it's a monster child, it can grow healthily in there, so no problem.
Stop!
You can't do that!
Now,
give in to the pleasure.
Become a nursery for fresh food...
Stop!
Don’t hurt Suzuna any further!
I'll make sure you feel it up to your womb.
If the womb gets direct ejaculation,
it will definitely be impregnated.
She will be pregnant with a monster's child.
Oh, no!
My spiritual energy is running out.
I'm about to turn back into Suzuna.
www.SubDESU-H.net
The next sacrifice...
Yakushiji Reika