What about that house?
lt's going according to plan.
That house and wealth
will become ours.
We received a report from our collaborator.
l see.
THE AKASHlRO FAMlLY... A FAMlLY DlSTANTLY RELATED TO ROYALTY
THEY OWN STEEL MlLLS, SHlPYARDS, AND A WlDE RANGE OF BUSlNESSES.
THOUGH NOT AS MUCH AS lN THE PAST,
THEY STlLL HAVE VAST WEALTH AND THlS HOUSE.
THERE ARE SlX PEOPLE lN THlS HOUSEHOLD.
HEAD OF HOUSEHOLD SHlGEYUKl TAKASHlRO
l beg you to be patient.
l promise to return the money l borrowed.
Just a little longer.
WlFE AZUSA
ELDEST SON YUSHlRO
ELDEST DAUGHTER NANAKO
THE MAlD RURlKO MATSUSHlMA
Yushiro-sama.
THE BUTLER KOlCHlRO KlRlYAMA
l AM ONE OF THESE PERSONS.
BUT FOR PERSONAL REASONS, l CONSPlRE WlTH YOU.
l DON'T lNTEND TO REVEAL MY lDENTlTY.
CONTACTS WlLL BE FROM ME TO YOU.
lT lS A PRECAUTlON AGAlNST YOUR BETRAYAL.
l WlLL MAKE MY DEMANDS LATER.
NANAKO HAS A BEAUTlFUL FACE AND BODY.
A GlRL WlTH A GENTLE PERSONALlTY.
BUT SHE HAS BEEN SlCKLY SlNCE BlRTH AND lS AN lNNOCENT YOUNG WOMAN
WHO RARELY HAS CONTACT WlTH PEOPLE OUTSlDE HER HOME.
SHlGEYUKl HAS NO MANAGERlAL SKlLLS.
HE lS A GlVlNG PERSON WELL LlKED BY MANY.
BUT THE REASON FOR THE FAlLURE OF THE AKASHl FAMlLY lS HlS lNCOMPETENCE.
THE EXTENT TO WHlCH THE FAMlLY lS STlLL STANDlNG
lS OWED TO THE STRENGTH OF YUSHlRO.
ORlGlNALLY, HE WAS THE SON OF A SERVANT.
HE WAS ADOPTED UPON THE DEATH OF HlS PARENTS.
HE lS NOW SHlGEYUKl'S RlGHT HAND MAN AND EXERClSES GREATER ABlLlTlES.
YUSHlRO WANTS TO FULFlLL HlS OBLlGATlONS TO HlS ADOPTlVE PARENTS.
TO DRlVE THlS FAMlLY TO RUlN,
THE MOST EXPEDlTlOUS WAY lS TO ENTRAP THE SON.
AS SUCH, l WlLL OBSERVE HlM UNTlL l FlND HlS WEAKNESS
WlTH WHlCH HE WlLL BE ENTRAPPED.
SlNCE MY LAST REPORT, l HAVE CONTlNUED TO OBSERVE, BUT THERE ARE NO RESULTS.
l WlLL PROCEED WlTH TODAY'S OBSERVATlONS.
Nanako.
Get better, Nanako!
Nanako!
Nii... Nii-sama.
Nii-sama. Nii-sama.
You seem better.
The doctor left this new medicine.
Take it from tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Nanako...
Nanako!
Am l going to die like this?
l'm scared. l'm scared, scared, scared!
You're not alone.
l'm with you.
l'll always be with you.
Nii-sama!
Nanako.
Nii-sama.
Nii-sama!
What's wrong?
ls it pity?
What?
ls it because of my health? l could die anytime.
ls that why?
Don't be stupid.
Nii-sama.
Nanako?
lt's nothing.
lt's just my imagination.
Huh?
Yushiro-san... you... you...
When mother found out,
Nii-sama was sent off to a school in England.
Mother and father both said he can come back
as soon as he cools his head.
Nii-sama.
lT'S OVER. lT'S ALL OVER.
THE REST lS TO WAlT FOR THE RlGHT TlME. WAlT FOR THE RlGHT TlME...
Nii-sama, how do l tell you what happened after you left?
Father's business didn't do well.
The company is near bankruptcy.
Mother has become catatonic and is reduced to just bringing me my medicine.
How long will this family last?
When will l see you again?
l don't know.
But l will always wait for you.
Until you return, l will always... always...
Then one day...
Who are you?
l surprised you. Excuse me.
l am a messenger for a past associate of your father.
l came with an offer on my boss' orders, but l was denied.
And what can l do for you?
The offer concerns none other than you.
Specifically, l came to make you the offer.
l asked your father for an audience, but...
What is this offer you speak of?
lt concerns how you feel, and how that can save this family.
What will you do?
l will come at the same time tomorrow to pick you up.
Until then, please take your time and think about it.
We'll meet again.
An offer where l can save the family.
l shouldn't. lt's too good to be true.
But...
lNSlDE A GOVERNMENT BUlLDlNG SOMEWHERE lN TOKYO
Thank you for coming.
Nanako-san.
l heard we can make a deal.
Correct.
Depending on your actions, the house and your father's business can be saved.
And what is involved?
You know, don't you?
For five days from today, we do whatever we want to you.
Those are the terms.
Preposterous. l never imagined such terms.
''Never imagined''?
lsn't that false?
You had a premonition, but you still came.
lsn't that true?
Consummate this deal.
lt will start soon.
Please rest for a while since you are going to take on many people.
l will see you again.
Why? Why am l in a place like this?
Even though l knew this was going to happen.
lt's because l spoke to you.
Don't you need to protect the house that Nii-sama will return to?
That's what l said to you.
Who's that? Who's there?
What are you so surprised about?
Nanako, it's me.
Did you forget?
We're always together. The two of us makes one.
Huh?
The first time you called out to me was over ten years ago.
You were alone and shaking in bed.
You were crying out, ''l'm lonely, l'm lonely''.
That's why l came to be your friend.
Nanako?
Yes.
Nanako. The same name as you.
Your friend.
Lies. All lies.
Nanako was my imagination. But you're...
You didn't realize.
But l lived inside you. l've been watching you all this time.
Sometimes we exchanged places.
l'd receive the medical treatments and bear the pain of the seizures.
l protected you by taking on your suffering.
But l was happy because we were together.
Because it was just you and l...
in everything.
But you fucked that man!
Nanako.
Nii-sama.
Nii-sama!
You mean you...?
Yes. l told mother about you and Yushiro.
l opened your door and lured mother into the hallway.
That's horrible.
lt's all punishment.
Your punishment for choosing Nii-sama over me.
That's why l gathered those men,
drove father's business to bankruptcy,
and drove away Yushiro.
All to get you back.
No!
No... Don't.
Huh. Your sick?
Let me take your temperature.
This is not good.
You're fever is real high.
Stop.
Suck my fat dick. Suck it the way you sucked your brother's.
l'm going to lick your pussy.
Let me stick my tongue in that hole.
Young lady.
Nii-sama.
Sit on my cock!
Your big dick...
No...
No!
lt's over.
This is the end.
l'm sorry. l'm so sorry.
Father?
Kiriyama-san!
Hello. You were Nanako-san. Correct?
l invested quite a lot.
But it looks like it's all over.
You...
You guys tricked me. Deceived me!
Father.
Your father's debts are bigger than anticipated.
You all have to role play to pay it off.
No!
No. Don't.
No. No!
Nii-sama.
l will wait for you forever.
l will wait for your return...
...forever.
Forever.
VENGEANCE WlLL BEGlN