My name is Al. I'm a human.
I ended up here in Cornelica, the town
of succubi, due to some reason.
I'm now living together with
a little succubus named Lily.
One day, I fainted while I was in a tool shop.
A barkeeper named Rosary-san took me,
and I ended up working at her bar.
However, she jumped on me
right when I lowered my guard!
I got distracted by her tits.
Why did I get so careless?
As Rosary-san relentlessly squeezed me dry,
Lily came to my rescue.
It looks like I made her worried sick.
I really am the worst for making Lily cry.
The two of us got along again
and got intimate right away.
I'm not sure why, but my memories
after looking at Lily's eyes are fuzzy.
But there's no way that Lily
will be preying on me, right?
Cornelica, The Town of Succubi
Cornelica, the town of succubi.
Fourth episode : Obscene and Decadent Cornelica.
Episode 4
Obscene and Decadent Cornelica:
Arune, Rosary, Hakura and Lily
Arune, Rosary, Hakura and Lily.
And just like this, I'm currently staying with Lily.
I'm going on with my life in good health as usual.
Who could it be?
Oh! Hiya, Al-san! How are you today?
Arune, what's up?
H-Huh?
Oh, I really feel bad for what you
have gone through a few days ago.
The truth is, I should've apologized sooner.
I'm sorry that it took me this long.
O-Oh no, it's fine.
It's already in the past.
No, please let me make it up to you!
Please let me treat you at Rosary-san's bar!
You see, we'll also be having
a little banquet there tonight!
B-Banquet?
I am quite afraid about this,
but I never saw Arune as sincere as this before...
I'm humbly asking you, Al-san.
My own integrity as a succubus it at stake here.
Of course, I already got permission
from Lily-san as well.
I understand.
I accept your good intentions.
Oh, thank you!
Wow, this is amazing!
This is the first time that
I saw the bar so crowded!
But now that I'm taking a good look,
all of the guests besides me...
They're all succubi?!
I have a bad feeling about this...
Hey, Al-san! Over here!
Wow, these dishes are amazing!
Can I really eat them?
I'm loaded right now, so don't worry about it.
And there's still more coming!
Welcome!
I heard about it from Arune.
Take your time and enjoy.
Oh...
Getting treated this much kind
of makes me feel bad...
No, don't be. Please eat your fill
without holding back!
It seems that Lily-san is gonna come
a bit later with someone else.
We should start without them!
Yeah, we should.
So delicious!
I'm glad that it suits your palate.
Huh, what's that?
It's on the house. It's delicious!
Whoa—!
Huh... What?
I-Is that me?
What's happening here?!
It's a huge success!
That's my new product, a magic potion.
It makes a clone of someone who drinks it.
Al, I'll be helping myself to you.
Rosary-san, stop!
No, I won't.
Look, here are my tits!
They're huge unlike Lily's.
N-No way, size doesn't matter!
Your cock is getting bigger though.
Your body is being honest.
Your thoughts don't matter.
What only matters is me sucking your vitality.
D-Don't! It's gonna come out!
N-No way, I just came!
Huh? I told you it doesn't matter.
I'll only be squeezing you dry
until nothing comes out anymore.
Yes, that's good! That's the way.
I-It's gonna come out!
Okay, next...
H-Help me...
W-Wait, don't get close!
You're not running away from me!
Here!
Whoa! Is this...
Yes! It's "Puppet Controller: Version 2"!
I learned from the last time
and improved its capabilities.
Alright, Al-san! Let's have some fun!
That's good, just like that!
I'll tighten up my pussy so please
keep shaking your hips!
Hey, come on! You won't be able
to come just from this much!
Please keep pounding me hard. Here you go!
No, it's gonna come out!
Isn't it fine? Please feel free to spurt it out!
I'll start the countdown!
Three... Two... One... Zero!
Hey there, Al-san! This isn't
the time to be sobbing!
Let's test how much you can
shoot out for this whole night!
This will be the next one.
No, stop!
Look, everybody is itching to get you.
Stop, don't tease me there!
Even if I get enough of you,
everybody's waiting.
This won't end so don't worry.
No way! It's coming out!
That's right, come!
That's it! That feels good, Al-san!
I think he's about to reach his limit.
Oh, then shall we go for the last spurt?
Phew... That was fun!
Yeah, that was satisfying.
Cornelica, the town of succubi.
Al!
Al, are you alright? Hang in there!
L-Lily...
My, oh my...
It looks like you got yourself
wrung out too much again.
W-Wait!
What do you think are you
candidly doing in front of me?
I'm reviving Al-san using my mana-infused milk.
This is a lifesaving measure,
so please calm down.
Oh my!
You don't have to rush.
My tits are not going anywhere!
My, my... Will he be alright?
Al-san hasn't fully recovered yet.
He'll be fine, I'll be sucking
their magic out from here!
He'll get well faster this way!
I see, so it was like that.
Al, you're going to be alright.
I'm going to make you fully forget
about those other succubi!
L-Lily, wait...
That feels so good. You're gonna make me come!
It's alright, don't hold it in
and come with all might!
Al-san, that's not good!
You have to drink a lot or you won't get well!
Lily, you're being rough!
You really are amazing, Al!
You're worn out, yet you already
got so lively down here!
Jeez, assaulting Al-san while he's at such a state...
Doesn't that make you
no different as other succubi?
I-It's alright since Al belongs to me!
We're in love with each other
so don't interfere, Hakura!
Well then, I'll have him do me with his mouth.
I already told you not to interfere!
Isn't it fine?
Al-san seems to love getting
a taste of both of us as well.
You're doing great, Al-san! That feels good!
Al, can you feel it? That's my cervix!
I'll use it to keep gobbling you a lot,
so you can come when you feel like it!
Here, don't you love it when
I keep grind it against here like this?
I'm the only one who has been putting
an effort on knowing about you, Al!
It's good that you love each other
but you lack a certain allure, Lily-san.
Wh-What's that?
It's something maternal which is a woman's trait.
What I'm saying is that your tits are lacking.
So what? Anyone will grow
theirs bigger in time!
H-Hey, Lily-san!
Don't be so reckless!
Don't push it. How about going
away somewhere else instead?
Granny!
H-How rude of you!
I'll show an unseasoned wench like you
how huge the gap between our experiences is!
Just as I wanted!
Let's see which one of us
will be able to satisfy Al!
I-I'm already at my limit...
Huh? Al, Are you alright?
Hang in there!
My, my... This is already too much for him.
Now that it comes to this, I have to
quickly end it by making Al come!
Help me here, Hakura!
I-I told you not to suck my tits right now!
Gosh!
Here comes Al's sperm!
My milk is overflowing!
That was great, Al!
Jeez, you went overboard!
Whoa! Al, that looks bad! Are you alright?
Lily, help me...
Al's body won't last if this goes on.
He'll be in serious trouble in time.
He's gonna be fine since
I'm going to protect him!
It's gonna be alright, Al.
I'll always be by your side whatever happens.
I'll keep saving you no matter
how many times I have to.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization