Huh? Where am I?
R-Rosary-san?
Yeah.
My name is Al. I'm a human.
I ended up here in Cornelica, the town
of succubi, due to some reason.
I'm now living together with
a little succubus named Lily.
When I went to help at the church,
I once again fell into Hakura-san's ploy.
After being told that the
supply of milk isn't enough,
I ended up squeezing breast milk
out of Hakura-san's tits.
Being powerless against Hakura-san's magic,
I was unable to even move an inch
away and my life force was sucked.
Just a little longer and I would've
ended up becoming her sex slave!
If Lily didn't save me back then,
I might have ended up in deep trouble!
I ended up having to stop helping at the church,
and that was when Arune called me over.
She wanted my help on testing her new products,
but I wonder if Arune's spirit
of research got lit up.
She coerced me into various unreasonable tests.
In the end, she drained me of my life force,
and it concluded with me losing consciousness.
Why did things turn out like this from that time?
Cornelica, The Town of Succubi
Cornelica, the town of succubi.
Third episode: Easygoing Cornelica.
Episode 3
Easygoing Cornelica: Rosary's Gaze and Lily's Feelings
Rosary's gaze and Lily's feelings.
Umm, why am I here?
If I remember it correctly,
I should've been at the tool shop.
When I went to the tool shop, I met Arune.
She squeezed you dry back there.
She said that you seemed free, so she asked you
for help at the store. Did she go overboard?
She told me that she did
something bad and apologized.
If you want to work, lend me a hand in this bar.
I'm happy that I can get myself a job,
but I'll end up getting attacked
by Rosary-san this time.
Follow me.
It seems that she's normally
giving me chores in this bar.
Thank goodness. I don't need to worry about it.
Hmm?
What's the matter? Want your cock sucked?
N-No, I'm fine! I'll keep on working!
Is that so?
That was a close one!
Even when I'm normally doing chores,
Rosary-san will jump on me when
she gets an opportunity!
I can't let my guard down!
H-Hey...
Should I help washing the dishes?
Is that so?
Then, would you put these plates back into the shelf?
Understood.
Uhh... It's cramped in here...
H-Huh?
I-I'm stuck!
Excuse me... Umm, Rosary-san...
Yeah...
Wait, that's not what I meant!
R-Rosary-san, wait...
I knew it, you were holding it in.
You already got this hard.
Rosary-san!
Stop making a ruckus.
I'm only stroking your cock.
Th-This is bad! If Rosary-san
shakes her hips like that,
I won't be able to get away from her!
Hmm? Are you trying to endure it?
Not that it matters.
Don't do that!
I'm not bewitching you.
I'm only squeezing your cock.
No, it's coming out!
You came a lot, huh?
Good boy.
Hmm...
Looks like you can still come.
Do you love tits?
You were always looking at them.
You've been staring at my tits
throughout the day.
Here, can you feel the softness of my tits?
I'll be doing you just like this,
so keep on shooting more semen out!
They're so soft... They feel good...
This is bad! If this goes on, I'll end up
getting wrung out dry again!
You're rubbing your face against my tits...
So, that's how much you like them...
Then, come one more time just like this.
Yes, that's the way...
You can keep going on, right?
Stop this already! Please stop!
N-No more! Any more than this and I'll really...
It's alright, don't hold it in.
Shoot it out when you feel like coming.
You're about to run out of anything
to shoot out soon, after all.
Cornelica, the town of succubi.
Yes... We've only just begun.
L-Lily?
Oh...
Uhh...
Huh?
A-Al, are you alright?
Are you not hurting anywhere?
Lily...
Gosh, I was so worried!
You're not going home long after
going out from the church!
I couldn't find you anywhere else!
I tried looking for you everywhere,
and when I finally found you
in the bar, you got attacked again!
I thought that you're gonna die for real!
How did you end up that way there?!
Sorry for making you worry.
You're working for the sake of this town,
so I couldn't take in the idea
of me not doing anything.
I don't want to just rely on you.
I want to be able to help you.
Al?
I don't want you putting
yourself in dangerous situations.
I'll protect you so always stay by my side.
O-Okay...
Oh, Rosary's magic hasn't fully worn off yet.
In that case, I'll need to properly treat you.
Lily...
How is it? Here, does this feel good?
It feels good...
Being wrung out dry by other girls
was hard for you, wasn't it?
I'll be gently caressing this one for you.
You got so hard down here, Al!
You feel good on your nipples
despite being a boy, huh?
It's throbbing and twitching... That's so cute!
Lily!
Yeah, are you about to come?
You can shoot a lot of it out.
Shall we go for another round?
Look, Al... My pussy is making a squelching sound!
Doesn't this feel very good?
Are you gonna ejaculate just like this?
N-No way... Put it in...
Put it inside you, Lily!
Umm, but aren't you ending up
having sex with other girls pretty easily?
You'll be the only one! From now on,
I'll only do it with you!
Hurry up, I'm begging you!
Isn't that right? Don't you belong to me, Al?
Very well said!
So, you came, huh?
But we're still going to continue like this.
Al, can you feel it?
Your cock is a tight fit with my pussy!
We're perfectly made for each other!
Hey, Al... Doesn't it feel great?
You don't have to think about anything else.
Just let yourself feel good.
That's amazing, Al!
This is starting to make me feel good as well!
Good!
Here, Al...
Hey, Al! I'm talking to you!
Oh, Al... You can see nothing else but me!
It can't be helped, gosh...
Stay with me forever, okay?
We'll always be together.
Hey, Al! We're not done yet!
Until the scent of other girls goes off you...
...we'll keep going on!
You belong to me.
Both of your body and heart...
And even what's inside your cock... They are all mine!
Uh-huh... You can come as many times as you want.
Give me plenty of your semen!
Al...
Look only at me.
Feel my hands!
I want you to give all of it to me, just like this!
I'll take everything into me all the way!
You're about to come again!
It's alright, shoot it out!
Wait, wait! I wanted to drink all of it!
Stay by my side from now on, Al.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization