Beings that are referred to as
"succubi" exist in this world.
They are female demons that seduce men.
These children of the night milk those
men of their vitality afterwards.
They used to sneak around the world luring their prey,
but humans then started to hunt down a lot of demons
and they were never seen again.
The remaining succubi
founded a place for themselves.
And there, they lured men, safely draining
them off their vitality to their heart's content.
Nowadays, no succubi live in the human world.
Their way of survival today
is luring their prey and taking their time to savor it.
This is a land where they can live in peace.
It is the demon town of Cornelica.
Cornelica, The Town of Succubi
Episode 1
Danger-filled Cornelica: A Paradise for the Succubi
Hey, Al!
Oh, Lily!
Hooah!
Whoa!
W-Wait, Lily?
You worked hard, Al!
Let's hurry up and go home!
Due to an unexpected turn of events,
I ended up in Cornelica, the town of succubi.
And that's when I first met Lily, a little
succubus girl, who then helped me.
There are a lot of succubi in this town
and things get scary for me from time to time.
At those times, Lily comes to my aid
and we somehow manage to work it out.
The two of us have overcome a lot of things
and we finally figured out how
I can go back to my own world,
But in the end, I...
Hmm? What's the matter, Al?
Nah, it's nothing.
It's good that I'm able to get a job cleaning here,
but it's a little hard since this place is huge.
It'll take me a lot longer before I'm done.
Isn't this something Hakura asked you to do?
Just whiz through that and let's go home.
Well, that's kind of...
That will be a problem.
You have to properly do the job I asked you to.
My, my... Al-san...
Doesn't this place look a lot tidier now?
Hakura-san...
Well, yeah...
Then, how about taking a short break?
You can resume your work after that.
Right... I'll just continue working.
Wait, Hakura! This place is quite
clean already so isn't that enough?
Let Al go home already!
My, my...
I'm just about to make some tea.
I-It's alright, Lily. Let's at least
have a sip for the moment.
Yes! Feel free to join us, Lily.
Then, let's head this way.
This somehow smells fishy...
It's delicious!
I'm glad to hear that.
Ugh... Huh?
My body...
Al? What's wrong? Hey?
Hakura, what's happening here? What did you do?
My, my...
They're nothing but tasty-looking leaves
that I picked up from Hilbert Forest...
You got them from the forest?
You made Al drink something made from those?
My, my... Please don't get so angry.
Wh-What are you doing out of nowhere?
If it's an effect of the leaves from that forest,
then I'm sure that it'll get cured
by making him ejaculate.
Here you go!
I'm going to make you squirt and feel good, okay?
W-Wait! What are you getting
started at so suddenly?!
There, there... Let me handle this.
I'll make him come in no time.
Look...
You got this hard, it's twitching and throbbing...
It looks like it's gonna burst any minute now.
Oh my, some fluid oozed out of the tip!
Are you about to shoot it out?
There's a lot that came out, huh?
It tastes great!
Oh my, it looks like you haven't had enough yet.
Stand aside, Hakura! I'll do it instead!
It got big now.
Just wait for it, Al.
I'm gonna squeeze you dry using my pussy.
Was the pleasure surprising for you?
It's alright, come whenever you feel like it.
My, my... You look like you're in pain!
Alright then, I'll let you suck onto my tits.
There you go again!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Don't you like it whenever I do this, Al?
Your cock grew even bigger again.
You're feeling good, huh?
You're sucking it so much...
You love tits, huh?
Th-That's not true!
It's my pussy that's making Al feel good!
Look, look! Your cock is already bulging!
You're about to come, right? It's alright...
Come! Come! Come—!
Wow, you came this much...
I've been telling you...
Al is mine, so I'm gonna cure him myself!
Don't just take his semen without permission!
Isn't that fine?
Even Al-san seems to have taken a liking on my tits.
That's not true!
I'm gonna squeeze him dry using my own body!
Jeez, let go of him!
I get assaulted like this from time to time,
but Lily handles things for me so
I somehow manage to live through.
We got ourselves in such a mess...
Jeez!
That Hakura always feasts on you!
Just because her tits are a little bit bigger...
Yeah, I'll be careful next time.
Hey, let's eat something delicious for supper.
Can't we dine out every now and then?
Yeah, sounds great.
I got some cash to spare thanks
to my work at the church.
Shall we splurge a bit of it?
Alright then, let's go!
Rosary, we're here!
Huh, Rosary and... Arune? What's the matter?
Lily...
Hiya, you two.
There aren't any customer here.
Did something happen?
The appliance...
Huh...
It's alright, I'll explain it to them.
Rosary-san contacted me,
so I came here to repair one of
her broken kitchen appliance.
It's one of our products, so we
offer product support for it.
But since Rosary-san has to be here
with me while I do the repairs,
she wasn't able to do all the other work for the bar.
So even when I got done with the repairs,
the customers ended up
angry for not getting served.
Then, is there anything I can do to help?
Oh, me too! Me too!
Oh, isn't that great?
Are you fine with that, Rosary-san?
Yes, that will help me. Thank you.
Lily will handle the guest seating
and wiping up of tables.
Al will bring the ingredients
here from the storehouse.
Okay, leave it to me!
Roger that!
Be careful of the ingredients.
They have something inside of them
that is dangerous to humans.
Umm, the wheat flour is...
Oh, that one?
Huh? This is quite heavy!
Oh no, I made a blunder...
Huh? Is this a bedroom in the bar?
Why...
Oh, looks like you're up now.
Oh, that's good to know.
U-Umm... Why am I here?
What is Lily doing right now?
Al-san, you got in contact with a bit
dangerous ingredient in the storehouse.
You're lucky to get away from it just with fainting.
I got tired working on the bar,
so I left it in Lily's care.
Lily is a little busy at the moment,
so she won't be coming here any time soon.
U-Umm...
Why are you suddenly...
Isn't your body still feeling sluggish?
It's alright, just stay put.
It's been a while for me so
I'll be milking a lot out of you!
What did you just...
I imbued you with a bit of my mana.
Don't worry, it'll just immobilize
you for a short time.
You're delicious...
R-Rosary-san... Stop...
Al, your cock is now fully concealed.
I'll do this for you, okay?
It grew bigger, now I can easily rub it.
Rosary-san, don't do that!
Hmm? This is great.
I'll do it even more.
Come on, don't hold it in.
Aren't you about to come?
It's coming out!
I'm up next, right?
I couldn't contain myself waiting for this!
It's been long since I had to do the work milking
someone using my pussy, so this is a bit hard for me.
Me too, I haven't had enough of squeezing you.
Hoo-ha! Hoo-ha!
Rosary's tits and my pussy...
Aren't you happy to be able to satisfy
yourself with both, Al-san?
It's here, it's here! You're about to come!
Take this, take this! Come, come!
I knew it, creampies sure feel great!
Your sperm is gently flowing around inside!
Isn't that great, Al-san.
Alright, then. Onto the second round...
It's my turn next.
Rosary-san, I can't breathe with these on me!
It's alright, it feels good when
you're on the verge of fainting.
Th-There's nothing okay...
Oh... You'll end up crashing Al-san for real.
He might even die if things go wrong.
It's alright.
He'll get used to this.
You're right there again!
You can come when you feel like it.
How did that kind of play feel for you, Al?
Does the idea of becoming mine fancy you?
Al, are you alright?
Lily...
Oh... She's awfully angry...
Lily, you meany.
You're both so mean!
Al is mine, so don't lay your hands on him anymore!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization