Beings that are referred to as
"succubi" exist in this world.
They are female demons that seduce men.
These children of the night milk those
men of their vitality afterwards.
They used to sneak around the world luring their prey,
but humans then started to hunt down a lot of demons
and they were never seen again.
The remaining succubi
founded a place for themselves.
They lure men there, safely draining them
off their vitality to their heart's content.
Nowadays, no succubi live in the human world.
Their way of survival today
is luring their prey and taking their time to savor it.
This is a land where they can live in peace.
It is the demon town of Cornelica.
What?
Lily, what are you doing...
Oh, Al!
Just wait for a moment.
You looked like you're about to come, so...
Like this?
Stop talking while sucking me!
I want it!
I want it all until my mouth overflows!
I'm... Coming!
Good morning, Al.
Good morning, Lily...
Cornelica, The Town of Succubi
Episode 2
Job-abundant Cornelica: Hakura's Milk and Arune's Magic Item
My name is Al.
I'm now living here in Cornelica, the town of succubi
due to some unintended turn of events.
I live together with a succubus named Lily.
She always ends up saving me.
I got employed by Hakura-san, the head of the church.
I help by doing simple tasks
like cleaning the church premises.
But in the end, Hakura-san is still a succubus.
She lured and paralyzed me.
She then drained me of my life force.
I wonder what would've happened
to me if Lily wasn't there.
After managing to escape from Hakura-san,
we decided to have our supper at the bar.
But the owner Rosary-san and the tool
dealer Arune-san are having trouble,
so we ended up lending some hand.
However, due to my carelessness...
I ended up getting caught by the two of them
and being squeezed a lot until I'm dry.
I shouldn't give Lily any more worries!
I'll have to be more careful from now on!
Hello!
Hakura-san, is something wrong?
Oh, Al-san!
You see, I made some mistake
on our food's inventory.
We don't have any more supply of milk for today.
I-Isn't that bad?!
Is there anything that I can do about it?
There's a lot of things I'd like to ask for,
but they would be a little tedious to do.
I'm fine with it!
If I'll be of any help for everyone,
I'll endure it even if it's a little strenuous!
Thank you!
I'll take you up on your offer, then!
This jar is where we store our milk.
Now it is just as you see.
It's empty up to the last drop, isn't it?
What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Yes, that's right...
It can't be helped if it's already empty,
so I thought that I'd fill it up
with my own milk instead.
C-Can't we just buy some
from somewhere instead?
That won't be good.
We won't have any milk for our lunch
preparation if we'll go out to buy it now.
Umm... Umm...
My milk won't properly come out even
when I try squeezing it out by myself.
Al-san, can you somehow lend me a hand here?
It really started spurting out!
We won't have enough at this rate...
Is there anything else we can do
to make more milk come out?
Let's see...
I'll need your love for that, Al.
L-Love?
Love is a feeling of devotion
towards another person.
It's a feeling when you dedicate yourself
to your partner and share the joy.
Inducing life force is necessary for producing milk.
Alright, please shower me with your love
as much as you want.
Okay...
That's it, please suck it as much as you want.
My, oh my... Are you perhaps
going at it a little too hard?
Bear with it a little longer, okay?
Mama will make you feel good soon.
Come on, you shouldn't let go of mama's tits!
Make sure to look me in the eye,
and rub my tits as well, okay?
No, I'm gonna come already!
That's it, alright!
You squirted out a lot, huh?
Good boy, good boy!
Uhh... Huh? I can't move!
My voice won't come out as well!
You're now completely under my spell.
You are already my son, Al.
N-No way... No, stop!
Good... That's good!
I can feel your love deep inside me, Al!
We won't stop until we fill this jar up to the brim,
so please do your best, alright?
Wow, this is amazing!
I never made this much milk before!
We'll have no more problems
with milk from now on!
I'll have you help me on this
from now on, alright?
Tomorrow, and the day after too...
I'll have you handle this task from today onwards!
No more! I can't take it anymore!
Hakura—!
Jeez! Enough of that already!
You were seducing Al for real earlier, aren't you?!
I'm not letting you off this time!
No more helping at the church!
Don't ever come near Al again!
My, oh my...
I went a little overboard, huh?
What am I gonna do now?
I'm sorry!
I got an invitation that I can't
refuse no matter what.
I'll get this done and go home in no time.
You should go straight home without any delay.
What Lily said was right.
I should go straight home to be safe,
but I'll just end up doing
nothing and being a burden...
Huh? Oh...
Well, if it isn't Al-san...
I see...
You sure are fixated about working, Al.
Is it something like...
"I want to be a good provider for Lily-san!"
Something like that?
It's not like that...
It feels something like unsettling
for me when I'm doing nothing...
Huh... You sure are a strange one, Al.
But regardless, I'm glad that's the case.
Huh? What do you mean?
Most of the stuff in this shop is my own handicraft.
They're my cute children, if I may say so.
Whoa... That's amazing!
However, I'm having some difficulties
on developing new products.
I don't have enough people to help me test them.
Oh... I see.
I'll help you here if there's anything that I can do.
R-Really?
By the way, what is this thing used for?
Huh?
Umm... Are you serious about that question?
Huh? Yeah.
W-Well...
You should be fine when you
see the work for yourself.
Follow me inside.
This is my workplace that I'm proud of!
The job that you'll do for me
will all basically be done here.
U-Umm... It might be late for me to ask this,
but I'm not doing anything dangerous, am I?
Everything will be fine!
The products made here are all safe even for humans!
I'll make sure that you won't be left alone here!
Moreover, you'll choose your own working hours!
See? Isn't it all safe?
Y-Yeah... You are right.
I-Is this your new product?
That's right.
I'll name it "Puppet Controller"!
Puppet?
You can make someone move as you wish
even without using any magic with that tool.
And together with this box,
You can make someone immediately do as you please!
Wait, does this mean
that I'm now under your control, Arune?
We're just getting started.
What's happening?!
This feature is called a "forced erection mode".
It can make any placid cock as hard as a rock!
Alright then, let the product testing begin.
Here you go, Al-san.
Pound my sopping wet pussy.
I-It's going in!
Hmm, yeah...
Looks like the fundamental motions are all green.
We'll test the piston motion next.
Please hump me with all intent.
What's happening? Only my hips are moving!
O-Ouch! My body hurts!
Oops...
So, I need to make a function where the whole
body does other things asynchronously...
Yeah, that's good to know.
It seems like Arune doesn't feel that I'm here,
except for her pussy that keeps on grasping me.
And I am here, being forced to shake my hips.
Hmm... The motion is monotonous
that it's kind of boring...
Should I set the timing of its motion to random?
It feels like I turned into a machine
to purposely make both of us feel good.
Oh! This is it!
What should I do?
I might end up wanting nothing
else but feeling good here!
Alright...
We can proceed with the stress test
with that stamina of yours.
S-Stress test?
That's right.
How heavy it can lift, and for how long...
It's a test to see how much it can withstand.
And with that being said...
Here, embrace me.
Okay.
You lifted me up with zero effort, huh?
Y-Yeah, well...
Well, I'm already light in the first place.
Then, how about when I do this?
This is not good!
Are you about to come?
It won't affect the test, so you may do so.
A-Arune, I'm already...
What are you saying? We're far from done!
Can't you lift my leg up or something?
Now, this is something noteworthy...
Just having your cock at a
different angle feels quite good!
Oh-oh-oh...
Okay then, put my leg down before we proceed.
Oh-oh-oh?
No matter how much I want
to enjoy using this tool,
it's all for naught when the
human it's on breaks down.
That pose should be fine for now.
We'll proceed to the next test.
Okay, then...
It's about time for me to reveal my secret weapon.
What I need when I still want to play
with a human who has exceeded his limits... is this!
I think I went overboard.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization