No-!
S-Stop this already!
Princess Chiori, Princess Chika! I'll save you!
Welcome, Prince.
However, how are you going to save them like that?
You're-!
Damn it, why are you doing this?!
What are you going to do with us?
O-Onii-chan!
Onii-chan-! Help us!
Then how about I let one of them go?
Which will it be?
Will it be Princess Chiori or Princess Chika?
They're both my precious sisters! I can't choose only one!
They aren't your real sisters, are they?
Shut up!
Help us, Onii-chan!
No! Onii-chan, help us!
You can't choose one, can you?
Then you'll burn in hell for all eternity.
Onii-chan, help us!
Please, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
You can't choose one, can you?
Chiori! Chika!
Onii-chan!
Just a little more-!
Chiori! Chika!
Onii-chan!!
Onii-chan, wake up already!
Even though it's the weekend, it's already past noon!
O-Okay, okay...
I bet you were up all night watching porno!
How long are you two going to be in Japan?
Hurry up and go before I graduate!
Sure, whatever. After lunch, then.
Eh? You're going to make it? Where's Chiori?
Chiori's on a date today!
Eh?
SubDESU-H
Presents
Mako-chan!
Chiori!
It was so scary!
Konaki-jiji was the best!
The Nezumi Jiji came on to me and felt my butt!
Eh?
But Ken-kun beat him up for me!
That's so cool!
How about we go ride the ferris wheel?
Chiori wants to go to a buffet!
Then how about we split up?
Let's meet up at the central plaza in an hour, then!
Sign: Closed
This time it's your turn, so do what you want...
No-!
No!
Eh?
Those two sure are bold!
So Ken-chan and Mako really are dating!
How's this?
Take this! Super counter attack, Ultra Hyper Spinner!
Hey! What a dirty trick!
Yay! Chika wins again!
Let's play again!
I've completely lost!
I'm going out for a bit.
Eh? Where are you going? Let's play again!
Oh really? Eh? Chika-chan is so strange sometimes!
Chiori?
Thanks for walking me home.
No problem, was it fun?
Yep! It sure was!
Chiori-chan... Um, do you want to go with just the two of us next time?
Yeah, sure!
I've always liked you, Chiori-chan.
So, will you go out with me?
Eh? But, I...
Chiori-chan-!
You can't choose one, can you?
Then you'll burn in hell for all eternity.
I guess I'll have to choose one, or...
Onii-chan, can I come in?
Sure.
What's up?
Nothing really.
I just wanted to be with you, Onii-chan.
Chiori won't shut up about it if she finds out that you were in my room.
It's fine, she's taking a long bath.
Then do you wanna play some games?
Onii-chan, you were thinking about Chiori, weren't you?
You looked like you were troubled when you came home.
I can tell. You're always worrying about Chiori.
What's with this all of a sudden? I think about you, too.
Then which do you like better? Me or Chiori?
What are you saying?
You're both my precious sisters.
Sisters?
That's right, you're my sisters.
That's why Chiori will leave me one day.
You're talking about Chiori again!
But I won't go anywhere... I'll be with you, Onii-chan.
I'll always be with you, so...
"So"?
Yeah, so...
Onii-chan, please only think about Chika!
Onii-chan, I...
It feels too good to touch my nipples!
Chi-Chika!
Chika...
If it's with you, Onii-chan, then I won't regret it!
O-Onii-chan's coming inside me-!
O-Onii-chan's big thing is hitting me where it feels best!
Chi-Chiori is-! I'm burning up!
Chi-Chiori is cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Onii-chan!
This is embarrassing...
Why?
Because my breasts aren't big...
I like them more when they're this size. They're cuter...
I'm feeling strange...
What does it feel like?
It's mysterious. It's kind of ticklish...
That's-!
It's fine, leave it to me.
Don't smell me down there! It's embarrassing!
No, no-!
O-Onii-chan!
Chika-chan! You can take a bath now!
I'm gonna make dinner!
Chiori, can I have a refill?
Sure, a refill?
Thanks.
You're welcome!
That's Chiori's job!
You don't mind if I do it, do you?
Yeah, that's fine...
Hey, after dinner, can you help me with my homework?
Yeah, okay.
No! You were with him all day! It's Chiori's turn!
That's because you were on a date with Shun-kun!
It wasn't a date!
By the way, did Shun-kun confess his feelings to you?
Ehh?
I knew it! I could tell.
Shun-kun was all lovey dovey over you.
Chiori, why don't you date him?
Ehh?!
I don't mind as long I have Onii-chan!
Onii-chan! Could you wake Chika-chan again?
Chika! Wake up! How long are you gonna sleep? You'll be late for school!
I bet you didn't set your alarm clock again!
Fine, then. If you give me a kiss, I'll wake up.
The princess awakes with the prince's kiss.
Hey Chika!
Um, this is-!
Eh?
Oh no! Did she find out what was going on between us?
Chiori...
You can't get married to your brother, you know.
But Onii-chan and I aren't...
I know you're not blood related.
Yeah.
But people around you don't think like that.
But, but-!
Do you like him that much?
I won't do?
I'm sorry...
But I think that having two of you will end up hurting your brother.
Why?!
If I was in his place, I wouldn't be able to choose.
Eh?
If I chose one, the other one would be deeply hurt.
I think that I might even hurt myself by hiding my true feelings,
rather than hurt you two.
I'm sorry, Shun-kun.
I love Onii-chan because he's my Onii-chan. It's not just anyone.
You don't need a reason to love someone!
I don't know why,
but before I even realized, he was a person very dear to me.
And... And my feelings became bigger and bigger!
Even if the whole world were to hate Onii-chan,
Chiori will forever be on his side!
That's why I don't care what anyone else thinks! I'm fine with it!
Chiori, Chika went off to school already!
I'm gonna skip school today!
I'm coming in.
What's wrong, Chiori?
What's this luggage?
Chiori's gonna go to America.
When I go, I won't come back.
I can understand why Onii-chan likes Chika-chan.
She's cute, energetic and she's reliable!
You're cute too, Chiori!
It's not fair that Chika-chan is hogging you!
Chiori likes Onii-chan too!
Chiori...
I know I shouldn't, but Chiori's gonna go off to America!
I'll go off by myself, so...
so please make memories for me as well!
I want you to do things you did to Chika-chan to me!
Otherwise, Chiori will...!
Otherwise, Chiori will...
Onii-chan, do anything you want to me.
Chiori...
Onii-chan, this is embarrassing...
Just hold still...
Onii-chan, I want to become one with you...
Sorry, I can't do that...
I see, since you have Chika-chan...
Chiori...
It's fine! I know that Chiori isn't as beautiful as Chika-chan...
I haven't gone all the way with Chika, either.
Welcome!
Are you ready to order?
What will it be?
An ice tea, green milk tea, Camille tea and an espresso, please
Could you not talk at the same time?
An ice tea, green milk tea, Camille tea and an espresso!
We had a lot of customers today, too!
It's all thanks to you guys!
It's because of my idea of Cosplaying, right?
Chiori's new menu was the hit, right?
T-This sure tastes great!
Thanks! Please eat a lot!
I could make something like that, too!
You shouldn't push yourself, Chika-chan.
I guess it's true that the only thing you beat me at is cooking.
I caught up to you in other areas too!
What do you mean?!
It's just as you think!
Chika, um...
Onii-chan, please tell me the truth.
Did you do lewd things with Chiori yesterday?
I...
I confessed to you before her!
But Chiori...
I'm the one who's at fault here!
It's because I...!
Why did something like this happen?!
Onii-chan!
Idiot! Go home!
This isn't where a child should be!
Don't follow me!
Onii-chan, what are you doing in a place like this?
Chiori, get me some water...!
Chiori...
Don't get in my way!
I'm making breakfast today!
Cooking meals is Chiori's job!
I was here first.
That doesn't matter!
It does!
I confessed to Onii-chan before you did!
That doesn't matter, either!
Why are you doing this?! You know that I love Onii-chan!
You knew that Chiori did too when you confessed first!
Chiori, you thief!
Chika-chan, you coward!
Chiori, you meanie!
Chika-chan, you bully!
You-!
I hate you!
I hate you too!
I hate you more!
I hate you even more!
Why did something like this happen?
I-I wonder why...
Sign: Closed
This shop has been closed a lot recently...
The coffee was good.
There were cute girls, too.
Did they go under?
I see...
But... I think I understand those two.
Maybe I should join in too!
Eh? A-Aya-chan!
Master, I don't like how you're acting at the moment.
Onii-chan!
Good morning!
It's already past noon!
Oops, you're right!
Hurry up and sit down. The omelette will get cold.
Let's eat!
It's been a while since we all had a meal together.
It tastes better when we're together, right Onii-chan?
Uh, yeah...
Onii-chan...
We've decided something...
We both thoroughly talked it over!
We've supposedly decided on the best option, but...
Sorry to cause you trouble.
Do you hate us now?
Of course not!
You're both my precious sisters!
Stay well in America!
Chiori, we promised that we wouldn't cry...
Yeah...
...Passengers boarding the flight to New York,
please make your way to gate 28...
It's nearly time.
Yeah.
We're off, then.
Hello Master, are you well?
Chiori and Chika have flown to America before I graduate,
and it seems that they'll be staying there.
Things have settled down since they left.
Well, it's like something big is missing.
Did you know, Master?
The saddening stories in movies finish in a matter of hours...
But they actually continue forever.
Please stay well, Master.
Eh? No way! This is the bad ending!
Chiori doesn't want this!
We don't want to leave Onii-chan!
That's right!
Okay, then! How about we just do it?
One, two, three!
Oh?
Chiori? Chika?
Sign: We're sorry, Mom and Dad! Chiori Chika
I wonder what happened to those cute twins of yours?
Hmm, I wonder too...
They're in America now.
Oh, it must be lonely, then.
Wouldn't it be good if they came back?
No, they can't, you see...
Do you want to bet on that?
1,000 points that they'll return!
I'm betting a cup of coffee that they'll return, too!
Eh?
Chiori? Chika?
We came back!
Onii-chan! We're back!
We knew it.
We both love you, Onii-chan!
I can't lie to myself anymore!
I know it's not allowed, even though we're not blood related...
You, Chiori, and me. We're three persons, but together we're two.
Chiori and Chika are one person.
We were born from the same egg!
We just happened to split up.
We know each other better than anyone!
We also know that we love you more than anyone else, too!
Humans are the ones that decided that
marriage should only be monogamous, right?
Can't we be together just because we love you?
Since getting married isn't happiness,
being together with you is.
Even if the whole world disapproves,
if we can be together...
Chika and Chiori will be the happiest people on earth!
Onii-chan, can we come in?
We've got something to talk about!
Yeah, come on in.
Onii-chan...
We've both decided...
We both love you very much!
So, we want you to do everything to us!
And we want to know everything about you!
If it's you, then we don't mind what you do.
We don't mind if you look at our breasts, down there, or even our butts!
So...
Onii-chan...
Please make love to us!
This is embarrassing!
Yeah...
No-!
I'll do it to you too, Onii-chan.
It's so big!
Chiori wants to lick Onii-chan too!
Chika-chan! It went in all the way!
That's unfair, Chiori!
Does it hurt, Chiori?
No, I'll be okay.
Onii-chan, please put it in Chika now!
Chika-chan! If you rub me that much, I'll wet myself!
Onii-chan, hurry up!
Okay! Lift your hips more!
Chiori wants a go!
Take turns putting it in!
It feels so good! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
No way that'll happen...
Hello. Are you doing well, Master?
With Chiori and Chika back,
it looks like it's going to be a fun lifestyle once again.
I wish times like these could last forever...
Onii-chan, can we come in?
We've got something to talk about!
Eh?