Madam, this is...
You didn't pay enough, Madam...
First Time
Which would you like today?
Onii-chan, help me study! I've got a big test tomorrow.
All right, but don't count on me too much.
No fair! Don't keep him all to yourself!
It's cause I'm not as clever as you, Chiyori.
C'mon, let's start studying, Onii-chan!
Hey now, I'm still at work.
There aren't any customers, are there?
There is one, over there.
I'll tutor you after closing time.
I'll hold you to that.
See ya!
Sorry about the noise.
Not at all. It's great to see you all having fun.
Nah, it's more like I'm being played around with by them.
Just like real siblings.
And also like little lovers.
Shall I get you another serving?
Is it on the house?
"Greetings, Master. How are you?"
"Three months have passed since you departed for your journey to search for new coffee beans."
"Incidentally, about the matter of my twin sisters, Chika and Chiyori,
I've let them stay over in a vacant room."
"I apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you. However, it should only be until they graduate."
"After they graduate from high school, I shall send them to America where my father is now."
"It has been many years since I last saw their faces."
"As such, I shall cherish the time that the three of us spend together for this short while."
When my father suddenly told me to take care of them,
I had no clue how to do it.
But it's all going surprisingly well.
A franchise store recently opened up beside our café, though.
They're sucking up all the customers...
It's nice to have peace and quiet here, Master.
Aya-chan!
Your coffee definitely tastes better than theirs.
Thank you very much.
I care greatly for my regular customers.
Onii-chan, wake Chika-chan up for me!
All right.
Chika! Wake―!
Onii-chan, you saw them, didn't you!?
No, I didn't.
Then I'll have you take me out on a date as punishment!
I really didn't see anything like your light blue panties!
See! You did see them!
If you don't take me out on a date, I'm gonna burn your dumplings!
Burn them, then.
I'll go up to the roof!
Be careful.
I'm gonna strip naked!
Ah! What are you doing!?
Date.
"Shopping with Chiyori."
That's not fair, Chiyori!
I don't wanna hear that from you!
What the heck? I got to him first, not you!
Master...
After we moved in together,
That's what you always say, Chiyori!
our calendar started to fill up with various events.
How about a shopping-date? That way we all can―
What!? That's not how it's supposed to work!
They write on it whenever they want me to accompany them.
Date
with Chika!
Shopping
with Chiyori!
If I'm okay with it, then I circle it.
Remember to circle mine, okay?
Heads will roll if you don't go out with me.
Onii-chan, make sure you're watching me!
All right!
I'm gonna go for the finish!
Yay!
Take that!
Chika!
Chika, are you all right!? What's happened!?
Ah! N-No, don't talk...
W-Wait...
Onii-chan, you lecher! Pervert!
I was trying to save you, so don't gimme that!
What was that?
You're pretty heavy...
This is cute, eh?
You're buying pigs again?
I can't buy them?
You can, but one is enough.
Around this time...
Onii-chan and Chiyori would be...
We bought so much! Onii-chan, are you all right?
What are you planning to do with all of these?
Eat lots and make lots of sperm so you can do it well at night!
Hey, don't say such things here!
Why? Did I say something weird?
Okay, that comes to 8,080 yen.
Are you paying in full?
Yes, I am.
I'm very sorry, but this card has been suspended.
No way...
Hey!
Why is it like this!?
Oh right, it seems we received a reminder letter last week.
Well this sucks...
Let's hurry back and tell this to Chika-chan.
No... I shouldn't do this...
Onii-chan...
What's happening to me...
The following day, I received an e-mail from Master.
He said that he was the one who withdrew from the account, because he needed money to buy some hard-to-find coffee beans.
Master...
Onii-chan, how's it look?
Right...
We only have 55,000 yen left in the cash register.
We'll have to make do with just that much.
Onii-chan, it's not much, but here, our savings.
Don't worry, I'll do something about it.
And also this...
It's a letter from Father.
Eh? What'd he say?
He said that his job's going well and our rooms are ready,
so he wants us to go to America.
The plane tickets were in the letter, too.
The café's not busy, so now's a great time for you all to go.
Onii-chan, you idiot!
How can we leave for America with the café like this!?
So what if we don't have money!
We'll be able to manage if the three of us work together!
You say that now,
but what're we gonna do about tomorrow's supplies!?
We just need to get lots of customers, right?
Leave that to us!
I'm going. Chiyori, come and help me.
Such a lively pair.
Oh, Aya-chan. Sorry about the ruckus.
Oh no, I don't mind.
Master, please let me know if there's anything I can do to help.
Thanks.
But I think I'll manage, somehow.
Café Re-Opening Day (Chika)
Let's do our best.
(Chiyori)
Ah, Onii-chan!
Welcome back, Onii-chan!
What's going on here...
You see, we...
Are you their brother? Nice to meet you.
I'm a classmate of Kousaka-san.
He's Shun-kun!
He advertised our café on the Internet for us!
Thanks for that. You've helped us a great deal.
Oh, it was nothing.
Excuse me a sec.
Chika, Chiyori. You too.
What's with your getups?
You don't know?
These are the costumes of the Wonder Café Princesses!
I know that you watch that anime every week.
But what I'm asking is, why are you dressed up like this?!
Because it's cute.
There's also one for you, Onii-chan.
Tomorrow onwards, Onii-chan will wear this.
This is the costume worn by the Cup Tea Prince when he proposes to us, the Princesses.
It's so cool, right?
I won't wear it!
Why?
How can an adult wear that embarrassing costume!?
My pride forbids it!
It'd be fun if our clothes match!
It'd be weird! How can siblings wear something like those!?
It's not weird!
Anyway, if you really like to cosplay that much,
then ask Shun-kun to wear that for you!
Shun-kun is a customer!
In any case, when I say I don't wanna, it means
I DON'T wanna wear it!!
Onii-chan, you bully!
Tyrant!
Hey!
Let's see... The only time I would ever wear those embarrassing clothes would be...
Would be!?
Never at all! Definitely never! Not even if pigs flew!
Excuse me! I'd like a menu!
I want more water!
Okay, back to work!
Sorry for waiting.
Please wait one second!
Orange juice, right? Please wait for a moment.
Sorry about the noise.
Actually, it's kind of invigorating to see it so busy.
Thanks for waiting!
Sorry for waiting!
Please come in!
Onii-chan, don't slack off! Make some coffee!
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for the food!
See ya later, Chika-chan!
Thank you very much!
Yay!
Now we just need to keep this up!
Yeah, we'll manage with this.
It's all because of Chika and I!
Onii-chan, you'd better thank us.
Yes yes, I'm grateful.
Yeah.
It's full, huh?
I'm sorry, we are completely full.
Unless you don't mind standing up with a drink...
Chika, cafés don't do that!
See you later then, Chika-chan.
Please come again!
Aya-san hasn't been coming lately...
Y-Yeah, you're right.
You're lonely cause she's not here?
No way!
I'm just worried about whether or not all the buzz is bugging her.
It's true!
Onii-chan's so cute!
You two...!
Stop playing around and start working!
Maybe it's better if we're not here, Chiyori?
Onii-chan could be holding a torch for Aya-chan.
So we'd be in his way?
Not sure...
Siblings can never be together forever.
That's so...
We're back!
Hey, welcome back.
I'm exhausted...
How could you ask your lonely sisters to buy stuff for you?
My bad. I'll make some coffee for you now.
Onii-chan, I've discussed it with Chiyori.
We want to go to America.
Uh, sure. The cafe's business is back on track anyway.
Lately, the number of customers who came for you have exceeded the amount who came for us in cosplay.
The coffee that you brew is the best!
The café's business is up and running now, so we're gonna go to America.
I want just the three of us to be together at the last day.
Promise us.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, the bath's ready!
Onii-chan, can we bathe together?
We'll help you wash your back.
We won't be able to do that after we go to America.
Hey-no, wait!
It's okay because it's our last time.
Yay!
Onii-chan, are you disappointed?
Don't be stupid!
It's big...
Stupid! Don't look at it!
Your face is red!
Onii-chan is so cute!
We had passed our time insignificantly.
It's as if we were spending our last moments together.
Chiyori. Chiyori!
We're leaving!
Oh, wait for me! I'm going too!
Chiyori, have you packed your luggage?
I packed most of them.
Oh man... I haven't even started yet.
The plane's leaving at two p.m. tomorrow, you know.
If you need anything, I'll mail it to you later.
Tonight's already the last time that we can be together...
Let's spend every second today together, okay?
Promise us.
Onii-chan, just close the shop for today!
We only have until tomorrow here!
Onii-chama~
Yeah, yeah.
I'll put up the closed sign.
Yay!
Then tonight's dinner...
...will be at a restaurant!
Closed For Today
Let's go, Onii-chan!
Wait for a sec.
It's a text from Aya-chan.
SAVE ME
CONDO
COME
SAVE ME
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
Something's happened to Aya-chan!
I'll be right back!
Wait, Onii-chan! We only have until tomorrow!
Didn't you promise to be together for tonight!?
I won't take long!
Onii-chan, do you treasure Aya-san that much?
Is she more important than Chika and I?
Chiyori...
If she's really that important, then go.
Sorry.
Chiyori...
Chika-chan, why am I crying...
Chika-chan, you're crying too.
I don't care about him anymore.
Aya-chan! Aya-chan! Are you okay!?
Aya-chan!
Aya-chan, I already called the police. They'll be here soon!
You bastard!
Master, I...
I had a boyfriend that I had dated for a while.
But then he entered a distant college and had to move away.
We were only able to meet occasionally.
I was lonely as well, but...
I think that he was lonelier than me.
He made quite a few girlfriends.
Gradually...
He stopped coming back during the holidays.
It seems that he's had sexual relationships with those girls.
After many girls, he completely changed...
He used to be such a serious and kind person.
But...  He told me, the one he could only occasionally meet, that he wanted to break up.
So...
So I...
I really wanted to know how he came to obtain those feelings.
I tried to make friends on dating sites.
But...
I still don't know what to do.
Master...
Master, you've played with many girls.
Is it fun?
Aya-chan...
Guys...
...Are just born like that.
But...
It can't be with just any ordinary girl.
Even if they have a sexual relationship,
If the couple cannot connect their hearts, then they won't be able to climax.
Humans are such that being hugged by someone and feeling their warmth can soothe them,
But if the feelings themselves don't come from the heart,
Then it's wrong.
It can't be with just anyone.
It's important to choose who you will do it with.
Master... I think I understand it now, more or less.
I feel that I can really open up to you.
Master, please hug me!
I...
...love...
...Master.
Aya-chan...
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan!
If she's really that important, then go.
I want just the three of us to be together at the last day.
Didn't you promise? Onii-chan, you idiot!
Onii-chan...
Good bye.
Take care.
Chiyori...
The departure's at 2.45 p.m...
You retard!
Yeah, I am.
I promised them we would be together for the last day.
If I just let them go,
I might not be able to meet them again.
I... I...
Chika...
Chiyori...
It's the Cup Tea Prince! It's the Cup Tea Prince!
Hey, you biker! You're speeding, please pull over immediately!
I'm sorry! Let me pass!
Chika! Chiyori!
Chika... Chiyori...
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
At that time...
It was my first time realizing...
That I'd lost something precious to me.
Welcome back!
Onii-chan, you're late!
Chika! Chiyori!
Why are you here!?
Weren't you going to America?
What happened yesterday?
What happened to you and Aya-san?
A-Aya-san had some trouble with various things...
Ooh, Onii-chan is wearing the costume of the Cup Tea Prince!
You're right!
Why?
Could it be that...
You went to the Narita airport wearing that?
Eh? Seriously!?
You're so cool!
I wanted to make it up to you since I broke our promise!
That's why I wanted to send you off while wearing the costume you like!
It was really embarrassing.
Is that so?
Since you've gone to such an extent,
we won't just leave you and run away.
This cafe won't be able to survive without us.
So if that's the case, we have no choice but to live together with Onii-chan.
But why is Chiyori's room empty, then?
That room doesn't get too much sun,
so I decided to move next to Onii-chan's room at the southern side.
So you two'll be living on either side of my room?
It's just so unfair to have only Chika living in the room beside Onii-chan!
Right?
That aside,
you broke our promise!
So as punishment, you'll have to date me!
No fair! You're going with me!
With me!
With Chiyori!
Let go!
What's this? Father's letter?
No!
Let's see...
I'm sorry.
Something happened in Father's job and he wants us to stay in Japan a while longer.
I see...
So...
Didn't you just say that without you the café wouldn't survive?
And that I'm pitiful?
And with that...
Please take care of us from now on!
Chika! Chiyori!
We're sorry!
Don't apologize! Sit down right there!
No way!
Oh no you don't! Sit down!
Sit down, now! You're not getting any sleep if you don't!
All until morning!
Sorry! Seems like I've been fooled all this time! Really, sorry!
However, the gods haven't given up on me just yet!
I've struck it rich at the casino that I bought outta desperation!
I'm gonna put some in our account - but only a little, okay?
Seems like I won't be back for awhile yet, so take care of the café for me.