Excuse me...
Miss, you didn't pay enough for the coffee.
SubDESU-H
Presents
Onii-chan, please help me with my studies.
I have a test coming up.
Sure, but don't rely too much on me.
You're hogging him, Chika-chan!
I'm not as smart as you, Chiori.
Anyway, let's get started, Onii-chan!
Hey hey! I'm working right now!
But there aren't any customers!
There's one over there, see?
I'll help you after I close the shop.
That's a promise, okay?
See you later!
Sorry for the disturbance...
No, it's fine. You three sure get along!
Well, it's more like I'm being used than getting along with them.
You're more than siblings; you're more like young lovers!
D-Do you want a refill?
Is that your treat?
Hello. How are you doing, Master?
It's been three weeks since you left to find better coffee beans.
By the way, about my step-sisters Chika and Chiori...
They're living here in one of the free rooms.
Please let them stay until I leave high school.
Once I graduate,
they're supposed to leave for America where our father lives.
It's been a few years since I met my sisters,
but it feels as if I had them all along.
I was wondering what would happen when Dad suddenly told me
to take care of them,
but it's actually going pretty smoothly!
However, since that cafe chain Tanny Texas opened over there,
customers aren't coming here as often...
But isn't it nice and peaceful here, Master?
Aya-chan...
But your coffee tastes so good...
Thank you very much!
We must value loyal customers.
Onii-chan, please go wake up Chika-chan!
Yeah, yeah.
Chika! Wake up...
Onii-chan, you saw me changing, didn't you!
I didn't. No way!
Then as punishment, you'll go on a date with me.
I really didn't see anything! I didn't see those sky blue panties.
I knew it! You did see!
If you don't go on a date with me, I'll get mad!
Go for it.
I'll climb on the roof!
Be careful.
I'll get naked!
What are you doing?!
Go on a date with me.
Shopping with Chiori!
That's unfair, Chiori!
Why would it be...
Master, since the three of us started living together,
we've begun filling out the calendar.
When they want to go out with me, they write it there.
Shopping with Chika!
Date with Chiori!
Whenever it's been decided, I circle them. But...
Please circle Chiori's!
If you don't go with me, you'll be in trouble!
Onii-chan! Make sure that you're watching me!
Okay, okay!
Here I go!
Okay!
Chika-!
Are you okay?!
What's happening?! Hey!
N-No, don't talk!
H-Hey-!
Onii-chan, you freak! Pervert!
I was just trying to save you! You're too mean.
What?!
You're quite heavy...
Isn't it cute?!
You're buying another pig?
I can't?
Um, you can, but let's just get one!
I bet that right now...
Onii-chan and Chiori are...
We sure bought a lot! Will you be okay?
What are we going to do with all of this?
You can eat a lot to get some energy for tonight!
Hey, don't say that!
Why? Did I say something weird?
The total comes to 8,080 Yen.
How many install payments?
Just one, please.
I'm terribly sorry.
It looks like your card has been declined at the moment.
What? Really?
What the hell?!
I think we got a letter about this a few days ago.
This isn't good...
Let's hurry home and tell Chika-chan!
No! I can't-!
Onii-chan-!
What's going to happen to Chika?
The next day, I got an email from Master.
I’m sorry, Shinya. I had to pay an informant for the details of the farm that grows legendary coffee beans, and I needed some money. I apologize, but please lend me some of the cafe money.
TL note: The animators failed here since with the same line is repeated twice in the second line.
It was Master who withdrew the money.
He apparently needed it for the legendary coffee beans.
Geez, Master...
Onii-chan, will we be okay?
Yeah, the only money we have is the 55,000 yen left in the cashier.
We have to get by with this.
Onii-chan, these are our savings. There isn't much, but please use it!
Hey, don't worry about it! We'll manage!
We also got mail from Dad.
What does it say?
He said that the job went well and that the house is complete,
so he said to come on over to America.
The tickets are in it, too.
The shop's like this, so this isn't a bad time for you two to go to America...
Onii-chan, you idiot!
We can't leave the shop and Onii-chan like this!
Who cares if we're low on cash!
If we work together, we can get through!
Even if you say that, what are we going to do about buying supplies tomorrow?
We just have to get a lot of customers, right?
Leave it to us!
Let’s go, Chiori. I need your help.
You guys sure are lively!
Oh Aya-chan, sorry for being so loud.
No, I don't mind!
Master, please don't hesitate to ask if you need anything.
Thanks, but I think we'll manage.
Shop re-opening!
Chika
Let's try out best!
Chiori
Ehh?!
Oh, Onii-chan!
Welcome home, Onii-chan!
What's happening?
Um, well!
Um, are you their brother?
Nice to meet you; I'm your sister's classmate.
This is Shun-kun!
Shun-kun advertised our place on the Internet for us!
Thank you.
It looks like you've helped us out immensely.
No, it's nothing.
Please excuse me.
Chika, Chiori, come with me for a moment.
What's with the get-up?
You don't know?
It's the princess costume for Wonderful Cafe!
I know that you two watch that show every week,
but I'm asking why you're dressed like that!
Because it's cute.
We've got one for you too, Onii-chan!
Tada!
Please wear this tomorrow!
This costume is from when Prince Cappuccino
confesses his love to us, the princess!
Isn't it great?
I-I won't wear that!
Why not?
An adult like me can't wear such an embarrassing costume!
My pride won't allow it!
It's more fun when we all match!
Wouldn't it be strange if we all wore such a thing?!
It's not strange!
Anyway! If you like cosplay so much,
why don't you ask Shun-kun to wear it?
Shun-kun is a customer!
Anyway! When I say I won't wear it, I really won't! {wtf raw fucking up at 10:43)
Onii-chan, you meanie!
Autocrat!
You guys-!
Well, if I was going to wear such an embarrassing costume...
If you were going to...?
I won't! I definitely won't! I won't I won't I won't!
Excuse me! Could I have the menu?
Could I get a refill?
Off to work, off to work!
Sorry to make you wait!
Yes! Please hold on!
Okay, right away!
Here you go!
Oh yes, right away!
Sorry it's so noisy...
No, it's fun with so many people!
Here you go!
Here!
Welcome!
Onii-chan, stop slacking off and make some coffee!
Sure.
Thanks for the coffee!
See you later, Chika-chan!
Thank you very much!
We did it!
If we keep doing this, we'll be fine, right?
Yeah, we will!
This is all thanks to Chiori and Chika-chan!
You better appreciate it, Onii-chan!
Yeah, yeah. I do.
Hello?
Oh? It's full?
Sorry, we're full at the moment!
Um, if you don't mind standing...
Hey Chika! They can't drink while standing!
Then we'll come later, Chika-chan.
Okay! See you later!
Aya-san hasn't come around lately...
Y-Yeah.
Are you feeling lonely without her?
D-Don't be stupid!
I was just wondering if it's a burden for her that it's so noisy now...
It's the truth!
Onii-chan, you're so cute!
You guys! Stop messing around and do your job!
Hey Chiori, doesn't Onii-chan want us here?
Eh?
Doesn't Onii-chan like Aya-san?
Ehh?!
Would we be in the way?
I wonder...
Siblings can't be together forever, can they?
That's...
We're home!
Yo, welcome back!
I'm so exhausted!
Getting your young and frail sisters to shop for you...
Sorry, I'll make some delicious coffee for you!
Onii-chan, I talked it over with Chiori.
We thought that we should go to America.
Yeah, isn't that a good idea? The shop's doing fine now.
More people are coming in for your coffee than our cosplay...
The coffee that you make is number one! So...
The cafe is in business again, so we're off to America!
On our last day, let's all be together.
Promise?
Yeah.
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, the bath's ready!
Onii-chan, can we come in too?
Eh?!
We'll wash your back, since we can't bathe together when we go to America.
Wait-! Hey!
Can we? This is the last time.
Y-Yeah...
Yay!
Onii-chan, were you expecting something different?
Like I would!
Whoa!
So big!
I-Idiot! Don't look!
Oh? You're turning red!
Onii-chan, you're so cute!
Shut-up!
The three of us played around merrily,
like we were going to miss doing it.
Chiori, Chiori!
We're leaving soon!
W-Wait!
Chiori is coming too!
Chiori, are you packed?
I've got most of it done.
Really? I haven't started at all!
We have to be there at 2 o'clock!
If you need other things, I'll send them later.
Today is the last day that we'll be together, isn't it?
Let's all stay together today, okay?
Promise?
Yeah.
Onii-chan, let's close for today!
We won't be here tomorrow, you know!
Onii-chama!
Okay, okay! Go put the closed sign out.
Yay!
Let all go out!
Let's eat at a restaurant!
Sign: Closed
Let’s go, Onii-chan!
Ok.
Hang on!
Mail from Aya-chan?
Phone text: Help me! Apartment, hurry
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
Aya-chan's in trouble!
I'll be off!
Wait, Onii-chan! We won't be here tomorrow!
You promised that we’d be together today!
I'll be right back!
Onii-chan, do you care about Aya-san that much?
Do you care about her more than Chiori and Chika-chan?
Chiori...
If you care about her that much, then go ahead!
Chiori... I'm sorry!
Chiori...
Chika-chan, why am I crying?
Eh?
You're crying too, Chika-chan...
I don't care about Onii-chan!
Aya-chan!
Aya-chan, are you okay?! Aya-chan!
Aya-chan!!
Aya-chan, I called the cops so they'll be here soon!
You bastard!
Master... There is someone I was dating...
But... He went to a far off university and he's boarding there,
so I don't see him very often...
I missed him too,
but he must have missed me more...
He had gotten some lady friends,
and he started to not come see me during breaks...
It seems that he's had physical relations with them, too...
He's probably done it a lot by now...
He was an honest and kind person...
But... He said that he wanted to break up since we were so far apart!
That's why...
That's why I wanted to know why he wanted to...
Through dating sites, I...
But... I really didn't know why!
Master, is it fun to play around with lots of girls?
Aya-chan,
some parts of men are made for that,
but it shouldn't be with just anybody.
Even if your bodies are connected,
it doesn't feel good unless your feelings are there too.
Humans feel safe when they're cuddling
and can feel each other's warmth, but...
Without true feelings, it just doesn't work.
It shouldn't be with just anyone.
Who it is is what matters.
Master, I think I understand.
I feel that I can understand if it's you, Master...
Master, please hold me!
I love you, Master...
Aya-chan...
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan!
If you care about her that much, then go ahead!
On the last day, let's all be together.
Promise? Onii-chan, you idiot!
Onii-chan...
Goodbye...
Stay well...
Chiori...
It's departing at 2:25!
Idiot!
I promised that we'd be together on the last day!
If they leave, I might not see them ever again!
I... I...!
Chika! Chiori!
It's prince Cappuccino!
You, the one riding the bike! Pull over immediately!
Sorry! Excuse me!
Sign: Boarding > third terminal
Chika! Chiori!
Chika... Chiori...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry!
For the first time in my life, I realized that I lost something precious to me.
Welcome home!
Onii-chan, you're late!
Chika?! Chiori?!
Why are you here?
Didn't you leave for America?
What happened last night?
What did you do with Aya-san?
Something terrible happened to Aya-chan, and several things happened...
Oh! You're wearing Prince Cappuccino's costume!
Whoa! No way!
Why?
Did you go to Narita Airport like that?
Ehh? No way!
Really? That's so cool!
I dressed up like this to see you two off
as some sort of apology for breaking our promise!
It was so embarrassing!
Oh really?
If you say that, then I guess we can't leave you.
You'll have a hard time running the cafe without us.
If it's like this, then it can't be helped. We'll live with you!
But why?
Your room was empty...
That room was quite dark,
so we moved to the south side beside your room!
Does that mean that I'm between you and Chika?
It wouldn't be fair if only Chika-chan got the room next to you, right?
Anyway, since you broke our promise, you'll have to date me tomorrow.
That's not fair, he's going with Chiori!
Me!
Chiori!
Geez, let go!
What's this? A letter from Dad?
Eh?! No!
What's it say?
I'm sorry!
Dad said that he was having some trouble with work,
so he said to stay in Japan for a little longer.
Oh, I see...
And you said that you're staying since I'd have a hard time running the cafe?
That you'd feel sorry for me?
So, um...
Let's get along, okay?
Chika...! Chiori!
We're sorry!
Shut it! Sit down!
No, no!
Don't say no, sit!
Sit down you two!
I won't let you sleep until you do!
No!
I won't let you sleep, then!
Sorry, it seems that I was tricked about the information before. I’m really sorry! However, the gods didn’t forsake me! I won the lottery I bought out of frustration! I’ll deposit some into the account. I won’t be back anytime soon, so please take care of the café while I’m away.