Rina, Anna-nee!
You both hold mom down.
Okay!
Got it!
Y-You can't do this, Takashi!
Stop!
You already knew about your two daughters
doing lewd stuffs with me, your son...
Yet you just stood out there to listen,
never confronting us!
And you masturbated while eavesdropping on us!
And here I thought that your daughters are indecent,
but it actually was 'coz they
got it from you, their mother!
What's with this situation?
My daughters are holding me down...
And Takashi, who I raised like he's my own son
is grasping on my tits
and relentlessly shaking his hips!
No! This smell...
I'm already...
Muttsuri Dosukebe
(Big Closet Pervert)
Russia Gibo Shimai
no
Honshitsu Minuite Sex Zanmai
(Seeing The True Hidden Sexual Nature
of My Russian Stepmother and Sisters)
Both My Older And Younger Stepsisters Are Lewd,
And That's Because My Stepmother Was A Slut
Komiya Rina
She's my younger stepsister, Komiya Rina.
She's an unruly gal.
She was taller than me when we were young.
As a result, she used to tease me a lot.
But the truth is, she's a masochist.
She's a pervert that gets intensely
aroused when she is being raped!
She was supposedly being blackmailed and raped,
but she's completely hooked in sex now.
Komiya Anna
She's my older stepsister, Komiya Anna.
She's the student council president of our school.
Maybe it's because she inherited mom's
genes that her body is well-developed.
So much that I'm having a hard time not to look at it.
That's what I thought...
She goes to a dubious club and has sex with men
every time she needs to vent out some stress.
She's actually a slut.
She's someone who indulges in orgasm
from her younger brother's cock.
What a bad honor student she is!
Komiya Yuria
She is my mother, Yuria.
My father got remarried to her.
It seems like she was a gravure idol in the past.
She dresses just like a typical housewife does,
but that doesn't fit with her voluptuous
body, making her look erotic instead.
My father has been away
from home a lot lately due to work.
So I thought that she might to be lonely...
She already knew about her two daughters
doing lewd stuffs with me, her son...
Yet she just stood out there to listen,
never confronting us.
And she masturbated while eavesdropping on us!
And here I thought that your daughters are indecent,
but it actually was 'coz they
got it from you, their mother!
No! This smell...
I'm already...
This smell...
It's been a while!
Back in my gravure idol days...
I had sex with a lot of men in the industry...
I've been smelling it every night.
That smell!
A young boy's cock...
Put it in, I'm begging you!
A cock after so long!
Even though I love sex,
that man totally didn't care about it!
You can't! If you do it that hard, I'm...
What the hell is this?!
I secured a lot of business opportunities
using this technique!
My body is getting into the groove by itself!
I'm nibbling my son's cock
inside my womb!
Not my tits!
My pussy is tightening up!
Give me your semen!
Pour a lot of your warm stuff inside me!
So warm!
And just like that, all three of them became my slaves.
It's just like I am in a porn comics.
But all of this is a result of me finding out
about the suppressed lust that these
three closet pervert women have.
That's right...
We can say that it's a win-win situation for all of us.
You even came here in the classroom
for her. You two siblings sure are close.
What's wrong, Anna? Are you not feeling well?
Anna-nee feels under the weather every so often.
I'll bring her to the infirmary
on my way back to my classroom.
Is that so? I'll leave her to you, then.
Infirmary
Your voice is too loud! They're gonna catch us!
It'll be fine for me though!
But you're the student council president, Anna-nee.
Won't you get in trouble in one way or another?
It feels so good!
My lewd moans are resonating in the infirmary!
We can't! We're totally exposed
to everyone outside!
If anyone catches us doing this,
my life will be over!
But still... But still!
Even though I'm the student council
president and have a boyfriend...
This is bad! I can't stop myself anymore!
I'm coming here at school from
being raped by my little brother's cock!
Coming! I'm coming!
Can you see me, everyone?
I'm Rina the Net Idol!
You can all fap while watching me today, okay?
Even though I'm live on stream...
A cock is penetrating me!
I'm getting watched
by everyone like this!
E-Everyone!
Rina is going to have a big orgasm!
Watch how Rina's pussy
is being rubbed!
I'm delighted with getting abused!
I'm squeezing his cock!
My lewd pussy is always ready
for ejaculations anytime and anywhere!
Please watch it being filled in with semen!
Hey, Taka-chan... Hurry up!
Onii-chan's cock!
Your cock is terrific!
Even though my daughters are here beside us...
You're slamming on my hips too much!
My womb is wrapping around your cock again!
Spurt it out!
Finish our procreative copulation!
This kind of family bonding is fine too!
Dad eventually came back from his long business trip.
However...
The slutty women in our house
couldn't hold themselves back as expected.
Even with dad being home,
we continued indulging ourselves with sex.
And we're doing it all the time once again
when dad is gone away
for yet another business trip.
Even when we're not blood-related,
we have to be intimately close as a family, right?
Happy Ending?
Happy ending?
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization