Welcome!
Anna-nee?
Taka-chan?
Complete
Clut
See their
true colors
Russian Step-Mother and Step-Sister
All you can have Sex
#1 My younger step-sister is a half-Japanese slutty blonde and my
older step-sister is a dignified, black-haired half-Japanese bitch
My name is Komiya Takashi.
I don't have that many friends and I don't have a girlfriend.
Ew, he's looking at us.
He just kinda blends in with the scenery.
But I do have something special.
And that's my family.
I'm back.
Oh, welcome home.
Welcome back, Taka-chan!
Are you hungry?
I have some snacks.
Komiya
Yuriya
Типично русское имя, ага... мужское, правда.
Или, в оригинале, это был яой?
This is my mother, Komiya Yuriya.
My father remarried to her.
Apparently she used to model when she was younger.
She wears typical housewife clothes,
but the imbalance between her bodacious body
and the subdued clothing makes it all the more erotic.
But now that Dad's been going on longer business
trips recently, she's been looking really lonely.
Komiya
Anna
Спасибо, что не Никита.
This is my older step-sister, Komiya Anna.
She's the student council president
at the school that we go to.
She has good grades and is incredibly popular.
Maybe it was due to her mother's genes,
but she developed really quickly,
maybe a little too quickly for her comfort.
Komiya
Rina
This is my little step-sister, Komiya Rina.
She's the complete opposite of her honor student
sister and leans more towards the frivolous side.
Growing up, she was always a lot bigger than I was.
And maybe because of the size difference,
she always picked on me.
I'm gonna take a bath.
I don't wanna take a bath after you, onii-chan.
Rina, you need to be nicer to your brother.
I don't care.
What am I going to do with her?
No...
Don't play with my boobs so much!
You sure you wanna talk to me like that?
You need to rethink the way you treat me
or else Dad is gonna find out what you do
in your free time and then you'll be out of here.
You closet otaku.
I know that you dress up in lewd
maid outfits and stream it online.
You don't want your friends or your family
to find out about this, do you?
These boobs are making noises.
Don't tell me there's milk in them!
They're so soft! My fingers are sinking in!
Holy crap!
Don't play with my nipple like that!
No...
This is like a dirty manga where he blackmails
me and does things to me against my will, but...
My boobs are getting hot and
my nipples are getting hard!
How long... are you gonna keep groping them?!
Hey, come on. Let me enjoy this more.
That's not what I mean.
I'm willing to...
use my mouth.
This is a guy's dick?
It's pulsating so hard.
It's so hot! It's as if it's an animal, separate from him.
It's a little salty and has a dirty flavor to it.
No matter how much I lick away the juices coming
out from the tip they just keep coming out!
So warm!
So this is a mouth-pussy?
Shit, this is amazing.
Your slimy saliva's clinging to my dick!
And more importantly, my dick is inside
my little sister's mouth-pussy right now!
You're taking it so far in that I
can't even see my dick anymore!
No way! He actually forced it all the way inside my mouth!
It feels so good when I pull you off of it!
Shit! I can't stop!
Just because I can't say anything with a dick in my mouth
doesn't mean you can say whatever you want!
I really hate you, but...
Every time he forces it down the back
of my throat, my head just goes blank!
What is this?!
My head's spinning!
Did I just cum?!
I came with just his dick in my mouth?!
So good!
His dick's gotten so hard!
Is he going to cum in my mouth?!
Is my stupid brother going to shoot
his cum out in my mouth?!
Rina!
Your punishment's not over yet.
Is onii-chan's dick really going to come inside me?!
My first time is going to be with onii-chan?!
Rina, you're so wet and warm inside!
I love it!
Don't... move!
I can tell that his dick is moving inside me so tightly!
He blackmailed me and is doing
this to me against my will, but...
No, my boobs!
No! Seriously, no!
I'm cumming! You're gonna make me cum!
No! My insides!
Anna-sama!
The person next to Anna-sama is her boyfriend, right?
They look so good together,
this could make a beautiful painting!
Anna-sama!
Please forgive us!
Pachinko
Karaoke
Komiya Anna
Welcome!
Anna-nee?
Taka-chan?
So doing dirty things with strangers
is a hobby of yours, huh?
Taka-chan, why are you...
I've been worried about how you've been coming
home late recently, so I looked around for you.
I was worried that you and your boyfriend
might be up to some bad stuff.
I act like an honor student at home and at school,
so I have no place to blow off steam!
That's why...
Let me do you.
If you have sex with anyone,
then you can have sex with me, can't you?
But Taka-chan, you're my little brother...
Then would you rather if other
people found out about this?
Everyone's watching.
You sure you're okay having
sex out in the hall like this?
Yeah. This is normal here.
Your dick's so hard, Taka-chan.
It digs against me every time I move. It feels so good!
Having sex with Taka-chan... my little brother... is bad, but...
The more I think about it, the more my pussy gets excited!
His pre-cum is mixing with my juices
and it's becoming a wet mess!
It's so dirty!
Wow, that's a lot of noise!
Yeah, and that moaning!
Sounds like some kind of animal!
They're watching! They're all watching!
They're all watching me get off on my little brother's dick!
Oh my god, it's so intense!
No! If you're that rough, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum! I'm really gonna cum!
My womb's being rammed
against over and over by your dick!
I... I'm gonna...
And this is where our new
secret sibling relationship began.
We're a twisted family.
But that's exactly what I've always wanted.
Why are you up so early?
Morning wood won't go down.
Can you do something about it? lol
Morning... what? lol
A slutty older sister like you has to know what I'm
talking about. Come over and take care of it already.
Fine
And here's Anna-nee's "Good Morning fellatio".
And then school sex with Rina.
No! I can't resist onii-chan's dick like this!
I might have been blackmailed and
he forced himself onto me, but I actually...
So you were doing this kind
of stuff with Rina-chan too, huh?
I kinda already had a hunch that you were.
I'm gonna...
Me too!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum so much!
The three of us are feeling good together!
We're such a close family!
Let's all cum together!
The three of us together!
Onee-chan!
Not... My boobs!
This isn't good!
My mind's going blank!
I'm cumming again! I'm cumming!
Takashi?
So you knew all along, Mom?
You knew, but you didn't even try to stop us.
Instead you just masturbated to us.
Get over here!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч