Rina, Anna-nee, hold Mom down, okay?
Okay.
You got it.
S-Stop, Takashi!
Stop this instant!
You knew that both your daughters
were doing dirty things with your son,
but you didn't even try to put your guard up.
And instead you used us as fap material.
I thought your daughters were dirty, but you're even worse!
What am I watching...
My daughters are holding me down...
And the child I raised as if he were my own, Takashi,
is vigorously thrusting his hips,
penetrating through my breasts.
No... this smell...
I...
Complete Slut
See their true colors
Russian Step Mother and Step-Sisters
All you can have Sex
#2 The reason my step-sisters are
so lewd is because step-mother is a complete slut
Komiya
Rina
This is my little step sister, Komiya Rina.
She's trendy and frivolous.
Growing up, she was always a lot bigger than I was.
And maybe because of the size difference,
she always picked on me.
But in reality,
she's a complete masochist and a real pervert
who gets turned on from people forcing themselves onto her.
The rape was supposed to be a way of blackmailing her,
but she's completely addicted to having sex now.
Komiya
Anna
This is my older step sister, Komiya Anna.
She's the student council president
at the school that we go to.
Maybe it was due to her mother's genes,
but she developed really quickly,
maybe a little too quickly for her comfort.
But she frequented a club where she could
have sex with guys as much as she wanted.
She wasn't an honor student, but a complete slut.
After all, you can't really call someone an honor student
if they can't stop cumming from their little brother's dick.
Komiya
Yuriya
This is my mother, Komiya Yuriya.
My father remarried to her.
Apparently she used to model when she was younger.
She wears typical housewife clothes,
but the imbalance between her bodacious body
and the subdued clothing makes it all the more erotic.
But now that Dad's been going on longer business
trips recently, she's been looking really lonely.
Even after finding out that her daughters
were doing dirty things with me,
she didn't even try to distance herself.
Instead, she used it as an opportunity to masturbate.
I thought your daughters were dirty, but you're even worse!
No... this smell...
I... can't...
I haven't smelled this in so long.
When I was still a model...
I had so much sex with people in that industry.
I smelled it every day... It was this smell!
Put your young dick inside me... Please...
I haven't had a dick in so long!
Even though I love having sex,
he would never do it with me.
Oh my god, you're doing me so hard!
What... is this?!
I worked my way up the ladder with this technique!
My body's getting so excited! It's...
I'm squeezing on my son's dick with my pussy!
No, not my boobs!
My pussy's getting so tight!
Give me your semen!
Pour lots of your hot stuff inside me!
And just like that, the three of them became my slaves.
It was like I was in some porno.
But this was just the result of breaking through
the exterior of these completely slutty girls.
Yeah, you could call this a win-win.
Wow, you even come to class together?
You all must be really close.
What's the matter, Anna?
Not feeling well?
Yeah, she's not always in the best of health.
I'll take her to the nurse's office on the way back to class.
Really? Thanks.
Nurse's office
You're being way too loud!
We're gonna be found out!
I don't really care though.
But since you're the student council president,
I can't imagine it'd be good for you.
It feels really good!
The dirty sounds are echoing across the walls!
No... They can see us!
If they find out what we're doing...
My life will be over!
I know that but... But I...
I'm the President and I even have a boyfriend,
but I... I can't stop!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum in school
from my little brother's dick!
I'm cumming!
Can you all get a good look?
I'm the internet idol, Rina!
Watch me and fap all you want, okay?
I'm being filmed while I have a dick inside me!
Everyone can see me like this...
I...
I'm gonna cum so hard!
Watch me as I cum from being fucked by this dick!
I'm just happily taking in this dick even though
I'm being put through so much embarrassment.
So please watch as this...
This dirty pussy that can take cum in whenever
and wherever... is pumped full of semen!
Please watch!
Hey, Taka-chan, hurry...
Onii-chan's dick... His dick... It's so good!
My daughters are right next to me,
but I'm getting fucked so hard!
My womb's gonna wrap around your dick again!
Cum! Plant your seed inside me!
This kind of family relationship isn't so bad...
Dad came back from his business trip.
But...
There was no way that the slutty women
of this house could hold back.
We had sex all the time in the house
even though he was right there.
And even after Dad left on another
business trip we just kept having sex.
Even if we're not connected by blood,
family members need to be close to one another, right?
Happy ending?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч