l took it.
lt smells like Jun-kun.
Oops, l was so into Jun-kun's smell, l almost suffocated.
l'm so glad l took this.
This is making me want to do it.
Jun-kun's smell is so good...
Just smelling Jun-kun's scent is making me wet.
lt feels so good.
l'm going to scream!
My finger is inside me...
Doing it while smelling Jun-kun's scent, makes me feel like Jun-kun is playing with me.
lt's amazing.
l'm going to pee.
No! No! No!
l'm so bad.
What are you looking at?
Oh, nothing.
Does it taste good?
Yes, it does.
Did Ms. Keiko make it again today?
l made everything other than the pork and the eggs.
l see.
What do you mean by that?
lsn't the cabbage shredded nicely?
l think there's something there but...
...he seems out of reach.
l wonder why.
Mom's late.
lt's pouring out, l hope she's okay.
Okay, okay, you don't have to keep ringing the bell.
Jun-kun.
J-Jun-kun?
The bath's ready. You want to take a shower?
l mean, l'd like you to get in but...
l don't mean anything by it but...
You're chilled to the bone, if you don't warm up, you'll catch cold.
No thanks.
Okay. l know...
l'm being overbearing...
lt's not that.
l don't deserve such kindness.
That's not true.
l mean l just don't want you to catch cold.
Thanks.
Mom's awfully late, isn't she?
Ms. Keiko's not coming back.
Huh?
l don't think Ms. Keiko's coming back.
What do you mean?
Sae and Jun-kun...
l hope you will forgive my sudden disappearance.
l have come to realize that l don't deserve to be in your lives.
l'm sorry.
Especially you, Sae, l don't think you will ever be able to forgive me.
So, goodbye...
Why are you bringing me this letter from my mom?
Um...
l have lots of questions...
Why so suddenly? What caused this?
But most of all, why did you bring me this letter?
Why?
Um, calm down and listen.
l didn't mean to hide it from you or anything.
l thought once things calmed down...
....like after l graduated...
What are you trying to say? Just say it!
Nothing can be worse than Mom leaving.
l'm seeing Ms. Keiko.
What are you talking about?
This is no time for jokes.
l'm not kidding.
At least that's what l thought...
But...
What?
You and Mom? That's sick...
lt's none of your business.
Yes it is!
She's my mother!
l know but...
How many years apart do you think you are?
Age doesn't matter!
l love Ms. Keiko.
lt's not about age, she's my mother, and this is sick!
But l still love her.
l know she's your mother, but l still love her.
But why did she leave?
Well...
She did seem happy lately...
l thought something good happened.
l wonder if it was because of you.
But if that were true, why would she leave?
Well...
And if you were really going out with her...
...why would she leave without talking to you?
There's something you're not telling me.
Stop hiding it and tell me, she's my mother!
But...
Ms. Keiko, your boobs are leaking so much.
lt must mean that you feel good.
lt must mean that you accept my feelings.
Jun-kun...
No...
l'm a teacher...
...and l'm old enough to be your mother.
l don't care about that.
l see you as a woman, that's all.
And don't say you're old.
That makes me sound like a freak.
No, no, no, no, no.
lf you do that, my boobs are going to squirt!
lt's sweet.
lt tastes like you.
Ms. Keiko, l'm suffocating a bit.
Can you help me?
No, l can't do that.
Because...
Fine then.
Using my hand soaked in your milk to jack off is like having you jack me off.
l'm about to come.
Wait.
Why?
Because...
You want a taste of it, don't you?
Go ahead.
Ms. Keiko's boobs are sandwiching my...
Jun-kun, you seem different now, cute...
Ms. Keiko, l'm going to come!
Jun-kun, please come...
Go ahead...
Jun-kun, that's too much.
You naughty boy.
l'm sorry.
Let's have you clean this up.
Go on, lick it off.
He was watching me the entire class.
l must be getting off on his gaze.
There's no other reason why my boobs would leak like this.
ls it because of yesterday?
l gave into him in the heat of the moment...
But...
Ms. Keiko!
This means you feel the same way as me, right!
Your sweat, your milk, your skin...
lt feels so good.
No...
Jun-kun, not here.
What if someone comes in?
No, no, no, no, no!
lt's going to come out!
Jun-kun, you're like a baby sucking on my boobs.
lt's nice to be able to suck on your tits, but...
...if l'm a baby, l can't be your lover, so l will not be your baby.
Jun-kun...
Maybe it's unfair for me to say this...
....after what happened yesterday...
...but l really like you.
Don't be silly.
l'm an old woman.
Besides, l'm your classmate's mother.
l don't dislike you...
...at all.
Then...
No, it can't be.
Don't make that face.
l may not be your lover, but l am your teacher.
l am a teacher who has your best interest at heart.
l think that l can do all kinds of things for you...
...in your mom's place with after school activities.
Yes.
Jun-kun, wait.
Yes?
Don't skip out on club this afternoon.
lt's my time together with my favorite teacher, l'm not going to miss it.
Oh, Jun-kun.
l'll see you after school.
So... why would she have to go away?
lt's very unpleasant and very grotesque...
...but there's no reason for her to leave.
Well...
There's a reason!
There's a reason why my mom had to leave.
Tell me!
l think it's because of today.
lt's already 6 o'clock.
l have to get dinner ready.
What a drag.
l guess a cup-o-ramen will do.
But that's a pain too.
Did l hustle too much with Ms. Keiko?
Who's that?
Coming!
l came.
Ms. Keiko!
Don't be so surprised.
l told you l could be a stand-in for your mom too.
Did you think it was an empty promise?
No, not at all, but...
l didn't think you'd...
ls it a problem?
Not at all...
l mean, l'm really glad...
lt makes me happy to hear that.
Jun-kun, you always eat pastries for lunch...
...and l figured your dinner is instant ramen...
l knew it.
l'm going to make you chirashi sushi loaded with vegetables.
Jun-kun, it's almost done!
Jun-kun, it's going to take a little longer, l wish you'd sit and wait.
Ms. Keiko, l take it by coming to my house that you accept my feelings?
Wait, Jun-kun, no...
l asked you not to do this.
l can't have you do this.
But we're alone.
That's not why l came.
Usually, when you go to a guy's house knowing you'll be alone...
...this is the motive.
lt wasn't like that.
You always say that!
''That's not what l meant'', or ''l'm too old for you!''
But...
You say that but you let me part of the way in, then you push me away...
No, Jun-kun, please understand...
lt's like you enjoy toying with me.
We get close and you pull away, l pull away and you pursue me.
Ms. Keiko.
Stop, Jun-kun.
l don't mean to do that.
You're saying that to confuse me more.
l'm going to carve my mark in you so you don't leave...
...so you don't go far, far away.
Ms. Keiko is sucking my...
Ms. Keiko...
l'm going to come!
Jun-kun, this is enough for today.
No.
l can't bear it anymore.
You want to do it too, don't you?
l...
Look at how much your boobs are leaking!
This must mean that...
But you and l are student and teacher.
And Sae...
Who cares about that.
You may have lots of other things, but all l have is you.
Jun-kun, no, stop...
lf you do that, there's no turning back.
No turning back?
Great...
That's what l'm after.
No, stop!
You say all kinds of things, but l think you feel the same way l do.
Why?
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
Why? Why!
You love me too, don't you?
You've done so much for me, and you let me in...
And we're here...
l should be so happy, but why do l feel so empty?
You poor child.
Doesn't it feel good to kiss?
Now move.
Yes.
Press into me.
Please, more...
l love this!
Jun-kun! Jun-kun! Jun-kun!
Everytime you move it rubs my boobs, and it feels good!
So good!
You're so wet it feels good.
Jun-kun, l'm embarrassed, don't say anything.
You feel good too, right?
Right?
Don't say things like that.
l'm going to come...
Boobs, my boobs...
l'm going to come!
l'm going to come, too. l want to come inside you!
Ms. Keiko, can l?
Jun-kun, what a naughty boy you are.
l'm coming! l'm coming!
Jun-kun, Sae's classmate, is going to come inside me and make me come!
Ms. Keiko?
To Jun-kun and Sae
Ms. Keiko...
So you forced yourself on her and she let you.
So she took off because she was so ashamed.
That's what happened, isn't it?
Anyone you tell is going to think that.
Don't just sit there!
l guess it can't be helped.
Thief.
l called you a thief!
Nagumo, that's not what l intended.
You took my one and only family from me.
And now you say you didn't intend to?
And Mom's the worst.
Please don't blame Ms. Keiko, it's all my fault.
Don't call my mother by her first name!
Nagumo...
lt's true.
Mom knew that l liked you.
And she betrayed me.
She had an affair with you!
And she was laughing at me the whole time l was dreaming about you.
Nagumo, you...
Why should you have noticed?
You were a boy in love, too, consumed with your own feelings.
And she was my mother!
You both betrayed me!
You stomped all over me!
Nagumo, l'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
You stomped all over my feelings and stole my family!
l'm not so desperate that l need you to comfort me!
You said you would do anything, did you mean it?
Yes.
Anything?
Fine.
Then become my family.
What...
Then do what people normally do to become family, and become my family.
Nagumo...
No, call me Sae.
We're going to be family.
lf that's what you want, Sae.
Then first....
First, lick my feet.
Like a lover would...
Make sure you lick between the toes too.
That's good.
More...