Sae, you don't have to do that.
l'm getting better, aren't l?
We've been doing it every day for a month.
No, l'm going to come!
lt's okay, l can swallow it.
How?.
What?
How can you do that?
Jun-kun, are you serious?
l mean...
Girls can do anything for the guy they love.
Even something like that.
lt makes me think that l am being marked by you...
...that l am yours.
You can do it again, can't you?
Jun-kun, you're inside of me.
When we're pressed together like this, it feels like we're one.
lt feels so good.
l want to stay like this forever, but l want to move.
At first it hurt.
But lately...
lt's rubbing...
My pussy's getting rubbed.
l want to rub it more.
No! Wait!
lf you do that...
Don't do that!
No, don't stop!
What do l want?
lt's so deep!
Jun-kun's...
Jun-kun, l love you!
l love this.
Play with my boobs!
Look how big they got for you!
My boobs!
No!
My boobs... feel so good!
lt's so good!
lt feels so good.
My nipples are erect.
Jun-kun, together...
l don't want to be the only one feeling so good...
l'm going to come!
l want to come together...
Jun-kun!
Jun-kun! Jun-kun!
l'm coming! My belly is hot!
l'm going to...
Me too! Me too!
Again, please...
Your penis! l love your penis!
Jun-kun! lt's so good!
l'm so happy!
l'm happy!
Jun-kun, kiss me!
lt feels so good! lt's so good!
Don't pull out.
lnside, come inside this time!
Deeper! Deeper!
Jun-kun is inside of me!
Sae, l'm going to come!
Come inside, l...
You're going to make me come!
l want to have your baby!
Come lots!
Wow, look how much you came.
lt's gushing out of me.
l could do this with you forever.
l can keep coming and coming.
lt sounds silly, but it's true.
You're up.
Want to have breakfast?
Sure, l guess.
This is like...
...we're newlyweds.
Jun-kun! You don't have anything on!
Why are you embarrassed?
But it's different when we're in bed.
So we'll have dinner at my house tonight.
Sure...
But...
What is it?
Why keep going back and forth?
Nope.
lf you're away from home for more than one day, it's unsettling.
Besides, it's not such a big deal.
ls that how it is?
Yep, that's right.
We should split up now.
Why can't we go to school together?
You don't get it.
There's a certain freshness this way.
l'll see you there.
ls this how you want it to be, Ms. Keiko?
ls that true?
lt is!
Nagumo.
lgarashi, you've been eating sandwiches lately...
l made some extra lunch today, so please, have some.
Sae, you go!
You're so aggressive!
ls this why your cooking has gotten better?
No, that's not why.
l'm getting better because Mom's been gone a month, taking care of Grandma...
...so l have to cook for myself.
Being modest?
Nagumo-san, is Ms. Nagumo still not back?
My grandmother isn't doing well, she's getting very old.
l see, it's just that she's been gone so long...
Could you please talk to Ms. Nagumo about it?
Okay?
Bitch!
You were watching.
l wish you had said something, then l wouldn't have done that.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's go shopping for dinner and go home.
Jun-kun, what do you want to eat tonight?
Jun-kun?
Sae, can't you get in touch with Ms. Keiko?
You know that we can't keep playing house like this.
When Ms. Keiko comes back, l don't know what will...
...happen between the three of us...
But l do know that we can't be doing this.
Sae.
l don't agree.
Let's go.
Sae, stop it.
We're at school!
Competition swimsuits fit really tight.
You feel absolutely everything.
So l get really horny after practice.
l've played with myself in here while thinking of you.
You got horny seeing me like this, l'm so happy!
Sae stop...
l'm going to...
No.
lt feels good to me, too, to do you with my mouth.
l can't...
Come!
l'm covered with your stuff.
Oh yeah, l haven't done this for you yet...
Make it all wet like this.
Your thing is so cute.
Sae...
Stop.
l am going to come...
lf l do...
Go ahead...
Will you like me more if you come?
Your thing is getting bigger in my boobs!
l'm coming!
My pussy is getting all wet from your thing.
l want to put it all the way in.
l bet if you put it in all the way, l'll explode.
Oh no...
My womb wants to come real bad.
l...l...
So hot...
lt's too good!
l'm going to come!
Jun-kun...
No, no, no, no!
lf you do that, l'm going to come again!
l'm going to come!
l like your penis so much it's making me crazy!
My answer to your question...
You don't have to think that way.
l want to take care of you...
Not now!
Not now...
Jun-kun! Jun-kun! Jun-kun!
You'll come over tonight, right?
What am l doing?
l have to do what she wants.
That's what l have to do.
l hurt Ms. Keiko and l hurt Sae.
l tore them apart, and l have to atone for that.
l keep thinking that Ms. Keiko will come back soon.
And then we can be together again.
But there's no way!
Neither Sae nor Ms. Keiko will be the way they used to be.
l am the worst.
9 o'clock.
Sae...
Hello, Nagumo here.
Jun-kun? Why are you there?
Ms. Keiko...
lt's you, isn't it?
Jun-kun...
Why? But...
Keiko, l don't want to be apart anymore.
Just for now, just for now.
No, no...
lf you suck my breasts...
You know how l get when you suck my breasts, don't you?
l'm going to come...
My milk is going to come out.
My milk is going to squirt all over you like a dog in heat!
Ms. Keiko, your milk is the best aphrodisiac.
l just have to rub it onto my dick like this...
My pre-ejaculate is coming out.
We both squirted like two abstinent teenagers.
Wait, just stay like this for a while.
lf that's what you want.
l can't believe we've only been together once...
And?
...but our bodies fit so well together.
Keiko...
l wonder if l'm a nymphomaniac.
l'd love it if you were.
Because it means you want me that much.
You've been calling me Keiko this whole time.
Does it bother you?
l'm sorry.
lt makes me happy.
l am the happiest older woman in the world.
Keiko! Keiko! Keiko!
Jun-kun! Jun-kun! Jun-kun!
Sae...
l'm sorry about last night.
You stayed up all night waiting for me, huh?
Uh, yeah...
l wasn't myself yesterday.
l wasn't myself.
l didn't believe you anymore.
But l thought about it all last night.
And l realized that you do care about me.
Was it a dream?
The feel, the taste, the smell of Keiko...
Was it all a dream?
Jun-kun?
Uh, yeah?
l thought about it all night and l decided.
Jun-kun, let's go to the police together.
Sure.
Okay.
l'll get breakfast ready then.
Ms. Keiko...