www.SubDESU-H.net
Nobu...
Daddy!
From today,
my boy...
This is your new family.
That day I got myself
a sister.
W
Imouto
“Little Devil with
an A-Cup”.
Part 1: 「I hate you, you stupid brother”?!」
Onii!
Don't use my slippers without permission!
Miyu.
You’re gonna give me your athlete's foot so don't wear it!
I don't have athlete's foot!
Then I'm going to get your brother-germs, so don't come close to me!
What do you mean by my "brother germs"?!
Don't make that face!
Miyu-chan!
Don't fight with your brother first thing in the morning.
Yo...You’ve got it wrong! I’m just lovingly teasing him.
I love Onii!
And you love me too, right?
Onii!
There was a delivery.
Onii?
Bust cream, cleavage enhancing pads and a breast pump...
Onii-chan!
Oh... Miyu...
What do you think this is?
It was sent in my name,
but I don't remember buying this kind of stuff.
Did I accidentally click on the wrong thing?
That's... mine.
Eh... Umm...
W-What?
Don't worry about them, they will start getting bigger from now on.
Y-You're the worst! This is sexual harassment!
Idiot brother! Retard-brother!
A-And I prefer them smaller – they’re cute.
Why you, Why you, Why you...
W-What?
Why you, Why you...
Why you... Why you...
Miyu, stop now!
Ouch...
Jeez! You stupid brother!
Sorry.
Pervert! Idiot! Horn dog!
Hurry up and get away!
I'm going to tell mom that you sexually assaulted me!
What am I doing?
Miyu is my sister!
No!
Don't look!
Don't!
No!
Miyu, you're so cute.
Onii...
You’re scaring me...
I'm sorry! It's all my fault!
Please forgive me!
I-It's okay...
I was also at fault.
I won’t tell mom...
So...
I understand.
In return I'll buy you anything you want.
Don't worry, they'll start getting bigger from now on.
And I prefer them smaller – they’re cute.
Empty compliments, all of them!
But...
He said I was cute for real earlier.
I wonder if they will get bigger if I stimulate them?
The thing that was pushing against me earlier...
It was a dick, right?
So it’s that big...
Will something that big really go in here?
I'm eventually gonna lose my virginity.
Today Onii was a bit scary...
But...
When I resisted he stopped, and...
He called me cute...
Oh no...
I've only been thinking about Onii...
Anime
Games Shop
I told her I would buy her anything, but...
Cosplay Costume Shop, specializing in fetishes for boys.
X CHANGE
Onii-chan!
Don't break your promise!
Why is it a cosplay shop?
Especially a female clothing store...
What kind of punishment is this?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Are you aware of how to put the undergarments on?
Huh?!
For beginners I would recommend this stick-on one.
No... um...
It's really easy to use!
No, really. I'm fine.
Then I'll throw this in too.
I'll show you how to put in on the changing room over there.
This release was done by SubDESU-H, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Um, I said don't worry about it...
Onii!
Miyu!
What’s taking you so long! I'm tired of waiting!
S...Sorry.
Onii-chan is mine!
Y-You! T-T-T-That was my first kiss!
M...Me too, that was my first kiss too!
Miyu...
I’m so flat that it probably won’t be much fun to touch me.
They suit you well, Miyu, they’re cute.
My nipples are tingling!
I have to lead her like a man...
Ouch!
L-Let’s just stop!
It hurts so much! No!
Miyu...
I'm sorry.
I'll take it out now!
Don't!
Miyu?
Don't take it out!
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Really?
Yes.
M-My insides… are… tingling!
Onii-chan, it feels good!
Miyu!
I'm about to cum!
Cum...
Cum inside!
I can't do that!
Hey, Miyu!
I...I want it...
Onii-chan!
I-It’s a safe day today.
It's sticking to my womb!
It feels so good!
Onii-chan!
I love you!
Me too.
www.SubDESU-H.net