www.SubDESU-H.net
There, there.
Hey, Miu!
Onii-chan!
Here, you forgot something.
T-Thank you.
Thank Mom as well.
She made that for you.
I know that!
Hurry up and go away already.
I feel sorry for your brother.
Miu, you shouldn't be so harsh on your brother.
I agree.
I'm so envious that you have such a great brother.
Is that so? I just feel he is nosy.
Miu, that's too cold.
I feel like healing your brother's wounded heart.
That's a good idea.
So how would you do it?
Of-course, by doing those kind of things...
That won't happen...
Because Onii-chan is for me only.
W
Imouto
“Little Devil with
an A-Cup”.
Last Volume
「I'm all over My Big Brother」
Are you regretting what we did that time, Onii-chan?
There's no way I'd regret something that pleasurable.
But nothing ever happened after that.
Your attitude was quite cold towards me.
So I thought you were regretful about it.
I was just feeling shy.
W-Was that so?
Then, can we do it here?
Crap, she'll get mad at me.
Okay...
Mi-Miu...!
N-No one will come here, right?
It's okay.
Onii-chan!
It feels good!
Does it hurt?
I wanted to do this again with you, Onii-chan.
That's why I was thinking of you while doing it.
Doing what?
Masturbating.
M-Miu!?
What's wrong?
Nothing. I thought I heard Miu's voice.
Wasn't it your imagination?
It was like a scream or something.
We will be exposed. Don't be so aggressive!
Oh no, I can't stop my voice from coming out!
I guess it was just my imagination.
Let's go back to the classroom already.
Okay then.
There's that weird smell, too.
Let's head back quickly.
Okay.
I wonder what that smell was...
Thank goodness.
If someone found out that we siblings were having sex here, we'd be expelled.
My lower body is going numb. Help me!
It’s wrapping me up inside. I'm about to explode!
Let it all out, Onii-chan.
It's hitting my womb harder and harder.
I'm cumming!
Are you okay?
Sorry. You're just so cute, so I just went overboard.
Onii-chan, I love you.
Done!
This is amazing.
Is this me?
You’re really beautiful, Onee-sama.
Hey, hey, Onee-sama.
Let's go and watch a movie.
Oh, okay then.
Then I'm going to get changed.
Huh?
But I just finished touching you up,
so let's go with you wearing that.
I can’t go out wearing this.
I really wanted an older sister.
It can't be helped, I guess. Let's go then.
Yay, I did it!
That was really fun.
Let's go out again sometime.
Am I going to wear this again?
But it looks so lovely!
You're cute too, Miu.
I get embarrassed when you say that so suddenly.
Did you know that there's a new cake shop over there?
Seriously!?
Oh, that's nice. Let's go!
Miu...
Shall we go home then?
Yeah, I want to be alone with you as soon as possible.
I didn't know a kiss would feel this good.
My breasts feel tingly.
Onii-chan, my breasts feel weird.
Don't tease it so much like that.
I'll go crazy again.
But you're so cute. I can't stop.
No, don't touch those weird areas.
You start to twitch whenever I move.
It's so cute.
I hate that teasing of yours.
Sorry, I'll be sure to do a lot of things that you'll like.
It's deep.
My womb might get crushed!
It's coming in.
Is it okay to do it from the back?
I can't see your face that way, so no.
No matter what, it's a no?
No, you’re going to play with my butt-hole again.
You can’t just say no every time.
Say "Please have sex with me from behind".
No, I don't want to.
If you don't want to,
then I guess it leaves me no choice.
No way, don't leave!
I can't do things that you don't want to do.
O-Onii-chan, do it.
Please, do anything to me that will make you feel good.
As I thought, this is scary.
Shall we stop?
No. Tie me up using those, so I can't escape.
With this, we can do whatever you like, right?
Miu, how cute you really are.
I'll do it here this time.
No... It feels kinda gross.
Stop it, Onii-chan!
It's okay. It will feel better soon.
It hurts!
No!
I don't want this!
Sorry, I'll pull it out.
Don't pull it out!
Are you sure?
Please continue with it.
It hurts, but it feels good.
It feels good... I might cum.
I'll cum!
Inside...
Release it inside!
I'll die!
I wonder why it feels so good...
Maybe it's because I'm doing it with Onii-chan.
Are you alright?
My kind brother, who's always there for me.
I love you very much.
Japanese Dictionary
Ah, there it is!
Onii-chan...
So he's been treasuring this picture of us.
I love you, Onii-chan.
Maybe I should stop using those breast pads.
He says I'm cute just the way I am anyway.
It smells like Onii-chan.
A book?
What could he be reading?
That liar.
Why did you just throw away my book without asking?
And what kind of book was that?
Was that book so important to you?
Hey, give that back!
Answer me properly!
I hate you, Onii-chan!
You don't understand my feelings at all!
What the hell?
Sorry for her being such a handful.
But Miu-chan actually likes you.
I wonder...
I was mad because she just threw away my things without even asking.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I don’t understand what she's thinking.
You like Miu-chan, right?
She just wants you to spoil her.
Spoil?
Yes. If it's someone she not close with, she'll be straight and courteous.
But what was going though her head...?
She must be jealous of the gravure idols.
That's kind of cute.
How did you know I was here?
I asked Mom.
Do you like big breasts?
Yeah, I like them.
But regardless of your breast size,
I love you, Miu.
You're much cuter than any gravure idol.
So you're that deeply into me!
Yeah, that's right.
It’s Onii-chan's scent.
Isn't that the deodorant spray?
I don't care about that.
You're mine regardless.
When you feel like masturbating,
call me so we can have sex instead.
Getting angry, but sometimes getting spoiled.
She's an emotional mix of sorts, but...
I like her exactly the way she is.
Ah, that's right.
I still have to write my name on your cock.
Woah, stop that!
Just joking!
But you really are the scary kind of person who might do it for real.
What was that for?
www.SubDESU-H.net
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You’re early today.
I wanted to be with you as soon as possible.
So you wore that?
I feel like you own me while wearing this, so I like it.
I'm also naked here.
You're such a pervert.
I'm just going along with your weird tastes.
I see. You're really a masochist type, aren’t you?
Not at all.
I'm the devilish pet that's all over her big brother.
www.SubDESU-H.net