There, there.
Eh?
}
Miu, Hey!
Bro?!
Here, you forgot this.
T-thank you.
You'll need to thank mom too,
since she made that specifically for you.
I know that!
Hurry up and go away!
I feel sorry for your brother.
Miu, you shouldn't talk like that to him.
I think so too.
If anything, I'm envious that you have such a cool brother.
You really think so?
He just likes to meddle.
Miu, you're being too cold.
I'm starting to think I want to heal your brother's wounded heart.
What a great idea.
So, how would you go about it?
Obviously, by doing this and that...
You devilish ero-witch..
That's not gonna happen.
Because brother is mine!
My little sister
Little Devil with A-cup
Episode 1: I'm crazy about my brother.
Do you regret what we did, brother?
There's no way I'd regret something that made me so happy.
But you've done nothing ever since.
Your attitude's been rather cold towards me,
so I thought perhaps you were regretting it...
That was just me being shy!
R-really?
Well then, can we do it here?
Eh?!
Oh crap, she's gonna get mad.
It's okay.
Huh?!
Mi-Miu!
Y-you're sure nobody's gonna come here, right?
It's fine.
Brother!
It feels so good!
Does it hurt?
I wanted to do this with you again, brother.
That's why I did it while thinking of you.
Did what?
Masturbation...
Mi-miu?!
What's wrong?
Well, I thought I heard Miu's voice...
Probably your imaginations, I think?
It seemed like a scream, somehow.
They're gonna find us, don't do it any harder!
Oh crap, I can't keep my voice down.
I guess it really was me imagining things.
Let's go back to the classroom then.
Yep.
I can smell something really weird here for a while too.
Let's head back quickly.
Yeah...
I wonder what that smell is...
Thank goodness.
If someone really did find out we siblings were doing it here, we'd be expelled for sure.
I'm going numb, help me!
So tight! I'm almost there.
Let it all out, brother!
It's hitting my womb so repeatedly!
I'm gonna cum!
Are you alright?
Sorry...
You're just too cute Miu, it drove me insane.
Brother, I love you.
It's done!
This is amazing!
This is supposed to be me?
You're so pretty, sis!
Hey, sis, wanna hear something?
Let's go watch a movie.
Ah, right.
Then, I'm gonna get changed.
Eh?!
I went through the effort of dressing you up and all, let's just go like that.
There's no way I can go out wearing something like this.
The truth is, I really wanted an older sister.
I guess it can't be helped. Shall we go then?
Yay, you agreed!
That was fun,
we should come again sometime.
You intend to make me wear this again?
Eh? It looks really nice though.
You look cute too, Miu.
I'm gonna get embarrassed if you say that so suddenly.
Hey, did you hear? A new cake shop opened over there.
Really?!
How great, let's go!
Miu.
Shall we head back then?
Yeah, I want to be alone with you as soon as I can.
I didn't know a kiss would feel so good.
No! My breasts are tingling!
Brother, you're making my breasts feel weird!
If you keep teasing it like that,
I'm gonna go crazy again.
But you're just too cute, Miu.
I can't stop.
Noo, don't touch me in weird places.
You twitch everytime I move,
it's so cute!
I hate you teasing me like that!
Sorry, I'll make sure to do a lot of things you like to make up.
So deep!
You're gonna crush my womb!
It's coming out!
Can I do it from behind?
Nope, since I can't see your face that way.
You're gonna say no regardless of everything?
You're just gonna touch my asshole again, so nope!
You can't just refuse everytime!
Say, "Fuck me from behind" now, go.
I don't want to!
If you're still gonna refuse, I guess I can't help it.
No way, don't go!
I can't do things you dislike.
B-brother, do it!
It's fine to do anything that makes you feel good!
Just as I thought, this is scary.
Want me to stop?
Bind me with those, so I can't run away.
With this, we should be able to do what you wanted, brother.
Miu, you're so cute!
I'm gonna do it here this time.
No, that's so gross!
Stop, brother!
It's fine, it'll start feeling good soon enough.
It hurts!
No!
I don't want this!
Sorry, I'm pulling it out.
Miu?
Don't pull it out!
You sure about that?
Do more, please!
It hurts, but it feels good too.
It feels good, I'm gonna cum.
I'll cum!
Inside!
Cum inside!
You're killing me!
I'm gonna die!
I wonder why it felt so good...
Probably because I'm doing it with brother.
Are you okay now?
My gentle brother, always being there for me...
I love you so much.
Here we go!
Brother...
So he's treasured that picture with me.
I love you, brother.
Wonder if I should stop using pads.
Since he says I'm cute regardless anyway.
It smells like him.
A book?
I wonder what he's been reading.
You liar!
Why did you just throw away that book without even asking?
What kind of book was that?!
And why is it so important to you?
Hey, give that back!
Answer me seriously!
I hate you, brother!
You don't get my feelings at all!
The hell was that?
Sorry that she's such a troublemaker.
But truthfully, she likes you.
I wonder about that...
I'm just angry because she threw away my stuff without asking.
I don't understand what's going on in her head.
You like her too, don't you?
The only reason she acts like that is because she wants you to spoil her.
Spoil?
Indeed.
If we're talking about someone unfamiliar to her, she's curt, and straight to the point.
Even then, what exactly is going on with her...
She's probably jealous of those busty gravure idols...
That's sorta cute.
How did you figure out I'd be here?
I asked our mom.
Say brother, you like big breasts?
Yep, I do.
But you see, I don't care about your breast size.
I love you, Miu.
You're a lot cuter than those gravure idols.
So you love me from the bottom of your heart, eh?
Yep, that's correct.
It's your scent.
Probably the deodorant, actually.
That's fine, you belong only to me, regardless.
When you feel like fapping, do it with me instead.
She gets angry, but likes being spoiled...
At times, she's a volatile mixture of emotions, but...
I like her for exactly what she is.
Oh, right.
I need to carve my name onto your dick.
Hey, stop that!
I'm just kidding.
You might just go through with it, and that's what scares me!
What was that for?!
I'm back.
Welcome back!
You're early today, eh?
I wanted to be alone with you as soon as possible, so...
Eh, so you got that carved?
This makes me feel like I belong to you, so I love it!
I don't have anyone else either.
You're a pervert, Miu.
I'm just going along with your perverted fantasies.
Oh, is that so? You're a huge masochist, huh?
Nope, that's not it.
I'm the devilish pet that's crazy about her older brother!