Alright, I'll be on my way.
Whoops!
You don't have to be that worried.
I'll be back once I become
a full-fledged monster tamer.
My cousin named Leroux had set out
for the royal capital.
It's already been ten months since then.
Oh my!
Is that Leroux-san's portrait?
Huh!?
Do you know her?
I do!
She's a regular at our shrine maiden café.
I'm glad that I found a lead!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm Leroux-neesan's cousin
and I'm looking for her.
Sounds like you had a hard time,
but it's alright now.
I think that you'll be able
to reunite with her soon.
Thank you!
My name is Sakihime. What's yours?
I am Eliza.
The Underworld's Maternity Princess
The underworld's maternity princess.
If you're looking for Leroux-san right now,
I'm sure she's in the deep cavern of Yamana.
Huh? Did she switch from monster tamer
to adventurer class?
It's not like that. They said that in this cavern,
monster tamers can find rare monsters
which can be turned into partners.
Sakihime-san, thanks for everything.
I'm gonna look for my cousin.
Hey, please take care.
Jupiri, Gospel...
We're tired of hiding from people in our wolf form.
That's so mean of Leroux-chan, though.
She already had Gospel-chan, but she's
still finding other rare monsters.
My master's impulsiveness isn't something new.
Let's find her right away and take her back.
Who knows what trouble she might end up into?
Gospel, can you follow Leroux-neesan's scent?
Yeah, it's mixed with the scent
of other adventurers
but I can smell her faint scent.
Wait, Eliza!
What are these? Take them off me!
N-No!
Stop! Don't do that!
It's so long and thick! Stop!
Stop!
No! A-Anybody...
H-Help me! Help me!
Make it stop!
What's happening here?
We have to help her.
W-Wait!
My, my...
Please wait for a moment.
Let's see...
Umm, I wonder which the right button is?
Hey! Stop watching and hurry up!
Anything's fine, so make it stop!
Umm, maybe this one?
No!
Stop...
No! D-Don't!
Stop fooling around!
M-Make it stop for real!
Is it this button?
That's enough messing around!
I won't let you off for doing this!
I'll never ever forgive you!
No, I can't take it anymore!
Stop! Help me! No!
Hurry up and make it stop!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh...
I'm coming... I'm coming...
I really can't take it anymore!
I'm coming! I'm coming! No!
My, my, my, my, my...
Oh, my!
I wonder if she's alright?
She's supposed to become a nursery...
What was that?
She might be one of the Akurem knights.
They seem to only capture female adventurers.
Don't tell me that they
got Leroux-neesan too!
Calm down, we haven't checked
the whole place yet.
I can smell my master further inside!
Let's go, Eliza!
Wh-Who are you?
I'm Zara, the Akurem knights' adviser.
The Akurem knights...
They're the ones who abduct
female adventurers.
And so? What are you gonna do about it?
What are these!?
Wh-What are you planning to do to me?
Where are Jupiri and Gospel?
Gos?
Oh, those doggies? I have no need for beasts.
I'm only looking for high-quality nurseries.
Nurseries?
What?
No—!
No way! No way!
Don't touch me there!
Ouch! Stop!
That won't fit inside! It hurts!
Don't worry, you'll start feeling good in no time.
You'll understand it with your body.
You're about to become a maternity princess.
No way!
No...
Stop! Stop this!
No... No... No!
What do you want to do to me?
This is a maternity princess's...
...ritual.
Ritual?
Maternity princess?
A maternity princess...
It is someone who conceives a baby monster,
give birth, and look after them.
A maternity princess's womb is
a nursery for spawning monsters.
Yes, you're no longer considered
a human from now on.
No! Don't stretch my insides!
Alright, it's gonna come out!
Stop! No! No!
I don't want that!
What's happening? It's shooting
something in my belly!
It's a concoction to prepare your womb
into becoming a nursery.
Your womb will be filled with this
and turned into an erogenous zone.
This concoction will spread
through your whole body,
turning it into an erogenous zone.
It means that you'll be able to feel
an out of this world pleasure
through your whole body.
No way... What's happening to me?
Something so cruel is being done to me,
so why am I feeling this good?
Not again!
No—!
Three things await anyone
who undertakes the ritual.
They happily become a monster
nursery after enduring the ritual.
And then, those who get overtaken
by pleasure end up breaking down.
In short, they go mad.
No!
Stop!
Those who lose themselves in pleasure
as maternity princesses
will no longer remember who they are
Stop!
or why they are still alive.
Make it stop! I'm begging you!
They just keep on living each day
to give birth to monsters without ever knowing why.
No, I don't want to!
Please stop!
Will you go through that same path?
Why am I here? Why do I have to go through his?
No... No...
No!
No! No!
No! No! No!
No! No! No! No!
I'm a wolf tamer from a faraway place!
I... I will find Leroux-neesan
and take her back...
We'll go back home!
No! Stop!
I don't want this! No!
I am Eliza!
I am...
I'm a wolf tamer named Eliza! I'm...
No—!
You're remarkable. You managed
to stay conscious.
Well, then.
You are about to give birth to a monster.
Its color will decide your rank
as a maternity princess.
I was expecting either a red or orange one,
but you gave birth to a colorless one.
Congratulations, you belong to the lowest rank.
Eliza-san and Leroux-san should have met by now
and enjoying each other's company.
I wonder what they're doing right now...
Are you alright, new girl?
Umm, where are we?
At the second jail of Akurem
knights' headquarters.
They keep the lowest-ranked
maternity princesses in here.
Oh, it's you!
The girl who got caught by
a robot at the entrance.
W-Were you watching back then?
I'm sorry. I didn't help you...
That's fine!
I'm supposed to be an adventurer.
It's my fault that I was captured.
So, you are an adventurer.
Huh? Are you not one?
I'm a wolf tamer from a faraway place.
Oh...
What are you doing in that cavern as a wolf tamer?
I only came there to find my cousin.
How did things end up this way?
I never managed to see my cousin,
and I got separated from my companions.
Wear something for the meantime.
You're still alive so you'll see them again.
Thank you, umm...
I'm Jard.
I'm Eliza.
Jard...
Jard, it's time.
I'm sure you'll meet her, Eliza.
Make it end!
Make it end already!
Hurry!
No! This is too much!
Huh? Umm...
Jupiri? Gospel?
I'm glad! It's Eliza-chan!
I'll open that up.
Eliza, what are you doing?
Hurry, before the patrol gets here!
Okay...
But how did you do it?
I'm not sure why, but that Zara let us free.
Enough of that, let's hurry up and scram!
Eliza... Jupiri... You two run away first.
Gospel...
It's okay, I'll go right after you!
Go and find my master.
I'm sorry, Gospel! I'm sorry!
Huh?
No way!
A SakuraCircle Project / Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji