I’m Mutou Wakana.
A young wife with a husband who is 15 years
older than me, and a three-year-old child.
Woah, Wakana, what are you doing?
I thought I'd just lick for little bit.
I-Id-Idiot!
What do we do if we wake Taa-chan!?
Besides, we're in a traffic jam right now
so someone around might see us!
It's fine, it's fine! We won't be noticed!
Papa-san's been so busy recently, you
haven't been with Wakana at all!
So let's use this time to get closer as husband and wife!
Just kidding.
Wakana, I'm cumming...
Papa-san, you can't, yet.
Hey, Papa-san...
We're finally out of the traffic jam...
You wanna have sex with your
cute wife in a mourning dress?
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
A Secret Wakana-San.
Hey, hurry and put it in, Papa-san.
Yes... Papa-san... more...
Yes... more!
Wakana... I can't... anymore...
Papa-san, you're cumming already?
Geez, Papa-san...
Please have another cup.
Ah, pardon me.
Ah, it's finally over!
Oba-san, thank you for the hard work!
Yes, thank you, too.
By the way, I didn't see Takashi-kun
today, is he not here?
I think he's up in his room studying.
He's failed twice already, you know.
Hum... I see...
He's an adult now, so he should at least
come down to say hello... geez.
Wakana-chan should talk to him about it, too.
Yeah, I'll go check on him later.
Ah, I finally got Taa-chan to fall asleep as well!
You're staying here tonight, right?
I have the bath ready, so go refresh yourself!
Who is it?
Is it Papa-san?
Hey, I thought someone was here...
Huh? My panties are gone.
Could it be...
Oh!
Takashi-kun... it's Wakana, can I come in?
Ta-ka-shi-kun!
Huh? Uh, yes!
What are you doing, Takashi-kun?
Oba-san was worried because you didn't show up earlier.
You need to take a break once in a while, you know.
Well, it doesn't really make a difference
whether I show up or not.
Besides, I have to study more...
I see... so by studying, Takashi-kun
means these kinds of things.
Ah...
This is my underwear, you know...
I wonder if I should tell Oba-san...
I'm sorry!
Wakana-onee-chan!
Takashi-kun... so you are interested in girls?
If you don't answer honestly, I'll
tell everyone about this, okay?
Yes... I'm interested...
I get it. Well, then Wakana-nee-chan will teach you well.
Wakana-onee-chan?
Takashi-kun, you can look more closely.
Wakana... Onee-chan...
Takashi-kun, don't be in such a hurry!
Look down here, too.
It's... kinda wet...
Your tongue is... inside...
No!
That... feels good!
Show me Takashi-kun's, too.
Wow! Unlike Papa-san's, it's so hard
and erect because it s young!
Wakana-onee-chan!
Wakana-onee-chan... I think I'm gonna...cum!
I'm sorry! Cumming!
Because you're so young you can cum this much...
And you're still so energetic, too!
Hey, hey, Takashi-kun, want to
put in inside me this time?
Yeah...
Yes, yes...
Wakana, where are you?
Wakana-san!
Wakana where did you go??
Want to have more... sex?
Wakana-onee-chan... I...
See? It's inside.
Takashi-kun! No... no!
Yes... yes, more! More!
More, more... go deeper...
Yes, that's right..
Yes, great...
I'm going to cum!
Hot stuff is coming out!
So much young semen is pouring inside my womb!
Hey, what happened today... is a secret...
between the two of us, okay?
Hey... Takashi-kun...
One more time... please?
Here, come from behind this time.
Do me! More! Thrust me more!
Hit deeper inside! More!
Yes! Yes, yes! More, more!
Yes...
More... deeper inside...
Yes... yes... that's right...
Yes, yes...
Huh? This is weird... I thought I heard Wakana-san...
Wakana-san? Where did she go?
Wakana-san! Wakana-san! Wakana-san!!