I was just using you all freaks through my shinpa thread!
You were never my buddies in the first place!
Sorry, I went too far.
But you're not being true to yourself either.
Can't do anything 'bout that.
I can fellate, but my mouth isn't good with it.
Akimi-chan...
Man, they're all united now.
All of them, are united.
Bet it would be great to be someone who can play with anyone without restraints.
Able to chat with anyone,
eating delicious food,
and have a good time with them.
I even prepared an entire room.
It's because I have this...
That's why I thought I didn't need friends.
Maybe it was foolish of me to think that way?
So Akimi-chan just wanted a place where she could belong?
And now she has gone back to square one.
I feel so refreshed after bursting out like that.
Touya, I don't need you here anymore so you can go home too.
She's trying to act strong, and she's quite putting up.
Well, part of it is my fault,
so I might as well cheer her up.
I can't just go home like this you know.
I'd like to use the bathroom and washing machine, if that's okay.
Shut up, just go away already.
And you're going to reek of semen if you don't wash up.
Then just go by yourself!
If I go now, I'll feel lonely being by myself.
Hmph, it can't be helped then.
The hard Knot          Shinpa
H-Ni Juu
#3 The Rainbow Color-shifted Invitation
You mentioned something earlier about someone who can play with anyone without restraints.
I feel the same way too.
I never would've come out and just kept playing with myself.
if it wasn't for the shinpa thread.
I'm grateful to you Akimi-chan, for making the shinpa threads.
You're not taking it off?
It's embarrassing so just go in first!
Die you lolicon!
The bathroom at my place can't even be compared to the size of this.
That chair, is it the type found in sex shops...?
Here I am, so cheer up now.
Why are you wearing a school swimsuit?
Why are you getting all stuck up with just a school swimsuit?
Idiot!
I heard from Natsumi that you like this sort of stuff.
That's why I even did it with my knee socks you know.
Happy now?
What is this...?!
It's nothing.
I just thought that using lotion would feel great.
All men have dreamed of this one way or another,
but not even one single fool has actually tried it out.
It isn't restricted to just guys you know.
One fool actually did!
This is amazing!
I think it would be really fun to play with my pussy in here!
Akimi-chan seems really happy now.
I'm glad she's a bit okay now.
Okay, human guinea pig done.
I see, so it's still useless if you can't even hold onto anything.
Geez, just fix me already!
It's quite fun to do this with you, Touya.
Thank...
Wait, I'm not supposed to say that!
You didn't have to kick me like that!
Sorry, my feet slipped.
So it feels great to be with Touya like this.
Did it hurt?
Why are you asking that while riding on top of me?
I can't caress it properly if I don't do this.
Her crotch within that lotion-drenched swimsuit is...!
Crotch: He means the area between the thighs with cloth folded in 2.
Oh, it went to the belly.
Sorry about that Touya.
Akimi-chan's active petite body is so slippery!
Akimi-chan's pretty light and tender...
Hey, I just felt like inserting your cock.
Wow, the head is going in.
It's just unfair for you to be penetrating a kid like me!
No, it's not!
It's in... but it isn't!
The warm and soft sensation at the back is already enough to make me crazy
and yet it's even getting rubbed within the cloth on her tummy at both sides!
Yes, this feels good.
This is great.
I wonder how great would this be if I use my own pussy.
Did you do it with Koharu already?
Can't you try asking me in a more reversed approach?
Did it go all the way in?
Is that your "reversed approach"?
Then...
Do you have a girlfriend?
Well, instead of an actual girlfriend,
I guess we're probably just friends with benefits.
Then that means you don't?
Those are just your sex friends, right?
Guess I don't have a partner too...
I'm just like you I mean!
See, I also have sex friends, but I have no special someone, or something like that!
I also stopped mingling with them once I grew to hate them!
Especially those who are the opposite of what...
Crap, I don't get this!
Why am I getting all flustered?
Oh yeah...
Seduce him, seduce him!
It's already this stiff so I'll just invite him with a bait!
If you become my boyfriend,
I'll always let you do my pussy raw.
So you want to do it too, Akimi-chan?
I wasn't lying back there,
but I just can't say such an embarrassing thing even if it's already at the back of my tongue!
It's just the two of us.
No one's going to laugh, and nobody's going to go away.
Did you feel great with me?
We already did it with knee socks, right?
Y-yeah.
I never thought that a kid like you could be that good.
Do you want to do something that feels even better?
H-hey!
I'm gonna do it even if you don't want to!
Even a kid like Akimi-chan gets this wet?
How far is it going to go?
Her tight insides are sucking me in!
It's all in.
I'm used to it already so just do whatever you want.
I wonder what this is?
It's the first time I've felt nervous while doing it.
It's like I feel relieved deep inside my heart.
Like my ears are getting warm, and I feel somewhat happy inside.
It's a feeling of happiness that feels so good
it makes me forget why I was even having sex before.
Oh, now I get it.
It feels good because I'm doing it with someone that I like.
I feel a bit pissed that a cock actually made me fall in love.
I'll make you feel great as my revenge!
Huh?
This is the first time that I've gotten conscious about it.
Could this be... love that began with sex?
Touya...
be gentle...
It's payback for driving my cock nuts with that knee socks!
Oh no, I'm going to...!
Hey, do you feel happy?
It's my first time so I'm not sure.
You've done it many times already, haven't you?
Die!
I mean this is my first time to actually like a guy!
And I'm not sure what to say!
I'm sorry!
Just do whatever you think would make your partner happy.
Like letting them cum inside or something.
I can't allow that.
If I get cummed inside now...
Touya, I'll...
Like letting me cum inside Akimi-chan!
He really came inside me.
It feels like his semen is spreading throughout my body.
This is the very first time that I've felt this good.
What was your reason for creating the shinpa thread?
I wanted the thing that everyone has at school.
The thing that everyone has?
A place to be, I guess.
Wasn't Koharu being left out in class?
But she still has some close friends that's why I was pissed!
I wondered if one could get closer to their hobby buddies than normal one's.
It was boring just by myself.
Was it boring being with just me?
I think it's not that bad.
Come to my place anytime.
It looks like we share the same interests anyway.
Ok!
Hey, you haven't kissed anyone yet, right?
The touchy-feely girl is here!
I'll give everyone a nice session so forgive me if I'm late!
Touya-san... and Akimi?
Nee-chan?
So that means...
My little sis.
My big sis.
Can the three of us talk about this for a bit?
I'm done!
Why did you plan on going to
the party with a fake name, Nee-chan?
You're the one at fault, Akimi!
I never thought that my sister would be the organizer.
And I even wanted to do lots of good things!
Hey!
Akane-chan, as long as it feels good you don't care who your partner is?
Women should properly take care of themselves!
Is that something you should say to all the girls you already did it with?
I'm Sorry!
Shame
on
my
head!
But you know,
for you to go to a sex party means that you're not really serious about Touya.
But, but...
You'll never know how compatible your body is if you don't try!
How unreasonable.
Why is that?
Don't compare me with some bitch like you who just loves to do it!
I'm not bitch! I'm trying to search for buddies!
It's a scale of conflict that only happens between people of the same level...
Besides, it's all because of your indecisiveness, Touya!
of course he'll choose me.
Because the throbbing of his hips is a sign of love!
Just choose between us already!
Em... Well...
Then let's decide on who's capable of satisfying him the best.
After that, the one who get ki-ki-kissed
will be the one to be his girlfriend!
I'm good with that.
I'm not just going to give up my Touya-san to anyone!
Wow, a chubby bunny!
I'm not going to lose either!
A knee socks bunny?!
Did you know Touya-san...
What?
Bunnies tend to have sex whenever they feel lonely, you know.
That's different from what I know!
Also, they have a strong territorial behavior
so they're quite vicious to those who come near their boyfriends.
What?
Does Touya also like having a blowjob?
See, we think alike!
Let me go!
I'm also good at that you know!
Besides, Akimi can't do this for you.
It's already this wet.
If you're that good, then try making him enjoy it instead!
Okay then!
It said that one who is good in conflict
is the one who is capable of sealing the enemy's
techniques to eliminate their fighting capabilities.
Not only did Akane-chan seal Akimi-chan's specialties, she even forced her to play using her own specialty!
Akane-chan's in the lead 2 to 1!
But that composure...
Does that mean she still has other weapons at her disposal?
Even if I lose, as long as Onii-chan calls me, I'll be just outside the door.
But it's a secret, okay?
I don't want to lose Onii-chan,
so I'll do my best!
An innocent-like Akimi-chan?!
If you think carefully, this situation is...
The older sister gets to just watch while the little sister does the blowjob!
Playing little sister is unfair!
Weak point spotted.
That looks so good...
I feel like cumming...
Geez, I'm going to lick it too!
So, does it feel good?
Oh, you came a bit.
It's still yet to burst out.
Onii-chan,cum here.
Spray me with your semen.
Do it, do it!
Fap Fap Fap Fap Fap Fap Fap Fap Fap
I'm going to release everything...
so take it all!
Wow, that's amazing!
I want to etch this very scene into my mind!
Have a good taste of it.
Open your mouths.
Woah, that's just horny!
Now, swallow it.
Onii-chan, I can't hold myself back anymore.
Let's just leave Onee-chan and go to another room.
Let's do it.
I never thought you were going to play along like that.
It'd be really bad for me if you wore a little sister wardrobe.
If you get it then just play along with it!
It feels really embarrassing whenever we get back to normal.
I'm not doing this anymore you hear me?
But if that's what makes you happy,
then I won't mind doing it again next time.
Touya-san's mine until he gets his first shot.
Hey, that's gross, stop that!
It's not a blowjob unless you drink all his semen.
Then I'll take everything that's left in your mouth, nee-chan!
We're still far from finishing.
Now I really can't cum anymore.
I'm about to pass out.
But it's still very stiff.
You want to do it, right?
If I can enter you both at the same time I would, but that'd be impossible.
Then let's do it.
Strike it big!
Touya-san...
Damn, I'm a man!
Hurry, hurry!
I'm going to do this till the end!
Here comes his cock!
Woah, the big clit and the small clit are eating me!
Akimi-chan's soft spots are rubbing hard against me.
It feels like, I'm violating the two of them at the same time!
No, just the clit is not enough.
Hey, what are you doing with your pussy by yourself for?
It's not me, it's Touya who went in me!
Because he loves me, and he's going to put it in whenever possible.
A kiss!
If you do not Kiss I might cry.
Feeling like you're number one there...
Both these sister's clits are so much different.
Be more gentle...
I'm Cumming...
I'm not satisfied yet.
This is my punishment!
I'm the bad girl so do it here.
Bad girls need to be punished!
Yo!
Where am I?
Smells Like... medications...
You're in the hospital idiot!
You fainted after doing it too much.
As your girlfriend, that was pathetic you know.
Stop acting like lovers already.
I'm the one who will be Nii-chan's wife!
Hey, just wait!
Find a new boy with those shinpa threads, okay?
Touya-san belongs to me! He will be only mine!
I don't need anybody else!
Wait!
What's all the ruckus about?
There are lots of shoelaces lying around...
Oh, could these be the ones featured in magazines lately?
Hey, let's fix the room first.
Well these are just pranks anyway.
What kind of hospital is this?
These things you know...
Are called shinpa threads.
If you find a person with the same color as yours,
you'll find your true love.
So the shinpa threads now are like that.
Then I'll just have to show him the color of my shinpa thread!
H-Ni Juu