It was the last day of summer vacation at school.
Second semester's right around the corner.
Jeez!
I'm definitely not going to be able
to finish my summer homework now!
This torrent of homework is just unending!
I'd say it's oppression!
Mei-chan, you're such a lazy bum.
I-I'm not!
Don't lump me with you!
Actually, I knew the exact reason why.
The truth is.
We spent the entire summer,
having sex every day!
Lazy Bum.
We originally intended to do our
homework properly at the start of summer vacation.
However, the moment we shared
our feelings, we suddenly went all out.
Hey, Yama-chan.
What is it?
We'll just have to somehow do our homework as always, right?
We still have five days before the deadline anyway.
I wonder if we'll ever finish it.
You're a lazy bum, you know
I'm not!
If I study with the top student, Yama-chan,
homework's gonna be a piece of cake!
Ehh.
Nope, not possible.
They say that when tempting
things are right in front of great guys,
they usually succumb to lust.
Not happening!
Comparatively, though,
I'm the type that thinks first before doing anything.
I'd surely like to experience such "personal lessons" firsthand.
I asked first, so no!
A-ny-way!
Consider this my down payment.
I'll be giving you some time later, okay?
"Mei's study partner."
Why you!
Slinking cat!
You're totally dazed after having
been kissed by Ayumi-chan, huh.
There's been rumors that she's also
playing a lot with boys from universities,
so I'm pretty sure that was just normal.
You're talking so casually about
someone that's not your girlfriend!
Don't tell me you've been cheating on me with her?
Of course not.
She's being spoken of casually even by other boys.
I guess, since you've been noticing
her even before we started dating.
Lustful brat!
But she's the one who appro...
Lecherous brat!
Jeez, come on, cheer up already.
I haven't done it with Ayumi yet anyway!
Yet?!
What did you mean by "yet"?!
I-I didn't mean.
Alright then,
as punishment, you're going to tell me
every single answer to these assignments.
There she goes.
The lazy bum.
You're going to be trashed by Ayumi
again if you keep that up, you know.
She's onlyslightly ahead of me in seatings!
#1 Aizawa Ayumi
#2 Usami Mei
Aw, jeez!
I don't wanna do my homework anymore.
And what do you think will happen
if you keep lazing around like that?
I'll... achieve perfect pleasure.
Oh, it's your phone, Yama-chan.
I'm going to go ahead and look at it as punishment!
Hey, your panties! They're getting stuck between your.
Oh, this one's Ayumi-chan's.
Lemme see.
Hey, don't just peek at other people's phones!
Wait, wha...
My reward for completing the homework.
H-Her boobs are big!
I'm fine with being your second, Y
I'm fine with being your second, Yama.
Second?
What did she mean by second?
I'm not sure,
but I just know that she's saying something very erotic!
M-Mei!
H-Hey!
W-Wait.
Yama-chan...
Mei, Mei...
Mei!
W-Wait!
Not inside!
It's going in.
Mei's insides feel so tender.
It's also very wet.
Stop sloshing it in and out.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Oopsie.
You can't just cum by yourself.
Just a little more and I could have.
Come on, do it to me like you usually do.
His dick is already so stiff.
What should I do?
My insides will just start to crave font the longer I ogle it.
It's not my safe day today, though.
I have to hold off getting cummed inside for now.
Mei, move your arms away.
Yama-chan, umm.
I-I might get pregnant if we don't use a condom today.
You don't have one?
I don't have one.
We've been doing it raw yet nothing really happened, right?
And you can't really restrain yourself at this point.
But.
I can feel the warmth of his click as it touches me.
Besides, you say you love it when I cum inside, right?
Right? Right?
Whoa.
I don't want him to be taken by another girl.
The sensation of my dick being squeezed
whenever I thrust in and out really is the best.
Oh no, my body is starting to remember as he fucks me.
The sensation of his stuff seeping inside and spreading inside.
She's still reacting so nicely despite her protests earlier.
I have to... restrain myself.
Oh no, it's going deep inside!
So deep!
Hey Mei,
let's record this too.
What?
I can't just settle for photos anymore.
I want to see you move, even when you're not with me, okay?
I beg of you!
It's okay. It's okay... right?
Things will somehow work out, right?
Your insides are really squeezing me tightly.
That usually weird feeling now feels even stronger.
Since you love being cummed inside,
you're also getting horny as you're filmed having sex.
I'm not!
I'm about to cum.
Can I?
No... stop!
We're doing it raw.
I-I might get pregnant!
I'll properly buy protection from now
on after we record how I cum inside you.
What?!
I don't even get that!
We've been doing it that way.
I'm sure today will be just fine.
He's probably going to fap often while watching it.
He's going to fap with me in mind where I can't see him.
Oh crap, I really can't stop anymore.
Here, come closer so I can see your face better.
When we go all out,
he always pins down my arms.
His dick feels so good.
So good... so good!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
He came already?
I don't care if I get pregnant anymore.
Th-That felt really good.
You came too much.
Oh wow, it's really pouring out!
It feels like your dick is still inside me.
But, I think it feels quite good to be
pinned down like that in the heat of the moment.
Whoa!
I was so absorbed, that I forgot to press the record button!
What?! My skirt's soiled with your cum!
So much.
You idiot!
We weren't able to do anything at all!
Four days before assignment deadline.
The next day.
Hey, are we really going to do this?
We're not done with our homework yet.
We can't concentrate because
we still haven't satisfied ourselves.
In this situation, the best thing is to
take a break and have a change of pace.
Besides, that wasn't actually enough for me.
Hey, you've been wearing your
swimsuit since we left the house?
On top of that.
Well, I did kind of suddenly decide that we'd go out.
I didn't have the time to buy a new swimsuit, you know.
Should I take it off instead, though?
At least pull your clothes up so they don't get soiled.
Oh, yeah.
For you to actually invite me here,
now you can't just call me a pervert anymore.
That's because you.
You're making such a perverted expression,
I thought I'd stop you here before you try to do it outside.
That's all.
I'll just leave it at that, then.
Your dick is pushing inside.
Mei, your voice, your voice!
Oh crap.
My heart starts throbbing as I think of
the possibility that we might get caught.
It makes me really horny.
You're practically gushing today, Mei.
That just now.
I told you not to raise your voice!
E-Even if you say that.
That smirking face.
I'm sure he's pushing all of my tender buttons on purpose!
You sure love this, huh.
Getting fucked deep inside with my dick angled upward.
No... oh no.
If he keeps rubbing that spot.
I'll just do what you want and cum outside for now.
Wait, no!
No.
Stop, stop!
Now that we've exercised a lot, I'm
pretty sure we can finally finish our homework.
It was good,
but he could have finished it by cumming inside me regardless.
So unfair.
Wow, whoa.
I can't rub it off, your cum is stuck on me like seaweed.
See?
All sticky.
H-Hey, can I have this swimsuit?
Don't get too cocky!
Ow, ow, ow!
That hurt quite a bit!
After finally deciding on it, the next stay we still...
Three days before assigment deadline.
He was still going all out,
even requesting to do it roughly since
he didn't get to cum inside me yesterday.
So I, being unable to resist.
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum inside!
Just cum.
We still have time.
Two days before assignment deadline.
It's okay.
Our minds just keep on coming up with
excuses not to do our homework and just have sex.
At this point, we can't stop it no matter what we do,
and we soon started to pay it no mind all together.
One days before assignment deadline.
All worries about getting
pregnant and completing the assignment,
were just swept away by the rejuvenating pleasure of sex.
And so,
Submission date.
I, Mei, and Ayumi...
Ouch!
Ow!
Ack!
...had to bear the wrath of our teacher.
Ow, ow, ow.
But, I guess it's good that the submission date was extended.
For Yama-chan to also be unable to finish homework,
looks like your laziness is
contagious, making them lazy bums too.
It's not going to end anyway, so I
felt that it was just a waste of effort!
You never submitted your assignment either!
Actually, that's the least of my worries.
I'll be quiet about this,
but only if you come along with me on the way home.
Besides,
you were sending Yama-chan weird images.
Just what are you trying to do?
The internet's such a great tool.
Studying only lessens play time, don't you agree?
What?
Well, I guess you're right.
To not do something that would just be a waste of effort.