You are terrible, Akane-chan!
I got exposed to anal sex thanks to that shinpa thread!
It felt lonely because Tooya-san wasn't able
to come home the entire night, but...
Thanks to that shinpa thread,
he experienced a new fetish first hand and matured a bit more!
Hello?
By the way, magazine-reading delinquents
in stereotypical comics,
generally read teen manga unlike
these losers there, don't they?
Hey, Akan-chan! Your voice!
You're laughing too loudly!
I'm going to drive your face into the next issue!
The only one who'll get driven here... is you!
This girl is from the Oubun dojo!
She's that blonde loli, isn't it?!
What was her name?
She's the one I used to play with when I was little.
Oubun Renji's only daughter
Oubun Koharu!
This guy's actual muscle is a delinquent herself
l-I-I'll remember this, loli girl!
Hey, wait up.
You wait up.
As always, cute yet totally violent.
He said I'm cute...
What's this Oubun dojo?
It's the dojo where she lives.
Her household is well acquainted with mine.
When we were kids, I was often her training partner.
I had no problems with her wanting only me as a partner but...
She never held back, so I always used to get beat up to a pulp.
But you see, you see...!
You were the only one who agreed to be my partner.
That's why I always fought at full strength.
Anyways, I came here to ask for your advice on something.
Also, also...
Why don't you ever come to our place anymore?
Well, that's...
Koharu's eyes have always been pure and honest
Her innocence, combined with her knack for
pleading is completely overwhelming.
You see, I wanna ask you something...
This girl also has a shinpa thread
and it's even a pink-colored one!
Eh, a shinpa thread?
You're not aware of it?
Well, I'm going to meet up with my friends soon.
We're going shopping together.
Hey, hey, I want to go to Nii-chan's place!
Okay.
Shinpa threads can randomly attract many
people depending on the situation.
Maybe it's still a bit too early for this kid?
Anyway I'm always okay with it
so listen to what she has to say.
Pink stands for...
anal! sex candidate?!
Shinpa threads are capable of turning complete
strangers into hobby partners
as long as it links both person's fetishes.
For her to show that to people randomly,
it means that anyone can screw her
as long as the interests meet!
Clitoris you see...
from above
then to the middle,
from below...
Also, if it's still stiff
halfway... Brazilian...
to the head...
if Koharu manages to find some suspicious guy out there...
I'm going to teach her somethings before
any weird bugs latch on to her!
The hard Knot         Shinpa
H-Ni Juu
#2 The Pink-colored and Milky White limitation
It smells like Onii-chan!
If you go out in that outfit,
you'll be inviting perverted eyes out there.
Eh, so you're looking at me that way!
Pervert!
What am I getting conscious for?
Besides, who in the world gave her
that dangerous shinpa thread?
But... for that short time that we didn't see each other...
She sure has filled up in the right places...
Nii-chan, you see...
A-Ah yes, advice right?
Is it weird for someone to masturbate with their butt?
Wh-What did you just say?
Whenever you touched my butt during training, it felt good.
And ever since my finger touched my butt hole, well...
I've been unable to stop myself from masturbating without touching my butt anymore.
Now I'm craving for a real cock in it.
What the...? I turned her into a pervert?!
Oh, no...
This room is full of Onii-chan's aroma.
Please, I want your...
I want your cock!
Wai-! What are you doing Koharu?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for turning you into this pervert!
No matter how much you change, I'm
still going to be your Onii-chan!
Can you kiss me?
I'm going to keep on asking until you say yes.
She really is good...
at pleading!
That was my first kiss.
Don't blame me if you end up regretting this!
Nii-chan's tongue...
It's been forcing its way in me since earlier...
To have his tongue push his way in and kiss me like this..
It feels so good that I might just lose it!
Wearing this thread would tell people that
you're willing to have anal sex With anyone, you know?
I was just afraid that someone might take you away.
You're the one who neglected me in the first place.
So what are you getting worried for?
I hate you.
Do you know what this is?
I always use that.
And when it comes to butts, I know a lot!
I'll be having sex once I get my butt cleaned.
Should I teach you how to use it, Nii-chan?
Don't be conceited, Koharu.
I also know a lot about it since I was also anal-raped by a girl.
So there are women out there who have cocks?
I'll tell you more about that later.
It just means that I know what it feels
like to have a cock inside of you.
Okay, show me your ass.
Do you also like doing it in the butt?
I like it...
I'm glad.
Onii-chan, I love you.
So Onii-chan is also interested in anal sex like me.
It somewhat feels amazing...
I feel more electrified than usual.
Onii-chan released it inside me.
Suck on this before your insides become idle again.
Woah!
I just wasn't able to resist looking at that face of yours.
Onii-chan, you pervert!
So masturbating with your ass isn't perverted?
Here, suck the tip in.
That feels great Koharu.
The usually violent Koharu is quietly giving
me a blow job after getting the enema...
Onii-chan, I wanna poo-poo.
And here I was getting excited being licked by you...
I can't keep it in!
Please wait a moment
I already said no and you still made me take the third enema.
Shall we stop for now then?
Okay, okay.
We'll top it off with this.
Try to exert strength like you would if you were in the toilet.
After the thickest part got in, it just went straight in.
It's still small, and yet it went very deep inside.
No way...
Onii-chan's hip is hitting my butt
His cock...
All of it is now inside me...
Tell me if it hurts, okay?
Even if you do it harder, I'll be fine.
Okay!
Anal sex...
This feels really good!
Because of your training, the hole
is squeezing me rhythmically.
It feels great!
Your insides are slowly wrapping me
with tenderness and warmth...
It feels good.
Stop trying to explain it in detail.
You may have beaten me a lot before,
but your look during anal sex looks really cute!
You've played with your butt too much, Koharu.
It only took a short time before it got loose...
Th-That's not it!
It's your fault for not being concerned with it be before!
It's all your fault!
Sorry about that.
Then, I'm going to completely fill you!
That means...
It means I'm going to cum inside to make up for it.
Onii-chan is widening it up from the inside.
Amazing...
It feels like something's melting from my back...
Onii-chan... no...
Woah, she's taking a leak!
I told you I don't want it, Nii-chan!
Ouch!
Not in the face!
Nii-chan, you pervert!
I'm throwing this away.
You're not going to use that thread anymore?
Yeah.
Because, I finally discovered that you also like butts!
My, I said it!
Now I don't have to fear about that shinpa thread, huh?
Let's leave the question about
me liking butts for now...
Even if this girl has a small back
she's already become a fine woman.
I'm float-hanging!
Your arms are also that of a fine man, Nii-chan.
Nii-chan...
Now that I've turned into a woman, could I become...
your wife?
I'm going to buy dinner!
No escaping!
It's Koharu... and a guy?
What kind of a person is a girl with a cock?
Be quiet!
It seems I'm going to add another friend.
Is there a person named Tooya here?
Who is it?
Sup!
Anyway, look at this image first.
Who is this girl? The way she talks is pissing me off...
How does she know...?
Is this really allowed?
And with that, let's have a nice thorough chat here.
Here, I have the keys and a map.
Just wait. Who in the world are you?
You'll know soon enough, so I'm going
to keep my identity a secret for now.
It's milky white-colored...
I'm going to wait in my room!
She's also wearing a shinpa thread?!
She tried to blackmail me with a fake
photo What in the world does she want?
Not only does she know my name, but my place as well.
I don't know what she's going to do if I just let her be.
Sorry for intruding.
Akimi-chan, that touchy-feely girl is still not here yet.
It's your fault for taking things too seriously.
In the first place, you were the ones
that started to follow it blindly.
She's here!
I'm about to...!
I can't hold it.
I can't...
I'm going to cum inside Akimi-chan!
I'm next!
For me to have sex with Akimi-chan...
I love you forever!
It's deep inside me, and it's big...
Akimi-chan, suck it in.
Suck my cock in.
Akimi-chan! Akimi-chan! Akimi-chan!
So you've kept your kneesocks on, Akimi-chan,
and it's making my cock go crazy!
It's like your feet are cocks and the knee socks your pussies!
Here, my virtual squeeze!
Don't move...
Let me enjoy your pussy more!
Akimi-chan! Akimi-chan, I'm cumming!
You're all boys and yet you can't even last long enough?
How lame.
If you're looking for tissues, we have some, Tooya.
This party is for people with the same tastes and fetishes.
It really excites me to have sex with everyone!
We might look like perverts to outsiders,
but it's been like living in heaven
ever since we met Akimi-chan!
If I called Koharu in, one of the guys would
have already screwed her ass by now.
So, you're the one who gave Koharu that shinpa thread!
What do you want from me?
I wanted a new friend at my party, you see.
I'm not your friend and I didn't come because I wanted to.
Don't ever lay a hand on Koharu!
And erase that picture!
So you're the Tooya that she's been
annoyingly talking about at school.
Are you trying to lecture me by preventing
me from contacting Koharu?
Wow, how erotic.
You say that, but this thing's already craving for it.
You didn't even properly explain it to
her, and yet you gave her the thread.
It's still too early for you all to show
your fetishes to the random public.
It's the shinpa that we're showing off, right?
I said it's dangerous!
Koharu asked you for advice about a private
matter without second thoughts.
If you had answered her honestly, then she
could have become your real friend!
Tsk, I don't like you.
Are you implying that to openly like is to prepare yourself to be backbitten by society?
We can't do that and that's exactly
why shinpa threads are used.
By wearing something that can only be understood by those who also like that fetish,
we could then find someone who could satisfy us.
You're right about that, but...
Besides...
Not all of them are as honest as Koharu.
Putting that aside, why don't you become my friend already?
Even if you act like you don't want it, you
won't be able to convince me with that.
I-It feels soft...
Here, look.
It's the knee sock that I normally wear.
It still hasn't been taken by anyone.
A virgin knee sock that has just been taken off?
Well, how is it? Clothing-fetish, Onii-chan?
How do you...?
Didn't you take it off while you were watching us having sex<?
You do have a fetish for clothing, right?
Y-Yes...
He said yes!
I'm going to stir you up more!
Damn, this the best... This is the best
service for the tip of my cock!
We'll try to treat you favorably as a group,
so please be our friend already.
But...
If you become our friend,
you'll always be able to do it with me and the others here.
If you want, I'll introduce you to whoever you like.
Someone like you can't possibly do...
I can.
Listen!
I'm the one who invented the shinpa threads!
She's the one behind it all?!
Everyday's fun when there are lots of friends to play with.
Then how about going for one round with a real pussy?
Akimi-chan!
Look, look, it's going to come out!
Then I'll just let it leak now, okay?
Her pussy looks like it also wants it badly!
Just kidding!
Were you expecting it?
Sigh... This girl...
Men sure do like this.
She's an absolute bitch!
You're actually my type, Tooya.
If you can last through it, then I'll
let you take a shot at my pussy.
Everyone cums quickly when done in like that!
No, you won't.
So try to bear with it too, Tooya!
No one can possibly resist this!
My back feels like it's being sucked in by the bed.
This feeling of totally getting weak from the inside...!
I was forced to cum by Akimi-chan!
Here, look.
The virgin knee socks were ripped open!
She's still stroking it after it just came...
This girl sure knows how to tease men.
This color, you see,
means that I'm looking for boys that can be bullied.
And you've also worn the male masochist
shinpa thread before.
How much do you really know, Akimi-chan?
I heard from Natsumi whom I borrowed this room from.
I also have a good set of cute clothes.
Don't you think we II get along just fine?
So just be my friend, okay?
If it comes to this
then I must somehow shake her off
and take the lead here!
You've been asking me to be your friend earlier,
but is that a confession?
Or do you really want a friend such as me?
What?
Do you think I'm confessing to you?!
That's embarrassing and beyond impossible!
Are you an idiot?
Are you stupid?
I want a friend!
Don't misunderstand!
Everyone here became my friend through a shinpa thread!
They're different from the crowd,
and if you become friends with someone with the same tastes,
you'll really be happy!
Without the shinpa thread, no one
could have met each other like this!
How about me then?
The fact that so many people are gathered
here is proof of your charm.
Isn't that right everyone?
Yeah!
She's gentle when you talk to her.
Her sharp tongue is just her way of hiding her embarrassment.
I see now!
She's timid, but sincerely wants to have friends!
Okay everyone!
Try to imagine a sweet, clean version of Akimi-chan!
Won't you be friends with me... ?
I'm happy!
Stop imposing your image of me!
You wouldn't even have looked at me
if it wasn't for the shinpa thread!
The shinpa thread was merely a link.
I am here right now because I was able
to become close with Akimi-chan!
S-Shut up!
I was just using you freaks with my shinpa thread!
You're not my friends or anything!
What's up with that?
Let's just ignore this girl and find more perverted buddies.
You're right.
If it's just friends with the same tastes,
there are lots more outside.
Things went from bad to worse...