My heart throbs as I think about the
possibility of us getting caught.
It's making me so horny.
You're so much wetter today, Mei.
Hey, I said you should lower your voice!
E-Even if you say that.
That smirking expression,
he's deliberately hitting my sensitive spots!
You sure love this, don't you?
Getting fucked deeply like this.
Oh no, oh no.
If he keeps on rubbing that spot I'll...
I'm going to cum outside like you usually ask me to.
Huh? Wait.
No.
Don't... don't!
Ow!
Ouch!
The week we're supposed to use to finish our homework,
was all spent just having sex with Mei.
We have one more week to submit it, but...
Wow!
Ayumi saw us doing it?
I might keep quiet about it if you come
with me before going home later.
I can't refuse her.
As someone who also didn't do her homework, she said
she wanted someone to help her with it this time,
but why did she call me out to this place?
I have no idea what she's thinking.
Five Days Before Homework
Deadline
The Naughty Kid
Hey, where are we going?
Just follow me.
Her hands feel so warm and smooth.
And those slender fingers, it feels like they're longer than Mei's.
Since she's been mean to me lately, my mind's
starting to fantasize about things.
No cheating!
A Mei in my brain?!
M-My pure heart is!
Yama-chan,
you're thinking about something other than homework, right?
N-No!
I know that I shouldn't cheat on you!
But this is really bad!
Once I start getting aroused, I won't
calm down until I've released it all!
So Yama-chan actually stands for shameful, huh.
Do you want a girl to actually say that?
Do you want girls to keep on saying that?
Stop!
I don't want to remember my class trauma from the past!
Ayumi's already got a grasp on my dick right now!
I can't do anything about it!
I have no idea what you're saying.
It's your hand that she's holding right now.
The nerves on my hands and my dick are connected,
that's why it feels as if she's directly holding my dick!
What?!
That's why!
Yama-chan?
So you're already this stiff.
Such a pervert. Mei's going to get mad, you know.
D-Don't tease it.
Please don't!
It's not sex if it's just using hands.
So please!
Oh, I didn't know that.
I actually think I'm better than Mei at handjobs.
Ayumi, Ayumi!
I'm alright being second to Mei-chan,
but I want you to look at me properly when we're together.
Ayumi!
Wow, lots of your perverted juices are dripping from the tip.
It's so wet now.
What is this?
Your fingers, they feel so good.
It's just your hands, but it feels like I'm inside a pussy.
Do you love doing it with a pussy?
Me too, I love doing it while being very close like this.
This is too much!
Which is better, this, or Mei-chan's pussy?
Th-That's...
You're stopping?
Why?
I was thinking of this.
So soft.
My tip is rubbing on her panties.
And beyond her panties... is her pussy!
Yama-chan, you're so cute.
This is embarrassing. Don't look at me like that.
If you don't look, then I'll just stop again.
N-No fair!
Please, please continue, Ayumi.
Hey, please.
Just let me cum already.
I wonder what I should do.
I'll do your homework, and everything else!
Please, it's my once-in-a-lifetime request!
He's so cute!
Ayumi's hugging me.
Her breasts are pressing against my back.
Aren't you answering that, Ayumi?
It's okay.
I'm not going to mind any other guy when we're together.
Then the rumor that you're doing it with other boys is...
Rumor?
Oh, well... I wonder.
Forget that,
so you're that interested in me, huh.
Th-That's not wrong, is it?
Because you're just too erotic.
More!
It's alright, I'll do it lots and lots for the honest Yama-chan.
Here, is it good?
Is it good?
Hey, does it feel good?
Your dick is still secreting fluids while twitching hard.
This is amazing.
It's really twitching a lot.
About to cum? Okay.
Just cum.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Amazing.
I'm...!
I want you to properly say that doing
dirty things with me was fun.
I-It was very fun doing dirty things with you.
You shouldn't have held back,
right?
Let's use signs whenever we meet.
Signs?
You don't want Mei-chan to get mad at you, right?
Y-Yeah.
Send this emote if you want to fuck.
A "yes" with be this smiley.
And a "no" will be this tongued fellow.
Someone will find out if we keep on texting using only words.
I see.
Alright, since it's getting dark already,
see you tomorrow.
Umm.
How about homework?
If you want to, then let's do it.
Let's... "do it"?
Four Days Before Homework Deadline
No good.
Nothing is going into my head,
and I still have to do homework.
But, Ayumi seems to want to do it with me,
so I just keep slacking off because I know
I have someone else to blame.
This might feel even better than yesterday.
I want to feel it more.
My seed is telling me to meet Ayumi!
For us to do it inside the gym storage room,
it seems you really wanted to meet me without delay.
I... couldn't have composed myself
after experiencing it yesterday.
Same here.
Are you ready?
It's already this big.
Ayumi, no.
What is it that I shouldn't do?
Here, you feel aroused with your ears, right?
But,
I wonder which will feel even pleasurable.
I'm going to have sex with Ayumi.
I've marked the dick of my friend's boyfriend up to its tip!
It feels different from Mei's... So tight
at the tip, and so wet at the end.
Just like how dicks have different shapes and sizes,
there are also different kinds of pussies
for the same number of girls!
The pleasure was so great,
that it felt as if her pussy was sucking away
all the guilt that I was feeling toward Mei.
J-Jeez, Yama-chan!
You're holding me too tightly.
E-Even if you say that, I can't possibly hold back!
You're dating Mei, and yet you're doing it with me.
So naughty.
I can't resist with you still having that image, you know.
I'm not going to tell Mei-chan,
so just rest easy.
I really just wanted to have you.
Damn, damn... dammit!
Mei, forgive me!
Yama-chan, you can hold me even tighter if you want to.
Ayumi!
Ayumi, it feels so good inside you!
Say, Yama-chan,
you like doing it with your partner
wearing a school swimsuit, right?
Eh? How did you know?
Did you already forget the picture I took?
Oh, yeah.
If you want, should I wear it next time?
What? For real?
I will, if you're willing to visit my room sometime.
Ayumi!
Ayumi... Ayumi, Ayumi.
I-I'm about to.
So you really love swimsuits, huh.
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
Ayumi, can I cum inside?
Sure,
but say that you love me as you cum.
Say that you love me!
Why are you saying that with such a tender voice?
If you don't, then I won't wear the swimsuit.
You love swimsuits, right?
– Swimsuits, swimsuits, swimsuits, swimsuits, swimsuits.
– I-I love you, Ayumi!
Your insides just started gripping me really tightly!
I cummed inside Mei's friend, Ayumi,
and it felt fleetingly fantastic.
Say Ayumi,
I never knew what you were planning to do, but...
Well... it felt very good.
Very good?
Also, I think keeping your hair loose like that is better.
Did she really feel happy when I said that it felt good?
I really don't know what she's thinking.
In the end, we never did do our homework that day.
Three Days Before Homework Deadline
Good morning.
Mornin'.
Ayumi-chan, you stopped fixing your hair in a ponytail?
Going for an image change?
One of the boys in our class told me that it suits me better.
I see.
My guilt's really haunting me,
but I can no longer stop.
How does it look?
This is the one that I use for my swimming class.
Whoa, this adult swimsuit looks very different
from the typical school-type one!
H-Hey, don't just snap pictures there.
Let's do it, please?
You want to do it with me wearing a swimsuit, right?
Yup, yup!
Two Days Before Homework Deadline
And so I had sex with Ayumi once again,
while my mind continuously asked Mei for forgiveness.
This feels so weird.
Wearing a swimsuit inside my room makes me even hornier.
I-I can't hold it anymore.
I'm going to cum!
Me too, it feels so hot!
My guilt finally caught up to me,
causing me to cram all of Mei's homework in that same night.
One Day Before Homework Deadline
I feel all dazed now because of that,
and when I consulted Ayumi with my unnaturally
lively dick, this happened.
Ayumi, wait, stop...! I'm going to cum again if you continue!
Hey, Yama-chan,
my parents aren't coming home tonight.
So stay for the night, okay?
Let's do our homework together.
S-Stay?!
Oh my, Yama-chan!
Are you okay not going your homework?
The deadline is tomorrow, you know!
It's okay, it's alright!
I did Mei's in just one night.
So it's okay, there's no rush.
Amazing, this is so good!
It feels so good!
If you keep doing that, I'll!
My love juices will!
In the end... we just welcomed the next morning.
Deadline
We haven't done our homework yet.
I even stayed over at your place for the night.
How will I ever explain this to Mei?
Why don't we just call in sick and ditch for the day?
With all of these consequences looming
overhead, why are you still happy?
I truly don't know what you're thinking.
Really?
I'm the type that thinks first before doing things, though.