General Term: Shinpa.
These are shoestrings that represent a specific sexual fetish for each color.
These are used to easily find partners of the same sexual tastes,
without meeting strange people from the net,
and also to start promoting offline meetings in certain areas.
Akane-chan, the girl who stops by every morning at the convenience store I work in,
holds a deep blue string.
This color means, "I'm looking for a cosplay sex partner".
For my ideal girl to be a pervert to such an extent...
You just wait, my cosplay collection...
To use this stuff from urban legend and ask her to have cosplay sex with me...
Like I can say something like that!
If I'm the one who makes the first move,
she'll most likely think, "You pervert"
and in the worst case scenario, my life would be over!
Yea well I suppose it was a short but joyful life span.
There it is... There it is... There it is! There it is!!
Whoah...
So, you are...
just like me...
One whose aroused by cosplay sex only!
I don't want that...
There's a pervert
in this store?
What?
Disgusting...
Well, I suppose it's true, but...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I saw you wearing that...
I hope you don't get creeped out by this, but...
Would you please "deep blue" with me?
The Hard Knot Shinpa
#1 The madder red invitation
Choose whatever you like.
Tooya-san!
We sure have the same tastes.
I'm afraid of being labeled as a "pervert",
so I have never actually worn them before.
Well, we're already past that age anyway, but you're also holdings shinpa,
that means you re actually a pervert, right?
The size of these clothes are quite small...
I wonder if they will fit...
I don't wear them!
Then how do you play with these?
I use them as pillow covers... As tablecloth pieces...
I spread them out on the bed and roll on them...
I also wrap my cock with them,
sniffing them, and finally jacking off with them...
I didn't mean that...
I think it would be a bit small for me.
Damn! Akane-chan is so erotically cute!
Changing Clothes
Thanks for waiting.
She's in P-E clo-the-s!
There are cuter dresses in there, why did you choose PE uniform instead?
You kept staring at my butt earlier, so I thought bloomers and butt combo would be the best choice.
Is it okay if i take this home with me later?
This sensation of the fabric pilling and the rubber texture on my butt,
are something that you'd only get from an authentic second-hand bloomer.
It's also quite tight, so it squeezes into me.
Even more so because I'm wearing panties inside.
Changing outfits also has an effect on our moods and feelings, right?
I don't do cosplay personally though.
For example, whenever you change into your work clothes your mind somehow switches into o whole different mode, right?
I see what you mean...
And the soft sensation of the bloomers is just right beside me...
How about we do a convenience store play?
I'll be the robber, then I'll push you down and steal "stuff" from you.
With that, you'll never forget my scent and warmth whenever you work there.
Wait, Akane-chan... you really are into this, huh?
Of-course. Our minds are really in sync and it's quite enjoyable when we are like this.
Besides, sliding into sex while flirting around, is...
is something that I really like.
The room is hot,
and I feel like I said something really slutty.
I'll have to make him take the initiative so I won't bethought of as a total slut!
Tooya-san...
Yes, bait him in! Making him do all the dirty talk is the key here... Alright!
If you get your erotic cock big like that in front of me,
I'll end up hoping to get messily ravished by you with my bloomers still on.
So not what I was going for!
I never thought you were this lewd.
I'll try to borrow a uniform from the convenience store next time.
So if you wear something like that at school next time you'll also end up remembering me?
But...
Geez, I don't care anymore if I'm lewd...
I came here to have sex anyway.
This is bad... if he penetrates me right now, I'll probably cum right away, definitely.
Wow, I never noticed these when I was working.
What a great pair of breasts.
Everyone tells me that.
So you were watching me when I came to the convenience store?
I thought you were pretty lively and cute, then I saw your string.
I wanted to get closer to you,
then I thought of using the string, but somehow ended up being treated as a pervert.
That's good.
That's not good!
There are a lot of guys who don't care about cosplay sex.
They're fools for sure!
Since I saw the string,
I was already looking at you erotically.
I had you wear all sorts of cosplays in my mind as I jacked off.
So you're even more of a pervert than I thought!
Akane-chan, it's about time...
Hey...
Normally, lovers have sex as a couple because
of the whole love factor involved but we don't hove that, do we?
What are you saying?
For pervert comrades the perverted way is the normal way!
Me too.
I wonder what's this is, I enjoy it when I'm with him.
I feel so happy that my heart is racing.
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm going in.
Don't just rub it there.
His cock's coming in!
Don't tease me... No...!
You said some really erotic things and your reactions were so cute that I couldn't help it...
You are like a young
boy in love!
What? You're the one who wanted to get in quickly.
When men want to do it,
they just have to wrap the clothes around it and masturbate, right?
How do girls do it?
Seriously you are gonna ask that from a girl you just met?
But you're wet all the way inside.
Your wet clitoris is also rubbing against me.
That's because, I couldn't wait to actually do it with you!
I was looking forward to this.
That's so cute!
How about teasing her a bit?
So you chose P.E. clothes because,
you wanted to do some physical exerciser right?
No...
I really wanted to do it.
Rea-lly wanted to...
What? I can't hear you well.
That's too bad, and I really want to have cosplay sex with you.
I like it...
Your cock, I like your cock... I like it, I love it!
When you move, my body becomes twitchy.
Even if it's just our first time,
we're really compatible with each other.
What was that called again?
Mutual partners?
My head's going blank, I can't think properly...
I'm going to release it inside.
I'm going to cum inside the bloomers.
No...Not... inside...
I'm cumming inside the bloomers!
What's this? It feels like an expanding water balloon that's stuck inside.
It's seeping through the clothing.
The bloomer might get pregnant.
We're not finished yet!
So you really came when I released it in the bloomer.
Tooya-san...
But...
You also wrapped your cock inside my cosplay and released it.
An aroused woman,
has her whole body as the erogenous zone.
Everyone would probably treat me with disdain,
if they witnessed me aroused to such a degree.
They'll treat me as a pervert,
and I'll be different from them once I'm a pervert.
Is it really bad for someone to be different from others?
If two "different" people come together, they become as one.
Is that any different from us?
Throb!!
On no!
Sorry!
Was I acting too close to you earlier?
Speaking of bloomers, it's fundamental to do it in a back position while you're fondling-my breasts.
If you don't know something that basic,
you're on idiot!
I can't look straight at Tooya's face!
As expected of the pervert and cosplay fetish Akane-chan!
It feels really good as your pussy seems to be pulling me in, but are you okay?
I came...
I said I came!
I just got it in.
How many times did you cam When l entered you?
That many?!
She must be embarrassed... How cute!
So I can release it inside, right?
If it's not okay, look at me alright?
You idiot!
Idiot, idiot!
I'm going all the way inside now.
I'm cumming,
I'm going to cum!
His cock is all the way in,
and it's filling me.
I never thought that fast rounds like this could be this hot.
We're not going to be like this next time, right?
Next time? Is it okay? Is it really okay?
I'd be lying if I said no...
Hey Tooya-san,
there are different costume matchups in cosplay sex, right?
Ah, like it's virgin and anal sex for shrine maiden costumes,
sniffing and cock rubbing for cycling shorts,
bondage play for...
As expected of Tooya-san, spoken like a true cosplay fetish expert!
That goes for you too.
I guess you really are the destined partner for me!
I want to live my cosplay fetish life to the fullest!
I have to experience the real thing to awaken me to more things.
Here, have this.
What do red strings symbolize?
That's a madder red string.
I'll become more of a love pervert!
No, I mean, what's the meaning of the string's color?
Oh it's getting dark, and I have to get a change of clothes.
You're going to stay for the night?
She's gone...
Tooya-kun...
As the manager of this apartment complex, I need to tell you something...
Huh?
That's a Shinpa, right?
Natsumi-san?
I'm wearing a blue one.
I never thought that I'd see a partner nearby.
But this one's a different color.
Why does she think of us as mutual partners?
Um, Natsumi-san,
where are we headed to?
Do you understand Tooya-kun,
it's already dark, and if we talk in the apartment, it will cause trouble to the neighbors.
As the manager, it is my duty to provide them with a pleasant lifestyle.
And I wonted to have an enjoyable talk with you,
at a place where we could be alone.
Spare me the details, but could you please take this off me?
I won't try to escape, so you don't need to do this.
I want to be close to you, not as a manager, but as a mutual partner.
Okay, Tooyo-kun?
The red string that Akane-chan gave me is clearly different from her blue string.
Why are we mutual partners?
Okay, we are here now.
There's a building in a detached place like this?
About the thing that we are going to talk about here...
Won't you move from that room?
It's going to be a hassle if you get all noisy in the room.
I'm not going to be noisy anymore
Then why don't we make a deal?
Tooya-kun will become my lover pet.
But you're wearing a ring!
Aside from the room, I'd also like to talk about the wrong string color...
This ring is a fake, haven't I told you?
But that's a lie,
and you're not listening to me!
I am listening.
Well, then why don't we start with your string first.
I'll tell you what you need to know.
Her lips and fingers,
are moving wildly about like a trapped fish!
My body feels like it's being taken away!
Take this...
Is this an adult's kiss?
What a slutty face for someone who just enjoyed having his mouth filled with spit.
How's the taste?
It's sweet,
and it has your scent.
It's so embarrassing, I can't look at her!
Look me in the eye!
She suddenly became angry?
She was gently playing with me earlier.
There, have a good taste of it.
Good boy, Good Boy...
That's good.
Natsumi-san complimented me.
Now, swallow it.
Good work.
What, did my body just...
I guess there's nothing wrong with the color after all.
So what's does that red string really mean?
A scarlet string means:
"I'm a masochistic boy".
What in the world did you do, Akane-chan?!
B-but that means the mutual partner thing...
You're not masochistic!
And the colors are still different!
Having different colors doesn't mean we can't do it.
Because, my string means.
"I'm looking for masochistic boys!"
Natsume-san...
I haven't taken a bath yet!
But my pussy wants to have
the full taste of your raw cock!
I thought you'd hate it if it reeks of my odor.
Then I'll get o mouthful of your cock first before putting it in next time.
But even if you don't have the string, you probably still have the full potential to own it.
Really?
The shape of your cock,
is also bent and curved,
so it hits the good spots
For this kind of man and woman play, the cock needs to be highly compatible.
It'd cause serious trouble for her family if I release it inside.
In this situation, I could just either bear with it, or release it outside.
But aside from that, if I ruin her mood...
I don't feel like it would just end with me getting kicked out of my apartment.
Oh, I haven't released my tits yet, have I?
Wow, it really feels like I'm forcibly raping you!
It doesn't feel, you are forcibly...
Stop! It's coming out...!
Her insides are trying to suck me further in!
It felt really good, right?
Your desperate look was really cute.
If you'd just agree to my wishes, I would make this an even better experience for you.
I'd really wanted to give in, but I am pretty sure I'll end up in the middle of a messy situation later on.
Before that I'd like to resolve the problem about my apartment...
Wait...
If she really wants me to the point that she'd risk getting her adulterous act found out,
then I also have the ticket to do her in!
We'll agree on a common ground
and fit everything right into their place!
I'll pledge my absolute silence in my room,
so why don't we just pretend that this didn't happen?
If you kick me out,
you'll never have the chance to taste this cock again.
So please,
it's okay if you're just going to get a mouthful of it once in a while!
But no matter where you are, I'd just hire a strong man to find you.
Only fools make unwinnable deals like that!
I never had a chance to strike a counter deal?!
It doesn't really mean that if it's not you I can't have sex.
And in your case, you have no choice but to follow my order to have sex.
We'll just have to put it that way.
Embrace me however you like, that's an order.
You just finished not long ago...
What a lively cock!
Don't release it inside, don't release it inside!
Try to count stones in your head!
This is for my apartment, it's not like I want to do this.
As long as I don't release it inside, everything will end well.
That's good.
You like breasts?
Yes, can I fondle them?
My, what a spoiled child!
The cursed roller!
Roll, roll!
My head feels really great.
My heads a cock?
No, my cock's a head!
Good boy, you're quite easy to tame.
I'll have your butt awaken too.
Eh? But that place is yet...
Yep, I won't take it just yet.
Yet?!
Even if I am looking for masochistic boys, to rape their butt would just be violent.
It's something that can only be done when both have already reached a mutual trust that is above normal.
You have nothing to be ashamed about.
Release your true self in front of me.
Natsumi, I'm already... It's coming out, it's coming out!
What's your blood type?
It's type-A.
That's good, keep it up, just release it all inside me!
No... My pussy's cumming
That was quite enjoyable.
How about you, Tooya-kun?
You're so cute, I might end up doing it again tonight.
Enough for today, I'm going home already!
Someone's waiting for me.
But with this, it looks like we have to spend the evening here together and wait for morning to come.
That's so unnaturally bent!
If we play to our heart's content until morning,
it will be possible for you to enjoy losing your virginity.
I was done in!
ls he still not back yet?