Alright! Good Work! This is the end of the exam!
Hey, Nana!
How was it? Did you get the last question?
The one where you have to draw a graph?
That's the one!
For that, you take the symmetry of the square of x and a, and multiply it.
So that's how! Not A, but you take the multiplication...
Chigusa-san, you were in top form for that test, no?
President...
It must have been.
Weren't you the second in the whole grade?
That was just by chance!
Hey Nana, do you have any secrets to doing so well? The secret to being so good!
Eh...
Chigusa-senpai!
Oh! How did the test go?
It was so hard...
If you don't study properly, you can't be in any club activities anymore!
Understood!
See you later.
Really~! Not only are you in the student board,
but you seem to also be fully active in clubs as well!
N-Not really...
Chigusa Senpai! Thank you for working so hard!
See you tomorrow!
Yeah!
Come on! Tell me the secret to doing so well in tests!!
Well... properly let go of stress, and get good sleep...
I've already heard so much about those methods!
Kaoru...
K-Kimomura...
My methods of unwinding...
My secret.. relaxation...
There must be some kind of secret method, right?
That is confidential.
What's about being confidential, Nana!
Exactly, I do have a secret!
This story is about how an elite student, Chigusa Nana,
and an S&M fetish, fantasizing boy, Sugimura Kaoru, performing taboo soft S&M.
A story of love, and friendship.
Kaoru's being so slow?
I-I’ll be right back.
And he did say that before...
Sheesh... It's been a long time since last time's relaxation, how long does he intend for me to wait?
What is this?! Doesn't this make it seem like I want to do it so much that I can't stand it?!
That is...
This is...
This costume...
w-was from that time...
Could you look after it just for tonight?
It’s my son Kaoru's, I’ll come pick it up tomorrow morning!
That day, if I hadn't taken that paper bag...
As I expected it fits me perfectly.
If I hadn't thought it would be interesting, and tried it on...
But...
What?
It suits...
Because Nana has pale skin, the black bondage suit is really...
very beautiful.
Um.. Nana, that's not good... hiding your body...
You have to show more of your beautiful parts...
I understand already!
That’s right, put your hands behind your head.
How does it feel?
Kaoru’s eyes...
It’s so tight all over, that’s mean!
I am responsible for putting on his clothes...
U-U-Undressing me.. the movements of my body..
Kaoru’s eyes are confused...
touching me...
We haven't done anything, but my breath quickened,
I felt hot, I felt shy...
My chest felt pain, no, instead of pain, it felt so good within.
Kaoru's eyes are running over my spine...
t-touching my ass.
M-My skin is tingling.
Really, he hasn't touched me but...
That's  impossible...impossible...that much...
What if I was really touched...
If I am touched now...
Your skin is tingling.
No, it's not that!
Can you stand it much longer, Nana?
No, that’s not it!
See, even your chest is becoming quite bitchy.
The clothes is gripping my skin tightly!
See, you're already itching for it.
No, it’s hard... to breathe.
If I’m touched by Kaoru now, what would I...
Those fingers...
With just those fingers, he feels through, trying to grasp its form and firmness,
thinking whether it should be touched or not.
What are you doing, Nana?
K-K-Kaoru! Umm... Welcome home!! How long...!!
Have you been licking over what happened before?
I guess it can’t be helped.
You really are...
a pervert.
Oh geez, should have told me earlier if there was a need to change!
H-H-How about we do this today, Nana?
W-Well, this can be quite difficult, it’s a lot more bound...
You’re not quite good with being naked,
I figure you might also be nervous wearing a swimsuit or anything similar, right Nana?
I, I just can’t help it, I don’t have anything else to wear.
Hey, is this okay already?
Yup, thanks for waiting.
Let's establish some rules today.
Rules?
Well, it’s because you’re body is quite erotic.
Y-You see, as a man I might not be able control myself,
so if you treat this as a request from me, I would like you to agree with my idea”
So, would it be a blowjob first?
Well, it’s true that any guarantee is better than none.
Okay.
Well then, let’s get started Nana.
Nana, I’d like you to do an erotic pose that you can think of.
Eh?
I can’t think up of anything like that so suddenly.
L-Like this?
This is good...
This is really good.
You’re truly a beautiful woman.
Here, have a look.
Well?
It’s just a part of your upper body, and yet it’s so erotic, isn’t it, Nana?
You see it immediately as soon as you check it out yourself.
That’s not true.
Okay, let’s proceed further.
Okay.
Nana, open your legs a bit.
Yes, that’s it...
Focus your eyes here, Nana.
Am I...
That’s good...
Am I really...
Nana, one more shot.
Am I...
Am I really, that erotic?
Really really good...
You’re really erotic.
You’re very erotic in that swimsuit.
All of the boys stares at you erotically.
It's really good...
It’s really really good, truly erotic.
Nana.
Your underarms are very pretty, aren’t they?
T-The skin and flesh around your navel also looks pretty, Nana.
I-Idiot.
Y-Your thighs look cute too, shapely and healthy.
I-I-Idiot.
It’s okay, I’ll take each and every one of it.
No, that won’t do, look back this way.
Eh?
Look at the camera.
Okay...
Okay next, try squatting down.
Eh? S-Squat down?
Squat?
Oh, not like that, Nana.
You need to squat down while opening your legs.
My legs... eh?
Eh!!!
Opening my legs, eh?
Like this?
No...
W-We’re finished with this pose right?
It’s embarrassing.
W-Wait Nana.
Just a bit more...
Just stay that way a bit longer, okay?
No- Hey, Kaoru!
W-What... What are you doing Kaoru?
N-No... Ka-o-ru?
What’s wrong, Nana?
W-What’s wrong?!
We’ve decided on this earlier right, Nana?
Have you forgotten?
We would take pictures of you being bound by rope.
Besides, it’s okay if it’s me right, Nana?
Is it really okay...
W-Wh- Hey Koaru! what is this?
It’s me who will now get heated up, anyway just leave it to me.
It's fine right, Nana?
What shall I do?
My heart is throbbing...
Alright... Kaoru...
This... this feeling.
I’m being tied up.
Smiling as he ties me up...
Ah, damn, that Kaoru!
I'm... I’m totally getting heated up.
Nana, you’re beautiful, Nana.
The feeling of being gripped by the rope...
I-I feel more conscious of its actual grip because my eyes are covered.
Nana, you’re beautiful, that tied up position suits you well.
II don’t know anything about that.
“Oh yeah, that's right, you can’t see right?
I-I’ll take a good picture and show to you afterward then.
Eh? F-From what position is he taking the pictures?
F-From the back of my neck? Directly at my back?
Z-Zooming the camera at far angle?
Kaoru, where are you?
The sensation of Kaoru's location sweeps by me even it I don’t like it!
Kaoru’s breath, his warmth...
All because my eyes are covered!
Kaoru,where are you?
Kao-ru? Kaoru?!
Kao-ru?
Wai- Ka- No...
Kaoru- s-stop... Kaoru-
Nana, that expression is good.
I-I’ve wanted to take a snap of that expression.
No, w-wait Kaoru, don't!
No-
No, Kao...
Kaoru! You idiot!
Ouch!
I though you would be happy with it.
Nana are you mad?
Of course I would be! Forcing my suddenly like that!
But...
Oh? Nana haven't you noticed?
Your starting to get aroused and your nipples are getting hard.
T-T-They’re not getting hard...
Eh? I don't get it.
I-It's my... It's my own body, but still I...
Okay, I’ll let you check it out with your own eyes then.
See?
Your hard...
My...
nipples.
M-My...
Nana, see, your face and expression is the only thing seen.
Should I send this picture to everyone? It’s your face anyway.
My... My...
This is... This is...
This face is my...
My body...
My expression...
My... My....
No...
Please stop this, Kaoru... please.
That was the promise right, Kaoru?!
The rule was if I said no, Kaoru will...
K-Kaoru!
Did we agree on that?
Just look at this picture.
Y-Your face, your nipples, it’s like you’re asking for a lot more.
You show up to everyone like a good girl,
presenting no interest whatsoever in anything sexual.
Even though the real you is actually capable of such expression.
I want to let everyone see.
As soon as they see this,
they'll immediately find out that the real Nana is, a pervert.
Ahh, damn that Kaoru!
I was totally...
He... He completely understand it already, didn't he?
That...
That, like Kaoru,
Did you wait long, Nana?
I am also a pervert.
So, let’s start Nana.
Y-Yeah...
Will we really do this?
Eh? What's wrong?
That was the plan for today, wasn’t it?
Now, hurry up and get ready, Nana.
Well then, I’ll wait here, and you head over to the vending machine over there and buy some coffee.
Huh?!
Now go, Nana.