Okay, good work everyone! The exam's over!
Hey, Nana!
How'd you do? Did you get the last question?
The one where you have to draw graphs?
Yeah, that one!
You split it into two problems depending on whether x or a-squared is greater.
Ah, that was it! It was a-squared, not a!
Chigusa-san!
You've been doing great lately.
President!
Don't you think so? You ranked second in the class last time.
I just got lucky.
So, do you have any tips? What's your secret to success?
Chigusa-senpai!
Oh, how were your exams?
It was sort of okay.
I totally blanked out!
You have to study hard, or you won't be able to do club activities!
Okay!
See ya.
Geez, they love you so much!
It looks like it's not just the student council that relies on you a lot, but your club too!
N-Not really.
Oh, Chigusa-senpai! Thanks for your hard work!
See you tomorrow.
Yup!
See?
So just tell me your secret already!
Well...
I let my stress out, get a good night's rest, and...
I'm asking how you do that!
Kaoru!
Geh, Creepymura.
My way of de-stressing...
My secret "release sessions"...
So?
You have something, right?
It's a secret!
What do you mean "secret," Nana?!
Yes. I have a secret.
This is a story of love and friendship between an honor student named Chigusa Nana
and an S&M-loving daydreamer named Sugimura Kaoru
who engage in softcore S&M for stress relief.
Kaoru's late.
I-I'll be back soon.
Even though he said that...
It's our first session in a long time. How long will he make me wait?
Wait...
What am I thinking? It's almost like I'm dying to do perverted stuff!
Is that...
This is...
This outfit...
is from back then.
Could you hold on to this just for tonight?
It belongs to my Kaoru.
I'll come get it tomorrow morning!
If only I hadn't taken that paper bag that day...
This fits me exactly.
If only I hadn't tried it on for fun...
But...
Whoa...
She looks great!
She has light skin, so black bondage costumes...
really look...
You're so beautiful.
Oh, Nana!
D-Don't hide your figure.
Show me more of your nice body.
I know!
That's it. Put your arms behind your head.
How does it feel?
Kaoru's stare...
It's pinching every part of my body. It's horrible!
He's imagining me n-naked...
Kaoru's eyes are caressing the outlines of my body.
I'm not doing anything, but it's becoming hard to breathe.
It's so hot... and embarrassing...
that the inside of my chest hurts.
Rather, it's like a light tickling inside my chest.
Kaoru's eyes are tracing the length of my back.
H-He's stroking my butt.
M-My skin is tingling.
But he's not actually touching me!
It's so tantalizing.
More...
That... much more?
I...
If he really touches me...
If he...
were to touch me right now...
Your skin is on fire.
It's not!
Don't you feel turned on, Nana?
No! Come on!
Even your breasts are throbbing.
The outfit's tightening around my skin!
Right? Don't you feel the itch?
No, it's so hard to breathe!
If Kaoru touches me right now...
What will I...
He's only using his fingernail.
I've been so anxious thinking about whether or not he'll touch me.
He's tracing my body as if he's confirming its shape and tenderness.
Nana!
What are you doing, Nana?
Kaoru!
Um, welcome back!
How long have you been standing there?
Were you fantasizing about what we did before?
Oh well. Nana, you're such a...
pervert.
My goodness!
Let me know beforehand if I need to get changed!
T-Today...
L-Let's take photos like this, Nana.
W-Well, replicating this exactly would be a challenge. It's a pretty tight bind.
Also, Nana, you can wear a swimsuit or something since you don't want to be naked.
I-I think it'll be really exciting.
Right, Nana?
Wh-What else could I do?
Th-This is all I have.
Um...
A-Are we ready yet?
Yeah. Finally.
Let's decide on some rules for today.
Rules?
Nana, you have a very sexy body.
Idio-
A-And being a man, I might not be able to restrain myself.
So if you don't have any problems with my request, please answer "sure."
Starting off with a jab, huh?
Well, some insurance won't hurt.
Sure.
Then, let's get started, Nana.
Nana, since we're here...
Strike a pose. Get into any erotic pose you can imagine.
This is so sudden.
I can't think of one!
L-Like this?
You look really nice!
Nana, you're such a beauty.
Here, take a look.
What do you think? You're just standing there,
but it's sexy, isn't it, Nana?
You can tell when you see this, right?
Not quite!
Well, let's continue.
Sure.
Nana, open your legs a little wider.
Good.
Look here, Nana.
Am I...
That's it.
Am I so...
Nana, one more shot.
I...
Am I...
perverted?
Very nice!
Nana, you're so dirty!
You look so naughty in that swimsuit.
This is how all the boys look at you.
Good, Nana! Very nice! This is incredibly hot.
Nana, your armpits are really nice.
The flesh around your belly button is cute, too, Nana.
I-Idiot!
Your thighs are just as nice. They're so plump.
J-Jerk!
Don't worry. I'll take pictures of it all.
Oh, that's no good, Nana. Look over here.
Look at the camera.
Su... Sure.
All right, next step.
Try squatting.
Huh? Squatting?
Squat?
Oh, no, Nana. That's not how you do it.
Squat with your knees spread.
My knees?
Spread... my knees?
What?
Like this?
No...
We've got enough of this pose, right?
It's embarrassing.
Oh, hold on, Nana.
Just a bit more. Stay like that a little longer.
Just a bit longer, okay?
Wait, Kaoru! Wh-What is this?
What are you doing, Kaoru?
No!
Kaoru?
What's wrong, Nana?
D-Don't ask me...
Wasn't this our plan from the start, Nana?
Or did you forget?
We were going to take pictures of you tied up with rope.
And you can trust me, right, Nana?
Yes, I'm supposed to trust him.
Wait, Kaoru! This is...
This will definitely get you excited.
Well, just leave it to me.
Is it okay, Nana?
What should I do? I'm...
getting so excited.
Sure, Kaoru.
This...
This feeling!
I'm getting tied up.
He's tying me up.
Oh! Damn it, Kaoru! I'm...
He's really turning me on.
Nana!
You look pretty, Nana!
I can feel the rope constricting me.
Th-The blindfold's making me imagine the outlines of my body I usually never think about.
Nana, you're pretty.
That rope looks very nice on you.
H-How would I know?
I see. That's right.
Nana, you can't see it.
S-So I'll take the photos carefully so you can see for yourself later.
Wh-Where are you pointing it?
M-My neck?
My back?
Wh-Where are you zooming in?
K-Kaoru? Where?
Oh, geez!
I can't help but search for Kaoru's presence!
Kaoru's breath, body heat...
It's because of the blindfold!
Kaoru, where are you?
Kao... ru?
Kaoru?
Don't... no!
Kaoru, stop! Kao-
Nana!
That expression is great!
That's what I wanted to capture!
Wait, hold on, Kaoru! No!
Don't!
No, Ka... Kaoru!
You idiot!
I thought you were enjoying it.
Are you angry, then?
O-Of course! Wh-What was that all of a sudden?
But Nana, didn't you realize?
You got aroused. Your nipples are hard.
N-No way they're hard!
What? I can't tell!
Even though it's my body, I can't...
Well then, Nana...
See for yourself.
Look.
They became really...
My...
...really big.
My... my...
Nana!
Look! It's just your face. It's your expression just now.
Huh? I... I...
May I send this picture to everyone?
Did I... did I...
It'll only be your face.
Did I make that kind of face?
My... My body...
My expression...
I... I...
No...
Please don't!
Kaoru... please...
Ka-
We made a promise, Kaoru!
If I say no more, we'll stop. That's the rule you made!
K-Kaoru!
Did I?
Here, look. J-Just look at this picture.
Your face and nipples say they want more.
You pretend to be a good girl in front of everyone,
as if you aren't interested in anything sexual.
The real Nana makes this kind of face.
I wish everyone could see this!
Showing them this face could change everything.
Everyone'll know that the real Nana is a pervert.
Damn it, Kaoru!
Kaoru... you...
Ugh...
You made me realize...
How I'm...
How I'm just like you, Kaoru.
I was waiting for you, Nana.
A pervert.
Then, let's begin, Nana.
Y-Yeah.
Are we really going to do it?
Huh? What's wrong?
That's what we planned to do tonight.
Come on. Time to get going, Nana.
Then...
I'll be waiting here, so go to the
vending machine on the other side,
buy some coffee, and come back.
See you, Nana.