Okay, good job!
Midterm exams
Literature
World History
Math
The exam's over.
Hey, Nana.
How did you do? Did you figure out the last one?
The one where we had to draw a graph?
Yeah, that one!
You find out whether x or a squared is larger,
and then you make two separate equations.
Oh, right! It was a squared, not a!
Chigusa-san, you've been at the top of your game lately.
President!
But I'm right, aren't I?
The other day, you were ranked second out of our entire grade.
That was just by chance.
Hey, do you have some kind of secret?
Some kind of surefire secret method, Nana?
What?
Chigusa-senpai!
Oh, how did your test go?
I think I bombed it.
I did okay.
You have to make sure to study hard.
Otherwise, you won't be able to attend your club anymore!
Okay!
Yes!
Bye.
Sheesh, they really admire you.
It feels like the student council and even the clubs depend on you!
T-That's not true.
Chigusa-senpai, nice work today!
See you tomorrow.
Okay!
See?
Come on, hurry up and tell me your secret method to success!
Well, just make sure to relieve your stress and get plenty of sleep.
But I'm asking about the actual way to do it!
Kaoru.
Yuck, Creepymura.
The way I relieve my stress.
My secret...
breathers.
So?
Huh?
You do something, right?
It's a secret.
Come on! What do you mean a secret, Nana?
That's right. I have a secret.
Nana to Kaoru
This is the story of an honor student, Chigusa Nana, and a young man with a wild imagination and a love for S&M, Sugimura Kaoru.
Their tale of love and friendship involves doing softcore S&M during breathers.
Kaoru.
He's late.
I-I'll be right back.
That's what he said, but...
Jeez!
It's been so long since I've had a breather.
How long is he going to keep me waiting?
Wait, what?
This makes it seem like I'm eager to do perverted stuff!
Isn't that...
This is...
These clothes...
are the ones from back then.
Could you hold onto this for tonight?
My son Kaoru will come by tomorrow morning to get it.
If I hadn't accepted the paper bag on that day...
I knew it.
This is a perfect fit for me.
If I hadn't gotten curious and tried it on...
But...
Nana.
It looks great on you.
Nana, your skin's so pale,
so against the black bondage suit,
your skin looks...
so incredibly beautiful.
Nana.
Y-You can't do that.
Don't hide your body.
You've got to...
show me more of the beautiful parts of your body.
I know that!
Yeah, like that.
Put your arms behind your head.
How's it feel on you?
Kaoru's gaze is...
It's pretty tight all over.
It feels horrible.
looking at me clothed,
but he's imagining me naked.
His eyes are looking along my entire body and touching it.
I'm not doing anything, yet it's becoming hard to breathe.
I feel so hot.
It's beyond embarrassing.
I feel this pain... deep down in my chest.
Actually, rather than pain,
I'd say it's more like a tiny itch inside my chest.
Kaoru's gaze is...
tracing the outline of my back.
He's touching my behind.
My skin is tingling.
He's not actually touching me,
but that makes me feel restless.
He might as well...
Might as well just...
do what?
I...
If he actually...
touched me...
right now...
If he...
touched me...
Your skin's tingling.
No, it's not!
Feeling impatient, Nana?
I'm not! Jeez!
Come on, your chest feels so itchy inside.
The clothes are digging into my skin!
Don't you feel restless?
Oh no.
It's hard to breathe.
Right now, if Kaoru...
If Kaoru touched me,
how would I react?
The tip of his fingernails.
He's only using the tip of his fingernails.
Whether or not he'll touch me...
stirs up a feeling of fright in me.
As if checking the shape and softness,
he traces along my body.
Enough.
Nana.
What are you doing, Nana?
K-K-Kaoru.
W-Well, u-um...
W-Welcome back!
H-How long h-have you been there?
Were you thinking about what happened the other day?
You're so hopeless.
Nana, you're such a...
pervert, aren't you?
Nana to Kaoru
Sheesh!
H-He should have told me earlier if I needed to change.
H-H-How about... w-we try taking this kind of picture today, Nana?
W-Well, it'd be pretty hard to tie you up exactly like this.
It's a pretty intricate binding.
Besides Nana, you probably wouldn't want to be naked.
I think... i-it'd be exciting if you changed into a swimsuit or something.
Don't you think so, Nana?
W-Well, I don't have any other choice!
T-This is all I have!
Um.
D...
Di...
Did you finish getting ready?
Yeah, sorry to keep you waiting.
Let's set some ground rules this time.
Rules?
Nana, you have a pretty lewd body.
Id...
I'm a man, so I might not be able to hold myself back, you know?
So if you don't have a problem with what I'm asking of you, just say you're okay with it.
Oh, he's starting out with a jab?
Well, better to have some insurance over none.
Fine with me.
So let's get started, Nana.
Nana, since we're already doing this,
strike a pose.
Take whatever sexy pose you want.
That's rather sudden. I don't really know what to do.
L-Like this?
That's really great.
It really is.
You really are pretty, Nana.
Come on, take a look.
What do you think?
You're only standing, but you look sexy, don't you Nana?
Now that you've seen it with your own eyes, you know, right?
That's not really true.
Then let's get on with the next pose.
Fine.
Nana, spread your legs a bit wider.
Good.
Look over here, Nana.
Am I really...
That's great.
Am I really that...
One more shot, Nana.
Am I...
Am I really...
that perverted?
Amazing.
Nana, you're so sexy.
You look so sexy in a swimsuit.
All of the guys stare at you like this.
Amazing, Nana.
Just amazing.
So perverted.
Nana, your armpits are beautiful.
The area around your bellybutton is also cute, Nana.
Idiot!
Your thighs are cute too.
They're so voluptuous.
I-Idiot!
It's all right.
I'll catch everything on camera.
Don't do that, Nana.
Make sure you look over here.
Look at the camera.
Fine...
then.
Then try squatting for the next one.
Huh?
What, squat?
Squat?
No, Nana.
Not like that.
Squat by bending your knees out.
My knees? What?
What!?
My knees?
Bend them out?
What?
Doing this is...
I don't like it.
I've held this pose long enough, right?
It's embarrassing.
Wait, Nana.
Just a bit longer.
Stay like that...
for a little longer, okay?
No, wait. Kaoru!
W-What? What are you doing, Kaoru?
No! Kaoru!
What's the matter, Nana?
W-What do you mean?
This is what we had planned, right, Nana?
Did you forget?
We said we'd take pictures of you tied up with rope.
Besides, you'd feel safe with me doing it, right, Nana?
Yeah,
I guess I would.
Wha... wait a second, Kaoru!
This is...
This will make it way more exciting.
Well, just let me take care of everything.
You're okay with this, right, Nana?
What do I do?
My heart's... racing so fast.
Fine.
This...
This feeling...
I'm being tied up.
I'm having... someone tie me up.
Damn it! Kaoru, you jerk!
I...
I'm... feeling...
so excited.
Wow.
Nana.
You're so pretty, Nana.
I feel the ropes digging into me.
My mind's distracted with the blindfold on.
I'm imagining outlines of my body that I'm not normally aware of.
Nana, you're beautiful.
You look great tied up with ropes.
Like I would know that!
Oh, really?
Oh, that's right.
Nana, you can't see, can you?
Well then, I'll take my time with these pictures and show you later.
Huh? W-Where is he taking the pictures from?
The back of my neck?
My back?
W-Where is he zooming in on?
K-Kaoru.
Where?
Jeez!
I can't help but search for Kaoru's presence!
Kaoru's breathing.
His body heat.
This is all because of the blindfold!
Kaoru, where are you?
Kaoru.
Kaoru!
K...
No!
Ka...
S-Sto...
Kao...
Nana, you have a great expression on your face.
T-That's the expression I wanted to capture on camera.
No!
W-Wait, Kaoru!
Stop!
No, Kao...
Kaoru!
You idiot!
I thought you'd be happy about it.
Nana, are you angry?
O-O-Of course I am!
W-What's with you a-a-all of a sudden?
But...
Oh?
Nana, you didn't notice?
Nana, your nipples are erect from being aroused.
T-T-They're not!
What?
They can't be!
I don't know if they are.
It's... it's my own body, but I...
Well then, Nana.
Look for yourself.
See?
Nana, they're getting...
My...
pretty big.
I... I...
I...
Nana.
Look.
It's a picture of just your face.
Can I text this expression of yours to everyone?
Huh?
I...
I'm making...
making...
making this kind of face.
My...
My body.
My facial expression.
I...
N...
No.
Stop it.
Kaoru.
Enough.
K...
Y-You promised, Kaoru.
You made a rule that said we'd stop if I said no, Kaoru!
K-Kaoru!
Did I?
S-S-See?
Take a look.
Look at this picture.
Your face and nipples.
They're screaming for more.
You pretend to be a good girl in front of everyone.
You act like you're not interested in anything erotic.
But the real Nana looks like this.
Don't you want everyone to see?
Once they see this face, they'll know right away.
They'll know the real Nana is a pervert.
Someone mysteriously whispers into my tear-filled eyes.
nureta hitomi no oku ayashiku sasayaku
I can hear the sighs of my hesitation echoing.
nurekikoeru hibiku toiki no tamerai
I don't want anyone to know of my impure temptations,
darenimo shiraretakunai inbi na yuuwaku
but I'll reveal everything about myself just for your sake.
anata no tame dake ni sarasarete yuku no subete ga
My search for this sweet fruit pushes me from chaos to madness.
kuruoshii hodo midare motomeru amai kajitsu
My memories from the past will never return again.
nidoto wa modorenai tooi kioku
On this endless night,
owaranai yoru ni
our hearts beat together.
nijimu futari no kodou
This illusion keeps repeating over and over again.
nandodemo nandodemo kurikaesarete yuku gensou
If I'm allowed to forget all about my daily life,
nichijou mo wasure subete yurusareru nara
I'll stop time and come crashing down.
toki wo tome ochiteyuku
I'll still feel you touching my bare skin.
fureta suhada kanjiru mama
Damn it.
Kaoru, you jerk!
Kaoru...
Later.
knows...
all...
of who I am.
I...
I'm...
the same as Kaoru.
I've been waiting for you, Nana.
We're both perverts.
Well then, let's get started, Nana.
Y-Yeah.
Are we really going to do this?
What? Something the matter?
Isn't that what we planned to do today?
Come on. Hurry up and get prepped, Nana.
Okay then.
I'll wait here.
Go to the vending machine all the way over there, buy some coffee, and come back.
Be on your way, Nana.