Alright everyone, good job on the exam. We're done for today.
Hey, hey... Nana.
So how'd the test go? Did you get what that last question was about?
That last one about drawing a graph?
Yeah, that one!
Well, comparing the values of both X and A squared, I think you might have to split the whole thing into two problems.
Ah, I see... so it should be squared A instead of A there!
Miss Chigusa... I see you've been almost flawless in your studies recently.
Council President!
Well, isn't that right? If I'm not mistaken, on that last exam you got the second highest score in class.
I only lucked out on that one though!
Hey, what's your secret to all this?
Yeah, how you're so smart and everything...how do you do it?!
Ehhh...
Chigusa!
How did the test go?
I don't know...
...somehow
Hey, if you don't study properly you might get kicked out of your clubs.
Alright~
Later then.
Seriously...always spoiling them like that..
Not only are you an excellent Student Council member, you're also good at your club activities.
T-that's not true...
Ah, Chigusa! Good work today!
See you tomorrow.
Yes!
See~... Alright then, you should start telling me how you manage to stay this perfect all the time!
Ummm, well...
There's something I do to release my built up stress...
Yeah..and that's why I'm asking you to tell me what "it" is!
Kaoru..
Wha-- Kimokura!
[Tl note: A pun on Kaoru's last name Sugimura, where Kimo means gross/disgusting]
The way I relieve my stress...
My secret....relaxant.
Well?!
You have one right?
It's a se-cret.. <3
"Secret"... what's up with that, Nana?
Yeah, even I have secrets too...
This story is about a model student, Chigusa Nana, and a male student who loves fantasizing about S&M, Sugimura Kaoru.
These two do mild S&M for relaxation purposes. And now, their story begins.
Kaoru's running late.
"I-I'll come back soon."
...is what he said.
It's been a while since we've had a session; why is he making me wait so long?
Wait...what am I thinking? If I keep looking forward to this so badly, it'll make me look like I'm the pervert!
Isn't that...?
T-this...
These clothes...
From that time...
Could you take this only for tonight?
It's actually Kaoru's.
I'll come pick it up tomorrow.
That day...if only I hadn't taken that bag...
As I thought...it fit me perfectly.
If I hadn't put it on just for fun...
But...
Nana...
It suits you...
Your skin is so white...so this black bondage is...
It's really...
Very beautiful.
Nana, you can't do that...
Hiding your body.
You have to show me more of those wonderful areas.
Oh, I know!
That's right, raise your arms behind your back..
How is it?
Kaoru's glance...
It's piercing me everywhere... it's the worst.
He's fantasizing about my upper body...
...n-n-naked.
The curves of my body are being dissected by Kaoru's eyes..
They're touching me. I'm not doing anything, but it hurts just breathing.
It's hot...
...and really embarrassing.
It hurts inside my chest.
Or rather than hurting, it's more like there's a soft tickling in my chest.
Kaoru's glance is...
...staring up my back.
He's...touching my ass.
My s-skin is tingling.
And he's not even touching me..
That's...so frustrating.
More--
More...that much more?
If I'm really..
Touched...
Now...
If he were...
To touch me...
Your skin is getting hot.
That's not true!
Frustrating, isn't it, Nana?
I told you, it's not true!
See? Even your breasts are trembling.
This outfit is getting so tight!
Am I right? Aren't you just itching inside?
No...breathing....it's painful.
If Kaoru....if Kaoru right now....touched me...
Just what would I...
With his nail...even just his nail...
It's surprising...thinking about if he's going to touch me or not.
It's as if he's checking first for my shape, and how soft I am.
Nana...
What are you doing, Nana?
Kaoru!
Umm, welcome back!
How long have you been there?
Reflecting on what happened before?
Guess it can't be helped, huh? Nana, you're really...
...a pervert.
Geez!
If you wanted me to change, you should've said so in the first place!
T-T-Today, um...
L-let's take some pictures like this first, Nana.
W-Well, doing this right now would probably be tough... it looks really tight.
And Nana, if you don't want to be naked, you can wear a swimsuit or something.
I-I think it'll be thrilling.
Right, Nana?
I-It couldn't be helped!
T-This is the only thing I have...
Um...
A-A-Are your preparations done?
Yeah, sorry to make you wait.
This time let's have some rules.
Rules?
Because you have a very lewd body, Nana.
I--
A-A-A-And as a man, you'll never know if I can hold myself back or not.
So, if there aren't any problems with the favor, I want you to always say "Sure!"
First, a jab.
Well, that's true, a backup would...
Sure.
Let's begin then, Nana.
Nana, since we're this far already...
A pose. Do any sort of sexy pose you an think of.
No way, just out of the blue...
Oh, I don't know!
T-This?
Very....good....
It's very good.
Nana, you really are a beautiful girl.
See? Look.
Well? You're only standing, but it's sexy, right, Nana?
When you see yourself like that, you agree, right?
Yeah...
Wait, that's not it!
Next one then.
Sure.
Nana, spread your legs a little bit.
Alright.
Look this way, Nana.
This much...
Good...
Was I.. this much...
Nana, one more.
I...
Was I...
...always this perverted?
Very good...
You're so sexy, Nana
Your body looks so sexy in that swimsuit.
All the guys look at you this way.
Good, Nana. Very good! It's really sexy.
Nana, your armpits are really beautiful.
That meat around your belly button is cute, Nana.
I-Idiot!
Your thighs are also cute. All so plump and lively.
I-Idiot!!
It's alright, I'll take pictures of everything.
Ah, you can't do that, Nana. Look this way.
Look at the camera.
Al...right.
Then...next.
Try crouching.
Eh? Crouching?
Crouch?
That's not right, Nana. Not like that.
Spread your knees and crouch down.
Knees?
K-Knees? Spread?
Eh?
Like this?
No...
I've stayed in this pose enough already, right?
It's embarrassing...
Ah, wait, Nana.
A little more...just a little more...
...like that, okay?
No, wait, Kaoru!
W-What are you doing, Kaoru?
No!
Kaoru?
What's wrong, Nana?
"What"...
Weren't we planning this together?
Forget?
We were planning to take pictures of you tied up.
Beside, if it's me doing it, it should be fine, right, Nana?
I suppose I should be a bit more relieved....
W-Wait, Kaoru! This is--
This way it'll be much more stimulating.
Well, you can leave it to me.
Isn't this alright, Nana?
What should I do? I...
...am so excited.
S...Sure, Kaoru.
This... this feeling....
I'm ....being tied up.
Being...tied up.
Oh! Damn, that Kaoru. I...
I'm....getting so aroused...by him....
Nana...
You're beautiful, Nana.
This rope...I can feel it wrapping around me.
Because my eyes can't see, I'm imagining things about my body I've never even thought about.
Nana, you're beautiful.
This rope suits you.
I wouldn't know!
Yeah, that's right.
You can't see.
T-Then, I'll take my time with the pictures and show you later.
W-What are you taking pictures of?
M-My neck?
M-My back?
W-Where are you zooming in to?!
K-Kaoru? Where?
Ah, geez!
I hate not being able to see where he is!
Kaoru's breath...warmth...
But...it's the blindfold's fault!
Kaoru, where are you?
Kao... ru?
Kaoru?
Wai-- no!
Kao-- s-sto-- Kao--
Nana!
That facial expression is good!
I wanted to see that facial expression!
No-- w-wait, Kaoru, you can't!
No!
No, K-Kaoru!
Idiot!!
I thought you were pleased...
Then...you're angry?
O-O-Of course I am! W-W-W-What was that all of a sudden?
But Nana, you didn't realize?
Nana, I can tell you're turned on. You're nipples are really standing up.
T-T-They're not standing, they aren't!
Really now? I don't know about that...
My body...even though it's my body, I...
Well then, Nana...
Look at yourself.
See?
Yours are...kinda...
My...
...getting large.
I...I....
Nana!
See? This shot of your face. Your expression right now.
Huh? I... I...
Would it be alright if I mailed this picture to everyone?
This....this...
Only this one of your face.
Did I have this kind of face?
My...my body...
My facial expression...
I... I...
No...
S-stop...
Kaoru... already...
Ka--
We promised, right? Kaoru!
That if I said "no" that we'd stop! The rule you made!
K-Kaoru!
Did I?
See, just look. This picture.
This face and these nipples are saying "Give me more!"
Before everyone's eyes, you put on a face of a good girl who isn't interested in anything erotic.
It turns out the real Nana has this sort of face.
I want everyone to see this!
This facial expression could change everything.
That the real Nana is a pervert.
Damn, that Kaoru!
Kaoru... with him....
Geez..
Geez, I've completely realized...
I...
That I....
That I'm the same as Kaoru.
I was waiting, Nana.
...was a pervert.
Well then, let's begin, Nana.
Y-Yeah.
We're really doing it?
Huh, what's wrong?
That was supposed to be the plan today.
Come on. Hurry and get ready, Nana.
Alright then...I'll be waiting over here.
Go to the vending machine on the other side and buy some coffee.
Have a safe trip, Nana.