Hamburgers
Teriyaki
Burger
Hey, Eri?
Sex is boring, don't you think?
I think masturbating would feel better.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I thought you and your boyfriend
are really into each other, Chihiro.
Yeah, I do my best to follow his
lead, but it never really feels good.
I've never even cummed once so far.
Isn't that just because you two aren't sexually compatible?
Sexually compatible?
You see, when you're in the
business of doing guys for money,
there are some guys who just make
you feel so unbelievably good.
You get to the point where you're moving
your own hips and cumming uncontrollably.
Yeah, I really hit the jackpot with that old guy back then.
He paid really well too.
For real?
Making money while making yourself feel good?
I'm like, super jealous.
The same old guy's paying me to
have sex with him on Saturday.
Why don't you come with me, Chihiro?
We can have a three-way!
Uh, I don't know...
I don't want to cheat on Yoshiki.
So, then...
How about you just watch us have sex?
It won't count as cheating if you're just watching.
Just watching?
You wanna know more about
what good sex is like, don't you?
Just imagining you watching us do the
deed is already turning me on like crazy.
Well, if all I'll be doing is watching...
Alright great. It's a plan.
I'm gonna let him know!
Sex with an old guy?
I wonder what's so amazing about it...
Go with the flow
Papa Life
Nariyuki! Papa Katsu Girls!!
JK x A wonderful sex life with an old man
H-Hey, wait a minute!
Eri, are you serious?!
Chihiro, get a good look.
See? Isn't his dick amazing?
You're kidding me. It's like double the size of Yoshiki's.
Let me help you feel good, oji-sama.
Let's make your dick get even harder!
So this is how Eri sucks dick?
It's really... dirty...
Oh, no, Chihiro watching me is making me even hornier!
Me too.
Seeing this is making my body...
It's making me so hot!
I love your dick, oji-sama!
So, please, take this huge dick...
And shove it into my pussy!
Wow she even said that.
They're really going to have sex.
They're going to have sex right in front of me!
It's so good!
Your dick's getting even bigger!
It's rubbing all around the deepest parts of my pussy!
Wow, all of that huge thing is going inside her.
It's all hitting inside her pussy!
Ch-Chihiro, are you watching?
Are you watching me having sex?
Yeah, I am.
I'm watching.
You're moving your hips on your own so much!
It's so dirty!
See? Look!
Look!
My nipples are so big and erect!
This is bad. I can't only sit here and watch anymore.
I can't hold myself back.
I want to feel good too.
Oji-sama, just wait a little.
I'm going to make you cum!
I'm going to make this huge dick shoot out its load!
No! No!
If you keep thrusting your dick inside me like that...
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum before you!
So good!
Your dick's twitching! It's getting hotter!
So you're about to cum too?
You're almost going to cum?
Go ahead! Cum!
Pump as much cum inside me as you want!
Huh? No way!
She's letting him cum inside her?
N-No!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Oji-sama!!
I'm cumming!!
I came again!
Your dick's too amazing, oji-sama!
Wow, that's a creampie. That's a creampie, right?
I... I don't even let my boyfriend really do that.
Do you wanna join in, Chihiro?
You wanna touch his huge dick?
T-Touch it?
N-No, I-I don't really want to...
You don't get to see a dick this big everyday, you know?
When are you going to have another opportunity like this?
I-If it's just touching it... it doesn't count as cheating, right?
Come on. What's it gonna be, Chihiro?
I-If you're insisting that much,
then I guess a little wouldn't hurt.
Okay, okay.
Then I'm tagging out.
Wow, it's really huge.
Come on, don't be shy!
You're here to touch it, not just stare at it.
Right.
Go on.
I'm touching it! I'm touching it!!
It's so hot and hard!
And it's pulsating!
See, Chihiro? Isn't his dick amazing?
Why don't you try sucking it? Yeah?
Huh? I couldn't...
H-Hey...
What are you...
I knew it!
Your pussy's on fire.
You got turned on from watching us fuck, didn't you?
B-But, I...
Try giving him a blowjob.
Having that thing fuck your mouth feels amazing!
This is really bad. I really can't hold myself back!
I'm so sorry, Yoshiki!
Yeah, that's it.
Now it's your turn to show us how dirty you are.
Oh god, no...
More! I want to taste more of it!
I want to feel this dick!
You're really getting into it!
You were that hungry for a dick, huh?
So dirty.
No, don't say that!
This is all your fault, Eri!
It has such a strong taste!
And it has such a lewd smell.
What's up with this animal-like dick?!
I... I can't hold back!
I can't stop myself!
Oji-san, you don't have to hold anything back.
Just shoot your cum onto Chihiro whenever you want to.
Give her that thick cum.
Sure.
The veins are bulging and it's starting to twitch.
He's going to cum.
I'm going to be covered in the
cum of a guy who's not Yoshiki!
Good. You cum too, Chihiro!
N-No, I can't!
No! No!
I'm gonna cum!
I knew it. You're hooked on his dick now too.
B-But, how could I not...
It looks like he's pretty into you too, Chihiro.
So, Chihiro?
What are you going to do?
H-Hey... Eri? Don't touch me the...
Your pussy's already soaked. Doesn't
that mean that you want to have sex?
Am I wrong?
I can't think straight!
I don't care about cheating anymore!
Oji-sama?
Looks like she's ready to go.
Alright then.
What's going to happen to my pussy
when this huge dick goes inside it?
It's huge!
Don't tell me you came just by him putting it inside.
What... Is this what cumming feels like?
This is too much!
Your dick is really amazing, oji-sama.
You've already got Chihiro head over heels for it.
What is this?
This is too much!
I won't be able to go back to regular dicks after this!
Chihiro, how's his dick?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Isn't it addictive?
His dick is hitting me all the way inside!
I can't believe it!
I can't believe that sex feels this good!
Your boobs are so soft, Chihiro.
D-Don't... rub...
My boobs...
They feel so good!
Look at your clitoris. It's hard.
Right there... Don't!
Don't...
N-No, stop!
If you keep going like that, I'm gonna...
Your body's extra sensitive because you just came.
Right now, I bet you could keep
cumming several times in a row.
N-No... That can't...
No!
S-Something... Something's coming!
No!!
Oji-sama, please teach her all about how good sex feels.
Sure.
I won't be able to have sex with Yoshiki
anymore if I keep having this amazing sex!
Their dicks are really that different?
Yeah, they're completely different!
It's stretching out my pussy and reaching
places that his dick never reached before!
It's thrusting all the way inside me!
This... This is bad! My head's getting all messed up!
Good, keep it up. Go crazy.
Get hooked on his dick just like I am.
This is what good sex feels like!
This is what a good dick feels like!
It feels good! It feels so good!
Chihiro, it looks like he's about to cum too.
N-No! I-Is he... Is he going to cum inside my pussy again?!
If he floods my pussy like that
again, I'm gonna get pregnant!
Don't worry. It's fine.
Even if you get pregnant, he'll look after the child.
His dick's getting bigger and bigger!
And it's starting to pulse really hard! I
can tell something really big's coming!
No...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
He came inside... There's so much hot stuff inside me...
Chihiro, you're shaking all over. I think
you let yourself go a little too much.
I-I've never felt like this before...
But we're just getting started.
Isn't that right, oji-sama?
Oji-sama, you're amazing! You're already this hard again!
Let me clean you up, oji-sama!
Having a three-way with two girls as cute as us
isn't something you get to experience too often.
Wow, I'm already getting into the
mood, just by giving him a tit-fuck.
What should I do?
Chihiro, your nipples are getting really hard.
Yeah, my pussy's getting really wet too.
My body's getting so hot!
It wants your dick so bad, it can't help itself!
Me too.
Seeing Chihiro get nailed like that made my pussy so wet!
Hey, oji-sama, put it inside my pussy next.
Your dick is so stick with my saliva and your pre-cum!
It has such a dirty smell.
His dick is starting to twitch!
So, he feels good too?
Go ahead, oji-sama.
Just cum whenever you want to!
Shoot your huge load all over our tit-pussies!
Oh no, just having your dick rub against
my boobs is enough to turn me on!
Oji-sama, hurry... please give it to us!
We're gonna squeeze out your cum with our boobs.
Come on! Come on!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
Cover us in it!
This isn't even just a private beach, it's a private island!
Oji-sama, you're the best!
So good! Your dick really is the best!
I love it!
It's going so deep inside!
I want your dick too...
Please give me your thick dick too!
Fuck me...
Wow, Chihiro, you're so bold!
You're spreading your legs so far!
I can see all of your pussy!
Look! Look!
I'm masturbating!
I want your dick so bad.
I can't wait any longer!
I'm churning up my insides!
It's coming... Your dick is coming
so hard and deep inside me!
You're really turned on right now, oji-sama.
You're getting turned on from Chihiro's masturbation!
No...
I can't stop!
I'm getting dirtier and dirtier!
I'm getting so turned on from you watching me, oji-sama!
Oji-sama... do me!
Do me harder!
It's okay.
You can be a little rough with me!
Make a mess out of my pussy!
Eri looks like she's feeling really good.
Are you about to cum with his dick?
Are you already going to cum?
This is bad. If you keep doing me
this hard, I'm gonna hit my limit!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Me too! I'm going to cum again!
My body's on fire!
My pussy's quivering!
Oji-sama?
Please... cum! Cum!
Cum inside me!
I'm cumming!!
This... This is what I wanted!
Your dick's filling every last bit of my pussy!
I'm getting licked by you!
You're sucking out all the cum you just shot in me!
Eri? I'm really happy that you asked me to come.
I had no clue that sex and dicks could feel this good!
Well I thought it'd be more fun if you came along!
It's embarrassing having someone watch you
have sex, but it kind of really turns me on!
I know what you mean!
I really know what you mean!
I feel amazing just from him putting it inside me!
Maybe that's what I want... to be watched.
Maybe I want someone to see
every last embarrassing part of me!
Wow, that makes you a big pervert, Chihiro.
Just like me!
What should I do? My pussy's being stretched out so far!
It's starting to get used to your huge dick, oji-sama!
My pussy's going to be so stretched out!
That's fine. There's no other dick better than his anyway.
He'll just keep satisfying us forever.
Oji-sama, you're thrusting it inside me!
You're going so deep... all the way to my womb!
Your thick dick is thrusting inside me!
S-So good!
It feels so good!
Oji-sama, shove it in me more!
Feel all the pleasure you can from my dirty pussy!
Oji-sama, thrust it in me! Thrust it in me! Thrust it!
Thrust it in me more!
I've never felt anything this amazing before!
This... This is making me go crazy!
Me too! I'm becoming even dirtier!
I'm losing my mind!
Oji-sama...
Does it feel good for you too, oji-sama?
Are you feeling good from our pussies?
It's okay. If it's the two of us, I'm sure we'll
both be happy to have you cum inside us!
Shoot as much as you want inside of us!
Oh, god... I-I'm gonna cum again!
Your dick is gonna make me cum again!
Eri... Me too!
I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum with my pussy!
We... We should all cum together!
You too, oji-sama!
Yeah, that sounds good!
Something big's coming!
Oji-sama, that's good!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!!
Y-Your dick is getting bigger again!
It's getting so hot!
It's twitching so hard!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Oji-sama!
Oji-sama's dick was so amazing.
I'm gonna break up with Yoshiki,
He doesn't even compare to oji-sama.
Yeah, we're done.
Let's have some fun together again some time.
Yeah!
Yeah, let's have lots of fun with his dick!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч