Hey, Eri...
Isn't sex kind of boring?
I think masturbation feels a lot better.
Eh... What's the matter?
Aren't you all lovey-dovey
with your boyfriend, Chihiro?
Well, I tried to talk to him about it.
I told him that it doesn't feel that good...
You see, he never ever made me come even once.
Doesn't that just mean your bodies aren't as compatible.
Not compatible?
I'm into compensated dating, you see...
And sometimes I get to have some sex
that feels surprisingly good from men.
And you know what? In my last work I was shaking my hips,
and I've been coming like hell!
That middle-aged man is a winner for sure.
The payment I got was also amazing!
For real? You feel good and get paid a lot too?
I really envy you...
I'm going with that man again on this coming Saturday.
How about joining us if you'd like to, Chihiro?
They call it a threesome.
Eh... That's kind of...
I don't want to cheat on Yoshiki.
Then...
How about watching us having sex?
It's not cheating if you'll only watch, right?
Only watch...
Are you not curious about how sex can feel good?
The thought of you watching us excites me!
Well, if I'll only be watching....
Alright, it's decided then!
I'll have to let him know about it!
Sex with a middle-aged man...
I wonder what's so amazing about it.
Nariyuki: Papakatsu Girls!!
Outcome →
PAPActivity Girls!!
Highschool Girls and A Middle-aged Man's Pleasurable Sex Life
Ehh... Wait a minute!
Eri... are you for real?
Chihiro, look!
See, isn't his cock amazing?
This can't be... It's about twice as big as Yoshiki's cock!
Hey mister, I want you to feel good a lot.
Get your cock even way harder.
So that's how Eri's blowjob is.
She looks so lewd somehow.
Oh no... I get so turned on from the
fact that Chihiro is watching me!
It's the same for me as well... If I am
to be shown something like this...
My body will get hot.
I love your cock so much, mister!
Hey, I beg you...
Use this huge cock...
Thrust it into my pussy!
Wow... She said such words...
They're really gonna do it!
They're gonna have sex in front of me...
Yes... Good!
Your cock got bigger again!
You're hitting up to the deepest parts of my pussy!
Wow, it's amazing!
That whole huge thing is going inside.
It's going inside Eri's pussy!
Ch-Chihiro, can you see it?
Do you have a good view of me getting fucked!
Yeah, I see it. I can see it!
You're shaking your hips on your own!
You look so lewd!
Here! Look! Look over here!
My nipples got this hard too!
This is bad... Even if I'm just watching...
I can't hold myself back!
I want to feel good as well!
Hey mister! Just you wait, okay?
I am gonna make you come!
I'm gonna make this cock spurt!
No! No!
If you keep thrusting your cock,
I'm gonna come!
I'm gonna come before you do!
Amazing! Your cock is twitching!
It's getting hotter!
You're gonna come too! It's gonna come out!
It's alright, shoot it out!
Shoot your semen inside my pussy all you want!
That can't be! Are they gonna go that far?
I can't take it anymore, I'm also gonna come!
Coming! I'm coming!
M-Mister!
I'm coming!
I came again!
Your cock is so amazing, mister!
Woah... Creampie! It's a creampie, right?
Even I never let my boyfriend do something that risky...
Hey, how about you, Chihiro?
Want to try touching his cock?
T-Touch it? That's...
I'm fine.
Does this huge cock not pique your interest?
Since you're here already, so...
If it's just touching...
It won't be cheating, right?
Hey there! what are you gonna do, Chihiro?
If you put it that way, then maybe just a little...
Okay then, we'll be switching places.
Woah... It really is huge.
Hey there, come on!
Don't just stare. Try touching it.
Okay...
Here you go.
I touched it... I touched it!
Wow... It's hot and hard...
And it's twitching.
Hey, Chihiro...
Isn't his cock amazing?
How about you suck it a little, okay?
Eh? That's...
W-Wait! What are you doing?
I knew it!
Your pussy already got this hot!
Did you not get horny from
watching us having sex?
But that's because...
Try giving him a blowjob.
It will feel like your mouth is
being raped and it's incredible!
Woah... I can't really help it.
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Forgive me, Yoshiki!
Yes, yes, just like that!
Show us your very lewd self this time!
I can't take it anymore!
More! I want to savor this more!
I want to feel this cock more!
You're being very proactive!
You're craving for a cock so much!
How indecent!
No... Don't say it like that!
It's your fault, Eri!
It has such a strong taste, and a lewd scent as well.
What's with this brutish stud cock?
This isn't good!
I can't stop myself!
Hey, mister! You don't have to hold back, okay?
If you're gonna come,
you can spray your slimy semen
all over Chihiro anytime you want.
Yeah...
His veins are popping out and
his blood rushes through them.
I'm gonna get poured with semen.
I'm gonna get splashed with semen
by a man other than Yoshiki!
Alright! Come together with him as well, Chihiro!
I can't do that! This is bad!
Chihiro ended up getting a taste of his cock too. I knew it!
That's because... I'm already...
He seems to like you too...
Hey, Chihiro! What are you gonna do?
Wait, Eri! Don't play with it so much!
Your pussy is already this drenched.
The truth is you want to do it, right?
I can't think straight anymore!
Cheating? I don't care anymore!
Hey mister!
Chihiro is already prepared for you.
Okay, then.
If this huge cock goes inside,
what will happen to my pussy?
It's so big!
Don't tell me you already came
just from putting it inside?
What? Is this what they call orgasm?
My head went blank just now!
Your cock really is amazing, mister!
You already got Chihiro allured on it!
What's with this? Incredible!
Now that I know about this cock, I'm already...
Chihiro... How's his cock? Feels good, right?
Isn't it addictive!
His cock is hitting deep inside me!
I can't believe this!
To think that sex can feel this good...
Your tits are very soft!
No...
Eri... That's my... Don't rub them!
My tits...
They feel good!
And your clitoris too.
It's hard as well!
Not there!
Eri... Don't do that!
No... Stop it already!
If you keep doing that, I'm...
Your whole body is so sensitive
since you just came earlier.
You'll keep on coming one after another with that.
Don't... Not that... That's...
No... You can't...
No... Coming...
Something's coming again!
No!
Hey mister, teach that girl a lot today
about the pleasure of sex!
Yeah...
Now that I know about sex that feels this good!
I won't be able to do it with Yoshiki anymore!
So it feels so far compared to your boyfriend!
Yeah, it feels completely different!
It's going in parts of my pussy that
nothing have ever reached before!
It's pushing around my deepest parts inside!
This is incredible!
Nothing else is going in my head anymore!
It's okay, it's okay. Go crazy!
Get hooked on his cock together with me!
This is a pleasurable sex!
This is a pleasurable cock!
I can feel it! I'm feeling good!
Chihiro, it seems that he's gonna come any time now!
No... He's coming inside again?
Is he gonna shoot into my pussy?
If he comes that much in me,
I'm gonna get pregnant!
It's alright!
Even if you get pregnant,
he'll take care of everything for you.
N-No....
His cock is getting bigger... It's filling me up inside!
Something big is coming!
I can't take it anymore!
Coming... Coming... Coming!
I'm coming!
Creampie...
There so much of hot stuff coming inside me.
Chihiro, you're body was trembling so much.
Did that blow your mind a little too much?
That's because... This...
I never had anything like this before.
We've only just begun. Am I right, mister?
You're amazing, mister.
You already got hard again.
We're going to make your cock clean.
It's not every day that we can have
a threesome with this adorable thing!
Oh no, I'm just giving a titfuck,
but I'm getting in the lewd mood again. What should I do?
Your nipples got so hard, Chihiro!
Yeah, and my pussy is dripping wet already.
My body is gradually getting hotter.
I'm craving for his cock that I can't help it!
It's the same for me too.
After seeing Chihiro getting fucked,
my pussy got so wet.
Hey, mister!
Put it inside my pussy next.
His cock is sticky with both his
pre-cum and our drool all over it!
It's giving off a very lewd scent.
Oh no... His cock is twitching all over!
He's feeling good from this.
It's alright, mister.
You can come whenever you like.
Shoot a lot of it on our tits... On our tit-pussies!
Oh no...
My tits feel good
from just rubbing them with your cock!
Mister... Hurry... Hurry up and give it to us!
We're gonna squeeze you dry
of semen using our tit-pussies!
Here you go!
Come! Come! Come!
Shower us with your semen!
Having a private beach,
and even a private island...
Just as expected of you, mister!
You're amazing! Your cock is really good!
It's the best!
It's going in that deep...
I want a cock too...
I want his thick cock
to slide in and out of my pussy too!
Oh my... You're so bold, Chihiro!
You're spreading your legs open so much!
Your pussy is out for the world to see!
Look, look at me!
I am masturbating!
I wanted his cock so much
that I can't take it anymore!
I'm fingering my pussy!
It's coming! Your cock is rapidly
thrusting deep inside me!
You're getting excited, mister!
You got so turned on after seeing Chihiro masturbating!
No... I can't stop myself already!
I'm getting more lewd by the minute!
Being watched by you
makes me feel so good!
Do it, mister!
Pound me harder! That's good!
You can be a little more intense!
Mess my pussy up!
Make a mess out of it!
Eri, you're feeling very good.
Are you gonna come? Are you
already coming from his cock?
This is bad! If I'm gonna get fucked so intensely...
I'm already at my limit!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Me too... I'm gonna come again!
My body is burning! My pussy is twitching!
I beg you, mister!
Come! Come! Come!
Give me a creampie!
I'm coming!
This is it! This is what I wanted all along!
My pussy is filled up with your cock!
You're licking me down there!
A-All of the semen you shot inside my pussy...
They're all getting sucked out!
Eri... I'm...
I'm really grateful of you for inviting me that time!
I never knew before that sex and cocks
can feel this good!
T-That's because doing this with you
is more fun than me doing it alone!
Being watched having sex is embarrassing,
but it makes me feel more excited!
I know, I really know what you're saying!
I'm getting excited while being watched right now!
It's like, I want to be watched!
I want my embarrassing parts to be seen!
Wow! Chihiro, it means you're a pervert!
We're the same!
What should I do? My pussy is getting stretched wider!
It's getting used on taking his huge cock in!
My pussy will end up gaping loose!
It's okay, he's an outstanding man!
He's capable of getting both
of us satisfied all the time!
You're poking in it, mister!
Deep inside my pussy, up to my womb!
Your fat cock is poking in it!
G-Good! That feels good!
Thrust it more inside me, mister!
My dirty pussy...
Have a good taste of my lewd pussy!
Hey, mister... Thrust it in! Thrust it! Thrust it!
Thrust it a lot more inside me!
I never had anything amazing like this before!
I'm... I'm going crazy!
Me too... I getting more lewd!
I'm losing my mind!
Mister... Are you feeling good too?
Our pussies are feeling good a lot!
It's alright... If it's with you...
We're okay with getting a creampie!
Shoot your semen out all you want!
This is bad! I'm gonna come again!
Your cock is gonna make me come again!
E-Eri... Me too...
I'm gonna come too! I'm coming with my pussy!
Hey... Together... Let's all come together!
Together with mister!
Yeah, let's do that!
It feels good, I'm gonna come!
T-That's good, mister!
I'm gonna come already! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Your cock is getting bigger and bigger again!
It's getting hotter! It's twitching!
I'm coming! I'm coming, coming, coming!
Mister!
His cock was fantastic!
I already broke up with Yoshiki!
He's got nothing compared to mister!
It's impossible!
Let's both have fun again next time!
Yeah! Let's have a lot of fun with his cock!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization