Hey, Eri...
Are we really doing this?
Of course! It's a request from mister!
If you don't do this right,
he won't put his cock inside.
Jeez... I'll do it, alright!
I just have to do it, right?
You're such a pervert, mister!
Hey, come on, Chihiro!
This is a livestream so go and start talking!
I am...
...in front of the camera right now...
...and I'm masturbating!
This is embarrassing!
You say that but your pussy is already a mess!
It's because since that last time...
I couldn't forget about his cock...
So I've been masturbating a lot of times!
Oh no! What should I do?!
My fingers are going inside with ease!
My pussy got so mushy already!
My nipples are hard as nails as well!
You're doing good! It's just like an adult video!
This is getting filmed... I'm getting filmed!
My masturbation...
Oh, très bien!
...is being watched by people all over the world!
! خام
Even though this is so embarrassing...
This is bad! I can't hold it back anymore!
Hey, mister! Please put it in!
I'll do whatever you say!
So stir my pussy using your huge cock!
Huh? Don't tell me that you already came?
Yeah... I came!
I came just from having his cock inserted inside me!
This is it! This is what I wanted all along!
His cock is so hard and huge...
...and it feels so good!
There, there, there!
I'm totally filming you having sex, Chihiro!
That's fine! Film me!
Film me a lot more!
Somehow... getting filmed makes
me feel more aroused than usual!
I'm feeling more and more lewd!
Mister...
You're kneading my tits!
Hey... I'm begging you! Play with my nipples as well!
Rub them!
Mister, you're so good at this!
Good! It feels good! I'm feeling it!
Every person that watches this livestream
is masturbating on you right now!
No! Stop saying weird stuffs like that!
Just imagining that makes my heart throb!
My body is feeling numb!
Mister... I'm sorry!
I'm already at my limit!
I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
I knew it... It feels good!
Your cock feels so good, mister!
Jeez... You're having fun on your own!
Let me have a turn as well!
But I can't stop myself!
His cock is so good that my hips
are shaking on their own!
Maybe I should punish a bad girl like you!
Huh? Wh-What is that thing?
Chihiro, you don't have any
experience in your ass yet, right?
I'll help myself with your first time.
Wait a second! You can't do that!
In my ass... No way!
No, no, that's impossible! It won't go in!
It's alright, it's alright!
Assholes can stretch wider than you think!
Look, it went inside!
Y-You can't... You can't!
No way... Pull it out!
Hey, mister!
Let's teach Chihiro about the pleasures
of double penetration!
S-Stop it, mister! Don't move!
No! No way!
They're rubbing... They're rubbing
against each other in my belly!
Just bear with it a little, okay?
It'll start to feel good in no time!
No! Eri, you can't!
My ass... Stop piston pumping my asshole!
No, no, you can't!
Chihiro, your ass is pulling inward...
and sucking my cock!
The truth is it's delighted!
I'm talking about your ass-pussy, Chihiro!
Y-You're lying! No way!
No... No—!
Stop this already!
Stop stirring it inside!
No way! If you do it so roughly!
My ass will get torn!
I'll get crazy!
That's alright! Come on, come on!
Get more and more crazy!
Why am I like this?!
Even though my pussy and ass
are both getting violated...
I'm feeling hot!
It feels so hot!
Right, right! That's the way!
Loosen your body up and make yourself feel it a lot!
No, you can't!
Mister, your cock is throbbing!
It's getting bigger!
I-Is it coming out? Is it gonna come out?
Are you going to ejaculate?
Your pussy is squeezing tightly,
so it looks like he can't bear it anymore as well!
N-No way! If he comes inside me now...
I'm sure that it'll feel incredibly good!
Mister... Eri...
I don't care whatever happens anymore!
Come... Come... Come!
I'm gonna come...
I'm gonna come from double penetration!
Okay! Come on, come, come!
Please, mister!
You should come as well! Shoot it out, shoot it out!
Shoot lots and lots
of your semen into my pussy!
Amazing...
I never had anything like this before!
I can't move my legs anymore!
Didn't it feel incredibly good?
You should be grateful to us!
Y-Yeah... Thank you...
Well then, for the next time
We'll show you lots and lots of me having sex!
Look forward to it, everyone!
Bye-bye!
Wait, Eri... Is this place...
Is everyone watching us?
This is our zero-gravity masturbation!
It's my first time to do something like this!
My body feels light!
This is bad! I'm gonna come already!
I'm gonna come in the outer space!
Me too!
I can't take it anymore!
Isn't the Earth blue...
You're right...
Mister! This feels good!
It keeps on rapidly hitting deep in my pussy!
Wow... Eri is feeling so good in front of everyone!
She is so lewd!
Hey, Chihiro...
Please, give me that cock!
I want a cock in my ass... my ass-pussy as well...
I want it!
Y-Yeah...
Alright then, I'll do it! I'm doing it!
It's alright, come on! You don't have to hold back.
Ram that cock into my ass with all your strength!
E-Eri... Are you alright?
Y-Yeah! I'm fine!
Your cock just felt so good that I came.
Wait, mister!
I'm okay! Start moving as well, Chihiro!
Harder... You can do it harder!
I-I understand...
Incredible!
The cocks are... The cocks are hitting each other!
They're rubbing against each other!
This is dangerous! This is kind of dangerous!
Eri, you're moaning with such a lewd voice!
Does it really feel good in your ass?
Yeah! This is the best!
Both of my ass and my pussy feel incredibly good!
I feel like I'm flying away!
No way, jeez! If you say something like that...
I'll start to get excited as well!
So even the ass feels good from something like this!
It does! Yes, it does!
You'll get addicted on this too when you get used to it!
Double penetration feels unbelievably good!
H-Hey, Chihiro!
I wonder if the audience can see us well!
Yeah! The big screen is doing a good job
of showing what we're doing!
I'm glad!
Watch me! Everyone, watch me!
I'm getting fucked by cocks!
Both of my pussy and my ass-pussy
are getting fucked by cocks!
I'm getting more and more lewd!
Eri... Your asshole is getting tighter!
This is bad! I'm gonna come already! I'm coming!
Mister! I'm begging you! Shoot it out!
I want you to make me come a lot
with your semen!
Amazing! It's gonna come! It's coming!
Coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Wow! So sex can make one feel this much pleasure.
It felt incredibly good...
Hey, mister!
I also want to feel even better!
I want to try having a hardcore sex!
Huh? What is this, mister?
I think I know what that is! Hand it over!
Eri... Could that thing be...
That's right! With this shiny golden cock,
our pussies will become connected!
B-But that's... Even though we're both girls...
That's embarrassing!
What are you saying?
Haven't we both already seen
each one's shameful side quite enough?
Come on! Hurry up already!
Didn't you want to try having
a more hardcore sex? Right?
Yeah... I want to!
I also want to feel even a lot better!
It went inside!
I'm now having sex with you, Chihiro!
No way! I can see where it enters both of us!
I somehow feel strange! My heart is beating so fast!
Hey, Chihiro! Are you feeling good?
It's good! It feels unbelievably good!
My hips are shaking on their own too!
I'm getting more and more lewd!
You can do it harder!
I'll move as well! I'll thrust it a lot
in your pussy too, Chihiro!
Let's both feel good together, us two!
I see, I'm sorry! You want to join too. Right, mister?
Oh, this middle-aged man... His cock got this hard again!
He got aroused from seeing us having sex!
Mister! Give your cock to me as well!
Let me suck your cock!
Incredible! While I'm in this lewd pose,
a cock is wreaking havoc in my body!
No way, Eri...
If you move that intensely,
you'll drive me crazy as well!
Feels good! It feels good!
Chihiro, keep thrusting a lot more!
I'm fucking Eri with a cock,
Eri is fucking my pussy
and mister is fucking my mouth!
My head is already a mess inside!
Chihiro! Your pussy is squeezing tightly!
You're also amazing, Eri!
Your pussy feels so hot and it's mushy!
It's so lewd!
Mister, are you putting it in?
Are you putting your cock in my ass?
It's alright, put it in!
Use your huge cock on my ass and make a mess...
Make a mess out of it!
Good!
Amazing! I can feel it reverberating!
It's like his cock is
fucking both of us at the same time!
I can't take it anymore!
M-Mister... I'm sorry!
I'm gonna come right now! I'm gonna come!
Eri, I'm gonna come too!
I'm going to come! I feel so hot!
My body feels so hot!
Mister! Please!
Come... come... come! I'm begging you!
T-Together...
Come together with us!
Shoot me with your semen!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
I-I came...
...a lot again!
This could become a bad habit of mine...
Yeah...
Sex with mister really is the best!
I won't be able to stop myself...
from having a sugar daddy!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization