H-Hey, Eri?
Are we really doing this?
Of course!
It's a request from him, after all!
You won't get his dick inside you if you don't do it.
F-Fine, I'll do it.
I'll do it, okay?
You're really such a pervert.
Come on, Chihiro. This is being broadcasted,
so do it with more enthusiasm!
Right now, I'm in front of a camera... masturbating!
This is so embarrassing!
Despite that, your pussy's so incredibly wet.
B-But that's because I can't forget the feel of his dick!
I've masturbated so many times after that, that's why...
No! What should I do?
My fingers are just sliding in!
My pussy's becoming a wet mess!
My nipples are so hard too!
You're doing great! This looks like a real porno!
I'm being filmed... I'm letting myself be filmed!
My masturbation's being seen...
Tres bien!
By people all over the world.
Come on.
This is so embarrassing, but it's too late! I can't stop!
H-Hey, please put your dick inside me!
I'll do anything you ask me to do.
So please mess up my pussy with your huge dick!
Huh? Don't tell me you came from that.
Yeah... I did.
I came from him just putting his dick inside me.
Yes! This is what I wanted!
Your dick's so hard and big!
It feels so good!
Come on, come on!
Don't worry, I'm getting every last second
of him pounding you with his dick.
That's good! Film it!
Film more of it!
This is turning me on more than usual!
It's making me feel dirtier than usual!
H-He's rubbing my boobs!
P-Please play with my nipples too!
Rub them good!
You're so good at this!
Good! It feels so good!
I can really feel it!
Everyone watching this stream is jacking off to you, Chihiro.
No! Keep that weird stuff to yourself!
Just even thinking about it makes my heart race!
It makes my body so tingly!
Oji-sama! I'm sorry!
I'm at my limit!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It really feels so good.
Your dick really feels so good!
It's no fair if you have all the fun.
Let me have a turn!
B-But I can't stop!
His dick feels so good, I can't stop moving my hips!
I think a bad girl like you needs to be punished.
What's that?
You've never done anal before, have you?
I think I'll take your first time.
W-Wait! D-Don't do it!
I can't take it in the ass!
There's no way! Absolutely no way!
It won't fit!
It'll be okay.
Assholes can be spread wider than you'd think.
See? It's inside.
N-No! No!
No! Take it out!
Hey, Oji-san, let's teach Chihiro what
it's like to have two dicks in her at once.
S-Stop, oji-sama!
Don't move! No!
I-It's rubbing against my stomach!
Just hold on for a little longer, okay?
I'll make sure you feel good.
N-No! Eri, stop!
Don't move that hard in my ass!
No! No!
Your ass is twitching.
It's sucking in my dick!
It really likes it.
Your ass-pussy loves it.
No! That can't be!
No!
Please stop!
Don't move it like that!
I-If you're so rough, my ass is gonna break!
It's gonna make me go crazy!
That's okay. Come on, more...
Let yourself become even crazier!
Wh-Why?! My ass and pussy are being ravaged, but...
My body feels like it's on fire.
It's so hot!
Yeah, good. Keep it up.
Just relax and let your body experience the pleasure!
No! No!
Oji-sama's dick is starting to twitch!
It's getting even bigger!
I-It's gonna cum! It's gonna cum!
It's gonna ejaculate!
Your pussy's been nonstop squeezing on his dick,
so I think he's about at his limit.
B-But if I get creampied now, I'm gonna...
I bet it'll feel extremely good!
Oji-sama... Eri... I don't care what happens anymore!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum from these two dicks!
Okay! Cum! Cum!
Please, oji-sama!
You cum too, oji-sama!
Cum! Cum!
Fill me with your cum!
Wow...
I've never felt like this before...
I can't even move my legs...
Felt really good, didn't it?
You should thank us.
Yeah... thanks...
I'm up next and I'm ready to show you lots
of naughty scenes with me. Look forward to it!
Bye bye!
Wait, Eri, is this...
Are you all watching?
Are you watching our zero gravity masturbation?
I've never felt anything like this before.
My body feels so light.
I'm already about to cum!
I'm going to cum in space!
Me too!
I-I'm gonna cum!
The earth's so blue.
It really is.
Oji-sama, this is so good!
It's hitting me so deep inside!
Wow, Eri's getting so turned on in front of the crowd.
She's so dirty.
H-Hey, Chihiro?
Please give me your dick!
I want a dick in my ass... my ass-pussy!
I want it!
Y-Yeah. Here I come.
I'm coming.
Yeah! Come!
Just shove it in there with everything you got!
E-Eri, are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
I just came because it felt too good. That's it.
O-Oji-sama?!
I-I'm okay!
You should move too, Chihiro!
Y-You can be as rough as you want to be!
Okay.
Wow, they're hitting against each other!
They're rubbing against each other!
Oh my god, this is... this is insane!
You sound so dirty right now, Eri.
Does your ass really feel that good?
Yeah! It feels amazing!
My ass and pussy feel so amazing!
I feel like my mind's going blank!
No, if you keep talking like that,
you're going to make me excited too!
So anal feels that good, huh?
It does! It really does!
When you're used to it,
you'll like it even more, Chihiro.
Double dicks are so good!
H-Hey Chihiro, do you think
the audience can see this all right?
Y-Yeah, they fan see it on the big screen.
There's a crystal clear image of you up there.
Thank goodness.
Watch! Everyone watch me!
I'm being fucked by a dick!
My pussy and my ass-pussy are both being
fucked by dicks! They're becoming dirtier and dirtier!
Eri, your ass is becoming really tight!
Oh no, I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Oji-sama, please cum.
Make me cum really hard with your cum!
So good! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Sex can really feel that good?
It felt so good...
Hey, oji-sama, I want to feel really good too...
I want to try having crazy good sex too!
What is this, oji-sama?
Oh, I think I know what that is.
Let me see it.
Eri, is that...
That's right. We're going to connect
our pussies with this golden dick.
B-But, that's...
We're both girls. That's embarrassing...
What are you talking about? We've both seen
each other in tons of embarrassing situations.
Come on, hurry!
You want to try even better sex, don't you?
Right?
Yeah, I do.
I want to feel better than I ever have!
It's inside!
I'm having sex with you.
Everyone can see us having sex!
It kinda feels weird.
It's really making my heart race!
Hey, Chihiro, does it feel good?
It does!
It feels so good!
My hips are moving on their own!
I feel myself getting even dirtier!
You can be rougher.
I'll move more too!
I'll thrust it in your pussy really hard!
Let's feel good together!
Here.
Oh, right. Sorry. You're in this with us too, oji-sama.
You're already so hard again, oji-sama.
He got turned on by watching us have sex!
Oji-sama, give me your dick too!
Let me suck your dick!
Wow, I'm in this dirty position while
a dick is rampaging around inside of me!
No, Eri, if you're that rough, I'm gonna lose my mind!
It feels so good!
It feels really good!
Chihiro, shove it in me more!
I'm fucking Eri with a dick
and Eri's fucking me with a dick.
And oji-sama's fucking my mouth with his dick!
My head's a mess!
Chihiro, your pussy is tightening around me so hard!
Eri, you're so amazing!
Your pussy's so hot! It's getting so wet!
You're so dirty!
Oji-sama, are you going to put it in?
Are you going to put your dick inside my ass?
Go ahead, put it in.
Make a mess of my ass with your huge dick!
W-Wow I can feel its every move!
It's like he's fucking both of us with his dick!
I-I can't...
Oji-sama, I'm sorry, but I'm going to cum already!
I'm going to cum!
Eri, I'm going to cum too!
My pussy's gonna cum!
It's so hot! My body's on fire!
Oji-sama!
Please, cum! Cum! Cum!
Please!
Cum... cum together with us!
Shoot your cum all over us!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I came so much again...
I could really get hooked on this...
Yeah, sex with oji-sama is really the best...
I don't think I can give up this sugar daddy life.
translator: hikarucon
timing: govna (да, хреновый тайминг...)
edit: braden
quality control: fyurie (а этот вообще непонятно зачем нужен...)
softsub: торрент иваниваныч