On the 30-minute ride I take, something upsetting always happens.
Today as well.
W
Natsumushi
Funeral Flowers for Winter Insects
「
」
The train is about to leave.
Please do not try to rush onboard!
I've tried changing trains several times, but...
Somehow, he always finds me.
At one point, someone nearly found out, but...
I couldn't stop him from convincing them that
it was under some sort of mutual consent.
I've never had the courage to say what I want...
That's why,
every day, this man feels me up...
The only thing I can do is bear with it...
I-I have to bear with this...
I can't make him angry, so...!
No! Not... Not my butt again-!
He's going to play with it again!
Huh...?
I wonder what happened...
Has he had enough?
Don't worry, Tomoe-chan...
We're not done yet.
What does he mean?
What's wrong? Don't tell me that...
You wanted more?
No, I didn't!
Why would I think that?
There's no way...
Then how about this?
If you can look me in the eye and say that you don't want this,
then I won't do it anymore.
I can say it...
I can say it!
I can say that much, can't I?
I can... I must...
I must-!
I must say it properly-!
I must say it!
Um...!
We apologize for the crowded carriages.
Please let the passengers getting off exit first.
The train at station number two is about to leave.
There's no way she could have said it anyway.
She's a girl who bottles things up.
I guess she did pretty well by looking me in the face, though.
She sure is brave and fun to bully!
I guess I'll have some fun with her while she's discouraged about herself.
I'm sorry!
No, that's okay.
Hey-! W-Wait! What is this?!
No-!
Let me go!
Please let me go!
You probably shouldn't shout so much...
It might be bad if someone found you.
Are you that scared?
If you really are, bite my tongue as hard as you can.
N-No! He's licking inside my mouth...
H-He said I should bite...
There's no way I could...
You didn't bite me.
He's saying that because he knows I couldn't do it.
That's unfair!
Wha-?!
What are you doing?!
D-Don't-!
Your wet tights smell good, Tomoe-chan...
N-No, don't! Please don't sniff me!
Huh? You want me to lick instead?
N-No!
S-Stop! I-I'm dirty down there!
Hey Tomoe-chan, your juices are soaking through your panties.
T-That's not true!
T-That's your saliva!
I guess I'll compensate with this...
Huh? What a great reaction!
You must know how and what this is for...
I-If you touch me there, I'll-!
I knew that you were wet!
No, don't... Not there-!
I can't feel your insides like this on the train, so I was worried.
I was worried that you'd become a girl who could only become aroused by your clitoris...
Hey, hey...
You have to take it in properly!
You look like you're fine though, since you're feeling aroused from this.
I-I'm not feeling aroused-!
I was just surprised-! I'm not feeling aroused-!
Oh, right. Don't worry, I've got another one for you.
I hope you'll be satisfied if I put this on your clitoris too.
Please-! Please stop it-!
Huh? What's wrong? Is it too much?
C'mon, you have to say it, otherwise I can't put it any lower...
We're not done yet!
I'm going to make you cum until you've lost your mind!
No! I-If he continues to do it while I'm still cumming-!
No more-!
Oh? You can't hold your voice in any longer?
I wonder what would happen if I played with your favorite hole now?
No-!
N-Not my butt-!
Hmm, you have to tell me what I can't do...
N-No way...!
Hey, if you loosen up at all, my finger might slip in!
P-Please don't rub me there today...
Oh! You actually said it!
Then I must give you your reward.
Yes! You're tightening around me!
Don't-!
N-No! Not at the same time-!
Your muscles tend to squeeze both holes,
so I bet you can feel the vibrator inside you better!
If you keep doing this...!
You must be reaching your limit now...
No!
I don't want to cum from my butt-!
C'mon! Cum again, cum again!
Oh no, you've completely wet yourself!
You can't go outside like this, can you?
Natsumushi
That morning, I was nodding off near the door from last night's work...
Huh-?
H-Hey-!
P-Please-! Don't ask questions, just stay still-!
I was surprised, or rather, I didn't know what was happening and I froze up.
She would rub me with those silky hands, and stroke the tip with her fingers...
Then she would lube me up with my pre-cum...
Does it feel good?
If you do it so much, I'll-!
It's fine. Hurry up, hurry up and cum!
I'd been backed up lately,
and on top of that something like this was happening... I couldn't help myself...
You understand, don't you?
It looked like she was surprised,
however she caught all my semen with her small hand.
N-No, you came so much!
I-I'm sorry...
I sure was surprised...
She was thorough, like she was showing me...
Watching her pink tongue was too arousing...
I became large again, even though I just came.
She flinched for a moment,
but she wouldn't fight back,
and I was surprised at myself for being so aggressive.
For safety reasons, please hold on to the railing or the handles.
I held her skirt up so no one would notice...
The texture of her tights...
She was so soft and smooth...
It seemed that she would get highly aroused from her ass. It was so cute!
Doe your ass feel good?
N-No! There's no way-!
It's like you're sucking me in here, though.
N-No, please don't say such things!
She was trying her best to hold her voice in, but that made it more erotic!
No! Don't do it so roughly-! Not so rough-!
No-!
After she came, I thought I should put my cock in there...
That's enough, Mr. Molester...
U-Um, I-!
Please wait behind the line.
It was unfortunate, however there was a really dangerous look about him.
It couldn't be helped...
Natsumushi
I don't know how long I've been here...
No, I might cum from just looking at your face...
I-I can't move... I-It's so frustrating!
My mind is going blank...
I'm going to cum in your throat, so bear with me.
If you want this to end quickly, try sucking on it.
I-It's painful!
I-I can't breathe properly!
Hurry-!
Please hurry up!
I'm reaching my limit-!
I thought my brain was going to melt from pleasure!
Oh, that's no good, Tomoe-chan...
I let out an extra potent one,
so make sure you taste it before swallowing, okay?
Rinse it around your mouth so you can taste it...
What a strange taste...
It's gooey and it's sticky...
That's very good. I like good girls.
Wait-!
Oh right, I guess you're embarrassed since I've never seen it directly.
N-No, I'm not-!
You're so hard here...
I bet you were waiting for me to do this...
Yes, that's good.
It looks like you're completely wet here, too...
You're quite a lewd girl, aren't you, Tomoe-chan?
N-No, I'm not! That's a lie!
How about we get to the main course?
Huh?
Please... Don't do it...
This the pussy I've been waiting for...
I'll finally take your virginity, Tomoe-chan!
N-No!
I-It's really entering me-!
It's all in!
I-It's throbbing inside me!
Please make my cock feel welcome!
I'll make sure that you remember the sensation... Even if you're home alone...
Virgin pussies sure are tight!
I can't believe I lost my virginity in such a place!
You're sucking me in, so I better cum inside you and not make you wait!
I-Inside? No-! Don't!
I'm gonna cum, cum inside your pussy!
N-No-!
N-Not inside!
No-!
No-! S-So hot-!
I-It's filling me up!
N-No...
I came so much!
No... I said not to do it...
I'll get pregnant...
Sorry about that, Tomoe-chan.
It felt so good that I came inside you a lot!
N-No way...
Um, what are you...?
I can put it in, right?
I-I didn't say such a thing! I...!
No-! No! It's too big!
No! He's putting his cock inside my butt too-!
Tomoe-chan, you're squeezing me here, too!
Geez, I really wish they'd cut me some slack!
Well, they're not doing it because...
N-No! Someone came in!
I can see them peeing...
D-Don't!
N-No... They'll hear me!
They'll see me here and... N-No!
Do your best, Tomoe-chan, otherwise they'll come at you to have a go!
No-! Why...? My butt, it's-!
No-!
No! My butt feels too good!
The pleasure is spreading through my body!
I can't hold it-!
Huh?
I-I can't hold my voice in!
Hey, what's wrong?
We're making the others wait, hurry up!
Y-Yes!
Huh? They didn't find us... How unfortunate.
You don't have to hold your voice in, now.
No! I wouldn't-!
Even if you say so, your ass sure is amazing!
It's really tight!
Tomoe-chan, I'm gonna cum inside your ass!
M-My butt! My butt-!
My butt, it's-! Please cum!
After that, he cleaned me up and gave me a change of clothes.
Apparently he had a uniform inside of a coin locker...
The only thing left is my memory of him.
He's a very bad man.
Yo.
Today as well, he's...