The thirty minutes between getting on the train and getting off,
that man waits for me.
Today... again...
molester 2   Winter Insect on a Flower
The train will be departing immediately.
Please step away from the tracks.
Then it’s time to get back on the train, again.
Somehow, he keeps finding me.
One time, someone almost figured out what he was doing.
Every time he forces himself on me,
I can't bring myself to stop him.
I'm the type of person who can't speak my mind, anyway.
Since I'm like this,
every day, this monster finds me... and touches me.
My only choice... is to endure it.
If I... endure it,
he won't get mad at me.
So...
Oh no! Oh no!
Not my butthole again.
He keeps fingering it.
Huh?
I wonder what's wrong.
Is he... finished with me?
Don't worry, Tomoe-chan.
We're no finished yet.
What are you saying...?
What's wrong?
Don't tell me,
Tomoe-chan...
Were you looking forward to this?
No way!
I wasn't thinking that.
I wouldn't!
Then let's do this.
Look me in the eye and tell me you don't like it.
If you can, I'll stop doing this.
I can say it...
I can say it.
This is nothing.
I must say it.
I have to.
I have to say it.
I have to make things clear!
Right now!
Um...
We apologize for the delay, passengers.
Please give those getting off the train the right-of-way.
The train will once again depart shortly.
I knew you couldn't do it.
You're the type of girl who stays
quiet and lets things happen to her.
There's no way you'd complain.
Just looking me in the face was a struggle for you.
Since you can't tell me anything
how about you let me do lots of fun things to you while
you're busy musing over why you're so spineless?
Oh, sorry!
Never mind.
H-Hey! What are you doing to me!?
Untie me!
Untie me, please!
I wouldn't scream if I were you.
What if someone finds us?
That'd be embarrassing.
You don't wanna do this?
If so, then you'd better bite down hard on my tongue.
No...
It's inside my mouth... licking everything.
He... He said I should bite it.
But I... can't...
So you didn't bite it.
He's saying things like that because he knows I can't resist.
So cruel.
What are you doing now?
N-No!
What a nice smell.
The smell of Tomoe-chan's black
tights brushing up against her pussy.
N-No!
Please don't smell it!
Oh? You'd rather I lick it?
No!
S-Sto...
No there!
Say, Tomoe-chan,
I see your panties are all wet. You wanna fuck, don't you?
Th-That's not true.
I-It's because...
I see, well, if I'm not satisfying you enough,
I'll just let this little guy help out.
What a great reaction.
Looks like you understand what this thing is for.
No... don't touch down there...
See? You're wet after all.
Don't... Not there...
Inside the train, I can't be this intense with you.
That was bothering you, wasn't it?
I mean, if rubbing your clit is all I can do,
that's not gonna get us anywhere.
See? See?
You'd better swallow it in your pussy.
It looks okay to me.
It looks like it feels good also, being inside of you.
No it... doesn't.
It's pulsating inside of me... It won't stop...
Is that so?
Well, don't worry.
I've got another one prepared.
If I get both your clit and insides at the
same time, that should satisfy you, right?
Please, stop it...
Stop it, please!
Huh? What's wrong?
Is it too strong?
Aw, shit.
You should've just told me
I can make it gentler.
There's still more.
I want you to cum until you go crazy.
He's pumping up the intensity...
No... don't...
Oh, so now you aren't able to be as quiet as you were before.
You really like anal, don't you?
I wonder what would happen if I added that in now?
No... not... not that...
Why not?
You'd better tell me.
Be... Be...
Come on, come on, just relax as it comes in.
Because... I am... too... sensitive down... there...
Don't finger it... so... hard...
Oh? So you finally told me clearly.
I'd better reward you for that.
Oh, it's so tight.
When I poke your asshole, your pussy naturally gets tighter.
I'll bet you're feeling it tingle more now.
If you keep doing that, I'll...
I guess you've reached your limit, eh?
Not my bottom... I told you... no!
Come on, just cum already.
Ah, your panties and skirt are all soaked in piss now.
You won't be able to go outside like this, will you?
That morning, I was really sleepy after a late night at work.
Wait!
Please... don't ask me anything.
Just stay still.
Well... I guess you could say I was shocked.
I had no idea what was happening.
So I just went with it.
Her soft, smooth hand stroked it gently.
Her fingertips circled around the hole.
She tugged and stroked it until it was wet.
Does it feel good?
Not so... intensely...
Don't worry about that.
Just hurry... hurry and cum.
It had been a white.
Also, with that kind of direct stimulation,
I didn't have a choice, did I?
You understand, don't you?
It looks like she was caught unprepared, but she
gathered all of my sperm with her little hands.
Oh no... So much.
I'm sorry.
As you can see, I was really shocked.
She was so casual about it –
like she was putting on a show for me.
The movements of her small, pink tongue...
were so surprisingly innocent.
Because of that, I got hard again, even though I had just came.
She flinched a little at first,
but she didn't protest.
I became so aggressive that I even surprised myself.
Please grab the handrails for your safety.
So the other passengers wouldn't
notice, I used her skirt as cover.
I loved feeling the sensation of her black tights.
They were so slippery and soft.
When I traced my finger around her
asshole, she seemed to really like it.
It was also really cute.
Your ass... Does it feel good?
No!
That's not...
It feels like your asshole is responding
quite happily to my fingers.
No... don't say... weird things...
Her voice sounded really strained, but it was also quite hot.
No... Not so roughly... so roughly...
After she came, I wanted to cum inside of her slippery pussy.
No... wait!
Okay, that's far enough, Mr. Molester.
Um! But...
Please exit the train on the left side.
Well, it was a big waste to leave her.
But that guy had a really scary look in his eye.
I couldn't fight it.
How long has it been?
I have no idea anymore.
Oh, shit.
Just the sight of you horny face makes me wanna cum.
I-I can't move my body.
I can't breathe.
My head is going blank.
Okay, I'm cumming into your mouth-pussy.
So just relax and take it all.
If you can't stand it and want it to end,
then suck harder. It'll end faster.
I... can't... take it... Hurry!
Hurry! Finish!
I... can't... take... it...
That felt so good I thought my brain would melt.
I need more.
Come on, that won't do, Tomoe-chan.
I gave you a lot of my thick stuff,
you'd better drink it all up. Okay?
Savor the taste in your mouth like that.
It tastes weird.
It's hot and squishy.
Good, you drank it.
I like smart girls like you.
Wait...
I see.
You're a bit shy because I've never touched your tits?
It's not that...
But your nipple's so firm and erect.
I bet you wanted me to touch it.
Yeah, that's nice.
Oh, your pussy is all wet again.
Tomoe-chan, you're kinda dirty.
That's not true...
That's not true at all!
Well, let's go ahead and get right to the main course.
Please... stop...
I've been waiting for this.
Tomoe-chan's pussy.
Well then, let's go...
Tomoe-chan's first time...
No!
He's really... inside...
It's all inside.
My insides are throbbing.
My dick feels great, doesn't it?
After you go home and are all alone,
you'll still be able to feel it inside of you.
A virgin pussy is really tight.
I'm actually... losing my virginity... in a place like this.
I'd better cum inside of you quickly.
Inside of me?
No! Not that!
I'm gonna do it.
Inside your pussy.
No!
Not inside!
No...
So hot...
Inside... It's coming inside...
Don't...
Lots came out.
No... I told you no...
I don't want... a baby...
I'm sorry, Tomoe-chan.
It just felt so good I had to cum lots inside of you.
No... way...
Um... what are you...
I can put it in, right?
I never said that!
I...
No! No! That won't fit!
No... not my bottom, too.
Tomoe-chan, this is really tight.
Jeez, I wish you'd give me a break.
– Now, now, you can't do anything about this, you know.
– Oh no!
Someone's coming!
I can see them peeing.
No... stop...
They'll hear us.
I'm in a bathroom... in my butt... No!
Just wait, Tomoe-chan.
If you yell out, they'll all step in line
to have a turn at your asshole.
No... Why in my butt?
No... My butt... I feel it in my butt...
My whole body feels it now.
I'm gonna cum...
I... can't... be quiet...
Hey, what's wrong?
The train is waiting. Hurry it up!
Yes!
Aw, damn, they didn't find us.
What a pity.
Although, now you can scream as loudly as you want.
No. I don't want to.
No? Even if you say that, your asshole is awesome!
It's so tight.
Tomoe-chan, I'm gonna cum in your ass.
My butt feels great!
Please cum inside my butt!
After that, he wiped my body and changed my clothes.
He left my uniform in a coin locker.
All I have left from that day is the
lingering sensations in my body.
He's a horrible person.
Today... again...
Translation: Voldemort
Edit: Rika-chama
Timing: Loserbait
Typeset & Encode: ShocWave