The train is about to arrive at station two.
Please wait behind the yellow line.
I can't believe it...
That habit of mine should have been cured...
But for some reason, when I looked at her, I couldn't help myself.
W
Natsumushi
Tomoe
「
」
Sorry about that, miss. Are you okay?
Y-Yes...
I-I'm sorry...
Does it hurt where I hit you?
If it hurts, please don't hesitate to tell me.
Does it hurt here?
U-Um... I-I'm fine, so...
Looks like you're swollen here...
It hurts, doesn't it?
Oh really?
That's good.
Are you hurt elsewhere? I'll take a look.
Looks like your ears are fine...
You're good here, too.
Jaw, lips, neck, collarbone...
Oh yeah, I've already checked your chest...
Next are your thighs.
I guess you're fine here, too.
Your butt's okay, too.
Are you feeling arousal instead of pain?
N-No, I'm not. Please stop...
N-No!
Looks like you're damp... Is it sweat?
Oh well, I guess you're starting to feel aroused from all of my fondling.
S-Stop it...
You're more lewd that I thought, Tomoe-chan...
Huh?
Please stop it already...
I can tell that your pussy is dripping wet...
No-! It's not!
I know that despite your innocent looks,
you like these kinds of things...
N-No, I don't!
It's not fair that you're the only one that gets to feel good, is it?
Can you stoke me with those beautiful hands of yours?
What?
If you do it quickly, no one will see it, right?
That's it. You're a good girl, Tomoe-chan...
Stroke it more firmly.
Then how about... I get started with you too?
That feels really good.
Your hands are so silky and soft...
I can't hold it back, I'm gonna let it out!
Catch it all with your hand.
I'm gonna cum-!
My name is Rina.
I go to school on this train everyday.
Noisy parents and noisy teachers...
Being at school or staying at home is truly boring.
Lately this has been my new hobby.
I rub innocent men's crotches over their trousers...
At first, they act surprised...
But their expression lightens up soon after.
I rub them gently like this to keep up the stimulation...
They can try to hold back.
But if they do that, I stop.
P-Please don't stop...
Their expressions as they shamefully beg are great.
It's such a thrill!
Yo, I was waiting for you...
W-Who are you?
You don't remember?
You molested me before, you know...
What?
This time, I'll make you feel good.
S-Stop with the jokes! I'll scream!
Go on, but all the people surrounding you have been your victims.
What?
You're sure to be remembered if you do the same thing at the same time in the same car.
S-Stop it, please...
I said stop it!
Then I'll join in too!
H-Hey!
T-That hurts!
Hey! Don't be so rough!
N-No way!
What's going to happen to me?
N-No, I'm not wearing spats today...
Don't make it dig into me like that!
My butt will be exposed!
S-Stop it already-!
No-!
W-What are they doing?! I can't go home like this!
What's this?
You're quite small here...
I like them a little larger, but...
Shut it! I-I'm still growing!
N-No! Not inside my underwear!
Huh? What?
Huh?
N-No way! That's my-!
P-Please, forgive me already. If they keep going, others will notice!
H-Hey! We're inside a train you know!
What's this? Looks like your nipples are already hard...
Are you getting aroused?
Y-You idiot! Be gentler! I'm a girl, you know!
I'm going to do it here as well...
No, don't touch me so much!
These are my favorite panties!
Looks like you're getting hot and wet down here...
I knew she was feeling aroused! She's soaking wet!
No way, no way! W-Why would I get aroused from this?!
You guys have been watching too much porn!
I bet you were waiting for something like this. You were rubbing crotches daily after all...
No, I didn't want something like this!
What? Wait!
No way!
Stop it! Stop it!
This can't be happening! I'm gonna be stripped naked on a train!
I knew it! You're soaking wet!
It's flooding out!
N-No... It's almost like more people are joining in!
Why isn't anyone helping me?
No! Let me go!
I won't do those things anymore! I'll lose it if they keep going!
We can't hold back anymore!
What...?
What's happening?!
Looks like you haven't had much experience,
but since you're this wet, I'm sure it'll slide right in!
Y-You're kidding, right?
N-Not that!
Young girls sure are nice!
They're so much tighter!
I-It hurts! Pull it out, pull it out!
This is too much!
I-I'm being raped!
I was stripped and I'm being raped by men I don't know on a train!
Do me over here too.
No-!
Hey, hey. You need to suck on it, otherwise it won't feel good!
T-They're so selfish!
I-It's just painful for me!
Why? They... they've all pulled out their cocks!
Everyone's masturbating to me getting violated!
No! His cock's quivering and getting hotter!
Don't get so excited!
It's embarrassing to do it like this!
They can see everything!
I'm peaking here!
I'm gonna cum inside you!
N-No way! Don't! Not inside, not inside!
What are you resting for?
We're not satisfied yet.
N-No way... They're not finished?
Natsumushi
I can't count how many times they came...
My breasts and pussy are all sticky with their cum...
We've taken embarrassing photos of you.
If you don't want them to be spread around,
come to this carriage at the same time tomorrow.
I wonder if I went too far...
Next is Tenma Sakauwe... Tenma Sakauwe...
No, I'm sorry!
N-No way! That was all a dream?
I wonder if I'm just sexually frustrated...
That must be it!
Being molested on a train is uncommon anyway!
A high speed train is about to go through station four. Please stand well clear.
Yo! If it isn't Tomoe-chan.
I'm happy that we're able to meet again...
I've been looking for you...
Something feels missing whenever I grope anyone else...
You have something that makes me want to molest you.
I don't want to be molested-!
What was that book you were reading?
I quite like historic novels...
Something about them is quite erotic,
and I've grown to memorize the details...
It was about a princess of the woods having her butt used...
Reading about the way her hole adapted to the dicks was great!
They would stimulate it like this...
No!
And then they would rub gently around the rim...
And just like that, it gets loose.
Isn't it lucky that you weren't heard?
I bet you came a bit.
I wouldn't have guessed that you'd like it so much!
Now I'm all excited as well.
Hey, can you feel how hard I've gotten?
Huh?
What's this? You've made it easier for me to touch you?
No! I wouldn't-! Don't!
Maybe a little higher?
I found it!
No way!
Alright, then.
Thanks for having me!
You shouldn't lie, Tomoe-chan...
You were aroused just by me fingering your ass!
Your pussy's so wet. You're soaking your tights.
No! Please stop this!
What if people hear your lewd sounds?
N-No way...
Huh? You'd rather me do this?
No-!
It's fine, I'll play with you down here, too.
D-Don't-!
Now what should I do?
I'll do it to you with my cock or my hands, your choice.
If you don't feel like choosing,
then how about I pound you with my cock?
What...?
If you're going to choose, this is your last chance.
Tell me which one you want.
Um... With your hands...
Huh? I can't hear you...
Please use your hands...
Don't you mean "Please play with my pussy"?
P-Please play with my pussy...
Okay then, lift your skirt up so that I can do it easier.
Wha-?!
Huh? You'd rather me do you with my cock?
I- I'll do it, then...
Your pussy's so smooth... and spongy...
It's so wet, too!
My hands are getting too slippery... The only place I can get a grip is your clitoris...
No-!
I can feel you quivering...
It's cute that you're so lewd, Tomoe-chan...
I'll do those cute lips of yours, too...
No-!
How is it? Try imagining that it's my cock and suck on it.
I'll finger all of your holes...
Sorry to disturb your pleasure...
but help me cum too.
Huh? No-! This isn't what you promised-!
Oh yeah? A guy can't calm down unless he cums...
These tiny breasts of yours feel great...
You're so sensitive here, too.
No...
I want to cum all over you, Tomoe-chan...
Huh? No!
This feels good!
Your clitoris is rubbing against me!
No! Please don't move!
Tomoe-chan, I know you're trying to stop me by closing your legs, but the tightness feels really good!
R-Rubbing against your pussy with panties and tights on...
Oh man, this might be better than the real thing!
The texture! The surface of the tights! The sensation of these black tights is-!
No! I'll wet myself! I really will!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum all over your skirt, pants, tights, and your legs!
I'll make sure it soaks in! I'll cover you with my cum!
N-No!
Look, I came so much.
I came this much because of you!
N-No, stop it...
Hey, lick me clean.
Wha?
If you don't, I'll wipe it on your uniform...
No, don't...
Cum stains tends to last. They're quite hard to get off.
If it's on the underside of your skirt, then no one will see it...
That's it, clean it up.
You have to use your mouth, too.
That's good.
Clean the ends of my fingers, too.
I can't get enough of you...