Line #2 going towards Tokyo is arriving.
Please stand behind the white line to board.
Dammit...
I thought I'd lost that disgusting habit of mine.
However, just looking at her...
I don't know why, but I suddenly have this irresistible urge...
molester 1   Tomoe
I'm sorry, Miss.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Excuse me...
Are you sure that you're not bruised or anything?
If it hurts, let me know.
Does it hurt here?
Um...
I'm okay.
Oh, I'm only trying to stop any swelling.
Does it hurt?
Really?
That's good.
I'll give you a thorough check-up to make
sure you're not hurt anywhere else.
Seems like your ears are okay.
The nape of your neck seems okay.
As do your chin, lips, neck, and collar bones.
Oh yeah, I already checked your breasts.
Your thighs are next.
Is it okay here?
Your butt seems okay, too.
Actually, does it feel good?
N-No, it doesn't.
Please stop.
D-Don't...
Something's gotten wet.
Is it sweat?
Hmm, perhaps your body's reacting
this way because you feel good?
No... S-Stop...
You're a bit more perverted than I thought, Tomoe-chan.
Please stop.
I can feel how wet and sticky you are even outside your tights.
No, that's not true...
You're trying to act calm, but...
you're really enjoying this, aren't ya?
No, I'm not...
Hey, it's not fair that I'm getting to do all the work.
How about this. Why don't you rub
my thing with your beautiful hands?
We need to finish this off quickly or
we'll be in trouble if somebody sees us.
Isn't that right?
That's right, Tomoe-chan, I can see you're a smart girl.
Rub it harder, please.
All right, I'll do it harder as well.
Hell yeah, this feels awesome!
Your hands are so soft and nice.
Dammit, I'm gonna cum.
Catch it all with your hand – like this.
I'm cumming...
My name is Rina.
I ride this train to school every day.
My parents are annoying.
My teachers are annoying.
Whether or not I'm at home or school, it's all boring.
This is the only interesting thing I've been doing lately.
I make weak men cum by giving them
a handjob outside of their pants.
They're a bit surprised at first, but soon
they start to show their perverted side.
Evidently the feeling of being partially touched is really exciting.
They almost never hold back.
However, when that happens, I stop.
Hey, don't stop...
It feels awesome when they start begging me.
It really gets me excited.
Yo, I waited long enough.
What are you doing?
Have you forgotten already?
You did the exact same thing to me before.
This time I'll make you feel good.
Stop screwing around.
I'm going to scream.
Sure.
However, you might wanna look around, first.
Everyone here has been molested by you.
The same train at the same time every day...
It's kind of hard to just forget about something like that.
Stop! Please, stop!
Let me join in as well.
Wait...
It hurts...
Hey, stop doing it so hard!
No way... What's going to happen to me?
Crap, I didn't wear tights today.
Not so hard...
Now my ass is showing.
G-Geez, cut it out already!
What are they doing?
How am I supposed to get off this train now?
Aw, yours are a little too small.
I'm the type of guy who likes to feel much bigger tits.
Shut up! I'm still growing you know...
S-Stop! Don't put your hands inside my panties!
Huh, what?
N-No, that's...
Ceez, just let me go.
If you guys keep doing this, other people will find out.
W-Wait, w-we're inside a train...
Hey, your nipples are hard.
Are you getting turned on?
Idiot, be more gentle.
I'm a girl.
I'm going to start right here.
No, don't touch me like that.
This is my favorite pair of panties.
Something's getting warm and wet down here.
I told you she's turned on.
See? It's sticky.
No! No way!
There's no way in hell I'm getting turned on!
You guys watch too much porn!
You play with guys' dicks every morning.
You really should've expected something
like this would happen one day.
No, I never thought about that...
What? Wait!
No way!
Stop! Stop!
No way! I'm being stripped inside of a train!
Amazing!
She's really wet down here.
It's overflowing.
No, there seems to be even more people.
Why isn't anyone saving me?
No... No...
Let go of me! I promise I'll never do this again!
If this keeps going on, I'm going to start feeling strange!
Hey, I can't hold back anymore.
What?
It seems like you're still quite inexperienced.
– But it should slide in easily if you're this wet.
– You're kidding, right?
Not that!
Wow, young girls feel the best!
Their pussies feel totally different!
I-It hurts!
Take it out! Take it out!
You don't have to do this! You really don't!
I'm being raped!
I've been stripped and now I'm being
raped on the train by men I don't know!
Let's keep your mouth occupied.
No!
Come on, suck harder.
If you don't, how am I going to feel good?
Stop being so selfish! I'm in pain here!
Wow... There are penises everywhere!
Everyone's masturbating because they're looking at me.
No... His dick is throbbing and getting hotter!
Don't get so excited!
This position is so embarrassing! It's like I'm some dog.
Everyone can see my private parts!
I can't hold back any longer...
I'm going to cum inside you!
N-No way! Stop!
Please, no! Don't cum inside!
What do you think you're doing?
We're nowhere near done with you.
No way...
This is going to keep going on?
I've lost count of how many times I've been cummed on.
My breasts and pussy are wet and messy from their semen.
We're taking pictures of this embarrassing event.
If you don't want them to spread,
then you better be on this train tomorrow.
I guess I went a little bit overboard...
Next stop is Tenma, Sakaue.
Tenma, Sakaue.
No... I'm sorry.
N-No way! That was just a dream?!
Geez, am I really that perverted?!
That's right.
The chance of actually getting molested
on the train is quite rare.
Express line #4 has now arrived.
Please stand behind the line and be careful.
Hey, it's Tomoe-chan.
I'm glad we get to meet again.
I've been looking for you.
When I touch other girls, it's like there's something missing.
You have this quality about you that
makes people want to target you.
I've never wanted to be molested.
What are you reading?
I preferred this one history book.
It was a big turn-on for me.
I can still remember the content.
There was a guy groping a girl's ass.
The description of her ass was definitely unforgettable.
She was being touched like this as well.
No...
If you massage the muscles around the asshole,
something happens that's absolutely amazing...
See? It loosens up.
Thank goodness no one heard you.
You just had a mini-orgasm, didn't you?
I never thought you'd like anal this much.
I'm really turned on, too.
Come on... Can't you feel it getting hard?
Oh, what's this?
You're inviting me to the front?
No, I'm not... Stop!
A little bit higher...
Found it.
No way!
Well then, pardon me for intruding...
Tomoe-chan, lying is bad.
You really do love anal, don't you?
Your pussy is telling me you do.
No, please stop...
Everyone is going to hear these perverted
sounds you're making.
No... Not that!
Oh, so you prefer my cock?
No.
Okay, okay.
I suppose my hand will have to do, then.
N-No!
Well, it's the same.
Both my penis and my hand can make
you feel good, Tomoe-chan.
You know, if the choice were up to me, I'd choose my penis.
It's the last chance you have to make your choice.
Tell me which one you'd like.
Um... hand...
I can't hear you.
Please use your hand.
To finger you?
Yes.
Yes, please finger me.
All right, flip up your skirt.
Oh, so you'd prefer my penis instead?
Fine, I'll do it...
Tomoe-chan, your pussy is really smooth,
soft, and just a little bit sticky.
My hand's getting all sticky, too.
It seems the only thing I can grab onto is your clit.
I can feel you trembling.
You're so cute and perverted, Tomoe-chan.
Let me molest your cute little mouth as well.
Yeah, lick my fingers like you're licking a penis.
I'm penetrating this so-called hole.
I feel kinda bad doing this now.
However, will you please help me ejaculate?
No! I thought we had an agreement!
That's right.
You know, until a man cums, he's still really horny.
Your small tits are the perfect size for my hands.
I don't mind them being small.
No.
Oh wow, Tomoe-chan, I really want to cum inside you.
No...
Oh, this feels amazing.
I'm hitting something.
No... Please stop moving.
Tomoe-chan, I know you're trying to
stop me by holding your legs together,
but, you know, that only makes it feel better.
Your pussy, panties, and tights... All at the same time...
This is even better than real sex.
Oh shit...
The feeling of your silky tights...
No, it's touching... It's touching...
I'm gonna cum.
I'm going to cover your panties, skirt,
tights, and legs with my cum.
– I'm going to completely cover you in my sperm!
– Stop!
Look, I came a lot.
This is your fault, Tomoe-chan.
No... Stop...
Come on, lick it clean for me.
If you don't, I'll wipe it on your uniform.
No way...
It pretty obvious what you were doing
if your uniform is stained with it,
and it's not easy to wipe off.
No one will notice if it's only underneath your skirt.
That's right, lick it clean.
Open your mouth wider or it won't work.
That's it.
Lick my other fingers clean, also.
You're totally irresistible, you know.
Translation: Manko-chan
Edit: Rika-chama
Timing: Loserbait
Typeset & Encode: ShocWave