After moving away from our parents,
me and my older brother Kuuya went
to the town where our grandfather lives.
It is an unsophisticated yet beautiful town,
something unheard of in bigger cities.
We met two girls there,
named Haruka and Yuzuki.
From the moment I saw how she looked at that time, I...
No...
I bet that Haruka stole my heart when we first met.
What's the matter, Kairi-kun?
Just thought how it was love at first sight...
Gosh...
Haruka, my dear sweetheart...
You can tighten your grip.
It might hurt if I squeeze it...
It should be fine as long as your nails don't scratch it.
Umm, how about this part?
I only rubbed it a little, but it got so...
I'll try to rub it a little harder.
Please don't hesitate to tell me if it hurts.
If there's anything you want me to do for you,
I want you to tell me without holding back.
If it's to make you feel good, I...
I will do anything.
Let's see...
I'll use my hands to stroke it against my mouth
like I am wiping it clean.
It feels harder than before...
...and it got bigger.
This is...
It should let your hands slide
more easily if you use that...
Use?
Wow!
To think that lubricating my hands
makes such a huge difference...
Even if I tighten my grip...
Look!
I can now give you a good handjob.
Your stiff thing is inside my mouth!
It's getting harder and bigger!
Your precum keeps on dripping out of the tip!
And you're also shaking your hips as well!
How does it feel inside my mouth?
Does it feel good?
H-Haruka!
I'm gonna come already!
I'm going to study more about lewd stuff, okay?
So that I can make you feel a lot good.
Natural Vacation The Animation!
So it's almost a year since we came to this town.
It's like this place has been frozen in time.
Hmm, Haruka?
Umm...
You see...
Hmm?
I have a dream.
You already know about how I love this town, right?
And that this town's population
has been in decline year after year.
I've always been thinking about
what I can do for this town.
I wanted to give something back
to this place where I grew up.
I want to use my only redeeming skill in cooking
and help revitalize this town...
Is that your dream?
Yes...
I've been thinking about it all this time.
But the days I spent with you
are full of joy and dear to me.
But in the end, I still want to
make my dream come true!
I'm going to a college on another prefecture.
I'll study about cooking and go back here someday.
Will you wait for my return?
I won't wait.
I won't wait. I'm going with you, Haruka.
Kairi-kun...
The whole year I spent here has been a lot of fun.
It's full of happiness.
However, it's all because of you.
It's because you were there for me.
That's why...
I'll leave this town too and help you
on making your dreams come true.
And that's what my dream is.
Kairi-kun...
Thank you.
Your glans is right in front of my eyes.
My heart is beating so fast right now.
How is it?
Do my tits feel good?
It just twitched!
The round swelling tip is throbbing.
The precum readily oozes out of it!
Does this feel good?
I'll make you feel even better.
It's thick, and there's so much!
W-Wait! Don't do that, Haruka!
It's still dripping out of the tip.
Haruka!
U-Umm...
Did my sperm taste that good?
Th-That's...
You're lewd.
Did I turn you off?
Nah, you're very cute.
I'm putting it in, Haruka.
It went in deep all of a sudden!
If it's with you, I really feel like
I can come over and over again!
If you say something like that,
I'll end up wanting lots of it.
You're so stiff down there!
It feels like I'm gonna melt down there
even though you just had it put in!
You're rubbing my tits!
Your fingers are squeezing them.
It feels so good that I'm starting
to see shimmering lights!
Good... It feels good!
But if you do this too much,
I'll end up going crazy from too much pleasure!
N-No!
I'm already...
Your sperm is spurting!
Your ejaculation is way too long...
Now It's all slimy inside me!
Haruka, you make such a very
lewd face from time to time.
I-Is that so?
I never really noticed it myself...
I love that side of you, though.
Me too...
Haruka?!
When you said that you love me,
my body unconsciously...
Darling, your dick twitched...
It's brimming with energy!
Your sperm got all slimy inside me.
It's slushing all over like it's swimming around!
We're making a lot of lewd sounds!
More... Please give me more!
I want more of your stuff!
You're stirring me up right there!
You're reaching deep inside me!
Right there, if you do that...
I want it inside me, which you
creampied and is now sloppy!
I want your thick stuff in it once more!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come again!
I got a second creampie with a huge amount...
It's spurting!
My womb feels like it's gonna melt even up to now!
Won't you mind staying like this for a little while?
I'm filled with so much happiness right now!
I want us to live more happily forever.
Yes!
Natural Vacation!
What's up with you being down since morning?
Hear me out, gramps!
You see, this girl seems to be avoiding
me lately and it bugs me to no end...
After moving away from our parents,
me and my younger brother Kairi went
to the town where our grandfather lives.
We met two girls there,
named Haruka
and Yuzuki.
Here, here!
You did great, Yuzuki!
Jeez, you're messing up my hair!
Whoops...
My bad, my bad.
It's all...
It's all thanks to you, Kuuya!
When my nerves got the best of me...
Yeah...
You were there to root for me.
Thank you!
It was going great between us!
Even so...
Why did she start avoiding me?!
Are you listening, gramps?
I will be out for a bit
Gramps
Everyone's so mean and cold! Why?!
Good afternoon!
Gramps, I brought something packed up.
He seems to be away, so I'll just come back later!
Wait!
Come with me, Yuzuki.
Uhh, Yuzuki-san?
Yes...
Is there anything you want to tell me?
There is, right?
Yes...
I'm sorry! I... Umm...
I've been acting strange this whole time!
Thank goodness!
Kuuya?
I was shocked since I thought
that you started to hate me!
There's no way for that to happen!
I...
Before that, let me say something first.
Kuuya?
I love you!
Yuzuki?
I'm sorry! Just give me a moment!
5 Minutes Later
Well...
There's something I want to ask...
There's something I mean to learn...
Okay...
What if I say that I love you?
In that case,
what kind of relationship
are we gonna end up with?
Of course...
...we're going to be lovers, right?
What are we gonna do as lovers?
Lewd stuff?
I-Idiot! That's too sudden!
So, what will your answer be?
Tell me properly how you feel too.
Okay.
I love you too.
Does it hurt?
It hurts, but moreover...
My happiness is way greater!
I was just thinking that our hearts and bodies
are fully linked to each other.
Thinking about that fills me with happiness,
and the pain kind of fades away.
But maybe we should stay like this for a little while.
Is it hard to move?
Won't it hurt if we suddenly start?
I love that side of you.
I'm gonna start moving slowly.
Okay.
You think you'll be alright?
Yeah...
It feels good, I think...
Then, I'm gonna increase the pace.
What should I do? My mind is going blank!
It's okay...
You can go faster just like this...
The sounds we're making are all over the place.
They're so indecent!
They're reverberating loudly!
I'm starting to feel good! I am!
It's getting snaggled inside! I can't believe it!
No way!
What should I do?
The heat...
And the pleasure won't stop!
Yuzuki, did you come?
I don't know, but...
I'm sorry, but make me come too!
Wh-What's this? I got so sensitive deep inside!
You're going way too fast! This is so intense!
This is... No...
It won't stop!
E-Even though this is my first time...
Th-This is my first time, and yet...
No! No!
N-No—!
Kuuya!
Did that feel great?
Yeah.
I love you a lot.
So do I.
I-I can't breathe...
You're both leaving this town?
I'm sorry.
Nah, you don't have to apologize.
It's for fulfilling your dream, right?
Yes...
We're gonna support you two as well.
Am I right, Yuzuki?
Yeah! Of course, we will!
Good luck to you both, Haruka, Kairi!
Haruka's dream, huh...
What about you?
Me? I don't know...
Getting married here, and then having a child...
I think it will be something like that...
Then, my dream will be to become a typical husband.
You're as carefree as usual.
You're hurting my feelings.
I am being as sincere as always.
Yeah.
R-Right there!
My body feels numb!
The shivers won't stop!
I-It's too stimulating, it's gonna drive me nuts!
No, don't do that!
It's sliding inside me...
No, don't!
Coming... I'm coming!
I'm feeling good just from being pushed up!
I feel hot!
I feel so hot!
My groin feels strange from being pushed up...
It's coming again!
What should I do? I'm gonna leak!
It's coming out! Coming...
Coming... Coming... Coming...
I'm coming!
Wait... I'm telling you...
That I just came...
I'm losing it... I'm losing my mind even more!
My hips won't stop!
No... No way!
It's not calming down!
The shivers won't stop!
It feels good!
I feel... I feel another surge!
The pleasure is spreading all over me!
Shoot your sperm!
I want plenty of it!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
N-No! I'm coming...
I'm coming—!
Take care of your health, Kairi.
You too, nii-san.
Haruka...
I'll definitely be going back.
I'll be waiting right here, in this town.
Sure!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization