Chitose-chan...!
Onii-chan...
l wanted to see you.
lt's just the two of us now, Onii-chan...
lt's been three years now.
l was so surprised that you came back as a teacher.
Never mind that. Why are you here, anyway?
Mariko's key?
lt's the key to your room
that my sister threw away three years ago.
l'd wanted it for so long.
That's why l'd treasured it all this time.
Look. l'll walk you home.
Maybe l'm just too unsophisticated.
Maybe l'm just not very attractive to you.
Since so long ago...
...l've always loved you.
l've wanted to be with you for so long, Onii-chan.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Onii-chan...!
My body feels so hot...!
lt might hurt a little bit at first.
But it'll start to feel very good in a while.
Just relax your body.
Onii-chan...
Please be gentle.
Ow, ow...! lt-lt hurts...!
Onii-chan, l feel like l'm going to rip apart!
Good morning!
Good morning, Sensei.
Oh, right. Good morning.
l'd like to introduce your new lecturer to you.
This is your interim lecturer,
Shimotsukir Haruhiko-sensei.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan...
Please be gentle...!
lt-lt hurts...!
So? How was yesterday?
Huh?!
Oh, Tagami-sensei.
l'm sorry l startled you.
Uh, no worries.
How was your first day?
Oh, you mean yesterday.
Well, l was quite nervous.
To be honest, l don't remember it well.
l was like that too.
l could really tell when you made your introduction.
Did it really show?
No, l mean, you were amazing.
Sir!
Well, Misawa-san. What is it?
Tagami-sensei, could you take a look
at my swimming form today?
Sure. The competition is coming up soon.
l'll make a point of checking up
on all of you, every day from now on.
Oh, really? l'm so glad!
Misawa, we're about to have a staff meeting,
so you get back to class.
Then l'll see you after class, ma'am.
All right.
Onii-chan.
lt's her again. Hey!
Don't run in the hallway, Misawa!
Y-Yes, sir.
Don't these students
have any respect for this school?
Take that!
lf you're looking for Shimotsuki-sensei,
he's gone out for a walk.
Hey, Hotori.
lt's nothing urgent. No big deal at all.
Wasn't the Akagi here just now?
Was he giving you a hard time?
You do what you have to in the circumstances.
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
He's sniffing around the room and says...
''Someone's been smoking!''
''Hey, Kawada. You haven't been smoking, have you?!''
Like that.
How horrible. What a mean guy.
And then?
And when l tell him that he reminds
me of a police dog, he said...
''Don't you mess with me!'' And he took off.
That's hilarious!
Hey, what's the next painting?
There's just something missing.
You did well.
You just have to work on your turn recoveries,
and hold your breath a little more.
Yes, ma'am.
l hope l can make it in time for the competition.
You're doing just fine. Now, it's not like you...
...to lose confidence like that.
You're doing fine.
Yes, ma'am.
Just one more thing...
l'm sorry. She insisted that she come along.
This is my sister, Chitose.
l guess it's the first time you two are meeting.
This is your punishment for being late today.
l wanted to tell you l was going to be
late because of swimming practice...
Raise your ass a bit more.
...but you weren't in the art studio.
Like you were diving into a pool.
l see. So this is what it looks
like under that swimsuit.
l'm embarrassed, Onii-chan.
Please stop.
Why did you come to the staff room today
and completely ignore me?
There were other teachers around,
and l especially...
...didn't want Tagami-sensei
to know anything about us.
Then, why did you come here today?
Oh, you're such a tease, Onii-chan...!
Onii-chan...!
Considering how shy you are,
you sure are wet.
No...! N-Not with your mouth...!
No...!
lt's so embarrassing...!
Your juices are sweet.
Oh, Onii-chan. l...
l licked you nice and clean before.
Let's see you return the favor.
Come on. Suck on this.
Nice and gentle. That's right.
Twist your tongue around...
...like you were sucking it.
Stronger!
That's right.
Like you were licking an ice cream cone.
lt looks like you're ready.
lt-lt's getting bigger.
l-l'm scared.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Just get right into it.
Soon, you won't be able to get enough of it.
No...!
Can you feel it, Chitose?
That feels so good!
You're all dripping wet down here.
Hey, Chitose. Do you want me in here?
Oh, Onii-chan...
You're such a tease.
l won't give it to you until you tell me you want it.
Please, put it in me...
Somebody will see.
lt's so embarrassing.
No, no, no...
No? Shall l stop then?
You're so wet here it seems like you want more.
Oh, you're such a tease...!
l want more...!
lf you make too much noise, the neighbors will hear.
l feel like l'm going to go crazy...!
Do you hate me now, Chitose?
No, Onii-chan. l love you so much.
l get a rush even when you barely touch me.
l am only for you, Onii-chan.
Chitose...
lf l can make you feel good,
that makes me a happy woman.
Good night, Chitose.
Good night, Onii-chan.
He looks so cute when he's asleep.
Where are the spices...
Ouch!
Darn! Did l wake him up?
Onii-chan, breakfast's ready, so wake up!
Come on. lt's Sunday.
Onii-chan.
You said you were going
to reorganize the art studio.
Oh, yeah. That's right.
What? ls there something wrong with the taste?
Oh, my! l wonder what the others taste like.
lt wasn't supposed to turn out like this.
Where could l have gone wrong?
At least it's edible.
Oh, by the way, Chitose, are you sure
it's all right staying out like this?
Yeah. No problem at all.
After all, my dad's always so busy
and hardly ever comes home...
...and my mom's got the night shift at the hospital...
...and my sister's now living in a company dormitory.
But Sunday's when everyone's at home,
so l'd better get back there today!
Hey Onii-chan.
Hm?
l can come back here again tomorrow, right?
Sure.
Yay! That's great!
Shimotsuki-sensei.
Oh, Tagami-sensei.
You sure have a lot to do.
l can give you some help.
The rest is just grunt work.
So, you don't have to worry.
Oh, l understand that you are
a swimming coach certified by...
...the aquatics federation.
That's right. How did you know?
Well, l just happened to hear
from one of your swimmers.
You mean Misawa Chitose-san?
Wha...?!
We hear a lot about you from Misawa-san.
l understand you're a friend of her sister's?
Well, l guess you could say that.
Misawa-san's training hard
and keeping the swim team shipshape.
l'm really counting on her.
Really? l never thought she'd be a leader.
She didn't seem to be that type.
She seems pretty nervous these days though.
What?!
l think it's because of the upcoming competition.
Sensei?
Yes?
Have you had lunch yet?
Uh, not yet...
lf you'd like, l'll share my lunch with you.
Wow! lt's been a long time
since l've had such a great lunch!
Well, l guess you don't eat very well.
Huh?! Well, uh...
But are you sure l can have this?
Didn't you make it for a special someone?
l heard he was going to come
to the federation conference...
and so l put my heart into it...
...but today l was told that he was getting married.
So much for that.
l see...
But, you know, Tagami-sensei...
the way l see it, it was just an infatuation you had.
After all, if you were really in love,...
it wouldn't matter that he was getting married.
ln fact, that would spur you on even more.
And you'd try to steal him away.
That's what love should be about.
You are a passionate man, Shimotsuki-sensei.
And there's something
that's dangerous about you.
About me?
Naw, you can't be serious.
l-l'm just all talk, you know. l'm just blabbing.
Here.
Oh, that's right. Chitose was staying at her home tonight.
And she did mention that she starts
morning training today.
Well, l guess l should go show my support.
Onii-chan.
l see you're training hard.
Here's your breakfast.
l get really nervous
the closer we get to the competition.
l get scared. l get scared
and l don't know what to do.
How am l supposed to meet
everyone's expectations?
Chitose...