Onii-chan. Come on, Onii-chan.
You're going to be late.
Come on...
Wha...?!
What are you doing?!
No, Onii-chan... No...
l have morning practice.
Look, you're already this wet.
No...
l think you started getting wet
when l tied you up.
Yes, a little bit.
l don't know what's happened to me.
Do you hate me?
Not at all.
l'm the one who made you this way, after all.
Chitose...
You are mine.
Only mine.
l'm yours, Onii-chan.
lf it makes you happy,
l don't care what you do to me.
l'm going to be late for morning practice.
l'm going to get in trouble with Tagami-sensei.
Tagami...
...Huske, huh?
All right! Let's do another set!
Hayakawa, you're compensating
too much on your dives.
Tighten it up a bit. You'll lose points on flying.
Sensei...!
l'm sorry. l slept in.
l was up until late last night
doing homework and such...
...and l didn't get to bed until late.
l'm really, really sorry.
lt's not like l forgot about the practice.
Oh, it's okay. You don't have to worry
about it so much.
Sensei?
Hey! What did you say just now?!
How dare a student talk back like that!
l'm not talking back! l'm just asserting my right!
Y-You...!
Homeroom is coming up,
so you'll have to excuse me.
Shimotsuki-sensei...
Kawada...?
Hey! l'm not finished with you yet!
Akagi-sensei.
Oh, right. Uh, good morning.
Did Kawada do something?
l warned her about the dress code.
She says she has a right to free
expression. She has no respect.
l don't really see her as a problem student, though.
Well, l guess you could say l lost it a bit back there.
l might have yelled a bit too much.
Oh, Tagami-sensei. G-Good morning.
G-Good morning.
Has the date of the ceremony been decided?
Huh?
Oh, come on. Your wedding with Shimotsuki-sensei.
Well, that's...
Uh, l didn't mean... l'm sorry...
Well, l suppose you don't want to rush it...
l'd like to congratulate the both of you.
There's nothing so wonderful
as a wedding between peers.
You're awfully late, Haruhiko-chan!
lzumi! What are you doing?!
Hi! Would you like some snacks too?
Now, come on. You know you're not
supposed to eat here.
Of course l know that.
This is where you draw pictures!
You don't sound too convincing
when you're eating like that.
Hey, you know. That Hotori-chan hasn't been herself lately.
She's always in deep thought about something.
l wonder if it's about this morning.
And...!
Next Sunday we're going to do a drawing session!
What?!
l want to do a drawing session
and bring Hotori-chan's spirits back up.
What? You can't just...?!
lf you don't come, we won't be able to get in this room.
So, you have to come as well.
But l didn't agree to that.
So, that's the plan! See ya!
Oh, l'll give the rest of that to you. Bye!
Give to me?
How did she bring all of this in here?
Onii-chan!
Oh, that was exhausting!
You're early. What about your swimming?
Today's self-practice day. So, l skipped it.
When we stand like this,
it's like we're just student and teacher.
Hey, let's go on a date this Sunday. Okay?
Hm. lt seems the art club's doing a
drawing session that day.
What? What do you mean?
lzumi just decided on her own.
l'm their advisor, so l have to go.
What a drag.
Wait up!
Why would Yua just decide on her own?
You think l can keep up with her?
No.
See?
Shimotsuki-sensei?
ls there something...?
l had some time to kill,
so l'm just wandering about.
Uh, l want to talk to you about Miss Misawa-san.
l don't want you to misunderstand.
l'm not telling anyone about you and Misawa-san.
However...
However?
l don't think you two should come to school together.
And perhaps you should be more discreet.
l'm grateful that you helped me out back then.
However...
...it's not as if l asked for your help.
And talk of marriage, no less.
l'm sorry. lt was in the heat of the moment.
Heat of the moment, huh?
How did you feel when you saw Chitose and l do it?
You were envious, weren't you?
What?!
Weren't you getting off at the time?
Wh-What are you saying?!
You wanted to be in her shoes, didn't you?
lsn't that so?
How were you feeling down there at that time?
Please don't tease me!
You know what?
l love honest people.
Love?
Now, say it.
That you want to feel the same way she did.
l want to feel...
l just can't say it!
l see.
Excuse me, then.
Wait.
Please wait!
l'll say it! l'll say it!
So, please don't go!
l'm jealous of Misawa-san.
l want you...
...to make me feel...
Yes?
...like that. Please.
No, sensei...
No? lsn't this what you wanted?
You're all hard, even in this water.
Please. Don't say that...
P-Please! Don't...!
You've got a great body.
You head the swimming club, after all.
P-Please, stop it...!
lt's all hot and wet down there.
N-No... No, you mustn't...
Not in a place like this. Please...!
l'm only just getting started.
Oh, no...
You feel nice inside.
No... Water will get in...
Well? How do you feel?
No...! l don't know...!
Answer my question.
l-lt feels good! Like l'm going to go crazy!
What do you want me to do?
l want it...
...your...
Are you sure? A coach getting
fucked in a place like this?
lt's okay. Fuck me... Fuck me, please...!
Please! Hurry!
lt's so good!
lt's amazing...!
Oh, no! l'm going to...
...cum!
Sensei!
No! Don't touch me!
S-sensei.
l'm sorry. You gave me a fright.
Oh, well, uh...
l'm sorry for sneaking up on you.
Where is this painting set?
Just outside of Tokyo.
Near where l lived when l was little.
Painting was my dad's hobby a long time ago.
He painted a lot in front of the house.
l'd sit next to him and pretend to be painting as well.
Oops. l didn't mean to bore you.
Come to think of it, where's lzumi?
She said she's going to find a model.
A model?
l'm back!
l found a model!
Are you sure that l'll do?
No problem.
l'm sorry you had to come out.
Shimotsuki-sensei...
Not at all. l'm free right now.
You've got to relax, ltsuki-chan.
Or your beauty will go to waste.
Wha...? What can l say...?
Don't you think that's a bit overboard?
You sure know how to recognize
talent, Haruhiko-chan.
l didn't mean it as a compliment.
lt's okay. lt's okay. You're not very honest, are you?
Get real.
The clothes and the hair aren't even
the same as the model's.
Look carefully.
But l like this much more.
This isn't about what you like or dislike.
lt's supposed to look real.
l think it's pretty good. Keep going, Yua.
See? See? You're the one that's wrong about this.
Hey, wait... What's the point...?
A drawing should be beautiful.
You're just too uptight.
Wait a minute...!
Aren't you going home, Kawada?
Oh, Senseir.
l want to finish my painting this week.
This week?
l'm going back to England.
That's awfully sudden.
Have you told everyone?
l'm not really into getting all sappy about it.
My mother died when l was seven.
Kawada...
After several years, when my dad told me he was remarrying...
...l felt like l didn't have a place anymore.
So, l started to rebel.
l started hanging around with bad people.
l would drink and smoke and such.
And l pretended l was a grown-up.
Then...
...l was gang-raped for two whole days.
Over and over.
That's enough, Kawada.
Since then...
...l've always been terrified of men.
But...
l love you, Sensei.
K-Kawada...
l know about you and Chitose.
Even so, l...
...still love you.
l can't change the fact that l love you.
That's why...
...l want to say good-bye to my old self...
...and be reborn.
No, don't look...!
l'm embarrassed, Sensei.
When a man and a woman love
each other, this is only natural.
lf we love each other...
...l might just go crazy.
No... lt's embarrassing...
Kawada...
You're really beautiful.
Don't look at me like that.
No...!
You mustn't go down there!
No... l feel like l'm going to go crazy....!
l'm losing control of myself...
l just can't take it anymore.
Please, Sensei...!
Are you sure this is okay with you?
l can feel you...
...inside of me.
Sensei... Shimotsuki-sensei...
You feel so good.
l want you to feel it too.
Kawada...
...l feel it too.
l feel the nipples. l feel all of you.
l'm so happy. l want to feel it more.
l'm gonna cum!
l'm gonna cum soon!
Sensei!
Hey, Kawada.
Who was the man in your painting?
l'm sorry about all this.
l was actually happy when
that happened to me??
l'm sorry.
lt's practice for when l see my dad.
You saying l look like your dad?
Thank you, Sensei.
l'll never, ever...
...forget about you, Sensei.