N-No...!
Onii-chan...!
S-Somebody will see us here.
That feels so good, Onii-chan.
Onii-chan.
lf you're so worried about this...
...you just have to think
of me making love to you.
With you?
Yeah. Believe in me.
Just clear your mind
and only think about our love.
Onii-chan...!
ltsuke! Uh, l mean, Tagami-sensei!
Well, uh, you look wonderful as usual...
Huh?
Uh, l mean, uh,...
l guess the swimming competition is coming up.
Yes. Our students are training hard...
and have their sights set on the championship.
l hope you come out
and give them your support.
Yes, of course.
Tagami-sensei seems kind of down these days.
l wonder what's going on?
Look! Don't be walking around
these hallowed halls wearing that!
But you're wearing a jersey!
This just happens to be my uniform!
Damn bloody wench!
There's no respect around here!
Maybe l was a bit too harsh.
Hey, Kawada! Working hard?
Uh, look, it's not ready yet.
l'll show it to you when it's finished.
How can l give you any advice
if l have to wait till it's finished?
Come on, let me just take a look.
l said no. Please, Sensei...
Hotori...
Onii-chan?
Ch-Chitose...
Chitose.
Hm?
Don't be thinking anything
weird about me and Kawada.
Of course not. l believe in you, after all.
You liar. l can tell you're accusing
me with your eyes.
l already know. l heard from Hotori.
Besides, l plan on keeping you with my charms.
l'm the only one for you, right?
Well, l wonder...
You meany.
l wonder if people will ever find out about us.
But, l'm never going to leave, okay?
Tomorrow's your competition.
You do your best.
Okay. You'll come and cheer me on, right?
Sure.
Now, go to bed.
Good night, Onii-chan.
My god! ls it that time already?!
Mariko.
lt's been a while, Haruhiko-san.
You seem to be well.
Yeah. l see that you're still smoking.
l was told to quit. But this is one habit
l can't quite kick.
Do you smoke in front of Chitose as well?
Huh?!
lt seems that Chitose isn't around
the house much these days.
My mother's a little worried.
l told her that young girls like to
spend a lot of time with their friends.
But she goes over to your place, doesn't she?
Yeah. How long have you known?
On Sunday. She seemed so unusually happy,
l was curious.
Chitose called you, didn't she?
l pressed the redial button,
and l realized that it was you.
Lane No. 5, Kakinouchi Misato-san,
Yamato Swimming Club.
Lane No. 6, Misawa Chitose-san, Seiwa Academy.
When you get nervous, you just have
to think of me making love to you.
Believe in me.
Just clear your mind and only think about our love.
Onii-chan...
So, you still remembered my phone number, huh?
Not so easily.
So, what are you here for?
Do l have to have a reason?
No, but do you like chatting
with a guy you split up with?
Even though we did split up...
...l'm still in love with you.
You certainly have a strange way
of looking at things.
You once said that that's the part of me
that you found most charming.
l don't remember what
l might have said so long ago.
You haven't changed a bit. What a relief.
A lot's happened to me since we split up.
But you haven't changed at all since then.
l just ask that you take good care of Chitose.
That girl needs you.
What if l only see her as some sort of toy?
l believe in the both of you.
Why are you so quick to believe in us?
That's because the both of you are
the most important people to me.
l just now realized
why it is that l broke up with you.
lt's that honesty and trust of yours
that weighed me down.
l hated being thought of like that. That's why...
Take good care of her.
Hey, wait a minute.
Aren't you going to go see Chitose?
All Chitose needs is you.
Give me strength, Onii-chan.
Go for it, Chitose. Believe in me.
Just think only about our love.
Onii-chan.
Hey, what should we get her for a present?
Oh, for Rikako's birthday?
Come to think of it, today's Chitose's birthday.
Onii-chan's not here.
And l tried so hard.
Oh, maybe he's in the art studio.
Hello, Sensei. What on earth are you doing here?
Kawada! What are you hanging around
a place like this?
No reason. And l'm not ''hanging around'' either.
What about you?
Huh? Oh, hey, perfect timing.
You think you can help me pick something out?
l want to get some clothes
or something for a lady friend of mine.
Sure, but do you know her size?
Well, not exactly.
There's no use in getting
something that doesn't fit.
l thought it was a good idea.
But l guess l didn't think it through.
Do you at least have a rough idea
of her body proportions?
Roughly, l suppose.
Then maybe we can do something.
What do you think of this?
lt's not bad, but it's kind of bland.
l thought it would suit her.
Judging by the clothes you've been looking at,...
...l bet she's around the same age as me.
Yeah, l suppose she's about your age.
What's she like?
She's petite, and very gregarious.
That's just like...
What do you think of something like this?
Huh? For something like that,
she'd need to have a fair-sized chest.
Chest, huh.
lt's a gift for a lady friend, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Based on the image l have of her so far...
...l bet she'd look good in a ponytail.
Hey, l think this would suit her perfectly!
Don't you think it looks a bit too sophisticated?
No, it's not.
She's quite petite, but she's got a good sense of style.
l bet this'll look great.
K-Kawada.
Yeah, this is the one. Let's decide then.
Where could Onii-chan have gone?
Maybe he doesn't care about me anymore.
l hope that Chitose likes this.
l've been looking for you, Shimotsuki-sensei.
What's the matter?
The president of the academy wants to see you.
Come in.
l understand you wanted to see me?
Dean?
Yes, sir.
l've called you all here because we received...
...an anonymous fax addressed to the academy.
The content of this fax is, well...
Let's just cut to the chase.
lt's about you having relations with one
of our female students.
Huh?
ls it true?
lf it's true, then we'll have to
deal with you immediately.
And that's not all.
We wouldn't want the media to latch onto this.
We'll have to have you resign...
...so that you don't further damage
the reputation of this academy.
l believe that would not be necessary.
Why would you say that, Tagami-sensei?
Now, you just stay quiet.
Yes, sir.
Are you saying that there was no point
in us meeting like this?
Yes.
Could you explain why?
Shimotsuki-sensei is a dedicated teacher,...
...and he is popular among the students.
That fact may have led to misunderstandings.
But you don't find smoke where there's no fire.
Please excuse my private affairs,...
...but Shimotsuki-sensei and l are engaged.
Huh?!
Tagami-sensei!
Well, well, is that so?
So, the rumors were true, after all.
What do you mean?
Student rumors...
...about Shimotsuki-sensei and Tagami-sensei enjoying...
...lunch together on the rooftop.
Taking just one look at you,
l knew there had to be a mistake.
Well, we hope you carry
on with your good work.
Congratulations, Tagami-sensei!
l envy you.
To be able to sleep with
the Chairman's only daughter,...
and a babe to boot.
That's pretty impressive.
l can't believe Tagami-sensei's...
Why did you speak out like that, Tagami-sensei?
l was thinking about a student
with a bright future.
l was the one who sent that fax.
What?
l saw you.
You and Misawa-san...
...in the shower room.
What?!
l said before that l was thinking about
a student with a bright future.
That might only be half true.
Huh?
l just wanted you, Shimotsuki-sensei...
...to remain at this academy.
There must be something the matter with me.
Telling you something like that.
Don't come near me!
Please don't come near me. Please.
Please.
l don't want you to see my face like this.
l hope you take good care of her.
l understand.
l wish l hadn't fallen in love with him.
That's why l had to bare my soul today.
Where on earth did Onii-chan go?
Oh, Onii-chan!
l'm so glad you're home!
l heard that you won the championship.
Congratulations!
And also, happy birthday!
Wow! Thanks!
You remembered!
Of course!
Onii-chan!
So, open it.
Okay!
Th-This is for me?
l ran into Mariko today.
What did my sister have to say?
She told me to take good care of you.
Nothing to worry about.
Mariko's not the type to go blabbing.
So, l guess you still trust my sister.
Onii-chan, please tell me that l'm still yours.
Of course you are.
You'll never hate me or anything, will you?
Please! Don't ever hate me!
l'll do anything!
Anything?
l'll do anything.
Anything. Anything for you.
Well, then let's celebrate both
your victory and your birthday.
All right. Take your clothes off.
Can't you do it?
l-l will.
Now, why are you getting all shy
on me all of a sudden?
B-Because...
Onii-chan...
Did you do stuff like this with my sister too?
No, you're the first.
The first one who l wanted to make my own.
Then...
...do what you will to me.
Are you happy?
l'm not really sure.
l'm tingling all over.
Really?
This is incredible.
Here. Look at this.
Please, Onii-chan. Hurry up. Hurry up.
l did say before that this is a double celebration.
No!
l don't like this!
lt's embarrassing!
What are you going to do, Onii-chan?
This thick one is to celebrate your victory.
No! Don't do that! Don't put it in me!
Did you cum already?
Please. Forgive me.
Can't let you off that easily.
We still have something
for your birthday celebration.
l don't like this.
Please stop, Haru. Please stop!
Onii-chan...!
Please...! l want to feel you inside of me!
Happy birthday, Chitose.
Onii-chan...
l want it harder...!
l feel like l'm going to rip...!
l just want to feel you all over inside of me.
l'm so happy l was born.
Hey, Onii-chan. Wake up!
What do you think?
Yeah. You look more sophisticated this way.
Onii-chan.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
l feel like doing it again.
Silly. You're such a pervert.
Hey, Onii-chan, how about we go for a walk?
Yeah. lt might be nice seeing
the blossoms at night, just the two of us.
Look, Onii-chan. The blossoms are beautiful!
There was always one thing
l wanted to beat my sister at.
My sister's beautiful, stylish...
...very feminine and a good cook.
But you chose me instead.
l love the blossoms at night.
My spirit rises when l stand among
the falling blossoms.
l feel like l'm someone other than my usual self.
Have you ever felt like that before?
Chitose...
...l love you.
lt's the first time that you told me
that you love me.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
When we're like this,
it's like we're completely naked.
Your heartbeat, your breath...
...your scent, l just love it.
l want to share the same dreams with you.
Share the same pleasures in life,
and the same feeling.
l feel like l'm at one with you.
ln body and soul.
That's because... That's because l love you so much.
l love you, Onii-chan.