When you're finished with your
club duties, l'd like to talk to you.
l'll be waiting under the bell at 5:30 this evening.
l want to talk about what happened at the pool.
Haruhiko-san...
lt's amazing...!
Haruhiko-san...!
You mean here?
What if someone comes?
No one will come.
Wha...?!
No...!
You mustn't!
No!
No?
Stop it, Onii-chan...
What's this wet spot, then?
But, l can't help it...
lt's exciting doing it in a place like this at times.
But l'm afraid, Onii-chan.
That's too much! No...!
This is embarrassing, Onii-chan.
l want it now, Onii-chan!
l can't take it...
Stick it in me!
Yes, yes, Onii-chan!
You like it that much?
l'm just so scared...
...l feel it so much more!
Oh, yes! Onii-chan!
l'm gonna cum, Onii-chan!
lt's too much!
Can l cum now? Can l cum now?
Please, together...!
Onii-chan!
Huh? What was that?
Just pigeons. There's no one else around.
l heard it from outside.
Then, maybe it was a cat?
A cat?
A dirty little, stray cat.
Come on, don't joke around.
Maybe it was getting off on watching us.
Come on...
What are you crying about, Tagami-sensei?
l just don't understand you!
You called me out.
You even knew what you were going to be doing.
You're horrible!
l'm the type that likes to tease the women l love.
How could you be so childish?!
But there are women that like to be teased.
You were watching Chitose and l
the whole time, weren't you?
Did you get off?
How dare you.
Didn't you get all wet down there?
No. Uh, yes...
Oh, no...!
Well, well. You're all soaked.
Do you think you can love me?
Yes.
Then...
...get on your hands and knees.
What?
You can do it, if you love me.
All right. Let's see your tits.
B-But, this is the...
l want you to feel yourself off.
l-l can't do that!
Then, was your answer to me a lie?
N-No...
Then, get on with it.
Do it with more feeling.
l'm sorry...!
O-Ow!
Answer honestly.
You want this, don't you?
You're pretty good at this.
Lick it.
Working late tonight, Shimotsuki-sensei?
l'm doing the evaluations for all
my students.There's quite a lot.
All of those?
Tough work..
No, l'm actually enjoying it quite a bit.
Why am l enjoying this?
Look at me. What if he sees me?
l must be a pervert.
Oh, right. About you and Tagami-sensei.
Yeah?
A rumor about your engagement
is circulating among the students.
What a hassle.
You should be careful.
You're a popular man. Some student might come after you.
Oh, come on.
Just a joke.
Well, l'll see you later.
Good night.
l want it...!
l can't believe... But l want it so much!
Give it to me, Haruhiko-san.
Please.Just like last time.
Fuck me like crazy...!
Ready? You take it all, now.
That was good.
Oh, please, Haruhiko-san.
A rumor, huh?
lt's just a matter of time
until Chitose hears about it.
lt's gotten dark out.
l guess l should go home.
Uh, but...
...l haven't...
Haven't what?
l haven't been satisfied.
l'll owe you one.
C-Come on!
lt's punishment for watching.
lf you want me to love you,
you'll have to become more my type.
l will! l will, so please, right now!
Okay...
l got a present for you instead.
For me?
Starting tomorrow...
Sensei? Tagami-sensei?
What's the matter?
l've finished all of my sets.
Uh, Misawa-san, are you...
Yes?
lt's nothing.
Good work.
Practice is over, everyone.
See you later.
Thank you!
Good practice!
What's the matter?
Don't you have a lecture?
Shimotsuki-sensei...
...l understand that you'll be full-time next term?
l'm sure that's not what you came here to talk about.
By the way, did you like your present?
Yes.
Then, can l see it?
What?
You're kidding!
Here?
l want to see it in its full splendor.
Sure...
l hope no one comes around.
Pretty erotic panties for a proper lady like you.
Come on, this is the present you gave me.
Do you wear this regularly?
No!
This is incredible.
You're a dirty woman,
getting all wet in a place like this.
l did this for you!
l'm wearing it because l thought you wanted me to...
Feel me up...
Please...
Right here? Right now?
Yes...
...l want it right now.
l don't care what you do to me.
But, it's not right.
There's a school assembly to attend.
No...
Actually, l have another present for you.
Will you accept it?
A-And?
Well, l'll fuck your brains out.
l'd be happy to accept your present.
This year has been a good one for our school.
l'd like to make a few presentations on this occasion...
l want you to accept this.
B-But that's...!
lt's something l got specifically for you.
For me?
But this time you'll have to give it to me.
Sure.
lf you can bear it during the assembly.
Make sure it doesn't fall out.
Just with my panties?
That's no good. Considering you're this wet...
...you'll have to work at keeping it in.
That's impossible.
lf they knew that you're using
something like that to masturbate...
...l'm sure they'd all be quite shocked.
That's terrible...!
l can't take it. My pelvis is out of control.
l feel like l'll scream.
l'm going to scream.
And so, we will bring this assembly to a close.
What was he talking about?
Haruhiko-san...
l think it was more exciting just to watch you.
You have a lot of will power...
...Tagami-sensei.
l congratulate you from the bottom of my heart.
l hope you keep your promise.
All right?
l will keep my promise.
But, not now.
C-Come on...
You look like you're going to die.
lt would be better if l died.
l feel like l'm going to go crazy.
You're a true nymphomaniac, just as l figured.
Don't worry.
l'll carry out my part of the bargain tonight.
Really?
l'll be waiting at my apartment, Tagami-sensei.
Haruhiko-san...
Really?! Shimotsuki-sensei?!
He's going out with someone?
With who?! With who?!
Haven't you heard the rumor?
First l've heard of it.
Don't tease me!
What's this all about?
Shimotsuki-sensei is getting engaged to Tagami-sensei!
What a shock!
ls that true?!
Chitose. You know...
l hear it's true.
Some time ago at a staff meeting...
...Tagami-sensei came right out and said she was engaged to him.
And that Akagi was apparently pretty crushed by that.
Yeah, l heard about that.
That's right.
What a drag. l had my eye on Shimotsuki-sensei.
Come to think of it, l heard that
he's been having lunch with her.
Really? Are you serious?
l heard from Taniyama about the staff
meeting, so l'm sure it's true.
What a shock!
And to think that Tagami-sensei would tell them.
What's the matter, Chitose. Hey, Chitose?
Chitose?
Hello? Chitose?
Uh, Misawa-san, are you...
lt's nothing.
lt can't be.
There's no way it's true.
l didn't think you were going to come.
My shopping took a little time.
l'm going to be full-time.
What's the matter?
Nothing... lt's just from the onions.
Come on. You want to switch?
What's the matter? l thought you'd be all happy?
lt's not true, right?
H-Hey, hey. What are you talking about?
l'm sure...
...it's not true.
But l'm still worried.
No matter how positive l am...
...l still feel that you'll one day go to someone else.
Tagami-sensei's beautiful...
...and there's no way l can win you over from her.
And no matter how much l love,
l'll end up abandoned.
Don't be silly.
You're the only one l love.
l'm yours.
No matter what you might do to me.
l hope you believe me.
So, please don't abandon me.
l believe you.
l'll never abandon you.
You're the only one for me.
Come on, let's celebrate.
Sure.
Hi. Good to see you.
Uh...
...l decided to come.
Well...
...come on in.
Thank you.
All right, Sensei...
...go right on in.
Misawa-san!
Tagami-sensei!
No! Don't look!
Don't look! No!
W-What's this all about, Onii-chan?!
l just have another slave, that's all.
Why...?!
So, let's continue with the party.
Sensei...
Chitose, l want you to lick Tagami-sensei's pussy.
And do it with feeling.
W-What?!
l can't do that...
Do it like l do to you.
No, l can't do something like...
What were you to me, again?
l-l am your...
No, not there!
You're my...?
l am your slave.
l enjoy being my master's toy.
Do you want it?
l want it...!
l want your...!
Then, you do as l say.
Yes.
No! You mustn't, Misawa-san!
l just can't do it.
Please don't make me do it. Please, Onii-chan.
That's too bad.
l guess l'll just have to punish the rebellious one.
l'll play with this slave instead.
No!
l'm your only slave!
You belong to me.
You're not my only slave.
Please. Don't say things like that.
l'll do anything for you.
So, please, love only me!
No. l want you to sit there
and watch me love another woman.
Your favorite thing is going to disappear into her.
No.
l don't want to watch.
Then it wouldn't be a punishment.
Face this way.
Now, open your eyes.
l'm in ecstasy! Hurry!
lt's going in! lt's going in!
No...!
l don't like this!
Oh, finally...!
l'm sorry. l did something terrible.
So, please forgive me.
Then, will you obey me?
Whatever you want...
Anything that'll make you happy...
Anything?
l'll do anything.
Anything that you order me to.
So, please don't abandon me.
You are mine and only mine.
l'm not going to abandon you.
Now, l want you to make ltsuki feel good.
Yes, Master.
Sensei...
...you feel so good down here.
What an embarrassing thing to say.
You're very good at that, Chitose.
l'm doing it just like Master does it to me.
Oh, Misawa-san...! That's so good...!
How l can be letting a student of mine do this to me?
Yes, right there! lt's so good! lt's incredible!
l can't take anymore! No, l'm going to go crazy!
Now, just a little more, Chitose.
Yes, Master.
Oh, right there! That's good!
l don't care what happens to me now!
l'm going to cum! l'm going to cum!
l'm cumming! l'm cumming!
Well?
She's quite an amazing student, isn't she?
Even outside of swimming.
Okay, Chitose. Here's your reward for a job well done.
Onii-chan...
Hurry, l want your...
Please, l can't take it anymore.
Oh, yes!
l'm in ecstasy!
l'm in ecstasy! This is incredible!
Even when you share with ltsuki?
lt doesn't matter to me.
As long as you love me.
Then, let's show ltsuki that l can love you anywhere.
O-Okay.
l want to show Tagami-sensei what l'll do to prove my love...
...no matter how embarrassing.
Put it in yourself.
O-Okay.
What's the matter?
l-l'm fine. l can take it.
Sensei... Tagami-sensei...
This is who l am.
Whatever Haru does to me, it just feels so good.
This is the kind of dirty woman l am.
Are you watching me, Sensei?
Misawa-san...
...it's beautiful!
l'm envious.
Onii-chan, please...
Will you love Sensei too?
That's very generous of you, Chitose.
l'm so grateful for your praise.
l'm going to cum!
Sensei...
Chitose-san...
Yes, yes... lt feels so good...!
l'm going to cum...!
You know, Onii-chan...
Huh?
...Tagami-sensei says that...
...at this rate, l'll make it on the lnter-High team.
Yeah?
lf you're selected, how about we go on a trip?
Really?
And Tagami-sensei too?
You know, Onii-chan...
Huh?
...l don't know how to put this, but...
...l always thought that love was
about seeing only one person.
And that everyone else was a fake.
But...
...l've been thinking recently that that's wrong.
There are many ways to love.
lt's about how much you can feel from the other.
l think that's what's most important.
ln both body and soul.