Nee, ...Shiyo
Hey, ...let's do it
will you... make love?
Final Volume
Spring, the season of beginnings.
Hinekure Kyouya
I...
...got myself a girlfriend.
Hinayama Keiko
The Selfish Boyfriend
&
The Gentle Girlfriend
My girlfriend is that chubby girl.
She's Hinayama Keiko.
I imprudently confessed to her,
and I thought that It's all over...
And since then,
We already kissed...
Kyou-chan, Kyou-chan...
And we've gone all the way to the third base...
But she...
wasn't a virgin.
Even though that was my first time...
Keiko, there's a cream on your cheek.
Huh?
K-Kyou-chan?
Come here for a second.
Men's Restroom
This is embarrassing...
We're in the men's restroom!
Here, suck this.
Won't you listen on what your boyfriend says?
B-But...
Jeez, give it up! I want you to do it!
Oh... you're so impatient...
Suddenly sucking it deep—!
What the hell? She's so good at this!
It feels so good, it's like my hips are gonna give out!
Have you been doing this on your ex too?
Wait... I think I'm gonna come soon...
I'm seriously... on the edge!
Coming... I'm coming!
Have you settled down, Kyou-chan?
Classes are gonna start soon...
We should go back—
It's not enough...
Huh?
Kyou.... Kyou-chan?!
W-We cant! The classes are starting!
You're not wearing a rubber—
K-Kyou-chan... D-Don't!
Coming... I'm coming...
In the restroom... In school's male restroom!
I'm gonna come!
Huh?!
Kyou... Kyou-chan, somebody came in here!
I think we really should stop!
No.
We'll keep going, so don't make any noise.
Huh?
Huh... Hmm?
What?
Umm... Did you hear someone?
Did you? Maybe it's just in your head?
Uhh... Maybe it is...
Damn, that lesson in Math makes me wanna cry!
Kyou-chan... Stop!
Me too, it's scary as hell!
My voice will come out!
You serious? You can't be!
I'll shut that mouth up then.
Nah... In last quiz, you see...
Shit... I'm coming!
I'll shoot it out!
H-Huh? You can't!
Not inside—!
Shit, the bell already rang!
Let's go, quick!
Yeah, I'm sluggish.
You said it.
Right?
I'm out.
Huh? Where's Keiko?
Huh? Oh yeah.
Second
Storehouse
Where is she?
Kyou-chan! Stop...
You're skipping class... You're a bad-boy!
Shut up...
I won't settle down unless we do this.
Just shut up and behave yourself.
Huh?
Shit... Shit! Go inside!
Oh... You're hopeless.
You'll end up dejected if we left it alone like that.
Does it feel good? Kyou-chan, does it?
Shit... Having such a raunchy belly...
You're so erotic!
Kyou-chan!
I'm coming!
I'm gonna come too... I'm coming!
Kyou-chan, you're still lively down there...
It's okay... You can do it until you settle down.
It feels amazing!
Your dick... Your dick!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Keiko...
Keiko!
Kyou-chan...
You got it?
You're not washing my semen
down there for the entire day.
Yeah!
Hey, Keiko! Where have you been?
I was in the washroom...
Jeez... Class is almost over!
Sorry!
So, it was just me being paranoid...
I was worried, you know...
She willingly did everything I told her.
I know...
She's totally captivated by me.
But hey, you and Kyouya are going steady.
He always treats you harshly like that.
Just seeing it pisses me off at times.
Try to speak out on him every now and then.
Yeah, that's right!
Hey, I can hear you...
I... I don't really mind it.
Coz, you see...
Kyou-chan is adorable!
Jeez, Keiko. You really are...
The one who's captivated...
Oh yeah, now that I remember...
I'm gonna...
...might be me, for all I know.
Why is it only me who has
these supplementary lessons...
Ahh—! I don't want to do this anymore!
Hey, isn't this already enough, sensei!
The competition is just around
the corner and I wanna swim already.
Jeez, you...
I even reserved us this room so try
to take this a bit more seriously.
Stop being so tight-assed, Kazu-kun!
Woah... Hey, I told you not to call
me that when we're at school!
If you keep talking like that,
I'm gonna tell everyone that we're going out!
Hey, hey... Chie... Give me a break...
Just get that done as you were told.
Okay—!
Sensitive
Supplementary
Lesson
So hot...
Umm...
I'm currently studying like you told me to.
Don't mind me and go on.
You see, I'd also love to skip
this supplementary lesson,
but you should consider
the time and place for 'that'...
Wait... Wait, stop!
Stripping me here would be...
You... What's with the bandages?
Th-That's because...
It hurts whenever the tips rub against my shirt...
No... Why are you getting turned on?
That's because these are erotic!
Come on, focus on your lessons.
Oh, jeez...
Hey, you made a mistake there.
That's wrong too.
Hey there, are you taking this seriously?
Answer the questions properly...
You... Are you about to come for real?
Hey... Are you about to come and just holding it—
I'm not about to come!
Don't lie to me.
You're about to come, right?
Here, hurry up and come!
Come!
You're making quite a lovely
face for such a cheeky brat!
You really did whatever you like on me, bastard!
It's payback time, idiot!
J-Just wait a minute...
Damn!
You... When did you learn about this—
You're already bulging here.
Look, I'm gonna tease you down here too!
You're moaning like a girl. Are you
not ashamed of yourself?
Shut up!
You dare do something like this to your teacher!
I can't take this anymore!
Wait...
Why did you spray it on me?
Ahh, I'm so done for today!
Let's end the lessons for today, okay?
Let's continue it next time.
Not yet.
What are you doing?!
Wait, stop it!
I totally don't want to have sex in this place!
Hey, wait! Are you listening?!
You... Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Chie, your insides feel so incredible!
The truth is you're feeling good as well, right?
I don't! Idiot!
Don't pull my nipples!
Kazu-kun, you idiot!
Bonehead!
Hey, hey...
Didn't I tell you not to call me
by my name?! You're a bad girl.
You need some punishment!
Isn't it hot today?
Kazu-kun, don't do this!
Yeah.
Well, it's almost over so let's do our best.
W-Well be seen... We'll be seen from outside!
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
I'll start moving.
No... No!
Th-This is... so embarrassing!
You say it's embarrassing, but aren't you loving this?
Now what? Did you already
reflect on what you did?
If you learned your lesson, you'll listen to me—
I'm not listening!
You'll be the one in trouble if this goes out!
Now that it came to this...
I'll have to at least take you down with me!
Kazu-kun... Kazu-kun!
Chie... Chie!
No... Stop that!
I'm feeling so good now
and I can't think of anything else!
Kazu-kun...
I'm gonna come already!
Me too, I'm gonna come!
Let's come together!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
So...
In the end, we weren't able to do
the supplementary lessons.
What are we gonna do?
Umm...
Then how about we head home
and go for a second round?
I hate this watermark
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization