Spring. The season of new beginnings.
Hinekure Kyouya
I...
got a girlfriend.
Hinayama Keiko
The Selfish Boyfriend and
Tne Gentle Girlfriend
That kinda chubby girl is my girlfriend.
Her name's Hinayama Keiko.
I confessed to her out of the blue.
I expected her to say no, but...
Ever since then...
We've kissed...
Kyo-chan! Kyo-chan!
And we've even had sex.
But, she...
She wasn't a virgin.
I was though.
Ah, Keiko, you've got cream or your cheek.
H-Huh? Kyo-chan?
I'm borrowing you.
Boy's Bathroom
Kyo-chan...
This is so embarrassing.
You know that this is the boy's bathroom, right?
Here. Suck it for me.
Aren't you going to listen to what
your boyfriend tells you to do?
B-But...
Just do it already! I'm saying I want you to do it!
You're such an impatient guy.
You're going that deep already?!
What the hell? She's too good at this!
It feels too good... I don't think I can move!
Did she do this with her previous boyfriend too?
Hold up!
I'm seriously about to cum!
I'm not kidding!
I'm cumming!
All better now, Kyo-chan?
Class is about to start, so we should probably head bac...
Not enough.
K-Kyo-chan?
S-Stop!
We're gonna be late! You don't even have a condom!
K-Kyo-chan?
Stop!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm... I'm gonna cum in the boy's bathroom at school!
K-Kyo-chan, there are people here!
We should stop!
Nope.
Keep it down, okay?
What's wrong?
Didn't you just hear somebody?
Nope...
Just your imagination.
Hm, maybe.
Kyo-chan, I can't...
I'll help you keep your mouth shut then.
I'm gonna cum.
I'm about to cum!
N-No, don't!
Not inside...
Shit, that's the bell!
Hurry up!
Huh? Where's Keiko?
Oh, yeah...
Second Storage Room
Where'd she disappear to?
Kyo-chan? Seriously, knock it off!
Only delinquents skip class!
Can't you just stay quiet?
I can't cool off at all.
Just stay still.
Shit! Shit!
Go in!
Fine, I guess I'll help.
It'd be sad if you kept going like that.
Does it feel good? Does it feel good, Kyo-chan?
You're just letting your embarrassing
belly out for the entire world to see.
What's the matter with you?
Kyo-chan!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Me too.
Kyo-chan, you're still so hard.
Go ahead.
Keep going until you're satisfied, Kyo-chan.
It feels so good!
Your dick...
Your dick!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Keiko... Keiko...
Kyo-chan...
Listen.
You're going to go the whole day
without cleaning out that semen, got it?
Keiko, where were you?
I went to the bathroom.
Class is already over!
Sorry.
If she didn't even object to my request,
she must be really into me.
You got us worried for nothing.
You said it.
I'm surprised you're still with Kyouya.
Isn't he mean to you?
He sometimes just stares at you like he's pissed off.
You should be stricter with him.
Yeah, she's right!
These bitches.
I... I don't thing he's like that at all.
After all,
Kyo-chan's really cute!
I think... I might be the one really into her.
Why am I the only one stuck with remedial classes?!
Agh, I hate this!
Hey, can we just be done, Teach?
The tournament's just around the corner!
I wanna get in the pool and practice!
Listen, you...
I booked this room just for you.
Can you just be serious for one second?
Try seeing things from my point of view, Kazu-kun!
H-Hey, I told you not to call me by my name at school!
Oh, right, otherwise people would find out we're dating.
Hey, Chie, come on. Give me a break.
Hurry up and do that.
Okay.
Sensitive
Remedial
Classes
So hot...
Excuse me. I'm trying to do my work like you asked me to do.
Just keep doing it then.
I don't mind not doing these remedial classes,
but it'd be nice if you tried to think
about the place and time for this.
H-Hey!
Hey, knock it off!
I can't get naked here!
You have bandaids there...
It hurts when they rub against my clothes, so...
Wai... Why are you getting turned on?!
Because this is hot!
Come on, focus on your work.
Sheesh, you...
Hey, you got that one wrong.
That one's wrong too.
Are you even trying?
Focus on your work...
Are you... seriously about to cum?
Are you holding it back?
I'm not about to cum!
Don't lie to me!
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Come on! Hurry up and cum!
Cum!
You're such an annoying brat usually.
This is a good change of pace.
You really went all out there, huh?
You bastard!
This is payback, jerk.
W-Wait. Just wait!
Shit...
Where did you learn this?!
Looks like it's already rarin' to go.
Look, I'll play with you here too!
You're moaning like a girl. Aren't you embarrassed?
Shut up! How dare you do this to your teacher...
Crap, that's it...
Hey!
Why'd you shoot it all over me?!
That's it! We're done here!
Class is over too, right? Let's do this another day...
Not yet.
Huh?
Wh-What are you...
Hey, stop it!
I definitely don't want to have sex here!
Hey, stop! Listen to me!
You jerk! Big jerk!
It feels so good inside you, Chie.
Feels good, doesn't it?
It doesn't! You jerk!
Stop pulling on my nipples!
I hate you, Kazu-kun!
You big idiot!
Hey, come on. I told you not to call me by my name.
What a bad girl.
I think you need to be punished!
It's hot, isn't it?
Kazu-kun, no! Stop!
I know right!
Let's keep at it for a little more.
There are people outside! They can see!
Yeah.
I'm gonna move.
No! No!
This is too embarrassing!
Really? 'Cuz it looks like you're enjoying it!
Do you feel bad about what you did now?
If you've learned your lesson, then...
I'm not gonna listen to you!
You're the one who'll be in trouble if we're caught, Kazu-kun!
Now that it's come to this...
We'll just have to go all the way!
Kazu-kun! Kazu-kun!
Chie! Chie!
No... stop!
It feels too good!
My head's going blank!
Kazu-kun, I... I'm gonna cum!
Me too! I'm cumming!
Let's cum together!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
So...
We actually haven't really done any work in these classes.
What are you gonna do about that?
Uh...
Let's just go home and get right into round two?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub:  торрент иваниваныч