Mayu? Takuya?
Both your father and I won't be back until tomorrow.
So you two better be on your best behavior, okay?
Okay, we're leaving now.
Yeah, okay.
Day only for two
Onii...
Are you an idiot?!
What if Mom noticed?!
You're the idiot, onii.
You were totally ready to go too.
How can I help it when I have you turning me on?
Ew, that's gross.
When did doing this start to become normal for us?
At first it was just mostly fooling around, but after a while...
We just couldn't stop anymore.
This "relationship" of ours will probably end one day.
But when I look at her...
I can't stop myself!
Hey, don't be in such a rush!
Why are you so hard when you're trying
to have sex with your little sister?
I have such a perverted older brother.
Shut up!
You're the one who started all this!
You're licking too much!
H-Hey! I don't see a condom!
There.
Here, you can do me from behind.
Nobody's home, so you can moan as loudly as you want!
Onii... You're being even more rough than usual!
You're being too loud!
People outside might be able to hear you!
Shit, I'm gonna cum!
Me too!
I'm... gonna cum!
We're not done yet.
It's too early for you to be tired.
I know you're just acting tough.
I hope you don't give up now.
Yeah, keep talking.
My room
What time is it right now?
No... idea.
Don't play with my nipples!
Why you...
Payback.
That's good... It feels so good!
Onii... Onii, your dick is...
It's thrusting all the way into my womb!
I'm gonna cum again!
I feel like I'm gonna pass out.
My head's a mess.
Oh, shit.
We ran out of condoms.
Shit, I can't hold on!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum just like this!
Cum! Pump me full of it!
Hey...
You came inside me, didn't you?
U-Uh, w-well...
Take responsibility, 'kay?
You idiot brother.
Responsibility, huh?
Well, I guess...
Being the brother that teachers her
about that isn't too bad at all.
Don't cry about this later.
You dummy.
Takuya? Mayu? Are you two ready?
Hey, Takuya! Mayu?!
Can you say something?!
You're both going to be late!
Takuya?! Are you listening?!
Yeah, I know!
I'm coming now!
Sh-Shit...
Two people's  days
See you later.
Later. I'm meeting up with a friend.
Huh? First time I'm hearing about that!
Why should I tell you? You shitty brother.
What's her problem?
Holy shit.
Let's stop somewhere on the way home.
Sounds good.
When did you wanna go?
Hm, I'm not sure.
I wonder if that shop's open.
My little sister's been extremely cold to me ever
since we started going to the same school.
Mayu-chan's crazy hot.
And I mean that in a good way.
I'm so jealous of you Takuya.
I can't believe you have that amazing of a sister.
She might be my sister but she's annoying as shit.
Get out of your dreamworld.
But I'm not gonna tell them that we've been
in a carnal relationship for a while now.
We were so close until just a little while ago...
What's with her now?
Fuck, she really pisses me off.
That first year, Mayu. She's really cute, isn't she?
You see her tits?!
I wanna date her!
Should I try confessing to her?
No, don't do it. Give up.
I hear she has a boyfriend.
You serious?!
And so, like...
H-Huh, Takuya?
We need to talk.
Hey, what are you doing?!
My friends are waiting!
You're actually the worst!
Shut up, you dumb little sister!
Just shut your mouth for a second!
Why are you trying to fuck here?
Are you a monkey or something?
Ah, geez. Just stop it already!
W-Wai...
Why are you taking off my panties?!
You're not actually going to try...
No! No! Stop!
I don't want to get sticky at school!
I'm gonna kill you if you move.
You're the worst!
Stupid! Idiot!
Scum!
Perverted brother!
Geez, do you ever shut up?
Stop moving your hips and take it out of me already!
Take it out...
Shit... I'm gonna cum!
H-Huh?!
You're really the worst!
Stop already!
S-Seriously stop!
I did her... at school.
We're done now, right?
Take it out already.
Sorry, I'm gonna keep going a little.
Huh?! Do you have a brain?!
Are you actually a monkey?!
Seriously stop, you shitty brother!
Sto...
Oh, right.
Get me a soda.
Get it yourself.
Come here soon. Got it?
You made it look like I dragged you here kicking and
screaming, but you look like you're enjoying this.
Shut up!
I'm not!
Oh, yeah. Right there.
Shit... You're gonna make me cum already.
I'm cumming!
Drink it! Drink it all!
I really hate our next class.
Wanna skip?
Hey...
We don't have to today, right?
Let's just go home for now.
Just shut your mouth and keep it that way.
What's got your panties in a bunch?
You're being really annoying.
I'm perfectly fine!
Just shut up and let me do it.
Shit. What's going on. It's not going in!
Ah, damn it!
Damn it! Fucking shit!
Listen. I think it's about time you got yourself a girlfriend.
Shut up!
You're just saying that because you have a boyfriend!
Right?!
Yeah, you're looking down on me, aren't you?!
Like hell I can let that go!
Huh? Boyfriend?
Yeah!
That's why you've been acting so cold recently!
You've been distancing yourself and playing me like a fool!
You serious?
You were jealous?!
Wh-What's so funny?!
Like hell I have a boyfriend.
B-But I heard rumors!
And you're the idiot that believed those rumors.
Stop making fun of me.
So then what's up with the way you've been acting?
You've been acting so cold. Did I piss you off or something?
If I don't... I can't stop myself from wanting to do it at school.
What?
But I made her do it anyway.
I'm such an idiot.
Take off your clothes.
Okay...
Mayu! Mayu!!
More! More!!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum in deep in you as possible!
Y-Yeah, shoot it out in me!
Onii!
Mayu! Mayu!
Onii! Onii!!
I wonder what kind of guy Mayu's boyfriend is like.
Who knows.
Might be an ugly dude.
Hey, Takuya?
You hear anything about this?
Like hell I have.
So...
What kind of guy are you into?
Huh?
Where's this coming from?
Just something that popped into my head.
Someone who's not like my shitty brother.
Geez.
You cheeky, shitty little sister.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч