Nee, ...Shiyo
Hey, ...let's do it
will you... make love?
First Volume
Mayu, Takuya!
Me and dad won't be back until tomorrow.
You two get along together okay?
We're going now, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Futari no Hi
Onii...
You idiot!
What would we do if mom found us out?
You're an idiot as well, stupid brother!
Aren't you getting onto it already as well?
I can't help it when you're doing that to me.
Woah... Disgusting!
Oh my...
When was it again...
that we started doing this kind of things?
We're just half fooling around at the beginning.
But shortly after, we couldn't
stop ourselves going further.
This kind of relationship will need
to eventually come to an end.
But when I look at her...
I just can't help it!
Don't get too impatient!
To get this hard from your little sister...
What a perverted brother!
Shut up, you're the one that started this.
You're licking too much!
Wait... You're not wearing a rubber yet!
And here we go.
Here you go.
You can thrust it in from behind!
Our parents aren't home so you
can moan as much as you want!
Onii... You're wilder than usual!
You're voice is louder than usual too!
Won't you be heard outside?
This is bad! I'm gonna come!
Me too!
I'm coming already!
We're not done yet.
It's too early to get worn out.
Acting tough, are we?
Don't be giving up on me later, okay?
You're one to talk!
What time... is it?
I don't... know!
Don't tease my nipples!
You...
Payback time!
I-Incredible! That feels so good!
Onii... Your dick is...
thrusting deep into my womb!
I'm coming again!
I feel like I'm gonna pass out!
I can't think of anything else!
This is bad...
We already ran out of condoms.
Oh no... I can't hold it back anymore!
I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come just like this!
Come! Shoot a lot out!
Hey...
You came inside me, right?
N-No... You see... well...
You'll take responsibility, right?
Stupid brother!
Even if you tell me about responsibility...
But well...
As a brother, being told of that doesn't sound bad.
Don't go complaining about it later.
Idiot.
Takuya, Mayu! Are you not
done preparing for school yet?
Hey Takuya, Mayu! Answer me!
You're both gonna be late!
Takuya! Do you hear me?
I hear you! I'm coming now!
Damn it!
Futari no Hibi
I'm going now!
See ya.
I promised to meet with my friends.
Huh? I never heard about this earlier.
You didn't have to know, shitty brother!
What the hell...
That's dangerous, hurry!
Let's go somewhere fun?
Oh, great idea!
When will we go?
Oh, what should I do...
You should come.
It's not like that, but I think I can go just for a bit.
Really?
Since my sister entered my school, she's
been giving me an incredibly cold shoulder.
Mayu-chan really is wonderful...
in more ways than one.
I really envy you Takuya, having such a sister!
Nah, little sisters are actually just annoying.
You guys dream too much!
I said that but,
Mayu and I had a physical relationship ever since.
Even though she was clinging
that much on me last time...
What the hell's up with her lately?
Damn, it's getting on my nerves!
That freshman called Mayu is such a cutie!
Have you seen those titties?
I wanna date her! Should I try to confess to her?
Nah, just stop that!
She apparently has a boyfriend already.
Seriously?!
Yeah, seriously.
And then...
Eh... Aniki...
Let's talk for a bit.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
You even scared my friends!
You really are the worst!
Shut up, you shitty little sister!
Just keep quiet!
What's with that attitude, you monkey!
Jeez, I said stop!
W-W-Wait!
Why are you taking my panties off?
Don't tell me you want to do it!
No way, stop that!
We totally can't do this in school!
I'll kill you if you start moving!
You're the worst! Idiot! Retard! Nasty!
Perverted big brother!
Shut up!
Wait, stop moving your hips and pull it out!
Pull it out—
Damn, I'm gonna come!
You really are the worst!
Stop this, seriously! Stop!
We did it in the campus.
Isn't that enough? Pull it out already!
Sorry, just a little more!
Are you stupid? You really are a monkey!
I said stop fucking me, you shitty brother!
Stop...
> Ah, oh yeah.
> Buy me juice as well.
Mayu: Get it yourself.
(Yesterday)
> Come here later for
just for a bit, okay?
Come here later for just for a bit, okay?
All that loud objection when I'm dragging you here,
and you're now making a face longing for something.
Shut up, just come already!
That's it... I'm close...
You're really making me come soon!
I'm coming!
Drink it! Drink all of it!
The next class...
Want to skip it?
Hey...
Isn't that enough for today? Let's go home first.
Shut up, you're annoying!
Why are you so worked up?
Seriously, you're such a pain!
I'm not worked up! Just let me do it already!
Shit, what the hell? I can't put it in properly...
Shit! Shit, shit, shit!
Hey...
You should just get a girlfriend already.
Shut up! You're saying you're getting enough
already 'coz you have a boyfriend! Right?
You're always mocking me,
you shit! Is it that fun for you?
Huh? Boyfriend?
That's right!
Isn't that why you're treating me like that lately?
Aren't you making fun and ignoring me!
Seriously? Did you get jealous?
What's funny, damn you!
There's no way that I have a boyfriend!
But the rumors...
You're a plain idiot to believe such
rumors and get jealous all by yourself!
You're making fun of me... Then what's with that attitude lately?
Being so cold on me... Were you
angry at me or something?
That's because... if I don't do that,
I won't be able to hold myself
back while we're at school.
What's with that?
We ended up doing it here.
I looked like an idiot.
Take your clothes off.
Mayu... Mayu!
More... More!
I'm coming. I'm shooting
it in your deepest parts!
Squirt it all out, Onii!
Mayu... Mayu!
Onii... Onii!
I wonder what kind of guy Mayu's boyfriend is.
Who knows?
He could be ugly for all we know.
Hey, Takuya.
Haven't you heard anything?
There's no way I know anything about it.
Hey...
What kind of guy do you like?
Huh? Why are you asking
that out of nowhere?
Well... I just kind of got curious.
Someone who isn't like my shitty big brother.
Jeez...
Shitty cheeky little sister.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization