Now look what we have here.
Aren't you embarrassed by how hard it is, Yuta?
How can you be so aroused by your blood-related cousin?
Sister Summer Episode 01: S-Stupid...
Yuta Yamauchi, high school senior.
A poor student who for a certain goal
sacrifices the precious time of the summer vacation to studying.
First of all, it's you...
This is my cousin, Kei Higashide.
I usually call her Kei.
She's a twisted girl who refrains from no methods to make me do what she wants.
Though actually, maybe not.
And thanks to Kei, my summer vacation is taking a really twisted direction.
Here I thought you were staring gloomily at your bad results,
but actually you were ogling at something like this!
Hey! Don't-
You're that desperate to look at a girl's panties?
No!
What's with that expression? You were desperate, weren't you?
For now your big Sister's panties should be enough.
Now let's check your situation down there.
Wait, Kei!
Seriously...
I thought you matured nicely, but you turned into a plain pervert.
So, who's that girl on the photo?
Don't... do that!
You're so dishonest. I knew you were going to cum like this anyway.
Kei...
What? You're turned on by your sister's feet?
You're a real pervert, Yuta.
Your cock is all stiff and hot now.
Let's do it harder.
How is it? Do my feet feel good?
Your cock is tingling hard and so much juice is flowing out.
You're so cute... Should I... Should I kiss you?
It's okay, Yuta, don't hold back.
Cover my panties with your cum.
Yeah, cover me with all that sticky cum you have collected up in you!
Sorry.
Such a shame, I forgot my phone at a time like this.
Would you take a pic or two?
Point it this way.
Cherry blossoms are so beautiful...
Why do the petals fall so soon?
Send me that later, okey?
Don't forget it.
I came here just to tease him, but that picture turned it all upside down.
Kei...
I came here to tell you to be more self-confident.
Hey, what...
Now you're over-confident!
You're so wet down here, Kei!
Stop it...
Not my boobs!
Don't look!
Why? They're so beautiful!
Guys like big ones, right?
Mine aren't... that much...
Stop, Yuta!
Do you have the determination? We're cousi--
Yuta...
There's no turning back now.
You know that right?
You're your big sister's first.
You claimed a girl's maidenhead... That makes you a grown-up man.
Become a man, Yuta!
Does it hurt, Kei?
No... This is... Looks like I've to teach you this and that about girls.
But don't worry. It's a sister's duty to devote herself to her brother.
Do as you wish.
Amazing! So wild!
That is because your inside feels so good...
And the expression on your face just turns me on even more...
Turns you on? I didn't think...
This is embarrassing...
Amazing!
I can't take this...
I want that, then your expression will turn me on even more!
So deep... Amazing!
I feel weird...
Don't go so deep! Amazing!
You're messing me up!
You're twisting my insides around! I feel so weird!
Don't...
I'm full with you... from the lips to the deepest parts.
I'm about to... cum.
I'm about to cum... I'm cumming...
Let's do it... together! Together!
Yuta! Yuta!
So good...
I'm cumming!
Amazing!
My belly's full of Yuta's sperm...
I can feel your seeds deep in me...
Just what were you thinking, cumming inside me?
You didn't exactly stop me either.
I just... I didn't want to cum alone.
You men are so simple.
You go all out if women don't stop you.
You've really grown up as well, Kei.
Sorry about my boobs.
My friends at school said that guys only change if there's a girl in sight.
You've been studying really hard. Is it for that girl on the photo?
I'm having my exams next year you know...
Are you coming to my school?
I can help with studying if you--
Wait, hey Yuta!
You just cummed in me! So lewd!
Guys work hard for girls.
You turn my words against me...
Wait...
Wait a little, this way...
Don't, Yuta... Not this pose...
Listen to what I'm saying, Yuta!
Not there... I said not there...
This way it feels... a lot better than earlier...
I can feel your thick cock hitting my womb...
No... This feels too good, I'm about to cum already!
Yuta! Yuta!
No... You're too deep!
S-Stupid...