So what's your impression of my lap?
I want to lick it.
W
Ane
Nee-sama!
Second Chapter [Love, Loveeee]
Go away, pervert!
Wait up!
I'm over here!
Hey, Yuuta, do we look like a couple too?
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Could I get spoiled if we were a couple?
Yuuta, don't run away from me!
We ended up like that last time for some reason,
but it's also bad to lie about your real feelings.
Kei-nee, are you regretting it?
I already told you, I'll always-
You know, feelings won't be conveyed correctly unless you say them out loud.
How about confessing properly for once?
N-No… don't… Yuuta…
Listen to people when they speak…
Yuuta…
Sorry, but let me be spoiled, just a bit… just a bit more…
I too, really want to… like this…
You don't need to hold back.
But…
Don't… Yuuta…
Why do you want it, Kei-nee?
Don't make me say it…
You coward…!
I want… Yuuta's… Yuuta's… I want it…
This?
Yeah, that. I want your cock in me.
Don't… put it in so deep in one go…
You're doing it so hard…
My voice keeps coming out on its own…
It's harder than last time… It's bigger too!
Don't put me in this position…
It's really wet though.
But… No… No…
And besides, Yuuta's is too hot…
It's too good…
I'm turning into a pervert too…
No… I'm cumming…
No… I can't…
Huh… Y-Yuuta…?
I want to watch your face as you cum.
No…
I don't want you to watch me…
I'll cum this time…
I'm cumming…
Yuuta… Yuuta…
I'm cumming… I'm cumming…
A lot came out… Yuuta… came a lot…
These summer festivals aren't fun at all when I'm alone…
But I'll be cornering Yuuta if I keep on like this…
This really isn't working out.
Speaking of which, how's it going with that guy, Youko?
Oh? You mean Yamauchi?
Didn't you say you'd make him fall for you easily?
Oh, him? I completely forgot about him.
Seriously?
Is this about Yuuta?
More importantly, this sucks. The lock's broken.
Hey, could you watch out for anyone for me?
Okay.
So, give Yamauchi to me if you don't want him.
He's good looking.
Are you making a perverted noise?
Hey, don't you think Yamauchi would listen to anything you say?
I only talked to him because he'd look nice as a keepsake.
And I even gave him my phone number and email yet he hasn't even bothered to contact me.
W-Wait, what are you-
It's just like, I don't need a loser.
I'm guessing he's a pervert too.
Huh?
What would anyone like you know about him?
Yuuta.
Huh?
Here.
You can turn me into a mess, you can even think of me as that girl.
Kei-nee…
If you need a replacement, I'm…
I don't want a replacement!
No-
I don't care about her anymore.
Yuuta, but…
If Kei-nee's here, I don't need anyone else.
I want to be spoiled…
I want you to spoil me more, Nee-san.
You're a pathetic brother.
You wore this uniform when you were in high school, right?
Pretty much…
Hey, don't…!
I want to keep the Kei-nee from high school to myself.
Yuuta…
Hey, Yuuta, this is embarrassing!
I want to make the one I love most into mine!
Yuuta…
Then come… deeper…
I want to feel you until the very end…
I know we're not supposed to love each other this way,
but I want to be with you like this.
Forever… Forever and ever…
It's good…
I'm about to cum…
Yuuta…
I'm cumming… I'm cumming!
Nee-san…
I'm connected…
I'm connected with Yuuta…
I want you to call me Kei, not Nee-san…
I want to be your girlfriend, Yuuta…
It's so deep…
Yuuta's hot thing is reaching my deepest place…
No, I'm going crazy…
No, I'm cumming, no, Yuuta, together, together,
cumming, cumming!
There's so much… of Yuuta's hot…
You need to take responsibility.
Eh?
I won't forgive you if you cheat.