Well... well...
You're getting hard like this.
Don't you feel ashamed at all, Yuuta?
And you're feeling it while looking at your cousin.
W
Ane Summer!
Nee-sama!
First Chapter [I, Idiot]
Yamauchi Yuuta, 3rd year highschool student.
He spends his summer vacation time
studying as an exam student.
Anyway, you're such...
This is my cousin, Higashide Kei, known as Kei-nee.
She's one of many cousins, who's willing
to help a "younger brother" cousin like me.
Well... I might be wrong about that.
And then, because of Kei-nee, I'm able to experience surprises this summer.
I came here to see if you were lurking because
your exam results were bad,
But you're here looking at this kind of picture.
No... that's... something... you can't-
Did you really want to see a girl's panties so much?
That's not true-
What's with that face? Didn't you want to see them?
Well, you could watch your sister's panties for now.
Then, let me check how your thing handles this situation.
Wait, Kei-nee!
My goodness.
Here I thought that you would mature splendidly,
but here you are like the other perverted guys.
So, who's the girl in the picture?
Wa... Wait, you can't do-
Why you don't be honest with yourself?
Since I'm sure you would release it after this.
Kei-nee...
What is it? Do you feel excited from your sister's feet?
Yuuta is really a pervert, right~?
Your sturdy and hard penis is getting hot right now.
Let me be more intense for you.
How is it? Do my feet feel good?
Your penis is shivering between my feet...
And then there's so much juice coming out from the tip of it.
You're so cute.
Kiss... Do you want to kiss me?
It's okay, Yuuta. You don't have to hold back.
You can release all of your sperm into my panties right now.
Let it go... Give all of your saved sperm to me immediately.
I'm sorry!
I'm so unlucky.
I can't believe that I didn't bring my cellphone at a time like this.
Hey, you're not going to take it?
The photos.
Yes.
I will.
The cherry blossoms are really beautiful.
Why is that cherry blossom petal so little?
That photos... It'd be nice if you could send them to me.
Don't forget about it, okay?
I just want to tease him a little bit more.
But he's hopeless if he's looking at those photos.
Kei-nee.
I hope you can keep your confidence at max.
That's what I want you to be.
Hey, don't-
Don't get cocky...
Kei-nee pussy is really drenched.
You can't do that.
My breasts... No! You can't!
Why I can't do this? Your breasts are beautiful.
Is this why guys prefer the bigger ones?
My breasts... Aren't they-
Aren't they big... Yuuta.
Did you already prepare for this?
You know that we're cousins-
Yuuta...
It's too late to let you know that it's my first time.
Now that you put it in I'm sure you know,
it's your sister's first time.
You've already taken one girl's virginity.
Still, I can't blame you for doing that.
Be a man, Yuuta.
Does it hurt, Kei-nee?
It's not... this isn't-
Maybe I should let you know about a woman's heart after all.
Don't hold back.
It's my duty as your sister to receive all of that.
Do as you'd like.
Amazing, It's intense!
That's because inside of Kei-nee feels good,
and you're making an erotic face like that.
Erotic? I didn't mean...
to do that.
It's embarrassing.
It's great.
You can't do that!
I want to look... I want to look at Kei-nee's erotic face some more.
It's too deep... amazing.
I'm going to go crazy!
You can't do it that deep-
No... I'll go crazy!
Please hold back!
Or I'll lose myself for real!
No~!!
Inside of my pussy..
All of it... is with Yuuta penis!
That's... going to make me cum!
It's good...
Cum... I'm going to cum!
At least... let me cum... let me cum together~!
Yuuta... Yuuta...
It feels good.
I'm cumming!
It's too much...
There's a lot of Yuuta's sperm,
inside of my stomach...
A lot of Yuuta's sperm is...
going through deep inside of me.
What're you thinking, Yuuta? You even released it inside of me.
Even Kei-nee wasn't trying to stop me before, right?
I-I just don't...
want to cum alone, or something like that.
Guys are really simple with things like that.
You get cocky when the girls let you do that.
Kei-nee isn't not like most girls, right?
I'm sorry to let you touch something boring like that.
My friends from school said something to me.
That a guy would change his behavior because of what a girl wants.
You've seriously been studying by yourself lately,
Is that for the girl from the photos?
Next year, I'll be an exam student after all.
Why don't you go the same school with me?
For studying, I could teach you some of it.
Wait... Hey, Yuuta!
You just released it earlier, right? You pervert!
Any guy would do his best for what a girl wants, right?
You can even say something like that right now.
That's-
Wait a minute... We can't let this continue...
No... No, Yuuta, in a position like this-
Wo... Would you listen to me...
Yuuta!
That place is-
No... I said you can't do it in that place-
If you continue doing this...
The tip of your-
No, I can feel your thrusting!
Yuuta's big thing... is hitting my womb!
No! It feels....too good.
That makes me want to cum!
Yuuta... Yuuta.
No, you can't do it that deep!!
Idiot...