Sonia
age 1*
eyes odd-eye
hair white
heght 152
b-w-h 80-54-81
weighr 42
Lucy
age 19
eyes green
hair black
heght 158
b-w-h 86-58-90
weight 52
I'm a beginn.
W... Would you tting?
Nn... smell of ecchi.
It smells nice...
Go into heat...
Look at my face please spray it all over me.
This... go into heat.
Please copulater...
I cna't go on.
Hurry please stic it in.
Ahh! It's going inside!!
A-aa! No! No!
M-Mastar... Aa!
I'v never felt this way before!
I'm gonna go crazy!
It feels so good!
Go crazy! Go crazy!
Mastar! Mastar!
I'm coming! Coming! Coming! Coming!
Mastar...
Please teach me ecchi...
Alisa
age 29
eyes blue
hair blonde
height 132
b-w-h 61-56-78
weight 36
Ferriss
age 21
eyes pink
hair pink
height 176
b-w-h 96-64-102
weight 64
Nn nn! Go for broke!
Mew! No! No!
Mew! Fu-mew! No! No! Coming! Coming!!
Mew... Stop! It's my loss! It's my loss!
Mewwwwww!! Please fuck me deep and hard!!
Aa! Ahh! I'm look like a artificial vagina...
No! No!
Aaa! Go crazy! Go crazy!
Crazy! Go crazy!
No... No! No! No! Coming! I'm coming!!
It's pouring into me! There's so much... are you stupid...
Does this feel good? It smells nice.
Какой дебил писал это???
It's okay! Fill my pussy with all of your cum!
Meww! Threre's so much...
Carry out a pregnancy.
We're gonna have a child...
Fu-meowww! Oh yes! It feels so good!
My pussy with all of your cum!
Yes! Yes! Please go ahead and cum!
Cum please! Cum please!
Fu-meowwww! Mewww!! Yes!
Oh! Yes! Oh! Yes! Please! Please!
Гений дизайна шрифтов.. :(
It's pouring into me! There's so much...
You can still let out a lot more can't you!
Leroux
age 1*
eyes green
hair blonde
heght 163
b-w-h 88-60-96
weight 58
Lily
age 1*
eyes blue
hair blonde
heght 152
b-w-h 84-52-86
weight 41
Let me...
Look at my face please spray it all over me.
Go into heat.
Let me help you.
It's time for supper.
This is a specialty milk that my master. Dig in!
This... go into heat.
Was all of that milk drunk?
Nya that was great.
My master.
Mew he loves filth.
You look very delighted.
You are drooling.
To scrounge?
I cna't go on.
Hurry please stic it in.
Please my master...
Please me...
My master...
No! Master...! Master...!
Oh my God. Lily just fainted...
No... No... Mew!!
Mew! Master!
Amy
age 18
eyes blue
hair blonde
heght 167
b-w-h 92-58-96
weight 56
Imani
age 18
eyes purple
hair purple & blue
heght 162
b-w-h 96-60-90
weight 57
Are you coming?
No no stop.
Please wait.
Daddy, I want a lot hentai milk.
OK?
Nya.
Daddy, that was great.
Are you happy?
Please, Daddy, please.
Oh yea.
I'm comming! I'm comming!
Incoming.
Long... amazing.
It feels so good.
Please enjoy yourself as much as you want, Daddy.
Daddy, I love it rough.
Would you getting?
Please go ahead and cum.
Ah. It smells nice.
This... go into head.
Look at my face please spray it all over me!
I just can't go on.
I'm incoming.
This... go into heat.
Hurry please stic it int.
Ahh! It's going inside!!
Daddy? Do you wanna mate with me?
Mating's something that feels good, right?
It's wrong for parents to mate with children?
Yay! Mommy doesn't have to know, right?
Milk?
Daddy, I'd like a refill, please.
What's next?
No! Stop!
Wow, this is mating?! Mating's so great! I-It feels so good, and I start feeling really dumb! I'm turning into a cat!
I get to be a real girl cat! I get to be a real girl cat for Daddy!
Daddy, please...