Previously on Angel Tear.
Changing Lip!
So if we get your boss here,
we can produce an antidote. Is that right?
Precisely. But to do that, we need lust energy.
Then hurry up and gather it!
We need your help to do so!
We need to rape you.
You degenerates!
You have quite the fine ass, don't you?
He's violating every part
of my body that I've held sacred!
Watch closely as I make you into a woman.
It's going inside me.
That thing's going inside me!
Just a little more...
No! Stop!
Scream more!
Screw you! Screw you and
your disgusting penis!
Disgusting? You're going to be
getting a good taste of its cum!
No! You're being too rough!
I never thought I'd be able
to do this with you, Suzune-kun!
That hurts!
Now there's another penis inside me!
I love being able to shove my cock into you.
It really shuts your cheeky mouth up!
N-No!
Why is this happening? This is so humiliating!
A titfuck from an angel goddess is amazing!
No! Don't touch me there!
Get your hands off me!
You can feel pleasure from here too, you know?
I don't want to!
Just a little...
It doesn't hurt as much as it did yesterday.
I can tell that I'm getting wetter than yesterday!
The Targeted Angel Goddess
Angelita Betrayed by the Humans They Protected
Melancholic Female Teacher, Suzune
~ To Protect then get Fucked by a Chain of Meat Sticks ~
Not only was I unable to save him,
I was raped and violated by those lowlifes.
How will I ever show my face to the Goddess?
He came so much inside me
that my stomach was starting to bulge,
but it didn't hurt as much as the first time.
What? I'm busy.
I'll leave the documents for
President Zen's company funeral here.
Company funeral... for President Zen?
Y-You little...
Banish Spear!
I told you, that won't work!
Your physical attacks don't work on humans!
So what are you saying I do?
Menacing Crane Charge!
It worked?
President...
You fucking shop lifter! I'm calling the police!
That's Kazuya-kun!
U-Um, excuse me!
I'm this child's teacher, Shizumi Suzune.
His teacher? Perfect timing.
This kid was trying to shoplift.
You can see it on the camera!
Kazuya-kun?!
I'm sorry...
I-I'm truly sorry for what he's done.
This kind of thing becomes a habit.
It's better that he's disciplined.
He's not the kind of child who would shoplift.
I'll make sure that he's disciplined for his actions.
Please, sir.
It looks like this is his first offense,
so I'll let it slide for now.
Thank you very much!
Kid, you better thank your teacher.
I want to save him,
just as the Goddess saved me.
I want to talk to you about something, though.
Kazuya-kun, head on home.
Don't do something stupid
like that again, understood?
Yes... I'm really sorry.
Office
Thank you for what you did for him.
To tell you the truth,
what he did was really bad.
Is that so? In that case...
Honestly, thank you so much.
That's fine, 'cuz I was thinking of getting
to know you a bit better for that kid's sake.
Okay?
What the heck are you
trying to pull? I'll call the police!
But then I'd tell them about that kid.
But what he did is not related to this.
Then the deal's off.
I guess I'll just have to tell the police all about
what happened today. Oh, what a shame...
I-If I do this, you won't tell
anyone about what he did, right?
Yeah, I'm a man of my word.
Everything'll be just fine.
"Just fine?" All men are pigs!
I'll do it.
I can't believe I have to do this again!
Hey! What are you doing?!
I just wanted a peek.
I'll give you a new pair later.
End this already!
Are you getting into it now?
Your pussy's getting really wet.
That's not true...
Oh no! My body's reacting instinctively!
You're pretty good at this. You like sucking?
Shut up! This is only for that child's future!
Whoa, if you do it like that,
I'm gonna cum right away.
We've gotta savor this as much as we can.
You're blackmailing me into doing this.
Why the heck would I want to savor it?!
Are there any humans out there worth saving?!
You're starting to flood down there.
You must really get around, huh?
After all the things that they did to me,
my body's become dirtied.
Already?! It's pouring into
my mouth all of a sudden!
Oh, geez. Sorry about that. I'll take that
to the cleaners and get it washed for you.
N-No thanks. I politely decline
your offer. Are we done here?
Like hell we are!
That was just the foreplay!
Those other guys were like this too,
filled with nothing but lust.
He's already all the way
into my womb! It's so long!
Can penises really be this different
from person to person?!
How is it? It's reaching all the way to your womb, right?
I might be fast, but I'm big and I can keep on going.
Like I care! Just hurry up and finish already!
Oh, man, you're scary.
It might be best if I just let you
leave here all tattered and torn.
Shut up! You're just a...
If I weren't in this situation,
I'd never let a human get away with this!
Wow! Everything about you is just amazing!
You're going so deep!
What's going on! How deep is it pushing?
Just how far in is it going to go?!
I'll teach you a new pleasure
that you've never felt before.
It's reaching to the very back of my womb...
No, even deeper than that! It's going so far in!
It's so deep!
I'm going to plant my seed in you,
just like this. I can't wait to harvest it.
What?! No, you can't! Take it out!
I'm going to get cummed inside of again? No, not again!
No, please! Stop! Take it out, please!
Your pleas are falling on deaf ears.
I can feel all of his semen rushing out!
There's so much of it!
There's too much of it! If his cum goes that deep,
I'm definitely going to get pregnant!
You have my word.
I won't tell anyone about the kid.
Thank you...
I keep having to do it with such nasty humans.
Do I really have to save them?
I want to speak with the Goddess.
But, right now, she's doing everything
she can to protect the heavens.
Hey, Ms. Shizumi!
Kazuya-kun? You waited for me?
It's all my fault that this happened...
Don't worry about it, Kazuya-kun.
That's right. I was able to save this child's future.
Thank you, Kazuya-kun. Let's go home.
Yes.
Mr. Handa? I think I've got something fun for us.
Yeah, I'll talk to you later.
I might take a taste before you, though.
Kazuya-kun, never do anything
like that again, understood?
Promise me.
Y-Yes. I'm sorry.
It'll be fine. He'll change his ways.
If I just think about that, I think I'll manage...
I'm being fondled? Another filthy man?!
Would this teacher happen to be you?
That's the guy from before?
It seems like it is.
How does he know I'm a teacher?
What the heck?
Knock it off. I'll let you go with
a warning if you stop right now.
Is this how they made you go crazy
in that angel body of yours?
How'd he know? There's no way to even
look that up, and definitely not with a camera!
Is this a bluff?
Stop it! I'll scream!
Really? Because I could report you to the
Teacher's Association or the Board of Education.
Why does he have a picture of that? Who is this guy?!
You know what to do, don't you?
Your juices are spilling out,
but you're still trying to keep a straight face.
Your dedication to your image as a teacher is admirable.
You're getting excited, aren't you?
Are you starting to get wet?
Ms. Shizumi?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine. I was just trying to
hold back a cough, that's all.
This guy's taking out his dick here?
Wait, is he going to...
You're kidding! He really put it in!
He really put it in me!
We're on a train, but he still put it in me!
No, why is this happening?!
I'm having sex on a bus! There are all these people
and even my student here, but I'm having sex!
There's no way that no-one's noticed!
But as long as Kazuya-kun doesn't notice...
Oh, right. Ms. Shizumi...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: fyurie
quality control: fyurie