Please don't joke around.
I don't have the time to play with you.
I just came to greet him.
He really hasn't changed.
I don't mind leaving heaven,
but to be completely surrounded
by these filthy humans.
If it weren't for great people
like Yuri or the chairman,
I never would've thought
there was hope for their salvation.
I've been constantly doubting
the goddess's beliefs.
I should learn a little from the chairman.
This is...
Changing Lip!
Change Chairman Zendoui
back to normal this instant!
I've already corrupted his brain.
Foolishly tampering with it now
would only hasten his death.
Tell me how to save him.
Why would I tell you, an enemy?
Have it your way, then. Disappear!
What happened? Deppoinga?!
You couldn't be conspiring
with the demons, could you?
If you know about an antidote,
you'd better start talking.
If you don't...
Wait! Hold on!
The targeted Angel Goddess
Angelita Betrayed by the Humans They Protected
The Cool Female Instructor – Suzune The Glaring
Cosplay Goddess With a Filled Mouth
If we just call that boss of yours,
we'll be able to make an antidote, right?
Yes, but we'll have to gather lust energy
before we can do that, Suzune-kun.
I can't just call him from the demon world?
Since this human is working with the demons.
Get your preparations sorted and call him already.
I'm saying that you're an
important part in doing that.
I need to rape you.
You filth!
Didn't you want to save the chairman?
You have quite the ass, don't you?
H-Hurry up already.
You just need to gather lust energy, right?
Just doing something like this won't be enough.
What else are you planning to do?
I can't believe I'm being fondled
by trash like you for the chairman's sake.
Soon this "trash" will be raping you, though.
Oh, has it already begun?
I won't allow this to be done improperly.
What?
It's more efficient to gather lust energy
when more people are around.
These people are humans?
I'm going to be defiled by these filth?
Gross! He stinks! What is this?
He's rubbing my breasts.
Having to endure something like this.
It's like they're demons!
No way! No...
Don't use your mouth like that!
No! This is disgusting!
I can feel him spreading his saliva
over my nipple with his tongue.
We won't be able to get enough lust energy
if you aren't more aggressive, you know?
It stinks so much it's hard to bear.
My breasts are being fondled,
and his face is being shoved right in front of me.
Your nipples are getting hard.
I'll take good care of them for you, okay?
These filth are kissing, fondling,
and even licking me down there.
Wh-What was that just now?
What's this feeling?
Your clitoris is getting bigger.
Are you starting to feel good, Suzune-kun?
Clitoris?
You don't know what a clitoris is, huh?
No surprises there,
considering you're an angel goddess.
What is this? It feels like electricity
running through my body!
You're starting to get really wet down here.
He's gently pushing on my clitoris while playing with it.
It's going to make me go crazy!
E-Endure it! This is all to save the chairman!
I can't hold back anymore.
What is this? It's too big!
No way! There's no way that thing will fit inside me!
There's no point in forcing you.
I'll let you choose where this goes.
I don't care! Just hurry up and get this over with!
Stop! Why are we doing it like this?
Can't we just do it normally?
You said you didn't care, right?
I quite lile this position.
I'm having sex with an angel goddess.
It'd be a shame if the others can't see.
No! No!! Not in this position!
If you don't quiet down,
I might accidentally slip it into another hole.
So you're a virgin, huh?
No... It won't fit!
Watch how I force it into her
even though she doesn't want me to.
It's gonna go in.
That thing is gonna go inside me.
Just a little more.
No! S-Sto...
It went in!
That big, fat thing really went in!
I took an angel goddess' virginity!
Ow! No!
It feels like it's being ripped apart!
Whether it's going in or being pulled out, it hurts so much!
My vagina's going to break!
Every time he moves,
his penis rubs against me.
How is it, Suzune-kun?
Having my dick as your first is great, isn't it?
Hurry up and be done with it!!
Wai... You're being too rough!
It hurts!
You want it rough, don't you?
To think I'm really letting
a weak human have his way with me.
Looks like you're getting
used to it, huh? You're sucking me in.
No! His dick is making lewd noises with my juices!
This is great. How about I let some out right now?
Don't mess around! I'll get pregnant!
Shooting my seed into a squirming angel goddess?
Damn, you're the best, Suzune! Cry more!
Don't fuck with me!
You piece of crap! Your dick is filthy!
Crap, huh? I'll let you have a taste
of the cum from this filthy dick as I fill you up!
No! So rough!
No! Stop it!!
You piec...
Sto... No! Stop...
No way is this happening!
No!
It's coming out!
This filth's hot cum is flowing out into me!
I'll make sure I leave every single drop inside you.
No! I'll get pregnant! I'll have a child!
I don't want to have a child
with someone like you!
He filled me up with all this cum.
I can't believe I get to
do this with you, Suzune-kun!
Ow!
Another penis is thrusting
deep inside me!
There's so much cum coming out from inside.
I never thought I'd see you looking so slutty.
It's coming out!
All of his cum is going to come out!
Does the way you're looking at me mean that
you've already grown accustomed to the taste of cock?
No! There's no way that's true!
Just hurry up an...
This is to save the chairman.
I only need to endure this!
Just how long will you be able
to keep up that strong act of yours?
My dick is already at it's limit.
It's flowing out again!
A different penis just came inside me!
It's too early for you to be tired.
Now there's another penis inside me!
I just couldn't hold back after seeing you like this.
How about this time I cum on your face?
This dick was inside me just now.
Why is it in my mouth?
Sticking my dick into a
cheeky girl's mouth is just great!
No! Take it out!
That's my ass! That place isn't clean!
I'm going to let it out just like this!
He came on me!
He came all over my face!
No!
They came inside me again!
And not just inside, but on my face, too!
There's so much dirty cum.
It stinks! It's so disgusting!
You... people.
Better remember this.
After I rescue the chairman,
I'm going to make you regret this!
Yeah, this is all just to rescue him, right?
Because of that, there's really
no helping it if you don't like it.
What happened yesterday wasn't a dream.
I'm an angel goddess, but...
Just what should I do to save him?
I can't just call the goddess for hel...
Why did you call me here
so early in the morning?
You even ordered a school vacation.
My company is backing this school, after all.
I can do whatever I want with it.
You only do what's convenient.
It's fine if we just finish up already, isn't it?
You want it that badly?
This is only to save the chairman.
If it's for that, I'll endure your filthy dick.
You still talk to me like that?
Well, whatever. Put these on.
You filthy pervert!
This is even better than I imagined, Suzune-kun!
J-Just get it over with already!
What are you doing?!
I'll be having fun with you like this today.
This is so humiliating.
An angel goddess' tit fuck is just amazing!
Sandwiching such a disgusting
thing between my breasts.
Now, just like that,
try putting it in your mouth.
N-No way! Why would I do that?!
You still don't understand?
Get to it!
Disgusting! This stinky, disgusting
thing is filling my mouth up!
You're kidding! He's going to cum
with his dick inside my mouth?
Drink up all of my thick cum!
He really came in my mouth!
His cum is flowing into my mouth!
This amount! He's still cummmg! I can't breathe!
You won't be able to breathe
if you don't swallow it, you know?
He wants me to swallow it?!
I can't breathe.
It's going to overflow! No!
It tastes like rotten fish.
It's spreading all over my throat!
That costume really is great.
So sudden.
Dressed like this...
and with a human I'm supposed to be saving!
It's wetter and smoother than yesterday!
It's sucking me in even harder!
That's not true at all!
Why does my body feel weird?
Wasn't I tighter yesterday?
You can say whatever you want,
but your body won't lie.
No! Not there! Let go of me!
You can feel good from here too, you know?
I don't care! Stop it! Let go of me!
Why does it feelgood?
I shouldn't be feeling like this from such a place!
Just a little bit more.
It isn't hurting as much as it did yesterday.
I know I'm wetter than I was yesterday!
Your pussy is tightening up!
Don't worry, I'll fill you up in no time!
No! Not again!
I don't want to get pregnant!
It's shooting out inside me!
I'm going to get pregnant!
He came inside me again.
I don't want to carry this man's child!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: haidaraaaaa
editor: biskoi
encoder: punk4real
quality control: fyurie