Begone wicked ones!
Wonderful.
Not only can you defeat lesser demons,
but you can now even fight against ghouls.
No, it's all because of your guidance.
You’re quite capable on your own now.
We'll each embark on different tasks from this point on.
But it's been just a short time since I've learned to transform,
I did it all because you, Holy Rouge, were watching over me.
You will be fine.
I guarantee it.
Besides, I'll be there right away if necessary.
I understand.
One day, as we were coming home from school,
all the men inside the bus suddenly started harassing us.
That was all the doing of the creatures of darkness.
It was the work of demons.
They release a field that turns men sexually wild,
then they absorb the carnal energy that
come forth to replenish their strength.
Banish Spear!
Then by Suzune-sensei, a knight appointed
by the gods to fight the demons,
my ordinary days started to become extraordinary.
Thanks to you, their plans are always thwarted immediately.
But they still continue their attempts to gather carnal energy.
Please leave it to me.
I will protect this city in your absence.
The targeted Angel Goddess Angeltia
Betrayed by the people I've protected
Angel Goddess Yuuri ~ Moaning Sucking Carnal Service
Yuuri-chan and Suzune-sensei are together!
How lucky!
Shizune-sensei’s so hot.
Her sexiness is just...
Even Yuuri-chan,
having that body and still a very diligent honor student.
I just can't get enough of her!
Yes, my mother is a doctor, and l also aspire to become one.
I'm sorry for dragging you into this.
No, you told me that you were also saved by
an Angel Goddess when you were younger.
If I have the same ability to save others,
then by all means, let me assist.
It'll be okay Yuuri.
I know that you can do it.
I will! Please take care as well Suzune-sensei.
This again?
They’re really big as usual.
This is really unfair.
Being an honor student, while being popular and a nice girl,
and especially also having a good figure.
Jeez, Mio don't startle me like that.
Well, you looked kind of gloomy,
so I thought about cheering you up a bit.
I'm not going to be cheered up by that!
How about choosing one already?
I think it's still too early for that.
My, you're such a naive girl.
Though, your innocence doesn't really match your erotic body.
Erotic? Stop saying that.
I bet that Gorilla was looking at your
boobs during the entire P.E. class.
Gorilla? You even refer to teachers like that?
Man, her tits look really good as always.
I'm sure her nipples also look pink and pretty.
Damn, I'm going to try and fap once to the handkerchief
that Maeshima lent me earlier.
Hey, Gorilla's looking!
He's definitely looking at you with dirty eyes!
No way, teachers don't just look at their students that way.
You're just too pure Yuuri.
Someone might be fapping to you right now you know.
Fapping?
Come on, I showed it to you once in a porn video right?
My, you're really cute that way.
This is...
The park from before.
Mio, I have something to do, sorry.
I'm going on ahead.
Is that so?
Guess that can't be helped.
I'm sorry.
Changing Lip!
I'm sure I felt it in this direction.
Though I'm not really used to this yet.
That's...!
What's going on?
Wait, over there...
Demons, who reside in the astral realm
usually cannot make contact with humans
directly who are in the physical realm.
But, it looks like they certainly can.
Implanting my new creature inside
someone from the human realm,
seems to have produced a completely unexpected effect.
I'm not going to let you do this any longer.
Finely Air!
I can't beat it with just that huh.
It... It hurts...
Now, what are you going to do?
My creature now has the ability to kill
humans that you need to protect.
How dirty...
This is bad.
If I evade the attack, it would hit this human behind me.
The damage isn't too serious thanks to my suit,
but if this continues...
Quite tough it seems.
I would probably have to use something
much stronger to breakthrough it.
However, your defense isn't too impressive.
L-Let me go!
If you move even a bit, his arms will be torn off.
No, whafs this?
It's moving towards weird spots.
T-This feels gross.
No way, how can it get through?
This suit doesn't just protect from attacks, it's also
supposed to make the wearer untouchable, but...
Was it due to a human acting as a catalyst?
Never thought that the side effect would be this.
I wonder how much more it can do,
I shall watch and see.
What weird things are you blabbering about with this short skirt?
Couldn't agree more. What a slutty outfit.
So this is what they call an Angel Goddess?
I see, so this slutty outfit is that of an Angel Goddess!
This is bad, these people are about to...
Please escape now! Hurry!
What is this?
I'm going to release all of your carnal desires.
Oh no, these people are now in the same state as the ones before.
P-Please come back to your senses!
Fight it!
Those sure are big breasts.
They're also very soft and bouncy.
P-Please stop!
Her legs also feel very smooth.
Stop this already.
I beg of you...
No, that hurts!
Stop fondling my breasts so hard!
Your carnal desires look very nice,
and I'll be taking it.
Hey, what are you doing?!
Huh? Gondo-sensei?
Go away.
Just find someone else on your own.
Thank you very much.
Sensei's isn't affected or anything.
That's why he saved me.
He really is a teacher after all.
Oh my, what a twist of events.
For a human to hold this much energy within him.
What? Hey...
What are you doing?
I thought you were Maeshima from afar,
But I never thought I'd meet someone even better.
Are you one of those they call an Angel Goddess?
No, please stop!
Why?
Didn't he come to save me?
I thought you were something,
but I never thought you'd be the type
to be at a park for this kind of play.
No!
Stop, please!
Why?
Gondo-sensei is touching me all over.
His energy alone is already equivalent to hundreds of other men.
For someone like him to exist,
I must search more diligently.
That's...
Oh no, that's a dick.
Why did he pull that out?
You're too uptight, I won't even be able to insert mine in there.
Geez.
What should I do?
What will he eventually do?
That's...
Are you okay?
Please cover it with this.
The handkerchief I gave him.
Someone might be fapping to you...
No way, he's using a student's things for this.
Damn, using Maeshima's handkerchief like this sure feels good.
Oh? Why are you looking at it so intently?
Are you interested in my dick?
Hey, you look a bit like Maeshima.
Your friends and family might be dragged into this,
so it's imperative that you protect your true identity.
If Maeshima would just dress like a slut and
show her panties more often like this,
then I could assault her and make her my dick's slave.
No way, I never thought that he was thinking of me like that.
This can't be real.
This just can't be real right?
I can't fuck you, so I'll just spray my semen all over you.
What is this?
This sticky stuff smells gross!
Oh no, at this rate I'll...
There's one last resort that you can use if you
are captured and can no longer fight back,
however, it depletes all of your energy, so you're
at a risk of dispersing your transformation.
Use it only when you really have to okay?
But, anymore and I'll...
Woah, what is this?
My suit is starting to disperse.
I have to get out of here quickly.
What in the world was that?
Huh? She's gone!
Damn, what the hell just happened?
No, no.
I still can't completely scrub the smell away.
He wasn't being controlled or anything.
He did that despite not being affected...
Tomo-kun, the bathroom's ready now.
O-Okay.
I wonder what's wrong?
He seemed to be in a hurry to leave.
You can't look at that Onee-chan!
Tomo-kun, was that an Angel Goddess?
I j-just thought she's kind of cool.
I'm going now.
Cool?
Ah Angel Goddess?
I see, so Tomo-kun sees them that way.
I was thinking of consulting Suzune-sensei,
about the incident with Gondo-sensei yesterday but,
I guess she's on an investigation right now.
But...
You will be fine.
I guarantee it.
Besides, I'll be there right away if necessary.
She said it's okay to contact her during emergencies.
This is Yuuri.
Suzune-sensei, I wanted to consult you about something, so...
I see... I'm quite busy right now...
I'm sorry, umm...
I'm sorry Yuuri, but it'd be better for me if you call later...
I see.
I wanted to consult with you as soon as possible.
Sorry about this, I'm going to call you again later.
What should l do?
Why do this...
Stop this already!
Do you want to be exposed?
Why did this have to happen?
I'm sorry Yuuri but right now I'm...
This is something really unexpected.
Never thought an Angel Goddess' actual identity is...
No, please...
Any harder and I'll...
Oh no, if everyone finds out...
I'm going to have to impregnate you now.
No, not inside.
Oh no, not like this again.
Suzune-sensei never called after that.
Was she really busy?
Sensei...
Is something wrong?
N-No, everything’s fine.
If you'll excuse me.
I can't consult sensei for this.
If something unfortunate happens,
I just have to make sure that it won't happen again the next time.
There's nothing you can do about what's happened already.
So you'll just have to work on preventing it from happening again.
There's nothing you can do about what happened...
He's right.
There's no point in sulking over it.
True, it's a bad experience,
but that very experience will help me prevent
the exact same thing from happening again.
I can feel it here again.
I guess that's because this is the point where most people gather.
If I preemptively wait here...
Wind Fo...!
No, this can't be.
He's now tainted.
It's okay.
I can do this.
I'm going to protect this city while Holy Rouge is away.
Finely Air!
W-Why?
Why is he not purified?
Finely Air!
Angeltia, this must be hard on you.
However, your purification powers won't work on him.
This is special type of taint.
A s-special taint?
No way, for my purification magic to be useless...
Angel Goddess right?
He says that I'm going to become a demon if this continues.
It's your job to save me right?
Hey, Ms. Exhibitionist, save me will you?
Th-That’s...
W-What should I do?
He is tainted with semen.
He tells me that I'm going to be purified
if you can suck out the semen inside me.
T-The stuff that he squirted on me yesterday?
Hey, give me a handjob already.
You're not going to save me?
It's your sworn duty to save people right?
Right?
No way, he's telling me to do exactly what he did yesterday...?
Hurry up and do it!
Oh no, the pain!
Am I really going to become a demon this way?
No way, do I really have to do it?
This can't be.
Why is this happening?
I'm sorry Mom...
You won't be getting any semen out that way!
You do it this way.
There, move it like that.
Oh no, it feels warm and stiff.
And it's twitching.
No, stop!
Don't try to stop me!
I don't know how long this will take so do it properly already.
No, no...
I have to hurry up and make his semen come out to purify him.
What? There's something oozing out...
This is...?
I'm cumming,
and I'm going to squirt it all over your slutty body.
So move it!
No way, he's going to squirt on me again?
That gross stuff...?
Lots of stinky stuff is on me...
But, I've now purified him.
It's still too early to feel relieved.
No way, why?
What? It didn't work?
Am I going to become a demon now?
Why? This can't be...
He's about to become a demon?
Wrong.
His energy is so immense,
that alone won't purify him.
Well, it can't be helped then.
That leaves us with no choice but to use your pussy to purify me.
What have they been doing there?
Eh? An Angel Goddess? But wasn't
she giving him a handjob earlier?
Wait, they're having public sex?
Is that Angel Goddess for real?
I beg of you, stop this please!
I'm going to save you using another way.
What? So you’re not going to save me?
Are you just going to leave me here?
Hmph, so you're proud that you save lives,
but here you are, nothing but just cuteness to show.
No, don't! Stop!
Just shut up and just save me already!
It's going in.
This can't be, sensei's thing is actually inside me.
Why does this... ?
No way...
I-It hurts! It hurts!
Stop!
An Angel Goddess' virgin pussy eh.
Not too smooth,
but it wraps around me very nicely.
No, I don't want this...
They’re really doing it.
Is she getting fucked raw? Wow...
For real? And here I believed in her...
Now I lost faith in her.
She just too slutty.
That's amazing, I want to fuck her too!
It hurts...
Why?
I'm saving people and yet...
Why did this have to happen?
This is terrific.
It's the first time I've tasted a virgin pussy like this.
It's really trying to suck me in.
No, sensei's dick is inside me.
No way...
Why? Why?
Tomo-kun, why?
Oh no, I'm being watched.
No way.
Oh? It suddenly got tighter, starting to get horny now?
Then just throw yourself away and let your instincts go wild.
No...
This is... just...
Why? Why is Tomo-kun...?
I can't let him see me like this!
No, I want this to end quickly.
No, I want it to end now!
Are you starting to get horny now you angel bitch?
You're really something.
I need to make him ejaculate quickly and escape.
I have to stay as the Angei Goddess that Tomo-kun admires.
Amazing, this is just too erotic.
I want to do her too.
What are you saying?
It's the worst just thinking about the
possibility of being saved by her.
I just saved them, so why...?
I... I...
I didn't decide to save people for this.
No, please ejaculate already!
I didn't start saving people for me to
be looked down upon by Tomo-kun.
I...
I wonder what babies from angel bitches would look like.
Get impregnated well okay?
That can't be, no!
That must not happen!
I must not get pregnant with this!
That's just...
Too late to do anything now.
Please, I really can't get pregnant!
Stop this, I beg of you!
I'm getting impregnated while Tomo-kun is watching.
Why?
No...!
I'm saving people, so why?