At this rate, what will happen next?
I believed in his words before.
What should I do for him to...
He knows of my other identity.
It's not over yet?
How many times have we done it already?
Angel Goddess pussies are the best.
Stop this, please.
For me to be treated like this after saving people...
I'm...
It's coming again!
Lots... A lot is being poured inside me again.
Here, clean this up.
This was just inside me a moment ago.
It'll be over soon as long as you do what I tell you.
I-I get it.
This power was given to me so that I could
fulfill my duties as an Angel Goddess,
but this is how it turned out.
I can't purify him even after doing this much.
What should I do now?
Of course he won't get purified.
Huh, what?
Humans are indeed interesting.
That girl named Maya, just who is she?
Sensei, good morning.
No, no, I must stay cheerful.
Not only are you my student,
but you are also my friend's daughter.
I will always be here for you.
He's trying to cheer me up.
His eyes look far different than from those men.
Sensei, I'm already quite grown up.
Well, you're right.
You're already at that age.
Is he feeling nervous?
His hands feel a bit sweaty.
Safe.
That was really close.
Sensei, you've already gone far on your own.
Original Animation
The targeted Angel Goddess Angeltia
Betrayed by the people I've protected
The targeted busty purity - Yuuri "Taken down by the smile she protected"
I want to report this to Suzune sensei but,
I can't seem to contact her.
A transfered student, huh...
No way, even here?
But this is school!
Also...
Not that way, this way.
Maya, so it is you!
Are you really sure about that?
Am also a demon,
but my objectives are quite different from them.
I'm quite interested in this world.
Though, I can't really understand why you won't kill
even after they've done these horrible things to you.
I won't let you do that!
I'm not about to let a demon just go.
The serious type, huh?
Now you've captivated me, Angeltia.
Or should I say, Maishima Yuuri-chan.
H-How?
I know a lot of things.
I know all about Tomo-kun, your Mom,
and even your friend Mio-san.
W-What are you trying to do?
I want you to do something for me.
You'll have to follow me if you hold your loved ones dear.
That can't be. Why are you doing this?
Sorry, but you really have no choice.
T-That's Tomo-kun's...!
Want me to bring out the hand that held this next?
Stop.
Do you understand now?
Though, it'd be bothersome with you all soiled like that,
so go home and clean yourself.
I don't think I can transform here.
Changing Lip!
This is... wait...!
Maya, you...!
Now, it's time to have fun.
I wonder how much built up sexual desire will grow.
M-Maya?
What? What just happened?
They say that it was simply made of materials from this world.
No way, Sensei?
See? Just like I told you, Sensei.
It seems so, but...
You can't really hesitate at this point.
I get it.
If I can help her with my own energies.
Energy?
You're the only one I can count on, Sensei.
I can't save her on my own.
Give her strength!
What? Maya is...
What are you saying to Sensei?
Why is Sensei...? Wait!
Just wait!
Stay still.
If you don't get on it now,
it'll end up just like your run in the park.
Maybe even worse with that outfit.
In the park?
Does Noriyama-sensei know about what
happened with me and Gondo-sensei?
Besides, you're the one who's doing all this.
I see. Then, there should be something
my aged penis can do for you.
S-Stop, wait!
Maya's lies are getting to him!
Oh no, it's dripping.
Maya, are you afraid?
I really think this isn't...
She's just about to run out of energy.
It'll be alright if you transfer some
energy to her with your dick now.
Okay?
I don't want to cum.
And this is Sensei's!
But...
S-She's right.
Good girl.
I see, it's all for you. Okay then.
I may not be of much help,
but if it's for you then I'll do it.
Sensei is seriously worried, even though this is all her set up.
The dick of my father's close friend.
It looks like it's twitching.
I'm sorry if it's sweaty and dirty.
I'm already too old,
so it might look all worn out.
It really reeks of sweat,
of his smell.
Oh no, I'm starting to really think of it as disgusting.
You can't cum just yet, Sensei.
The energy transferred is stronger the harder I do this, right?
Sensei is supposed to be doing this for me,
yet I feel scared.
Oh? What's wrong?
It won't cum if you don't take it in.
T-That's...
Maruyama-ensei, why do you have that expression?
I have to... take it in.
I-I can't breathe, his dick is really thick!
Even bigger than Gondo-sensei's!
How many years has it been since it's been sucked like this?
Ever since she died...
I-Is this something to be emotional about?
It's been built up for a long time due to him being alone,
and it's especially more effective because it's you doing it.
Don't say weird things like that!
And he doesn't really know I'm actually Yuuri!
You can suck on it with more force.
I have to suck harder? But I've just started to properly take it in.
I don't mind if you get a bit rougher.
Even if you say that...
So you're still not used to this, huh?
Oh yeah, why don't I guide you properly?
I can't breathe!
Sensei, it's starting to really hurt!
Why does he keep on doing this terrible thing?
You take the entire thing in, until the tip reaches your throat.
No, it's too painful.
He's ramming it in to my throat too roughly.
Just a little more.
Keep it up.
Keep it up... and it will cum?
Sensei...
How much is he going to cum?
It feels all sticky and gross.
You can't waste a drop,
you have to take all my energy in!
Sensei still thinks that he's doing this for my sake!
I really can't breathe now.
But, I have to drink it all...
Yes, that's right.
Sensei just did such a terrible thing.
He's aroused.
He's done all this with an ecstatic expression on his face.
Oh my, she looks quite worn out.
Maybe it wasn't enough?
I-I'm okay, I'm already fine.
You can't lower your guard just yet.
What is this?
Why?
I was mistaken.
We need an amount that can make her spring into action!
So mine wasn't enough?
No way...
That's not true.
It might not have been enough with just her mouth.
You have to pour it in more directly.
No, Maya is starting to suggest weird things again to Sensei.
This is...
S-Sensei, I'm going to try and cover the exit for you.
So please, give her more strength!
What should I do?
Directly.
You have to pour it in directly.
No way, after letting me suck it, she can't be...
I see, so there's no other way.
No, if he does it to me, I'll no longer be able
to remember him for who he was before!
Let me go.
I can see Sensei's expression maliciously warping.
I'll give you all of my energy!
No! Stop it!
Sensei, this is school!
You can't do this!
But we don't have a second to waste!
So I'm going to save you right now!
Oh, but you're probably just craving for it, right, Sensei?
That's not true...
I myself can give the energy that will satisfy you!
Sensei, don't, don't!
Senseis entering me...
No, this can't be...
Does it hurt?
I'm going to be as gentle as I can.
His words are still sweet, it's unfair.
Sensei don't, any further and...
I beg of you!
I'm sure you'll be satisfied when it starts to get used to mine.
What is he saying?
Sensei just pushed it all the way in.
Sensei's thing is...
I'll be moving gently.
It's thick!
It's shorter than Gondo-sensei's, but...
He's already inside me.
You can be saved this way, right?
I never thought it'd be this joyful.
No, there isn't a single fragment of joy in this!
Sensei is really doing it to me...
It's starting to get wetter.
So it feels better now, right?
Why?
It hurts, and I hate it,
yet my body is starting to get aroused.
I'm going to pour my energy in to you.
No, don't, Sensei,
please don't!
Sorry if I'm a bit quick.
But, I can do it many times if needed.
No...
Sensei is starting to go crazy.
This person, who was very kind to me before.
He's getting more aroused, and is being
more forceful with each passing second.
No, stop this, please!
Sensei's going to cum!
I don't want this, no...
No...!
It's pouring inside.
His thing is pumping cum inside me.
I'm really going to get pregnant with this!
What? It's still not enough?
Okay, I'll try once more!
S-Stop!
No, any more and I'll...!
Oh! Seems I really was able to help.
I was able to help Yuuri-kun.
N-No, this is all Maya's set up.
Sensei was just...
Yuuri-kun.
No!
I'm sorry, but this was the only way to save you, Yuuri-kun.
Was he really planning to save me?
But, I...
P-Please don't come any closer.
Yuuri-kun, you see... I really...
I'm sorry, but please leave me alone.
What did I just do?
Her expression was just...
Even if it was all to save her, that was simply...
If you say that, then she might just
go to Gondo-sensei for help again.
T-That can't be!
But he's in the campus, right?
If she happens to find him...
M-Mio? Gondo-sensei?
Don't worry.
He's not conscious at the moment.
Maya!
Now then, for your next activity.
You need to make him cum.
One for Mio, Tomo-kun, andyour Mom.
Do it, and I'll spare all of their lives.
That's just...
If you don't hurry up and make him cum,
they'll soon suffocate slowly until they die.
T-This is unfair!
What is it that you really want?
Making me do all these terrible things...
I told you, I just want to have fun.
You're really getting used to this already, anyway.
For this round, I'll spare Mio-chan.
This is weird.
He'd already cum around this time before.
You need something more stimulating.
How about using your own body?
Mio seems to be alright for now.
But Mom and Tomo-kun right now are...
I'll...!
Sensei, I think she's calmed down a bit now.
It'd be bad for her to be left alone too long.
You're right.
I was thinking about it too much.
I'm a failure as a teacher.
Hurry up.
Why?
Cum already.
If you don't, I'll...
What should I do to make him cum?
Please cum.
If you don't cum quickly...
Hurry...
Oh wow, I never thought you'd bend this far.
Talk about being mentally unstable.
This cannot be...
It's all because mine was insufficient,
that she had to do it with Gondo this time.
Oh my, your precious student is already shaming herself in there.
Are you just going to watch?
I never knew carnal desires could grow this big and this fast.
I'm going to let it out all the way.
It feels gross, but I have to make him cum, or else Tomo-kun will...
Hurry up and cum, if you don't I'll...
I've already come this far, why is he not cumming yet?
I have to make him cum quickly.
Why?
S-Sensei?!
Don't look, please don't!
Looks like you really weren't satisfied earlier.
Sensei, please wait.
Please, not right now.
I... I have to make him cum.
This is bad, I need to make him cum now!
So you were the one who made the first
move when you did it in the park.
Made the first move?
I was forced back there, even now I'm...!
What should I do?
I have to make him cum, or else Tomo-kun will...
Sensei, this isn't what it is!
This isn't!
But I'm sorry!
I'm already speaking to you and yet...
So you really crave for semen that much.
Sensei, wait, what are you doing?
Please wait just a second!
That's my butt!
I said I'll cum for you as many times as needed, didn't I?!
No, I...!
No, not there, Sensei!
It's in there, his dick is in my ass!
That's not where you put it in!
Why?
The two dicks are pushing against each
other between my pussy and ass!
No, not there, Sensei!
Sensei, stop, please don't!
My ass feels weird.
Oh no, something's coming out!
Please stop!
Why? We 're in school, and yet, my teachers are...!
Why?
If you really want to squeeze some cum out,
why won't you take mine?
That's not it!
That 's not it, Sensei.
My insides, my ass feels weird.
I'll make sure you're only satisfied with me.
This is all for your sake!
No, this is not for my sake at all.
I don't want this anymore...
Do your best until the end, okay?
Maya, it's all your fault that he...
Sensei, don't!
Please don't cum in there!
Oh no, Gondo-sensei's dick is penetrating my womb!
Don't, Sensei, please pull it out!
If he cums now, my womb will be filled with cum.
I won't pull out, not unless you admit that you want my cum!
Sensei, no!
That isn't it, Sensei, Gondo-sensei's dick is...
Why?
No, no, no!
He won't stop until I admit that his is better.
Mine is better, right?
You'll only want my energy, right?
Yes, I want yours and yours only.
I'm even forced to say these things.
I think I'm going crazy!
Okay, I'll pour it inside then.
Why? You can't...
No, this...
It's going to be poured inside my ass.
Something's about to be pumped inside my ass!
Oh no, the two dicks are rubbing against each other.
I'm going to break.
I'm going to break if this continues!
Both of them came.
My ass and my womb are both filled with cum.
But, with this, I was able to save Tomo-kun.
Seems I have finally satisfied you.
Amazing!
Maruyama-sensei's carnal desires were on fire!
It's really different when it's built up through the years.
I wonder what I'm doing.
Dragging everyone into this...
Even if she erased their memories,
Mio still...
Other demons have now disappeared since she came here.
If, because of my sacrifice, she doesn't harm the world...
But Sensei is still...
For me to feel repulsed even as I remember him like this...
If I resist, Tomo-kun and the others will...
Then I'll just have to let myself take the punishment.
But...!
Onee-chan?
Tomo-kun, what's wrong?
Even though Mom's on night shifts, she's also worried.
You've seemed really depressed lately.
Sorry to worry you, I'm fine.
I'm going to try and become someone that can protect you.
I want to be strong like an Angel Goddess.
Tomo-kun, thank you.
So Maya also erased his memories from that night...
Yup! Because I'm a man after all.
I have to protect his smile,
so I have to do my best.
I'll be counting on you.
I feel like his smell from that time has seeped into me.
But, I need to endure this...
For Tomo-kun's sake.
I'm coming.
Tomo-kun, who's there?
Is it a visitor?
Yuuri-kun, I came to replenish your energy.
W-Why are you here, Sensei?
Where's Tomo-kun?
Why?
Tomo-kun sure is growing up to be a good boy.
He's with Maya right now.
No way, Maya is with him?
Kimie is working the night shift, right?
I think we can get on with this at our own pace.
He's saying this with that usual warm smile of his.
It feels really creepy.
I'm really glad that I'm finally able to help you this way, Yuuri-chan.
He's still saying that it's for my sake,
but his mind is already warped.
Tomo-kun, you sure look cute.
I'm not a kid anymore. I'm a man!
Oh, so you're a man.
But do you have experience?
Experience?
What? If you don't even know about that, then you're still a kid.
W-What experience?
Want to know?
I'm a guy, so I want to know all about it.
Okay then.
Maya Onee-chan, will tell you every-single-thing.
My pussy is filled with Sensei's dick.
Yuuri-chan, it's okay, right?
O-Okay...
He's no longer the Sensei I know.
He's now just focused on pouring cum inside me.
No need to hold back, you know.
Holding back? But I'm...!
Tomo-kun will hear, if I moan loudly.
I can't let that happen.
It's going deep inside my womb again.
No, you can't, Sensei.
If I get cummed inside again, I'll get pregnant.
I see, then I have to give my proper greetings
to Kimie-san one of these days.
S-Sensei, what are you saying?
You mustn't...!
Sensei is saying weird things again.
Why is he...?
I'll take responsibility for you.
I'll even think up a good name for the baby.
N-No way...
Stop this, Sensei.
We're going to do this till dawn.
Here goes my first shot.
Stop, Sensei. Please, I beg of you!
You can't, don't...!
Feels good, right?
Boys need to experience at least this much.
This is weird. I'm feeling weird, Onee-chan.
Let Onee-chari;take care of everything, okay?
Sensei, don't...
He already came five times,
yet his dick is still stiff.
At this rate, he'll really keep on doing this until morning.
You're feeling a little dizzy in this heat already, right?
Why don't we continue this in your room now?
N-No, don't!
I can't let him violate me in my own room!
I really can't let him!
This is for Tomo-kun as well.
You're right, the night is still young, anyway.
W-Wait, I need to go to the toilet.
Sensei, umm...
The toilet is right here.
I-I can't do that!
What are you saying, Sensei?
It's okay, we'll just let the water wash it away.
N-No way...
Tomo-kun, there, that's the spot.
Onee-chan, this is amazing!
I'm... I'm..!
It feels good for me too.
Your dick is simply amazing!
Onee-chan, so this is "experience."
I'm now an adult!
You're now an adult.
You have to show Yuuri-chan what you've learned.
Yeah, I have to show this to Onee-chan.
I'm being carried by you, Tomo-kun.
Amazing...
Take me to the bathroom.
S-Sensei, no...
Don't look...
Yuuri-chan, your pee looks beautiful.
Oh, I'm already good to go again.
Sensei...
H-He inserted it in again.
He's about to pour cum inside me again!
Sensei, wait, the door...
Please stop!
Sensei, please!
No, I absolutely can't let Tomo-kun see me like this!
Onee-chan, I'm an adult now!
W-What? His voice seems weird.
And what is he saying about being an adult?
Tomo-kun is...!
No way, no way!
Tomo-kun is having sex with Maya!
Tomo-kun, your dick is amazing.
My pussy is being penetrated all the way.
Your dick is really amazing!
I'm going crazy with it!
Tomo-kun, no way... no way...
His smile, is starting to look distorted.
Onee-chan, Maya Onee-chan is amazing!
It's my first time feeling like this!
Your dick is amazing!
It's also my first time feeling like this!
I think I won't be able to live without it!
Tomo-kun, give me more of your dick!
Okay, I'm going to do my best.
Because I'm a man.
Sensei, your thing is hitting me deep inside.
Amazing, this is simply amazing!
It just feels too good!
No, this isn't right!
What... am I doing?
Your dick is going deep inside.
My womb is being pushed hard.
I'm being violated like this, yet... why?
His dick is starting to make me crazy.
I'm...
I'm going to break...
I wasn't able to do anything.
I...
I don't want to cum like this, yet...
I wasn't able to anything with my
bestowed Angel Goddess powers.
Tomo-kun...
More, make me more crazy with it!
Completely fill my pussy with your cum!
His dick is stirring me up inside.
Tomo-kun's smile has also disappeared.
This, this is making my pussy lose it.
I'm sorry, tomo-kun.
I wasn't able to protect you.
No, I don't want any more of this dick...!