Stop messing around!
I don't have time to deal with such things.
I just came to give a proper greeting.
He's usually like that.
I just came from a Goddess Assembly,
and now I'm back here again surrounded by lowlifes.
If marvelous people like the Principal and Yuuri weren't here,
I wouldn't have even thought of saving the people here.
I wonder how many times I've already gotten
in trouble attempting to do just that.
Maybe I should try to learn a thing
or two from the principal as well.
This is...!
Changing Lip!
Get away from President Zendoui
and go back whence you came!
I've corrupted his mind now.
You'll just kill him if you try to purify him now.
Then tell me how to save him.
Of course I won't.
You're my enemy.
Then forget it.
Begone.
What's happening here?
Whoa, a big-boobie!
No way, could you have been collaborating with these demons?
If you know a cure, then this is the time to speak.
Of maybe you just want to...
Wait, just wait!
The targeted Angel Goddess Angeltia
Betrayed by the people I've protected
The Cool Teacher Suzune The Alluring Cosplay Goddess
You mean if you call your boss, you can create a cure?
That's right.
But, in order to make it, I'll require carnal energy, Suzune-kun.
I can't call forth anything from the demon realm.
This man, who's been collaborating with the demons, could...
Then gather the stuff up and call him forth.
Which is why you're vital for me to do that.
I need to rape you.
You beast!
You want to save the President, right?
You have quite the firm ass.
J-Just get on with it already.
You need this to collect carnal energy, right?
It won't do with just this.
What are you planning to do?
For me to be abused by this beast like
this just to save the President...
And that beast is about to rape you now.
Oh, so you've begun already.
I won't let you get too much of a headstart.
Wh-What?
I can gather more carnal energy efficiently if you're gang raped.
These are people...
This beast is about to...
No, this is gross.
And it stinks, what the world is this?
My breasts are being fondled.
I can't believe I have to endure all of this.
They're just the same as demons for stooping to this level.
This can't be.
No...!
H-He's putting his face on it.
This feels really gross.
His sticky tongue is trying to twirl itself inside,
and his saliva is starting to fill my mouth.
You can't do it half-assed like this.
You have to respond properly too, or else
I won't be able to gather carnal energy.
It stinks, I can't breathe.
My breasts are also being fondled, and all of
their faces are pressing onto weird parts.
Your nipples have started getting hard as well.
Why don't I take real good care of them, just like this.
Getting kissed, having my breasts fondled, and the sensation
of these beasts pressing their faces down there...
Oh no, what was that?
What in the world is this?
Your clit is starting to have a hard on.
Are you feeling horny now, Suzune-kun?
My... clitoris?
You don't know anything about your clit?
That's an Angel Goddess for you, I guess.
What is this? It felt like a surge of electricity
just jolted through my body.
Your love juices are starting to overflow.
No, my clit is still being caressed gently,
and flicked by his tongue.
My body's starting to feel weird because of it!
I-I have to endure this.
In order to save the President.
I can't endure it anymore.
What is this?
It's too big!
I-It's not possible.
That just won't fit!
I'll give you a headstart and let you choose
the position you'd like to be fucked.
Like I care about that!
Doesn't matter how, but just finish this already!
Stop! Why are we doing it in this position?
Just do it normally.
You said it doesn't matter how, right?
I prefer this kind of position, you see.
I get to have sex with a Angel Goddess after all.
I have to put on a good show for everyone else.
No, no!
I don't want to do it in this position!
If you don't keep quiet, it might enter a different hole.
As I thought, you're a virgin.
No...
It won't fit.
Everyone's now watching how you're being turned
into a woman by a partner you don't want.
It's going in.
It's inside me.
Just a little more.
S-Stop...
Please stop...
It's all the way in.
That big... thick thing...
It's ripping me apart.
The Angel Goddess, Suzune-kun's virginity, is now mine!
It hurts.
He's going to cum inside.
Every last drop inside me.
It already hurts as it eases its way in and out.
My insides feel like they're getting torn apart!
His dick is scraping my insides as he moves.
So, how is it, Suzune-kun?
Feels amazing with us your as first partner, right?
Just end this quickly already.
It's pushing too hard.
It hurts.
You wanted it hard, right?
I'm being toyed with by people who are even
more despicable and weaker than demons.
Looks like you're getting used to it already.
It's trying to suck me in.
No, his dick is starting to become wet with secretions.
And it's making all these sloppy sounds.
I can't get enough of this.
Let me cum first inside her.
Stop messing around!
I'm going to get pregnant with that!
Oh, impregnating a defiant Angel Goddess!
This is just the best, Suzune!
Come on, cry out louder!
Shut up!
You trash!
This stinking dick is...!
Trash, you say?
Then I'm going to give you a taste of this stinking dick!
This is too intense!
No, please stop!
You...!
No, stop... please stop!
It's pumping inside.
This trash's cum is pumping inside me.
I'm going to pump it deep inside till it gets full.
No, I'm getting impregnated!
I'm going to get pregnant.
I don't want to bear this man's child!
I'm filled with this guy's cum.
I never thought I'd be able to fuck you like this.
It hurts!
Now somebody else's dick is inside me.
Cum is dripping from your hole.
For me to be able to see Suzune-kun in such a lewd state.
It's pouring out, and it's being stirred inside as he fucks me.
Such a passionate gaze, is my dick already
burned that much in your memory?
No, of course not!
Just end it already.
I have to endure this for the President's sake.
I wonder just how long you can resist.
Do you feel full with my dick already?
It's pumping inside me again.
Another man's cum is pumping inside me.
It's still too early to rest just yet.
Another man's dick is about to fuck me again.
I just can't help myself as I look at you.
I'm going to squirt it all over your face this time.
Th-This just fucked me inside earlier.
No way, it's in my mouth now?!
Why am I...?
It feels fantastic having this same cheeky mouth suck on me.
I've had enough.
That's my ass!
That part is dirty!
You're going to have to take all of it soon.
He just came on my face.
And it's all over my face!
He came inside me again.
It's inside me, and it's on my face, too.
There's so much dirty cum.
It stinks, and it feels gross.
You all...
Remember this,
I'm going to make you all regret
this once I rescue the President.
But you've done all of this to save him, though.
Though it couldn't be helped that you tried to resist.
What happened yesterday was no dream.
I'm an Angel Goddess, and yet! don't know
what to do to save the President.
I can't just consult the Goddess about this...
Calling me out this early...
You even ordered me not to go to school today.
That school is at our financial grasp.
I can do whatever I want.
Just doing as you please...
Can we just finish this quickly?
Oh, craving for it already?
This is all to save the President.
I can endure a beast's dick if that's what I need to do.
You still have the nerve to talk like that?
Ah well, just put these on.
You perverted monster!
Oh, this is even better than I imagined!
I really love this, Suzune-kun.
Just get on with it already.
Hey...!
I'll enjoy myself with this today.
Why did it turn it out like this?
This is just too humiliating.
An Angel Goddess' tit fuck, such pleasure!
For me to put something this terrible between my breasts...
Try to suck it.
Wh-Why do I have to do that?
I don't want to!
Do you still not understand?
Do it already!
No, my mouth is being filled with this stinking thing.
This mustn't be!
This can't be happening.
He's going to cum while I'm doing this?
Drink every drop of my thick cum!
He's cumming.
His cum is filling my mouth.
How much can he pump out?
It's still flowing!
I can't... breathe...
It'll continue to be difficult for you if you don't drink it.
Drink? Is he serious?
But, this is indeed becoming really difficult.
I might just drown from it!
No...
It's thick, stinky, and absolutely gross.
It's clinging to my throat.
I really love that wardrobe of yours.
It's suddenly...!
Doing something like this, while wearing such an outfit,
with the people whom I'm supposed to save...
It's already wet, and it slid all the way in very smoothly.
It's sucking and gripping me even harder than yesterday.
I don't... care about that!
My body feels weird.
Why?
It just felt so tight before.
Your body can't lie no matter what you do.
No, that's not true.
Please, let me go.
You can also feel pleasure from this spot, you know.
I don't want any of that!
Stop!
Let me go!
My ass? I definitely won't feel pleasure from there!
Looks like your tough act is just about to end.
It's not as painful as yesterday?
I can feel it, it's filling my insides even more than before.
Your pussy is gripping me tightly.
Don't worry, I'm going to pump it all out shortly.
Stop! Don't cum inside me anymore!
I don't want to get pregnant!
It's pumping inside me..
His cum is flowing inside me, I'm being impregnated!
He came inside again.
I don't want to get pregnant with this man's child.