Netorare Fighter
Yaricchingu!
W
Netorare Fighter
Amazing, It's all the way in!
Then, I'll start moving it.
How is it Ai? The feel of my penis?
My pussy and ass hole is all filled with those big thing!
Inside of me is feels like rubbing off.
This is the first time for me!
That's of course, you've always doing it only with Randy isn't?
I've hold it untill now,
but I 've always want to squeeze this big breats of yours!
There!
Ai's drenched pussy is sucking on my penis...
It feels like I'm being eaten by you!
Then, let's us put inside the other hole of yours.
How is it, the feels of your breasts?
I'll put in her mouth! There..there..!
Inside of Ai's totally great!
How is the feels being fucked in all of the hole of your body?
The milk which come out from your breasts feels sticky.
Your ass hole feels tightly!
Randy, you can't do it so suddenly...
Shit..shit..shit..Ai!!
Alright, I'll let it out in your breats!
There, I'll spread it in your face!
Be sure to drink all of them!
Ai. I'm gonna let it out!
I'm gonna let it out in your pussy!
I can't hold it anymore!
I'm gonna cumming inside again!
My pussy is full of it, all of you doing it with all of my hole...
Ai..Ai..Ai...
Randy, It's amazing!
I won't be defeat by her!
It's rubbing untill the deep of me.
Shit..shit...
My milk is spreading out..feels good!
I can't stop it!
Cumming..I'm gonna cumming...
Let it out...
Just let it out the way like this!!
Too intense, I'm gonna break out!
Even though I'm being fucked this hard,
all the parts of my body is feels so excited!
It's strange..that it feels so good!!
It's not only my ass hole..but my breasts feels round and round...
It'll be cumming..with all of your cum!
Here!
Ai...
It's out!
It's..coming out!!!
He..he..he..It's totally spectacular!
With your cooperation, now I've got new data
for my next experiment.
But, don't you think it's over.
This drug is purposed for all of the world,
but I can't get the right data with this level.
If I use this drug in the extraordinary body like all of you have,
then I'll get the good information from your body
as a gamble figther.
Though you might not realise that
I've install a scan chips in your neck,
but you can't remove it right now.
Since when...?
Through various experiment,
those chips would send me the information
all of your reaction with the drugs.
If you remove it by yourself,
it will self destruct.
Then...
Stand up, this is not the end.
Look!
Look at this gamble fighter dome.
I'll make Shirusaki's special appearance in here.
Before it's the welcome party,
but right now is the real showtime.
What is it?! Release me!
Shit..you Gil!
What are you gonna do with chaining us in this chair?
Don't feel that rage.
I've reserve those special seat for all of you to watch.
Then, let's start Shirusaki's special show!
I still feel the effect of the drug inside of me,
but it's for Randy and everyone.
Ready..go!
I can see Ai's big breasts!
Do it!
Make her strip all of them!
What is it Shirusaki Ai? Di you feel weaken by showing your breasts?
I still..can go on!
What a weak kick.
Did your hips still that weak?
There..there!
Let the spectator see it too.
No~!!!
There you go, I'll spread your pussy & ass hole to them.
Don't spread it all!
I can see Shirusaki Ai's pussy clearly!
Stop it!
Your pussy is still drenched a lot after being fucked up,
let me taste of it.
You can't lick over my pussy...
That's right, I could see that you ass hole is want it too.
I can see that you had experience in this hole too...
I can feel that you're licking inside of my ass hole...
No...!!!
You're flowing out just being lick over your ass hole,
what a great view for the spectator.
That's...
Inside of my ass hole is rubbing off...
I'm gonna be crazy!!
If this continue then I'm gonna be cumming...
Everyone's looking at it...
Though it's embarrassing, but my butt feels good!
No..no...!!
I don't want you stir inside of my ass hole!
Butt..my butt feels hot!
Ai's already cumming, Sally.
If you want to cumming too, then work harder that that.
Did you come?
If this continue then you're gonna cumming with your ass
in front of that all spectator, right?
That's..not in the front of this a lot of people...
If you stir in the deep of there, I'm gonna...
Cumming!!!
The fight is over!
Shirusaki's fighter is completely knock-down!
What a sparkling knock-down you have, Ai.
Then, let's us continue with the next stage of this.
It's a punishment game, right?
From here would be the real showtime.
But still, I never saw the pervert and masochist girl like this.
That's why, It's the perfect time to use all of our thing isn't?
The fight is mine,
but I don't want you money bet in this fighting gamble,
What I want is to see your defeatism in your woman's face.
When you're face is wanting something to sucked in,
that's the time you want to release something from your body!
I'll let your juice keep flowing out from your pussy!
There's so much bitter juice come out
from my penis by touching your body.
Sucked it, so it won't wasted.
Your hard nipples is hitting on my penis.
The juice keep flowing out from my pussy,
I feels gonna meltdown.
Then, If my breast keep being squeezing like that...
Your nipples is standing this hard enough,
just said if you feels that good!
If you're not said it then I'm gonna fucked in your lovely pussy.
That wouldn't be enough with only rubbing on your body like this.
Here, here..here..here...
There's one in here too.
The tip of their penis is rubbing on my mouth,
It's like kissing with me...
Of course you can't hold it, right?
Just said, If you want to drink our semen.
I can't hold it..It's too much good..I want their penis...
That's good, drink all of it.
Drink it properly.
With the smell of theirs, I'm gonna..cumming...
There, I'll release it!
Release in this lewdness woman!
As I thought this woman is totally lewd and masochist.
She drink all of it with so happily.
Looks like she want something more than that.
What a lewdness looks of her,
Inside of this stadium is flowing the smell of her pervert's juice.
Lucky for you, Shirusaki.
All the spectator in this dome is totally feels gonna fucked at yours.
Then let's give her some service and make her more dirty.
No, It's embarrassing!
Don't lie, you bitch!
You want your excited pussy to be fucked the next one, isn't?
The juice is drenched a lot from your pussy.
Said it you want to sucked it by yourself.
If you want so badly, I'll give it to you.
It's inside!
Amazing!
I feels that too!
Ai!!
Don't yell that loud.
This seat is peacial reserved for you to watch it.
The show is still continue after this.
Then the next one, I'll take the data from all of you.
My penis is getting excited...
It's hot..the juice is flowing from the tip of it...
Just release the special ability of yours,
let me see the ejaculation power for my data,
Don't hold it back.
I can't..I can't let myself ejaculate by watching
Ai's getting fucked like this...
But..If I saw Ai's face like that...
My..my penis would...
There, just release all of it.
Release it off untill the end of your limit.
What a view!
From Ai's fighter pussy, there's so much juice drenched out!
Shit..gonna out..gonna coming out...
The big breasts shaking a lot!
Me too..coming out!
Coming out!!
This sticky and hot feeling...
What a drenched a lot of yours.
No, that's not...
I just can't stand like this.
Hey, open the front one of hers.
Heh, you can't hold your penis anymore?
Then I'll give the front one to you.
Oh..your ass hole is getting excited to get it fucked.
From behind too?
Just from the tip of my penis, you've already drenched that a lot.
Here I come..there!
I'm coming too!
No~!!!
Inside of me is rubbing off...
Her drenched pussy is easily sucked at my thing.
I'll let you drink my saliva.
Open your mouth!
No~!!!
What a good breasts!!
Her pussy hole is totally amazing.
This big breats and her ass hole can't hold out anymore.
Then I'll let Ai's pussy filled up with my semen,
I'm gonna let it out.
You can't do it inside...
We'll release it inside of front and behind of yours.
You can't be...
The milk is flowing out from my breasts again...
It feels like inside of me being fucked that hard...
I'm cumming!!!
Being fucked in those hole of me is melting down me.
Hey..hey..the semen is flowing out from both of your holes.
With this, I can easily stir it up both of those holes.
It's good to be inside of your drenched butt!
There..there..just release that off..with this one shot.
Your mouth is wide open, there!
Her body is keep scrubbing on my penis,
this lewd woman still can't get satisfied with before.
My penis is getting excited being fucked with this pervert's mouth.
Many times I'm being fucked with those hot penis,
I just can't think of anything else...
Release it..I'm gonna release it!
Me too...
For all of excited spectator in here,
after this we're gonna enter the second program.
We'll give you a chance to fucked with our Shirusaki Ai.
Please enlist yourself after this.