www.SubDESU-H.net
Mamayu... Mamayu, you’re amazing.
Oh no, don’t stare at it.
It’s so naughty.
Mamayu, can I suck it?
No... you can’t.
Don’t, Hiroaki-san. Don’t!
My producer will get mad at me!
An idol isn’t allowed to do such naughty things.
Then you’re a bad girl, Mamayu.
Even though you’re an idol, you’re dripping so much naughty juice.
Well, it’s your fault, Hiroaki-san.
It’s because you take out your sexy cock in front of me.
Mamayu will get in trouble for this.
I’m sorry, Mamayu.
You know, I won’t tell your producer.
I want to see you be even naughtier.
Geez, Hiroaki-san, you bad boy.
You’re coming inside me!
This is...
Mamayu... Ma...
Mamayu... this feels great.
Me too... your cock makes me feel so good.
I’m losing my strength.
Mamayu is being fucked by Hiroaki-san.
You’re rubbing around inside me.
Mamayu, I’m so turned on too.
I love you, Mamayu!
Hiro—Mamayu... is cumming now.
Oh, wow!
Mamayu, I’m cumming...
Mamayu, you’re the best!
Mamayu! Mamayu!
Today’s sex was the best.
Has my technique improved?
Eh, Mamayu?
Mamayu?
Who the hell is “Mamayu” you idiot?!
I’m your wife, Reiko!
You asshole!
I know I look like that teen idol Mamayu,
but after six months of marriage all our sex play is still about Mamayu—what the fuck is that all about?!
I’m not Mamayu!
Fine, I understand.
I’ll throw out all your Mamayu merchandise.
I’m sorry! Anything but that!
I absolutely refuse.
I mean, who wants a husband who lusts after a teen idol? That’s sick.
Don’t say that!
That reminds me, Taniguchi from college...
He said he was going to come over today for a little housewarming celebration.
Eh?! What are you saying all of a sudden?
Hey, Hiro, are you there?
W
Netorare Zuma
Reiko
Wow, you really do look like her.
Hiro often brags about it when we go out drinking.
He says, “I have Mamayu as my wife."
Hiro, how can you say something so embarrassing?
I’m sorry!
Now, now, when you think about it, it’s your fault, Wifey.
Because you’re just too cute.
Oh no...
And if you take a good look... it’s clear you’re much more glamorous than Mamayu.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Pardon my bluntness, but you turn me on much more than that idol.
T-Taniguchi-san... oh, stop.
Hey, man, don’t go seducing other people’s wives.
Don’t be jealous.
But Hiro sure is lucky.
He really was obsessed with Mamayu.
A man in his thirties, obsessed with a teen idol.
To a hopeless guy like that, suddenly, a great woman like you appeared.
This has to be a miracle.
A miracle.
That Hiro, I can’t even imagine how happy he is right now.
Yes, but I...
He won’t have sex with you unless you pretend to be Mamayu?!
Taniguchi-san, be quiet! Hiroaki-san will hear you.
Well, if that’s the case, there’s a simple way of resolving this.
What is it?
It is... to continue with your Mamayu-play with Hiroaki.
And for even hotter, fun sex...
Taniguchi-san?
How about playing with me?
I can’t...
Tanigu...
Wai—Taniguchi-san!
As I thought...
You sure have a sexy body, Wifey.
Stop it... we can’t do this.
Stop it! Stop it, Taniguchi-san!
Oh? Wifey, are you from the Kansai region?
That turns me on even more.
Then, how’s this?
You can’t! This isn't good...
Wh-What are you doing?
You act like you don’t like it, but then what’s this stuff all about?
Wifey, you’re so wet.
No... I don’t wanna do this.
Then I’ll do something that feels even better.
Wh-What?
Taniguchi-san, we can’t do anym—
We can’t!
But we can. Doesn’t it feel good?
Yes, but... Hiro is... Hiro is...
Please, stop it.
Do you understand what you’re doing?
If we do this and Hiro...
You have a sexy pussy, Wifey.
You’re much sluttier than Mamayu, aren’t you?
Don’t say it!
You can’t... if you suck me that hard, I’ll moan.
Please, mercy. Have mercy, Taniguchi-san.
Oh, shit, your pussy is slippery-wet.
What should I do? Hiro will see...
Don’t worry.
He won’t wake up.
Hiro has always been like that, since college.
But...
See? Your nipples are so firm.
You can’t hold back anymore, can you?
Besides, your pussy....
It belongs to me.
You can’t!
This is really bad.
Oh god, this is wrong, but it feels good.
Doesn’t it?
Your pussy likes me best.
Oh no... this is wrong...
What are you doing?
My dick is better than Hiro’s, right?
No... I can’t say...
Taniguchi’s dick... is longer and harder...
It really is amazing.
It’s going in much deeper than Hiro’s ever does.
Taniguchi-san, you’re getting me off!
That Hiro, why does he obsess over Mamayu? Why idols?
Reiko’s body is much sexier and worthy of obsession.
Hey, Reiko?
You’re gonna be my fuck-buddy from now on.
I’ll release all the pent up sexual frustration from your body with my dick.
Yes!
Taniguchi-san, your dick is great.
Taniguchi-san, from today on I’m your fuck-buddy
From now on, you will make me feel good with your dick.
That line... I want Hiro to hear it too.
Come on!
Fine...
Hiro...
From today on, I’m going to be Taniguchi-san’s fuck-buddy.
Taniguchi-san’s dick... makes me so wet....
Sorry about that, Hiro.
But I’m the one who will satisfy Reiko.
It feels so great!
Do whatever you want with my body.
So please let me cum!
Please let me cum, finally!
Reiko...
Cum. Cum, then.
Make sure to cum a lot in front of Hiro!
I’m cumming!
Hiro...
I’m sorry.
Hiroaki-san, Mamayu’s sailor uniform.
Does it turn you on?
It does! It does, it does! Mamayu
Mamayu, your sailor uniform drives me crazy!
We can’t do this.
My producer will be furious this time.
We’ll keep it a secret.
We’ll be fine as long as he doesn’t find out.
Really? It’s a secret, then.
Hiroaki-san, I only do this with you.
Yes, I promise.
Don’t slurp so loudly.
Mamayu, you really are a naughty idol.
You’re overflowing.
No don’t tease me.
Mamayu is like this... because of you.
Okay, I’ll make it all better.
Yes!
Mamayu’s insides... are overflowing with you!
Mamayu, your pussy is amazing.
It’s so hot. It’s squeezing me tight.
Hiroaki-san...
What if the producer and I were doing naughty things too?
What would you do?
I can’t allow it!
You’re my wife!
I’m the only one allowed to fuck you!
So rough!
My pussy will break apart.
I’ll visit again next week.
Until then, be sure to...
No!
Mamayu feels so good.
Mamayu is... Mamayu’s pussy...
Belongs only to you, Hiroaki-san!
Mamayu, you’re the best.
Mamayu, Mamayu, Mamayu, I can’t stand it!
Come in deeper!
Your dick, put it in all the way!
Mamayu, if you squeeze so tightly, I’ll cum.
Then cum! Hiroaki-san, cum because of my pussy!
I’m cumming, Mamayu.
I’m cumming inside, Mamayu.
Mamayu... Mamayu...
“Until then, be sure to store up lots of sexual frustration.”
www.SubDESU-H.net