No, stop it! Not more of this...
Look Shirusaki, everybody can see your pussy clearly.
Stop it! Don't spread my pussy!
Hey, they're showing it on screen!
This is embarrassing.
Don't stare at me like that!
Look at her drenched, pink, pussy!
I want to fuck her, hard!
That's what my job is.
No! Don't put that thing inside me!
Don't put that in!
Here it comes... It's going inside you!
It's coming inside me... There's so much of it!
It'll rip me apart!
This tightness is unstoppable!
Don't move!
I can see her clit!
His penis is turning her inside out!
No!
I don't want this! Don't look at me!
You liar! You're gettin' excited being watched by them!
Here!
That's...  no... no!
I'm going to come! I'll fill up your insides!
He came so much!
That's it for her!
Ai...
Netorare Fighter
Yaricchingu!
W
Netorare Fighter
Harry, are you sure she's on this ship?
Yeah. Sari informed me that she'd made contact with Ai during her investigation.
Ai...
Sari said she was locked in a suspicious-looking VIP cabin!
That must be it!
Ai!
I figured you guys would be coming right now.
Gil! And Dick!
Onizaki too!
You guys were behind this?
Ai! What's happening with you?
R-Randy!
What are you doing? Stop it!
No!
Ai!
Gil, you bastard!
Randy, are you alright?
Yeah, but something's in the way...
There's a wall of thick glass dividing this room.
Oh no!
Ai...
Randy...
You guys are trapped like a bird in cage.
So just stay out and watch!
You're a coward! Why are you doing this to Ai?
You guys have been in our way for a long time.
This is just a little thank you.
No!
Now, let me have me some fun with these breasts of yours.
Wait a moment, Dick.
First let her taste this lotion of pleasure.
This contains a specially made stimulant that can penetrate the skin,
but we're fine since we took the antidote earlier.
Stop it!
Ai Shirusaki... I'm going to rub all of it on your breasts.
No... don't rub that stuff on me!
Sure, you say that now...
But once I apply it, you'll begin salivating, and you'll start losing your mind over the pleasure of having your breasts touched.
No!
This is too much for my hands.
Your breasts are first-rate.
Don't suck it!
Your hands feel so slippery and weird!
She's excited from having her breasts played with.
Why do my breasts feel this good?
It seems the effect has taken her over.
Or perhaps... you're just naturally this lewd.
T-that's not true!
Oh, my hands slipped!
Ai!
Well, these seem to be different to earlier.
Look! They're hardening from the pleasure.
Don't look at me... Randy, Harry, Ryo...!
Your nipples sure are hard!
You're one hell of a perverted ninja.
That's not...!
Don't suck on my breasts!
You're feeling it, aren't you? Just be honest.
Hey... hey, her other breast is feeling lonely.
You're being played with by these men, and your nipples are hard...
What a lewd woman you are!
You're stretching my nipples!
I'm going crazy from having my breasts sucked!
These sensations are too much. Please, let me go!
We can't do that.
There's no way we can stop now!
Good! That's so good!
Oh yeah! My nipples are hot!
My breasts... my whole body feels so good!
The drug's sinking in. Makes you feel like you're ascending to heaven, right?
Feels good to have your titties licked and sucked, huh?
This feels so good! More! Suck harder!
Ai, you're...
I'm so sorry, Randy!
I...
Now it's time to spread those legs open!
Stop it!
How's she look down here, huh?
D-Don't look at it!
I knew it! She's drenched and sticky!
I'll give that pussy a good lick!
My clit... my clit!
Please, not there!
You've got one hell of a butt, here.
Your hot dick's rubbing up against my butt!
Your nipples and your clit are totally erect! You lewd whore!
Excellent. Your pussy is drenched. Serves you right!
Don't make such loud sucking noises!
Ai... Ai...
Your juices are flowing like crazy.
No, don't stop! Please don't stop!
Which feels better, your nipples or your clit? Tell me!
I-I can't... say something like that!
Really?
My nipples! I love having my nipples stroked and pinched!
Guess she does prefer having her nipples teased.
That's right! My nipples are my weakness!
If you keep teasing my breasts, I'll go crazy!
Then I'll make you feel even better!
If you suck my breasts that hard, I really will go crazy!
I'm so hot, my pussy won't stop getting wet!
Your sweat tastes delicious!
You've gotten excited all over, you perverted woman!
Something's coming!
It's coming! It's coming!
My breasts, my nipples... they feel so good, I'm going crazy!
The drug's almost taken control.
We're gonna keep teasing you until it has!
N-No...!
Both of my breasts are being sucked! Please stop it!
What's this feeling?
Something's coming out of my breasts!
Her nipples really are hard!
Here it comes! She's gonna spread it!
Coming! It's coming!
Something's coming from the tip of my nipples!
It's coming!
It's out, Shirusaki! It's your lewd milk!
This can't be! Milk... Milk is spraying out!
Why?
Ai's spraying milk!
Oh man, it tastes great!
T-This can't be...  I can't be lactating!
It's so good!
No, don't tease my nipples that much!
It won't stop! The milk won't stop flowing!
Your feet are soaked with your milk and nectar.
No!
Take that! Your lewd breasts are still leaking milk!
I'm being milked like a cow! I'm going to come while my breasts spray milk!
I'm coming!
You came just from having your breasts played with?
The drug not only affects feelings of lust and desire, but also enhances your basic female functions.
Well? Can you bear the pleasure of your breasts?
I can't... take it anymore!
Please, fuck me!
Thrust me with your hot, big, dick!
I want you to stick it in me, really hard!
Ai...
Hey, don't give me that face.
It's your turn after this.
What's with this gas?
I feel sick to my stomach!
Shit!
Gil, you bastard...
You're mine now.
What is this!? Untie me!
Damn you, Gil!
I thought I'd test my new concoction on you, just for fun.
Thanks to the ingredient we added to the gas, you fell asleep and got boners!
How do you like that, huh?
Looks like you've been hard since we started fucking Ai!
Harry! Ryo!
Shit! Why am I the only one spared, Gil!?
All right, let's start the show.
Ai?
Harry, please... my body can't take this, and I'm about to lose my mind.
Please! I beg you!
I can't fight it! My body's melting down, and I'm starting to go crazy.
Help me! Please!
My nipples have been hard and tingly this whole time!
Ai...
Now get to fucking.
If you don't have sex with Ai, who's been injected with the drugs, she might never be herself again.
Harry, my body's hot and I feel really lewd.
Stop it! The drug's effects are robbing me of my sanity, too!
It's OK, Harry.
Do whatever you want to my body.
Don't hold back just because I'm Randy's girlfriend!
Ai, Harry! Stop it!
Please, Harry! Lick my pussy!
What a perverted pussy... I can't help but lick it.
It feels good when you lick it like that! Do it harder!
I'll return the favor by relieving your suffering penis.
It's gotten so big that I can barely get it out!
It's so big and hot, and smells so nasty...
It's beautiful!
Ah, not so suddenly!
Delicious! It's so good!
Ai, your fellatio feels so good!
Your penis is the greatest!
More, Harry... lick me more!
Shit!
My penis is about to burst just listening to you guys!
Harry's nose is rubbing up against me!
Harry, please...
Give it to me, Harry!
Ai!
Ai, no! Anything but that!
I'm sorry, Randy. But my body's hot and my pussy's drenched.
It's hopeless. I can't bear it anymore!
Stop it, Ai!
What about Randy?
Yes! This is it!
This is what I wanted!
Ai, Stop it!
Good... your penis is so hard and thick!
It's rubbing up against my insides, right up to my womb!
Brother... Ai...
Sari!?
What are you doing here?
I was also caught by Gil and given the drugs.
Say, Randy... how about we have some fun ourselves?
Just look at you...
Did you get hard from watching Harry and Ai have sex?
Don't joke with me, Sari!
Please, let me suck it!
After watching those two, I can't go on...
Your penis really is just like your brother's...
My mouth is almost filled by the head alone!
In that case, I'll wrap my breasts around it.
Sari, no! More of this is...
What did you say? Sari!?
Please forgive me.
Sari!
I'm sorry, Harry.
But I can't take it anymore!
Harry, this isn't...
Sally and Randy...
Forgive me, Harry.
But I can't help myself!
Ai, and Harry...
Randy's penis tastes so good!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come, Ai!
Do it! Come inside me!
I'm gonna come too!
Coming!
Sari, I'm about to come too!
It's OK! Go ahead and come!
Ai!
Sari!
How are the drug's effects?
You're still nowhere near satisfying them.
No, Harry... give me more!
Your penis is just too good!
My hips won't stop! I wanna be fucked more!
Ryo!
Ai, my cock's about to explode!
Ryo! What happened to your shackles?
They released them a moment ago!
Now entangle your bodies and feed your desires, like wild animals!
Whoa! So these are Ai's breasts!
Don't grab them so hard!
Here, give me a breast-fuck! Here goes!
Ryo's hard, big, penis is coming at me!
Shit, this is too much!
Suck on it, Ai!
Amazing! Your penis is so big, it won't even fit!
My penis feels so hot!
Your drenched juice and milk are making it all slippery! I think I'm going to come already!
She's leaking like a fountain... What a lewd pussy!
I'm gonna fuck you again, Ai.
It... it's inside me again!
My pussy's being filled up with Harry's big penis!
And Ryo's hot cock's fucking my breasts! Oh god!
Your wet, sticky breasts are squeezing my penis!
Ai, I'm gonna come!
I'm coming while spraying milk again...
I only just came, so if you keep thrusting, I'll come right away!
Your insides feel so good, I just can't stop moving my hips!
Go ahead! Fuck my little pussy more!
Hey, looks like you're having yourself a good time!
It seems the drug's taken good care of you.
How about we give you a hand?
Look, here are some of your favorite dicks!
Still, these breasts are really big.
You can practically fuck them!
Look at them spraying all this milk! These perverted breasts!
Please don't talk like that!
I'll make things a little easy for you, with this lotion.
The head's getting stuck on her nipple... It's really great!
Don't rub your penis on my breasts!
No, don't rub my nipples!
This feels so good!
Ai... I want to thrust it in you, too!
Ryo, what're you doing!?
See... your asshole is already very drenched!
This way it won't get ripped apart, right?
You're not really going to put it in my butt, are you?
That's exactly what I'm going to do!