No, stop it! No more!
Look Shirusaki, everybody can see your cunt clear as day.
Stop it! Don't spread it open!
Hey, they're showing it on screen!
This is mortifying!
Don't stare at it like that!
Check out her sticky, pink pussy!
God, I wanna do her so bad!
That's what I'm here to do.
No! Don't shove that thing inside me!
Don't put that in!
Here it comes... It's going inside you!
It's coming inside me... So deep!
My pussy's gonna tear!
This tightness is unbelieveable!
Don't thrust!
I can see her clit!
His dick's turning her inside out!
No!
I don't want this! Don't look at me!
You liar! You're gettin' turned on by being watched!
Take that!
Oh god...  No... No!
I'm gonna cum! Gonna blow my load inside you!
He came buckets!
That knocked her up for sure!
Ai...
NTR Fighter Fucking!
FAKKU! Presents
You sure she's on this ship, Harry?
Yeah. Sally informed me that she'd made contact with Ai during her investigation.
Ai...
Sally said she was locked in a suspicious-looking VIP cabin!
That must be it!
Ai!
I figured you guys would be coming about now.
Gil! And Dick!
Onizaki too!
You guys were behind this!?
Ai! Why are you doing this?
R-Randy!
What are you doing!? Stop it!
Nooo!
Ai!
Gil, you bastard!
Randy, are you alright!?
Yeah, but something's in the way...
There's a wall of reinforced glass dividing this room.
Dammit!
Ai...
Randy...
You guys are trapped like rats.
So just stay put and look on in frustration!
You fucking weasel! Why are you doing this to Ai!?
You guys have been a thorn in our side for some time.
This is just a little thank you.
No!
Now then, I think I'll have me some fun with these sexy tits of yours.
Hang on a sec, Dick.
Wait till after we smear her with this aphrodisiac lotion.
This contains a specially made aphrodisiac that can be absorbed through the skin.
But we're unaffected since we took the antidote beforehand.
Stop it!
Ai Shirusaki... I'm going to rub plenty of this into your giant tits.
No... Don't rub that awful drug on me!
Sure, you say that now...
But once I apply it, your mouth will water, and you'll start losing your mind just from having your tits groped.
Nooo!
Impressive. They're too big for my hands.
Your tits are first-rate.
Don't grope them!
Your hands feel so slippery and weird!
She's in heat just from having her tits played with.
Why do my breasts feel this good?
Seems the aphrodisiac has taken effect.
Or perhaps... you're just naturally this slutty.
T-that's not true!
Oh dear, my hands slipped!
Ai!
Well THESE seem to tell a different story.
Look! They're completely stiff from the pleasure.
Randy, Harry, Ryo... don't look at me!
Your nipples are totally erect!
You're one whore of a ninja.
No I'm not!
Don't suck on my breasts!
You're getting turned on right? Just be honest.
Hey now, her other tit's feeling lonely.
You're being triple-teamed, and your nipples are rock hard...
What a sluttly little kitten you are!
You're stretching my nipples!
I'm going insane just from my tits being sucked!
This feels way too good. Please, let me go!
'Fraid we can't do that.
There's no way we can stop now!
Yes! That's so good!
Oh yeah! My nipples are burning!
My breasts... my whole body feels so good!
The drug's kicking in. Makes you feel like you're ascending to heaven, don't it?
Feels great to have your titties licked and sucked, huh?
This feels so good! More! Suck harder!
Ai, you're...
I'm so sorry, Randy!
I...
Now it's time to spread those legs open!
Stop it!
How's she look down here, I wonder?
D-Don't stare at it!
I knew it! She's all wet and sticky!
I'll give that bulging clit a nice tongue lashing!
My clit! Oh god!
Please, not there!
You've got one hell of an ass here.
Your hot dick's rubbing up against my ass!
Your nipples and your clit are totally erect! You fucking slut!
Good stuff. Your cunt's dripping wet. Serves you right!
Don't make such loud sucking noises!
Ai... Ai...
Your juices are flowing like crazy.
Ahh, don't stop! Please don't stop!
Which feels better, your nipples or your clit? C'mon, tell me!
I-I can't possibly say that!
Oh yeah?
My nipples! I love having my nipples twisted and squeezed!
Guess she does prefer having her knockers teased.
That's right! My nipples are my weakness!
If you keep teasing my breasts, I'll go insane!
Well in that case, I'll make you feel even better!
If you suck my breasts that hard, I really will go crazy!
I'm so horny, my pussy won't stop dripping!
Your sweat tastes delicious!
You get off no matter what hole, you little wench!
Something's coming!
It's coming! It's coming!
My breasts, my nipples... They feel so good I'm gonna lose my mind!
The drug's almost taken control.
We're gonna keep teasing you till it finally does!
N-No, please!
Both of my breasts are being squeezed! Please have mercy!
What's this feeling!?
Something's coming out of my breasts!
Damn, her nipples are so stiff!
Here it comes! She's gonna blow!
Coming! It's coming!
Something's leaking from the tip of my nipples!
THEY'RE LEAKING!!!
There it is, Shirusaki! It's your nasty slut milk!
This can't be happening! Milk... Milk is spraying out!
Why!?
Ai's spraying milk!
Oh man, it tastes great!
T-This can't be...  I can't be lactating!
It's so good!
No, don't squeeze my nipples that hard!
It won't stop! The milk won't stop flowing!
Your feet are soaked with your milk and nectar.
Nooo!
Take that! Your slutty funbags are still leaking milk!
I'm being milked like a cow! I'm going to cum while my tits spray milk!
I'm cumming!
You came just from your tits?
Not only does the drug affect lust and desire, but also enhances your base female functions.
Well? Can you bear to have only your chest pleasured?
I can't... take it anymore!
Please, fuck me!
Pound me with your hot, fat dick!
I want you to do me really, really hard!
Ai...
Hey man, don't give me that look.
It's your guys' turn next.
What is this gas!?
I feel sick to my stomach!
Dammit!
Gil, you sneaky little...
You're mine now.
Fucking!
What the hell is this!? Untie me!
Damn you, Gil!
I thought I'd test our new aphrodisiac on you guys, just for fun.
Thanks to the aphrodisiac we added to the anesthetic, you guys fell asleep and got boners!
How do you like that, huh?
More like you guys have been hard since we started fucking Ai!
Harry! Ryo!
Shit! Why am I the only one spared, Gil!?
Alright, let's kick off the show.
Ai?
Harry, please... my body's throbbing, and I'm about to lose my mind!
Please! I beg you!
I can't fight it! My body's burning up, and I'm starting to go crazy.
Help me! Please!
My nipples have been stiff and tingly this whole time!
Ai...
Now get to fucking.
If you don't have sex with Ai, who's been injected with the aphrodisiac, she might never regain herself.
Harry, my body's burning up, and I'm feeling really perverted.
Stop it! The aphrodisiac is robbing me of my reason too!
It's okay, Harry.
Do whatever you want to my body.
Don't hold back just because I'm Randy's girlfriend!
Ai, Harry, stop it!
Please, Harry! Lick my pussy!
What a filthy pussy... I can't help but lick it.
It feels so good when you lick it like that! Do it harder!
I'll return the favor by relieving your suffering penis.
It's gotten so big, I can barely unzip you!
It's so hot and fat, and smells so nasty...
It's beautiful!
Gah! Not so sudden!
Delicious! It's so yummy!
Ai, your blowjob feels way to good!
Your cock is the greatest!
More, Harry... lick me more!
God Dammit!
My dick's about to burst just by listening to you guys!
Harry's nose is rubbing up against me!
Harry, please...
Give it to me, Harry!
Ai!
Ai, no! Anything but that!
I'm sorry, Randy. But my body's been on fire, and my pussy's soaked.
It's hopeless. I can't fight it anymore!
Stop it, Ai!
What about Randy?
Yes! This is it!
This is what I wanted!
Ai, Stop it!
Oh god! Your dick is so hard and thick!
It's rubbing up against my insides, right up to my womb!
Brother... Ai...
Sally!?
What are you doing here?
I was also caught by Gil and given the aphrodisiac.
Say, Randy... How about we have some fun ourselves?
Just look at you...
Did you get stiff from watching Harry and Ai have sex?
Don't be ridiculous, Sally!
Please, let me suck it!
After watching those two, I can't go on...
Your dick really is just like your brother's...
My mouth almost gets stuck on the head!
Next, I'll wrap my tits around you.
Sally, no! Don't go any further!
What did you say? Sally!?
Please forgive me.
Sally!
I'm sorry, Harry.
But I can't take it anymore!
Harry, this isn't...
Sally, and Randy...
Forgive me, Harry.
But I can't help myself!
Ai, and Harry...
Randy's dick tastes so good!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum, Ai!
Do it! Cum inside me!
I'm gonna cum too!
Cumming!!
Sally, I'm about to cum too!
It's okay! Go ahead and cum!
Ai!
Sally!
Enjoying the drug's effects?
You're still nowhere near satisfying their lust just from that.
No, Harry... Give me more!
Your dick's just too good!
My hips won't stop! I wanna be creampied more!
Ryo!
Ai, my cock's about to explode!
Ryo!? What happened to your shackles?
Ha! They released them forever ago!
Now entangle your bodies, and indulge in your desires like wild animals!
Whoa! So these are Ai's titties!
Don't grab them so hard!
C'mon, gimme a titfuck! Here goes!
Ryo's hard, huge dick's coming at me!
Man, this is too much!
Suck on it, Ai!
Amazing! Your dick's so fat, it won't even fit!
My whole dick feels so hot!
Your drool and milk are making it all slippery! I think I'm gonna cum already!
She's gushing like a fountain... What a dirty cunt!
I'm gonna fuck you again, Ai.
It... It's inside me again!
My pussy's being crammed full of Harry's huge dick!
And Ryo's hot cock's fucking my tits! Oh god!
Your wet, sticky tits are squeezing my dick!
Ai, I'm gonna cum!
I came while spraying milk again...
I just came, so if you keep thrusting, I'll cum right away!
Your insides feels so good, I just can't stop moving my hips!
Go ahead! Fuck my messy little pussy more!
Hey, looks like you're havin' yourself a good time!
Seems the drug's done a number on you.
How about we throw you a bone?
Look, there's so many of your favorite dicks!
Seriously man, these tits are ridiculous.
You can practically fuck 'em!
Look at 'em spraying milk so shamelessly. Fuckin' nasty tits!
Please don't talk like that!
I'll make things a little smoother with the aphrodisiac lotion.
The head's getting stuck on her nipple... This is incredible!
Don't shove your cocks into my tits!
No, don't rub my nipples!
This feels so good!
Ai... I wanna plow you too!
Ryo, what're you doing!?
Wow, your asshole's already soaking wet!
Don't gotta worry about it tearing, huh?
You're not really going to put it in my ass, are you?
You're damn right I am!