I'm Tanabe Yuuka,
who always lived without any inconvenience up 'till now.
I got married to my best friend when I graduated from school.
Then I started my household life like I had always wanted when I was little, with my husband
My day is filled with calmness.
My husband loves me,
and I love him too.
It hurts... you've entered my deepest part.
I'm going to cum...
I can't hold...
Let me cum!
It's cumming inside!
Today as well after my husband has gone out to work,
I'm doing my housework as always,
and I'm waiting for my husband to come home.
W
NETO
RARE
Tanabe Yuuka no Dokuhaku
I thought that I lived in those common places...
Yes, who is it?
No~!!!
That was the voice of my daily life being destroyed.
No..No, you can't!
Wait, stop it!
At that time, I really didn't want it.
No...
For someone to touch my body beside my husband,
I thought that I had betrayed my husband.
If this continues, I can't even forgive myself.
That's what I thought.
But...
Most times, the nights I spend  with my husband isn't really filled with so much pleasure.
It's the first time in a long time that my body felt so much pleasure,
I felt so much strong stimulation inside of me,
then I remembered all of it.
And then the stimulation that he gave me,
it got stronger like a stream,
and it awoken the womanly side of me.
As my head was filled with that,
I couldn't even tell if it was my body or not.
It felt a bit linguidly.
But, at the same time I felt that sensation.
I was coming back...
As I saw how my body was stimulating against that man...
Be careful.
When I went to take another shower,
I began to think of all that happened in the daytime like a flash movie which keep flowing around.
As I watched those pictures inside my head,
I started to touch the parts of my body which that man touch before.
It was an unconscious act.
That same night, I felt so depressed about what had happen before.
No... No...
Why am I feeling happy about someone abusing my body?
He's arousing all of my emotions...
Stop it!
That's something I can't avoid.
No... No...
No...
Stop it...
I wonder if that man is going to come here again...
Then would he gave me those stimulation again?
I began to imagine all that I was thinking.
So that imagination is coming true after all.
Who is it?
When I opened the door,
I saw that man standing in front of my door.
And I invited him inside to my living room.
I can't hold back something that I want.
In front of all this reality,
I started my seductive act on him.
Inside of myself,
I never thought that I was going to act like this.
That's because something big, hard, was stimulating the inside of me.
That's what turned me on.
When I realized that,
I began to suck that thing with my mouth and my tongue.
As I sucked it,
my tongue kept licking around it.
I kept sucking it inside my mouth.
So it made the voice come out around it.
There's no one forcing me to do it,
it's me who wants to do it.
When I think that this thing will come inside of me,
it send thrills inside my body.
Even though I'm not doing anything with it,
I knew that something inside of my body was flowing out some fluid in my pants.
Then something came out.
Something came out from that man's thing,
It's something hot and sticky,
It kept spreading inside my mouth.
So many, many times I've thought about it.
What appeared before me was something that I wanted.
It felt like my throat was thirsty for water.
That's something I couldn't run from.
That's the sign of me making that man feel satisfied.
And then,
that man gave the reward to me.
There's no conscious feeling of guilty left behind,
So he began to give me all of those stimulations with the thrusting of that thing inside of me.
That's something I was waiting for,
then I turned into a slave of pleasure.
No~ No..you can't!
I'm cumming!
It came thrusting inside the deep part of me so many times.
At the same time,
the inside of my body was shivering,
and my consciousness was floating all around.
Then the stimulation was started again.
Cumming out!!
Then,
for the first time I felt at my peak.
My life with my husband has slightly changed over.
It's because I want to feel a bit of pleasure in me.
When I lost the guilt I felt for my husband, it reassured me.
Then that day, I invited another man inside.
There has never been so much stimulation inside of me before,
it made me feel no presence of my husband at all.
But then I wasn't aware, that I had started to think of my husband without calling his name with love as I always did.
What happened after that,
was something I couldn't imagine myself.
That was enough up 'till now,
but it isn't enough for me right now,
My best friend who I married after I graduated from school,
my household life that I wanted when I was little since I met my husband
My day which is filled with calmness...
Be careful.
My husband loves me,
I love my husband too.
It's big... It entered the deep part of me.
Even though my day continues with that man around me,
but then I started to think that It might be not be a coincidence.
More...
I want more of it.
No...
Cumming!
I'm Tanabe Yuuka,
who has always lived without any inconvenience up 'till now.
Today as well after my husband has gone out to work,
I'm doing my housework as always,
and I'm waiting for my husband to come home.
As I thought,
the one that set up all of this was my husband.
And then,
I coincidentally saw it.
The face of my husband who got excited at looking at my indecent and pleasured figure.
My common life doesn't exist anymore.