Haruka, I think I'm gonna cum!
Shuu-chan, cum inside me!
That was good.
Yeah, I think so too.
Being forsed to sleep with others.
Alright, I'm off to work, Haruka.
Okay.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Make sure you lock the door when I'm
not around, and put the chain on too.
Okay. You be careful too, alright Shuu?
Sure. See you later.
Ito Bank
Thank you for waiting.
Is the person holding #108 here?
Yes, that's me.
I drank a little too much.
Dad, you are too strict.
I'll do my best.
What are you drinking here all alone for, Tachibana?
Or was it Isumi?
Gotou-san, you're doing this on purpose right?
I've already been married for 2 years, you know.
TL Note: Implying that he took his wife's last name. In Japanese, there is one
word for marrying your significant other and taking their family name.
You might have a beautiful wife, but it's only
because you married into her family.
So, what're you gonna do now?
Ready to go to the next place?
I'm sorry, but you'll have to excuse me after this one.
Are you going home already, Tachmobu-senpai?
Kawai-san, it's actually Isumi.
Well, go on then. He says he wants to get home soon.
You know why, right, Kawai?
It's because of his wife's left and right assets.
He says he wants to go home quickly
and do some kissy-wissy.
Yuck! Sexually-harassing old fart.
Shall we play kissy-wissy together?
– No way
– No way.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Have you had dinner?
A little.
But I'll have some more.
Okay.
Well then, eat as much as you like.
Miso soup with
roots & vegetalbes
Grated yami
Stir-fried Beef and Garlic Shoots
Oyster soup with grated
daikon and spring onion
Fermented soybeans with Okra
This is a little too much.
You didn't have to go this far, did you?
Yes I do! I really want a baby.
Bon appétit!
That's the reason why I quit my job.
I see.
You must be tired, right? Sorry for being so selfish.
It's alright. I also want a kid, so I'll do my best.
Well then, shall we do it?
Yeah.
Tease her by going around...
Then finally, her nipples...
Okay, now we go down...
Nothing's happening.
Play some more with my boobs.
Stick your fingers in that hole while licking her...
And then, her boobs...
It's about time to...
Shuu-chan, your face is scary.
I'm so sorry. I shouldn't have said that.
No, it's not your fault.
I'm not too sure either, but...
This isn't making love, is it?
If we do it everyday like it's mandatory,
it's going to be hard on you.
It's not hard on me at all, because
I love you so much Haruka.
It's just that you are my first too, so I'm not used to sex yet.
Finally, after so many years.
I see. That might be it.
It's because we are both first-timers.
I love you too Shuu. I feel at ease
when we lie down like this.
Haruka!
Why do you want to be the manager for the rugby
dub? In middle school it was basketball.
They practically begged me. I can't just
turn them down then anymore.
You're always like that.
You won't turn down any request.
Shuu, how about now?
I can't do it today.
I haven't been able to do it with
Haruka for a long time now.
Haruka!
What are you doing?
What do you mean what am I
doing? Even I know this much.
Haruka!
W-Wait!
Because I'm good at giving massages...
Do you want to try doing it with another guy?
S-Sorry! Never mind!
We're back!
Welcome home.
How nice of you to come, Shuujirou-kun.
Sorry. Dinner's running a bit late.
N-No, don't worry.
Why are you and Dad always here?
Why not?
Isumi family
Tachibana family
We live right next door, and it'd be
double the effort otherwise, right?
That's true, but...
You hang around here way too much.
I never thought the two of you would get married.
Being together with both households, that's
what family is all about. It's curious, isn't it?
Yes, it really is.
Hey Shuujirou, when are you giving us a grandchild?
You sure you're doing it right?
I get it already. I'm seriously thinking about it.
No, you don't understand Isumi's feelings at all.
When you reach my age, it goes without saying
that you want this family to continue existing.
For that purpose I let you, my second
son, marry into the Isumi family.
What are you gonna do if you don't
make kids anytime soon?
I told you I get it!
Here you go, dad.
Oh, thank you.
But you have raised a good daughter.
She's a waste on Shuujirou.
The only thing left to do is to make kids, right?
Yes, we'll do our best.
With such a cute daughter, the baby will definitely
be cute as well, don't you think?
Ichida Urology Clinic
Nothing at all?
No, there is absolutely nothing out of the ordinary.
The only thing I can think of is that the sexual stimulation
between the two of you is out of sync.
To put it simply, aren't you forcing it a little?
Do you have a moment?
Uh, sure.
I feel bad for making it so hard on you.
I'm the one who should be sorry for
not being able to produce an heir.
No, I don't own a family business so it's
a bit strange to be speaking of heirs.
It's just that Haruka is such a sweet girl.
It's not that we are filthy rich or somethig,
but she understood my feelings
and started worrying about letting the man marry
into our family, in case she did get married.
But enough is enough.
I'm already grateful for the fact that
you married into our family.
Thank you so much.
That's why you don't have to stress over it.
I told Haruka the same thing.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
Thanks for the food.
Go ahead. Enjoy.
You really made a lot of this again today, huh?
The meat was on sale, so I went all out.
What do you think?
It's good.
I guess you really want a child, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I see. But we don't have to hurry, right?
Your dad said the same thing.
Why would you say such a thing?
I want a baby!
My dad has nothing to do with it.
I'm sorry.
Don't you want a child, Shuu-chan?
That's not what I mean.
Then, don't you want to have sex with me?
I told you! That's not it!
Then why haven't we been able to have sex?
I beg you. If there's a problem, I want you to tell me.
That's how we've always done it, up until now, right?
I-It's nothing really...
I understand. That's enough!
Shuu-chan...
I just want to ask one thing of you, Haruka.
This is what I want...
I want you to sleep with another man.
Translator: Jimaku-Danshaku
Translation Check: Hikarucon
Timing: v1touch
Typesetting: Ephemere
Editor: Punk4real