Netorare Fighter
Yaricchingu!
W
Netorare Fighter
Welcome to this secret party.
The hostess for everyone is the one and only woman gamble fighter,
Shirusaki Ai~ and,
The idol who dance's and sings, Asakura Aina!
Aina, even you?
But, didn't you have your teleportation to escape from this?
No, I can't.
Because of the effect of the drugs, I can't even concentrate to use it.
My power is draining...
Then everyone, the drugs is effective by now.The rest we leave to you.
No~!!!
So these are Shirusaki Ai's big breasts?
You can't~!!
Nice breasts!
Her vagina is drenched down here.
It's good and delicious.
I just can't hold these breasts!
You...suck at it...
What a perverted breast you have, the nipples are blooming like sakura petals.
No~!!
This lewd woman is dripping wet from her vagina, when I suck a little at her ass hole.
Don't say something like that!
It's delicious, do you feel good from my licking?
I... don't know...
No...
All of my body is being played with all these men,
even my lips... No...
Ai-chan~
I mixed all of our sprem in this bottle.
Why don't you taste it then...
How is the taste?
I'll fill up your pussy with it as well.
It's rubbing it!
You can't let it in~!
I can't hold back with your pink pussy.
You're off to a good start.
Good...
What's with this pussy? It feels amazing inside.
It's really amazing!
I can't hold it anymore.
Then let's fuck her together.
That's a good idea!
There... my penis is going inside you. Why don't you open your mouth, Ai-chan?
You like my penis, don't you?
Let me see all of your lewdness!
Did you getting excited by looking at Ai?
Your licking is getting better.
What's the matter? Did you forget about down here because you are licking penises with your mouth?
Move your hips by yourself!
This lewd tongue is stirring my penis.
That's good, your juice is making it easier to move my penis inside you.
What a lovely big breast, you're a totally lewd esper after all.
It's my first time tasting such a delicious nipple.
She's sucking at my penis this hard.
It's good... that's the way.
It's too much... I'm gonna come...
My body is getting hot with smell of all these penises...
I can't think of anything, but to drink all of their sperm.
Ai's tongue is rubbing all these sticky penises.
With a pose like this..I'm about to come soon...
It's too good with all this sensation.
I'm going to cum...
Me too.
Me as well.
I'll come inside of Ai's.
I'm gonna cum...
I'll let it out!
I'll fill up your pussy with semen.
Hey, It's lesbis show time. Why don't you let us see your good relationship?
Aina...
Ai-san, I can't stop it...
I'm getting crazy from getting fucked with all those penises.
Me too...
It feels good rubbing on each other breasts...
It tickles when Ai-san's nipples are rubbing on mine.
Here you go, a penis.
The way your butt and breasts are shaking, it's getting excited.
My breasts...you can't rub it like that...
Then...I'll do anal with you...
I'll do anal with Aini's then!
It's really tight!
Breasts...It's hitting my breasts...
My butt...my butt is...
Hot!!!
The nipples are rubbing against each other...It's...
My butt...my butt is spreading...
We're rubbing our bodies against each other and I'm feeling your thrusting in me too...
Ai and Aini's pussy are really great!
Here...make these feel good too.
Great, we're fucking her pussy and ass hole at the same time!
As I thought from gamble fighter, It's getting tight and tighter!
It's good in the front too...
They're doing it at my face too...
I'm gonna cum...
It's good...I'm gonna meltdown...
Ai-san...It feels good in my butt, I'm gonna cum soon...
Aina...Aina..I'm gonna cum...
It's gonna rip apart!!
Their pussy is sucking this hard, it makes me want to come...
Let's make it double with Ai and Aini's.
It's keep hitting at me, I feel like Aini and I are becoming one with each other's body.
I feel that something is gonna come out...
Cu...cumming...It's coming out...
We're cumming!!
It's coming inside me~!!!
For all the party participants, this secret party isn't over yet.
In here, we'll introduce you the third hostess for tonight.
Teryuu Sari!!!
This hostess is already prepared for you.
All of the guest, please enjoy yourself with this!
This penis is delicious!
More...harder...
Make it full with sperm!!
It feels good...
This penis is great...let me drink your semen...
It's gonna cum...
It's cumming~!!!
Ai, please forgive me...but If I see that...I'm gonna cum again...
The ejaculation won't stop...the effect of the drugs is too strong...
I'm...I'm...gonna cum too...
Hm...hm...Aren't you energetic.
Onizaki, what do you want from this?
Did you come to laugh at us as well?!
Huh, what you're talking about? I'm about to let you escape from this.
What? What do you mean with that?
What do you mean by letting us go, Onizaki?!
I have my own league as well, so I'll let you rampage in here on purpose.
In a little moment, the chip in you neck will come off as well and it's good for both of us.
Well, you might wanna choose to believe me and quickly save Ai and the others.
If not, we don't know what those guests will do with them.
That's it, all of you!
Get away from Ai and the others!!
Pull that disgusting thing out of her!
Here, the party is already over!
Sari, sorry for being late!
Are you okay, Ai? It's me Randy.
I've come to save you, open your eyes Ai!
Hey, what's the matter?
Do it...please put your penis in Ai's slave pussy...
Ai!
Master, I want to drink your love sperm again.
Please do it more with Aini's pussy.
It's the effect of the drugs, isn't?
What?!
Dick!
What do you mean?
That's I said It's the side effect of it.
Those women are already whore slaves.
What?!
What with this ruckus? Look at the mess of the party.
Gil-sama, they're trying to escape from here.
Hmph, they're people who don't know when to give up.
Did you know the drugs' development in Ai and the others bodies,
will continue to make them act like that and without the antidote,
they're beyond helpless.
Right now, they only know how to do it.
Just a moment later, I'll have samples of whores whom I can sell for high prices.
I won't let you interfere!
You made that thing that made Ai become like this...
I'll destroy your insane brain and this place as well!
So this is the sample of the drugs.
Because of their rampage, I can now take it.
Now all that's left is to take this and escape from this party.
Onizaki!
What?
Sorry, but you have to let me take those things.
I'm gonna need them to specify an antidote for them.
If not, why don't you try and beat me first?
I'm gonna..gonna save Ai...
Didn't I tell you to escape and not stay at my way?
You can't make those whores feel better after all that happened.
You brat, you up for this?
This time...I'll save Ai...
Ai!
He's fast!
Netorare Elbow!!
Did you feel that, Gil?!
The coast guard will come here soon.
What...?
With this your insane ambition will be over as well.
Damn you, just a little bit more...
This is the coast guard, please stop this ship immediately!
Ai.
Is it okay with you?
Randy...that's good!
Don't lie to me!
Just how many times you sucked those penises,You must be lying to me.
Damn it, just how many times I do I have to do it for to make you this wet?
Your body has become so erotic...
Ai, are your nipples getting hard for all this talking?
Randy, don't tease me~!
It's not only your big breasts, but your vagina is filled with your hot lewdness as well.
Good...
With this sticky feeling down here, your body is feeling that too, right?
Ai's having great side effects from the drugs than Sari and Aini,
the effect is taken much control of her body.
So I do this with Ai to stabilize the balance inside her body.
It feels good when I suck your breasts, doesn't it?
My breasts feels good...
With this I believe it can make Ai better,
then I'll make her balance comeback as the way it is.
But...
But, It isn't enough right? You want more semen filled inside of you, don't you?
You want them to fill up in this lewd pussy of yours!
Thrust...keep thrusting in me...
Please keep thrusting at my lewd pussy!
Please stir that inside me!
Sorry Randy, but my heart can't stop this feeling. Please keep it up until i reach my limit.
I understand, Ai. Hey, come in here.
Eh?!
Harry...and Ryo...why...?
Randy, what's with this?
Whow, Ai's pussy is sticky and drenched a lot down there.
Yeah, It's amazing.
But, we're...
It's okay.
Just do it.
No, Harry's looking at me like this...
Then without delay, let me fuck Ai's ass back there.
It's Ryou's big thing again...
It's really okay...with the two of you?
Randy, are you fine with me...?
Did you throw me away cause I'm this dirty?
It's okay.
I just couldn't hold it in before and now the tip of my penis is excited with it.
Yeah, If I look at this thing...I just want to stir it up with me.
Two of you...you've already become that big...
It's really tight down here, Ai.
As I thought Ai's ass hole is really tight as before.
Good~ Harry and Ryo's penises are good!!!
Ai..Ai...
My penis is getting sucked with Ai's really tight...
If you two fuck me that hard, I'm gonna...
It's..good...!
Sorry Randy, but I'm getting crazy with this~!
It's good...It's feels really good..,doesn't it Ai?
Good...the front and the back are rubbing against each other...
When Ai's getting fucked with all Gil's best, I can't do anything but feel really jealous with that.
That's why I feel so much excited with this.
Eh?!
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
Is that so? You're not angry with me?
Don't you hate my lewdness?
Why would you ever think that I would hate you?!
I just..I just want to see Ai's happy face!
Randy...
Ai, I love you.
Even though all those men made you dirty, that doesn't change how I feel about you in my heart.
That I love you.
Let me see more of it...
The dirty Ai that everyone loves,
The masochist and lewdness side of you,
It's getting tighter and tighter...
Here too and her nipples is getting hard as well.
Here, in fact you really wanted all those men doing this to you.
With this lewdness form of yours.
That's...
I feel that as well...as well as jealously, envy, and another feeling...
The real feeling.
That's right, make me feel more of it!!
That's why Ai, I'll always go with you!
It's Full Piston!!
More echos...here from the bottom...here...here!!!
All of your holes are filled up, are you happy with this, Ai?
It's really great inside Ai's pussy.
With all the flowing juice, It's getting easy to thrust into her ass hole...
My heart and my body getting fucked like this...It feels good...
Ai...
I'm gonna...
I'm cumming~!!!
Randy, I can't believe i was like this in front of you...
No, it's fine. That's...That's because you...
You make me...no...you make all men, feel so hot with your body.
You're the highest quality of women after all.