I'll see you later.
Ah, Shu-chan...
I just want to ask one thing of you, Haruka.
This is what I want...
I want you to sleep with another man.
W-Wait, Shu-chan, I don't get what you mean...
It's like I said. I want you to sleep with another man.
If you don't, I won't be able to have sex.
Why?
W-Why?
It has been like this for awhile.
If I don't imagine you with another man, I can't get it up.
So you don't love me...
No, I love you, Haruka! You're my one true love!
But what you said isn't right.
It's not normal!
That's "normal" for you though, right?
That kind of life is probably impossible for me.
Making love to each other normally,
having a child normally...
Even though I showed you who I really am inside,
you rejected what's normal for me and
aren't even giving it a second thought.
N-No, I can't get depressed.
I need to smile!
Haruka, what's got you so upset?
How about you try telling little 'ol sheep here...
Finding out just how little I knew
about Shu-chan really got to me.
So, you want to get to know him better, don't you?
With the kind of request he made,
that's not gonna be possible!
You just don't get it, do you?
It took a lot of courage to tell her all that.
All he's saying is that, as long as that happens,
he can have sex normally, right?
What's the harm in just trying it once?
Yeah, I don't think I can do it.
Will everything go smoothly if I just hang in there?
C-Coming!
Kuroheio Packaging Services.
Here's your package.
Could you sign for this?
Sure.
Thanks as always.
Thanks for the food.
Ah, no, you can't!
No!
Ma'am!
W-What kind of dream was that?
Shu-chan...
I'm the worst...
Haruka?
What's the matter?
Shu-chan...
A cool guy would be nice...
Someone who's nicer than you...
Someone with a nice smile,
Shu-chan... you're really okay with this, right?
Yeah...
Thank you, Haruka.
Ito Bank
Haruka
Nice to meet you. Sorry for the sudden message.
I read your book, Mr. Miyata.
Yasunori Miyata
Nice to meet you. Well, that's embarrassing.
Thank you for your comments.
Notepad
File (F)   Edit (E)
- Residence outside of the prefecture
- Has a wife and child
- High standings in society
- Sincere personality
- Feminist
Individual Investigation Request Form.
*indicates necessary blanks. Be sure to fill these in.
First Name *
Last Name *
Address *
Phone Number *
Have a nice day.
Thanks.
Yasunori Miyata
Nice to meet you. Well, that's embarrassing.
Thank you for your comments.
Haruka
You might think I'm a weird girl for saying this
since I have a husband but, I've fallen in love with you.
Maybe it'd be best if I stopped messaging you.
Haruka
You might think I'm a weird girl for saying this
since I have a husband but, I've fallen in love with you.
Maybe it'd be best if I stopped messaging you.
Yasunori Miyata
It's fine. I feel the same. I have a wife and child.
but I have become infatuated with you.
Yasunori Miyata
It's fine. I feel the same. I have a wife and child.
but I have become infatuated with you.
Yasunori Miyata
If it's okay with you, I'd love to go
out somewhere to eat together.
Results of the Investigatio
Haruka, is this guy okay?
Yeah...
Yasunori Miyata
I look forward to tomorrow.
Shu-chan, can you hear me?
On second thought, I...
Hey, Shu-chan?
Does this actually work?
Haruka-san?
It really is you. Nice to meet you in person.
Nice to meet you.
I was really taken aback, you're very pretty.
Oh no, that's not...
That wasn't just empty flattery.
Okay then, let's go.
Am I really going to have sex with this man?
Shu-chan...
There's a really nice view.
Would you like to look at it with me?
Are you nervous?
Don't worry, relax your shoulders.
This is my daughter.
She's so cute.
I know, right? She's the cutest in the world.
She's so cute. Actually, when we
went to the zoo the other day...
He doesn't seem to be a bad guy, but...
Sorry, your smile was just so pretty, I couldn't help myself.
Stop it!
No! We can't!
I know we can't.
But because of that, my heart's beating so fast.
This is bliss. My boring life is tiring me out.
I need a break from my work and my family.
You feel the same, don't you?
N-No!
This isn't right, but...
No...
I'm happy that you're enjoying this so much.
Why am I wetter than usual?
Oh no. No!
Are you really okay with this, Shu-chan?
It went in! Wow!
You can be louder if you want to be.
Right now, just feel good off me!
You just got tighter!
Haruka-san, you're amazing!
No!
Shu-chan...
You won't do it no matter what?
No matter what. Doing it in front of you is just...
Okay...
Then take this.
What' this?
There's a microphone inside that'll let me hear you.
But...
I'm worried about you.
Even if it's just for a little while,
I'd like you to have it on you.
This position is so embarrassing.
Are you going to cum?
That's fine. Cum.
I'm going to cum soon, too...
Shu-chan! I can't... anymore...
I'm still cumming!
Sir, would you like another coffee?
P-Pardon me.
I'll be on my way now.
I have this room reserved for the day,
so feel free to take it easy here.
H-Hey, you!
Shu-chan...
Haruka...
Shit! Her husband?
Shu-chan, I'm already...
I wanted you to stop this... this disgusting thing.
Shu-chan?
I wanna have sex.
Why are you so... How?
Shu-chan, wa-wait a minute!
I haven't washed it ye...
No!
Seriously, wait! Right now, my body is...
Haruka, you're turning me on!
There's another man's smell on you.
I can't take anymore! I can't!
Shu-chan, please be more gentle!
Shu-chan?
Oh no, i-it's rubbing!
It went in...
Just by putting it in, I...
You're moving already?
I can cum so easily now!
You're getting tighter! Does it really feel that good?
That's not... That's not...
It's okay. I feel good too!
Your pussy feels so good!
Wai...
– So good! It feels so good!!
– No! No!!
So good!
I'm sorry.
Haruka?
I'm sorry...
I'm the worst.
Seeing you get hurt made me feel good, but...
But now, I feel that for the first time in our
relationship, were really connected.
That's what I think.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
quality control: hyakupercent