Mamayu, you're amazing!
No, don't look.
You're so sexy.
Can I lick it?
No, you can't!
No, Hiroaki-san! You can't!
My producer's going to get mad at me.
Idols aren't allowed to do these kinds of lewd things!
That makes you a bad girl, then.
You're an idol, but you're getting so wet.
It's all your fault.
You're the one who put this dirty thing in front of me.
It's not my fault.
S-Sorry, Mamayu.
I promise I won't tell your producer,
so show me more of your lewd side.
Oh, you.
Hiroaki-san's dick is going inside me!
It's so...
No, I'm...
Mamayu, it feels so good!
I'm starting to feel good too!
My body feels so weak.
You're fucking my pussy so hard.
Your dick is hitting me so deep inside!
It feels good for me too, Mamayu! I love you!
Hiroaki-san... I'm gonna cum!
Together...
Mamayu, I'm gonna cum! You're the best!
Mamayu! Mamayu!
We had some great sex today too.
Has my technique gotten better?
Has it, Mamayu?
Mamayu?
Who the fuck's Mamayu?
I'm your wife Reiko, ya idiot!
Sure, I might look like her,
but why the hell have we been married for half a year,
but we've only had sex when I role-play as Mamayu?
I'm not Mamayu!
I know what to do.
I'll destroy all of your Mamayu goods.
I'm sorry! Please spare them!
No way!
She pisses me off! I'm a better woman than her too!
Come on!
Oh, right. Taniguchi, my friend from collage,
is coming over for a house warming.
What? You're telling me now??
Hey, Hiro. You home?
Wow, you're the spitting image of her.
Hiro likes to brag about you all the time when we drink.
He just keeps saying that he married Mamayu.
Hiro, how can you say such embarrassing things?
S-Sorry!
Now, now. The person most at fault is you.
Because you're too cute.
No, I'm...
Not to mention that you're even more glamorous than Mamayu.
I'll be blunt, I'd choose you any day over Mamayu.
Taniguchi-san...
Hey, stop hitting on my wife.
I'm not.
He's a lucky guy.
He was always so fixated on Mamayu,
and then suddenly, in his 30s, you appear.
Things seemed pretty grim for him.
This is what people call a miracle, don't you think?
Hiro is probably bursting from the seams with happiness.
But, I'm...
Hm?
You guys can't have sex unless you pretend to be Mamayu?
Shh!
Taniguchi-san, you're being too loud!
You're gonna wake him up!
Well, if that's the case,
there's a simple solution to all of this.
Huh? What would that be?
Okay, listen...
When you're with him, continue role-playing as Mamayu.
But for even hotter sex...
Taniguchi-san?
How'd you like to have some fun with me?
N-No...
T-Taniguchi-san...
T-Taniguchi-san?!
Just like I thought, you have a really sexy body.
No, stop. Don't do that.
No... Not there! You can't, Taniguchi-san!
Oh? You're from Kansai?
You're making me more and more turned on.
So, let's...
No!
What're you doin'?
How about you tell me what my hand is covered in?
Oh wow, you've gotten so wet.
No, no this can't be...
I can make you feel even better.
W-What?
Taniguchi-san we shouldn't be doin' anymo...
No...
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, this...
Hiro's gonna... Hiro's gonna...
Stop! Do ye even know what yer doin'?
If ye do this, you and Hiro...
You have quite the erotic pussy.
You're even more perverted than Mamayu, aren't you?
Don' say that!
If ye keep doin' it like that, I won' be able to hold my voice in.
Please... Please stop, Taniguchi-san!
Your pussy is already dripping wet.
W-What should I do? Hiro's gonna see!
Don't worry, he's not gonna wake up.
He's been like that for as long as I've known him.
B-But...
Look, your nipples are already rock hard.
You can't hold back anymore, can you?
Now, your pussy is...
mine for the taking!
No! Wha's wrong with me?
It feels so good!
It does, doesn't it?
My dick is the best dick for your pussy!
No! We shoul'nt be doin' this, but... it feels so good!
My dick feels better than Hiro's, doesn't it?
No... tha's not...
Taniguchi-sans dick is so thick, and so long. It's amazing!
It's hitting me in places Hiro never has!
Your dick feels so good!
Why is Hiro so obsessed with idols and Mamayu?
You're so much sexier than them.
I want to fuck you so hard!
Hey, Reiko.
From now on, we're friends with benefits.
I'll release all of your frustration with my dick!
It's so good! Your dick is so good!
I'll be your sex friend from now on!
Please make my pussy feel good
with your dick from now on!
Let's have Hiro hear what you said too.
Here we go!
Not like this!
Hiro... I'm going to be Taniguchi-san's sex friend from now on.
His dick is making my pussy so wet!
Sorry, Hiro. Looks like I'll be the one who satisfies Reiko.
It feels so good! Do whateva you wan' with my body!
Just make me cum!
Make me cum!
Cum, Reiko. Cum!
Cum right in front of Hiro!
Hiro, sorry...
Hiroaki-san, does my sailor uniform turn you on?
It does! It totally does, Mamayu!
I can't get enough of your sailor uniform Mamayu!
My producer's definitely gonna get mad at me for this.
I'll keep this a secret between the two of us,
so as long as no one finds out, we'll be fine!
I-It's a promise, ok?
I'd never do this with anyone else but you, Hiroaki-san.
Yeah, it's a promise.
Don't make those noises!
You're such a perverted idol.
You're already getting so wet!
No... don't tease me!
It's your fault that I got like this!
Yeah, I'll help you out.
My pussy's going to overflow because of your dick!
Mamayu, your pussy is so amazing!
It's so hot and it's sucking me in!
Hiroaki-san, what will you do if my producer has sex with me?
I'll never let that happen!
You're my wife!
I'm the only one who can have sex with you!
You're being so rough! My pussy's going to break!
I'll be back next week.
So until then, be sure to...
No! It feels so good! My pussy feels so good!
I'm yours and only yours, Hiroaki-san!
Mamayu, you're the best!
Mamayu! Mamayu!
Mamayu, your pussy is so great!
Go deeper! Push your dick all the way in!
Mamayu, if you get so tight, I'm gonna cum!
Cum! Cum with my pussy, Hiroaki-san!
Here I go! I'm gonna cum inside, Mamayu!
Mamayu! Mamayu!
I'll be sure to stack my frustration up until next week.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: bis
quality control: hyakupercent