My name is Tanabe Yuuka.
I’ve lived a satisfying life so far..
Blessed with friendship after the end my student life..
While small.. My husband managed a small business..
I lived a peaceful life, everyday..
I'm happy that my husband loves me..
I love my husband too..
Darling! You're hitting my deepest spot..
I'm coming!
No.. No more..
Let me come!
It's so deep in me..
Today, I'll be seeing my husband off..
Doing my daily housework..
Waiting for my husband's return..
Netorare, The monologue of Tanabe Yuuka.
Today, I thought would be peaceful like always..
Yes? Who is it?
Nooo!!
That was the sound of my daily life being shattered..
No, you can't!
Wait, stop!
At that time, I really hated it..
My body touched by a man other than my husband..
I thought I was betraying him..
As so, I couldn't forgive myself..
That’s what I thought..
However..
I found that stimulating experience which I've
sought from my husband many many nights..
My mind and body began to slowly
crumble from this new sensation..
I was feeling it greatly even though I knew it was wrong..
I remember it all vividly..
To that degree, the height of stimulation he gave me was..
Powerful and rhythmical..
It was waking up the sleeping woman within me..
My mind was blank-white..
It was my body yet not mine at the same time..
Somewhat dreamy.
However, it was that very dreamy sensation I craved..
When my senses came back..
I saw the confident towering figure of that man..
Take care..
While under the flowing water of the shower..
The events of that evening were
replaying in my mind like some movie..
Images in my mind joined together..
I started touching myself where he did..
It was an unconscious action..
That night I lost and fell..
I felt an unprecedented sense
of guilt when facing my husband.
The strange man played with
my feelings of joy and shame..
He dominated all my senses completely.
I didn't feel like doing housework.
I was dumbfounded, totally.
"Will that person come again?" I wondered.
And give me that unexpected sensation again..
I came to fantasize about these things..
And then.. That illusion became a reality..
Who is it?
I opened the door and instantly
took his hand as he stood there..
I invited him into the living room.
What I couldn't help but want..
Was now a reality in front of me..
I was highiy driven..
My confidence..
It bewildered even me, that it developed this much..
That thick and hard thing, rising before me..
It excited me..
Before I knew it I was already servicing him with my mouth..
Played the tip with my tongue..
Carefully handling it.
No matter what he released in my mouth or how often..
I made lewd sounds as I sucked it clean..
No one had forced me to..
This was what I had wanted..
Just the mere thought of having this inside me..
Made my spine tremble..
This did nothing to my confidence and..
I was unaware of the essence flowing out
from my depths, staining my underwear..
Then it happened suddenly..
His confidence just suddenly kept building up..
The Hot, rich fluid..
A lot of it spread into my mouth..
It kept pulsing, over and over..
I drank it clean till the last sweet drop..
The fluid slowly crawled down my throat as I swallowed..
I didn't want to let go of it..
Because, I thought if I satisfied him as a woman..
Then maybe..
I thought he would give me a reward..
My sense of guilt had already departes me..
And the new stimulus he would bring..
What will it be like?
I eagerly waited for it..
I had become a slave of pleasure..
No.. No..!
I'm coming!
Over and over again, he kept striking me deep..
This time my body turned numb..
In a sense.. It felt like I was floating..
My eyes were open to a new sensation..
I'm coming!
And thus..
I had reached an unprecedented peak..
Life with my husband slightly changed..
He took a little initiative pursuing pleasure..
I was entirely relieved being
embraced in the arms of my husband..
And so, that day I was embraced by two men..
Before going astray, I was satisfied with
my responsibilities to my husband.
I was careful..
Gently making the usual moans he was used to..
What would happen next..
I knew very well..
Until now it had been enough..
But, the me right now.. was unsatisfied..
Blessed with friendship after the end my student life..
While small.. My husband managed a small business..
I lived a peaceful life, everyday..
Take care!
I'm happy that my husband loves me..
I love my husband too..
It's in, coming so deep!
My relationship with that man continued as usual..
This rich level of brainwashing.. it was not my imagination..
Deeper.
Thrust more!
Not there!
I'm coming!
My name is Tanabe Yuuka.
I’ve lived a satisfying life so far..
Today, I'll be seeing my husband off..
Doing my daily housework..
Waiting for my husband's return..
I'm coming, coming again!
Then, I saw it..
The face he made watching my dirty pleasure..
My common everyday.. exists.. no more..