Oda Taibento operates the shopping square known as Toaru.
Because it's crowded and open at all hours,
Cam and Scott-senpai have teamed up to watch over the square.
Cam = Casting
Newmanoid Cam
Cam, hurry up.
Kay!
Jeez, this place is mobbed.
And what's more, I get the feeling the cameras
have been shooting just us for a while now.
Why is that?
Yes, well, you see...
It's because they all think you and I are Yuzetsu cosplayers.
"Yuzetsu"?
It's a popular series on TV right now.
Yuzu is kidnapped and is full of despair.
You're a character called "Kiryuu",
and I'm a character called "Asagi".
You see, Kiryuu and Asagi are lovers,
and they fight together against the
evil force that threatens the Earth!
I see.
So if we continue to pretend to be cosplayers,
we'll be less conspicuous as we investigate this place.
W-W-We're wearing disguises then!?
The basis of disguise is to blend in with ones environment
Then I'll blend in!
Bring the bed in, guys.
Okay, then... Cam?
Ah, Senpai!
Senpai!
Se-Senpai, are you lost?
lost
Lost
I-I'd better ask for help!
No, I mustn't.
If I do that, I wont be blending in.
Fear not, Senpai! Cam is presently a cosplayer.
In place of my lost Senpai, I'll pull off
our secret mission successfully!
Whoa, check that out.
It's Yuzetsu cosplay!
Yeah, that's the sexiest Asagi-tan costume I've ever seen!
Yeah, she's intense!
I believe we have a viable target friends.
Yes, Your Highness!
Hey, miss...
That's Asagi cosplay from Yuzetsu, right?
It's amazing! It's like you're the real Asagi-tan!
Ah! Really?
Hear that, Senpai? Cam is a perfect cosplayer right now!
Well then, Asagi-tan, strike a pose!
A pose?
Like this?
No, you need to look more like Asagi-tan!
Do you know anything about Asagi-tan!
Oh, dear! If I can't strike an authentic
Asagi pose, my cover will be blown!
Well, you see, this is actually my first time cosplaying.
Huh? Today is your cosplay debut?
An opportunity!
In that case, let me help you with your pose!
To commemorate your first day as a cosplayer,
we'll help you wit your Asagi-tan pose.
You really will?
Moe!
Wh-What are you doing?
That tickles.
What are we doing? We're helping
you with your character of course!
When Asagi-tan is attacked by monsters,
she's enveloped in beauty!
Is that so?
Urn, those are my boobs.
That's a great expression!
Is my reaction like a normal cosplayer?
Here's a way to make you look even more like a cosplayer.
My mind... is starting to go blank.
I'm starting to feel very naughty.
Cosplayers must be very naughty people.
Come now, Cam-chan.
Now it's time to be even more like Asagi-tan.
That tickles!
Very nice!
You're good at armpit jobs.
You might be the best cosplayer this square has ever seen!
Is that so?
So cosplayers also give armpit jobs?
This one too.
Wow, amazing.
Your cock is throbbing more, and if s hot.
My body is also getting warmer.
That won't do.
We must banish your fever at once!
You can make me grab your cock...
and you tan twirl my nipples with your cock..
There's no milk.
Cam-chan, pay more attention.
I'm gonna cum. Cam-chan, are you about to cum?
The cock milk has completely covered my body.
Good!
Now the real fun begins.
This is the best image-play of all! I'm putting it in!
I'm putting my monster dick inside of Cam-chan's pussy!
Huh? But that's...
This is Asagi-tan's big crisis!
You mustn't move or lose your glittering beauty,
if you want to keep looking like Asagi-tan!
Wow! Inside both my pussy and my butt.
Cosplay sure is amazing!
It feels so good!
I'm so full of cocks right now, I'm losing my mind!
My butt...
and my pussy...
Everything feels great.
Amazing! Your acting is perfect Cam-chan!
You're the perfect cosplayer!
That's right. I'm a cosplayer.
A naughty cosplayer.
Asagi-tan wouldn't give up at a time like this!
All the way down my throat..
That thick thing is all the way down my throat
Cam-chan, your cosplaying skills are so good,
that my dick has become this big.
I'm almost there.
Oh, almost.
I'm cumming!
Cumming!
A man's haughty juice... is inside Cam's mouth.
I'm full of cum.
Oh, Cam-chan, please take my cum too!
Okay.
Okay, next up, well make you look like a cosplayer like this!
I'm so flattered.
After all, this is my first time cosplaying.
I want... your cock.
Here I go!
Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
Wow! She's squeezing me tight!
If she squeezes me that tight,
I'll cum right away!
Inside of me. Please come inside of me.
Fill me full of cum. Drown my insides with your cum, please!
Amazing! I love cosplaying!
Cosplaying is so naughty, and I'm losing my mind.
I'm losing my mind!
Okay, I'm cumming! I'll fill your cosplaying body full of me!
I feel it throbbing and whirling inside of me.
Launching!
I feel it slowly flowing into me.
I'm so full of it!
My butthole and my pussy are being carved
into naughty shapes by your cocks.
It's making me so hot.
That's perfect for a cosplayer.
You want the inside and outside of your
body to look like the character.
Cam-chan, be sure to taste tons of our cum!
I will!
Please fill me up!
Fill me full of cum!
It's spilling all over the place.
Okay! For her final character building exercise,
lets blanket Cam-chan with cum!
I'm so full. I'm so full of cum.
Your cum is turning me all white.
You were really good, Cam-chan.
It gave us great motivation as the villains.
Now, give us a final smile.
What a relief.
Now, I won't hold back Senpai,
and our undercover mission will be a success.
Hey, Cam!
It looks like your partner has arrived.
Thanks for supporting our photography.
That girl was good.
She gave me my rape fix!
That's gonna keep me satisfied for half a year.
Thank you very much, rapists!
What's that fluid? Wh-What were you people doing?
We were just practicing being authentic cosplayers.
Thanks to that we were able to arrest the rapists
that had been threatening this convention.