Night Shift Nurses
Episode 6
T-this is...
Well, if it isn't Naoya.
He was waiting anxiously for
you right here, for a long time.
Did you forget him already?
That's awful... You tricked me.
That's an awfully rude thing to say.
It was your own fault for
making false assumptions!
I'm going home.
You didn't think I'd let you go,
did you?
How naive can you get, Nanase?
Stop it!
Sorry, but I can't do that!
No! Stop! Please stop!
Let me go! It hurts!
How can it hurt?
It's supposed to feel good!
It just feels gross!
You shouldn't lie!
You'll learn that soon enough.
Stop!
Don't... Stop!
How's that? What's this sound?
Please stop! I beg you!
Does this mean
you're starting to enjoy this?
That's not true!
Well then, it's time for your check up.
We're finally prepped, Ren.
We have this room set up so that
Naoya, too, can observe your physical.
Stop! Stop it! No! No!
Don't! Please stop!
Will you hold still!
Ren, it seems as though your
mind and body aren't in balance.
This is a secretion released
to help lubricate your pussy when...
you are accepting a man's penis.
It isn't easily secreted.
If that's the case, it means
that you want my cock!
You want me to stuff this
deep inside you, don't you?
You're wrong.
I am? Then whose do you want?
Naoya's?
You want Naoya's penis
inside of you, is that it?
That's not true...
What? I'm wrong again!
Then that means...
Dr. Hirasaka... please! I can't...
I got it! If you ask me
like that, how can I refuse?
You look as though
you weren't expecting this.
Just as I had surmised before,
you seem to like it in the ass.
But before I can grant your wish,
we have to flush you out.
No! Stop!
You don't want me to stop. You do it
for your patients all the time.
You would never do
something to someone else...
that you yourself weren't
willing to do... Right, Ren?
Stop! Please stop it! Stop!
Take it out! Take it out, please...
My stomach hurts... take it out...
It hurts... please take it out...
I took it out, as you wished.
Now that's amazing!
Looks like your other
hole wants something too.
What are you...
Well, this mouth is drooling
with hunger, so I'm going to feed it!
But that's impossible!
What a waste!
No! No!
It's not going in because
there seems to be a psychological...
block against
inserting foreign material.
So we'll just have to make
it easier for things to go in.
We'll insert this to ease that!
Now, here we go!
Don't!
It's primitive, but it'll work.
An expansion machine just for you!
Don't worry, there's no danger!
Probably...
Doctor... please... stop...
It hurts...
Keep going and let your bowels
explode right in front of Naoya!
No!
What are you doing?
If you empty out your shit,
you'll have more space!
I'm going to... explode.
Please... stop...
Then let it out!
No...
You can only do it
in front of the real Naoya?
No...
Oh, I get it now! You like to
hold back and twist your face up.
It makes you feel good!
Isn't that right, Nanase?
That's looking good.
Naoya's happy too! Look!
Will you shut up? I have to insert
these eggs, and I need silence!
See, now the mouth is opened wide.
Don't worry about salmonella.
I made sure to disinfect the eggs.
It won't fit anymore...
Yeah, you're right.
But this side is completely empty!
Okay, here we go!
Ah, now this is great! The walls
are tight and I can feel the egg bumps!
It hurts...
It hurts! It's twisting! No! Stop!
If you thrust too hard,
the eggs are going to break!
That's a good point, Ren.
Right now we're experimenting if
the eggs will break in this position.
No! I don't want that!
Stop, stop!
It hurts...
It hurts! The eggs! The eggs!
The shells are broken!
- Don't lie! It'll be fine! Here we go!
- It hurts! It hurts!
Stop!
Incredible!
Oh, so they really are broken!
This isn't good.
I guess we shouldn't
use raw eggs from now on.
I'm glad you decided to tell us
the story, but it's hard to believe...
The motive seems to be pretty obvious.
It's a simple grudge case.
Is that all...
That's just the kind of thing
a woman will do.
Ah, wait a minute!
Ren... about earlier...
Don't say it...
I really... you... No matter what,
I won't give up on you. So just...
Naoya!
I don't have the right
to go out with you anymore.
I'm tainted both in body and soul.
I want you to forget about me.
Don't say that!
Stop annoying her, Naoya Ohkawa!
Ms. Nanase is letting you go
by her own free will! Don't you get it?
That's bullshit! Get what?
It's your fault that Ren... Ren is...
I have nothing to do with it.
Ren made up her own mind.
You sick pervert...
Oh, you're going to punch
an untrained civilian again?
This time I'll make sure you
go to jail for assault and battery!
Wait! Don't do anything stupid!
Ren...
You might someday become
the next world champion.
Don't get your fists dirty
by hitting that thing.
"That thing?"
Naoya,
don't get involved with me anymore.
She dumped you.
Shut up!
I'll let you go today for Ren's sake.
Can you beat me
while in this feeble condition?
Instead, next time, why don't we have
a fair match with Ren as the prize.
I'll take you on any time!
Ordinarily, my experiment
would take ten years.
To complete it in a short time,
I'm going to need your help, Ren.
I don't think... I can...
At least one... No, two more
should fit! You're going to help.
I-it hurts... My stomach...
is going to explode...
That's not going to happen!
Look at all the pregnant women!
You don't see them exploding!
It hurts.
My stomach hurts. Please stop.
Be quiet! Shut up and deal with it!
What the hell are you doing?
You can hold it for Naoya, but
you can't hold it for me, is that it?
We're trying to measure for distance,
so quit jumping the gun, idiot!
Distance?
That's right! We're measuring
how far your shit will go!
I don't... want to do that! I can't!
Don't give me that look!
You've done it countless times,
and suddenly now you can't do it?
Up until now, you couldn't wait
to spray! Don't think so much about it!
Your body is saying you want to!
Just let it happen naturally!
T-That's not true...
Of course it is! Come here!
All living things have to shit.
It's a biological fact, Ren!
Don't...
This is amazing!
I never thought it could fly this far!
That's almost a full
two and a half meters!
Well, we'll call it a day...
The smell will bother the patients,
so make sure to clean this up.
I'm going to kill myself!
You idiot! Dumb ass!
What will killing yourself solve?
Suicide in a hospital?
You should be ashamed of yourself!
That's not why I'm doing it.
It's Naoya, then!
What the hell did Naoya do for you?
All he did was pamper you!
Don't say bad things about Naoya...
I'll just say this.
The one that needs you right now is me!
That's my girl. I need you too, Ren.
Don't think of doing something
so stupid! Take care of the rest. Okay?
Yes sir...
Then, good night. Sleep well and
have a nice wet dream about me!
Thank you very much.
Take care of yourself.
Doesn't this room smell a little odd?
What's the matter, Ms. Nanase?
Sorry, Akiko.
I must have had garlic for lunch.
Please don't eat or
drink in the examination room.
Maybe someone had anal leakage, huh?
There's no way that could happen!
I guess you're right! Sorry!
Who the hell would believe
this kind of twisted story?
You're trying to lighten your crime
by painting the victim as a pervert!
That's not true...
Then why didn't you tell the police
before you killed Ryuji Hirasaka?
Wait, take it easy on her.
Please continue with your story.
You should have
done a better job cleaning up!
If this gets out, you and I are fired.
The hospital's reputation
will be ruined...
and the staff and patients
will all have to go somewhere else.
Do you understand?
I understand...
Do you really understand?
Yes...
As long as you understand.
Now, Ren, go and wipe those tears.
You may think of me as a terrible man.
But I want to know everything
about you, and accept you.
I don't want you
to have to hide anything from me.
I want you to be your true self.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
Ren... where are you
taking me at a time like this?
What is it, Ren?
We've been waiting for you, Naoya.
Ren! What the hell is going on here?
Did you forget already? We are here
to have a fair match for Ren.
You said you'd accept anytime.
Yeah, I did say that!
So let's go and do that right now.
W-what are you doing, Ren?
Stop! Stop it!
Hold still.
Ren! What's the meaning of this?
I could never win in power against you.
So, this is a match to see
which of us can satisfy Ren.
What?
The loser walks away from Ren.
That will decide things, right?
Satisfy Ren...? What do you mean?
Do I have to explain everything to you?
Naoya... hold me...
Well, with a flaccid dick like that,
it's no contest. Ren, get him hard.
Stop it, Ren!
You don't have to listen to this guy!
What's the matter, Naoya?
You've never held Ren before, right?
If you're a man, get that
flaccid dick hard and be happy!
Shut up, pervert!
Ren, you're being forced to do this!
This isn't the real you!
You're the one forcing your illusions
onto her! This is what Ren wants!
Naoya! Watch carefully! This is
the real Ren that you don't know!
I love to get fucked
while someone watches...
I get turned on by shit trickling
from me... Can you love a slut like me?
O-of course.
Let's get started.
Yes, doctor.
W-what are you...
We're seeing how real
your love is. Now, Ren!
I'm putting it in!
Now, show her that you're a man, Naoya!
Really suck on him hard, Ren!
I can't get hard.
It's no good, Ren! Let it out!
Yes sir...
Now, Naoya! Eat some
of Ren's home cooking!
Fuck that! Don't assume
I'm a sick pervert like you!
How can you say you love her if
you can't even eat her poop?
How dare you say you love her!
Fuck!
You wimp!
You're nothing. You're all talk
when you say you love Ren!
Don't make me laugh!
Watch carefully! This is true love!
Doctor, it feels so good!
Yes! I'm cumming! Yes, yes!
I...
Whether this is true or not,
your statement is that you...
went through Ryuji Hirasaka's
torture and then you killed him!
Torture... hate...
If what you say is true,
then it's definitely a felony...
That's not it... No... You're wrong!
That's not it at all. I definitely
loved the doctor... Ryuji Hirasaka!