Look.
- Will you look at that?
- They've got the nerve.
What are they trying to pull off?
Stop the idle chat and listen.
NIGHT SHIFT NURSES
KRANKE #2, AI KODAMA
Don't get fresh with me.
What's with the attitude?
Don't touch me,
you pervert.
You're putting me down?
You fool!
Ouch.
What do you think you're doing?
This is what I'm doing.
It's too big.
You're so kinky.
We can't do this here.
No sense in being shy.
We're getting married.
You've got to be kidding.
I said that in the heat of the moment.
I can't believe you actually believed it.
What?
You mean to tell me...
Ouch!
...you were lying to me?
Huh?
No. Not in public.
I hate being lied to.
Have I ever lied to you?
Well?
You're foolish!
I've done some bad things,
but I never lied.
Do you see my point?
I want to be with you.
As long as you understand my feelings.
Now be quiet.
Suck me hard.
We're getting married.
We can fuck all we want
and nobody can say anything.
Doctor...
stick it in my pussy.
This is the perfect position
for an unruly girl like you, Hikaru.
I might fall.
I love it.
This reminds me
of when we first met, Hikaru.
I'm already
going to cum.
Somebody will find us
if you make so much noise.
You resist in the beginning,
but you always give in.
You're the kind of girl
that gets turned on by this.
And you know it.
You're just as perverted!
Yes. I'm a pervert.
Who's going to marry
a pervert like you?
Who would do this for you?
Only you, Doctor.
Let me ask you this:
what do you think of me?
You're a pervert.
What?
But I love you.
I'm in love with you.
Now that's the right attitude.
Doctor, I'm cumming.
Oh, no.
Somebody's really coming.
Hurry!
Shoot your hot load on me!
I'm cumming, baby.
I'm going to shoot my jizz.
Cum with me!
Your cum is so warm.
Runa.
Doctor, what are you doing here?
Uh, I was looking for medicinal herbs.
Medicinal herbs?
Yes.
We practice Western medicine.
But nature's medicines
are kindest to our bodies.
And our patients are delicate ladies.
Doctor, I love you.
Is this all the laundry?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
You don't feel good?
No. I'm fine.
Let me check.
Oh, you're fine.
But call the doctor if you feel sick.
Yeah.
Ai, I'm going home.
Relax and stay in bed.
Shall I close the curtains?
No, it's alright.
Hikaru...
Yes?
- Congratulations.
- What?
Your marriage to Doctor Hirasaka.
Marriage?
What made you think of that?
I realized I hadn't said it.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
- Well, bye.
- Yeah.
Hikaru.
Hikaru, you're not fair.
Everybody likes you,
and you're even getting married.
I'm envious of you.
Everybody loves you.
An operation?
This is a critical moment for Ai.
But she is still strong
so we have a chance.
Will she get better?
The prognosis is not good.
But it is better than doing nothing.
But, you know, there are risks involved.
Yes.
Think about it carefully,
then decide.
I understand.
Hikaru?
What?
Are you hiding something from me?
"Hiding something"?
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are.
Whenever you're solemn,
you're hiding something.
You have to confess.
Ai.
Is that all you were worried about?
Do you know how risky
this operation is?
You should be worried about other things.
What?
I know I don't have long to live.
Ai!
But I don't want to die like this.
I was born as a woman.
Ai.
I want to be a woman.
Hikaru.
It's complete.
A new tool for your experiments?
It's a new toy.
Let's try it out.
Do you like it?
I'm so turned on.
Good.
Now this side too.
Your ass will like it too.
The vibration varies so it won't get boring.
I can feel the head in my pussy
vibrating against the head in my ass.
Exactly as I had calculated.
Doctor, I'm going to cum!
I'll fill your pussy with my hot jizz.
I'm going to shoot.
Cum for me, Doctor.
I can use this on two women
at the same time.
I didn't know Ai was thinking about sex.
I thought I knew everything about her.
Of course,
she's not a kid anymore.
It's only natural that she is curious.
But what am I to do?
Maybe I'll consult the Doctor.
I didn't come here for this!
What are you talking about?
We're getting married, right?
You said you love me.
I did.
But today...
Whatever.
Let's get started.
It's nice and tight.
I'm glad I made it thick.
I'm going to make you cum.
How does it feel?
It feels so good.
Its going to get even better.
The amount of enema
is still an approximation.
I will gauge your reaction
to determine the best dosage.
Doctor.
Doctor Hhasaka?
What is it?
Please open the door.
A patient is in critical condition.
What?
Please tend to this
until the doctor-in-charge arrives.
But I am occupied.
But you're on the night shift.
Hurry!
Doctor?
Doctor, where are you?
Doctor!
I'm uncomfortable.
My stomach is filling up.
But it feels good.
It hurts so good.
I could share this with Ai.
But this is too much for Ai.
Poor innocent Ai.
Oh, yeah.
But she can't.
Am I being unfair?
I have to pooh.
My stomach's full.
Doctor, I can't take much more.
I can't hold it.
I'm going to pooh.
This feels so good.
It's going to squirt out.
Poor Ai... this feels good...
I can't hold it...
I'm getting delirious.
It's coming out.
It's coming out, out, out!
This is heaven.
When I get married,
I get to do this every day.
But, what about Ai?
Quiet.
You're too loud.
Stop it.
Let go, you pervert.
You're worried about Ai.
Huh?
You feel guilty that you're
the only one that's happy.
How can you tell?
I told you.
We're getting married.
Understanding my future wife
is my responsibility.
What do you think?
It's easy.
It is?
Is it fair for you to monopolize
all that pleasure?
If you're really concerned about Ai,
you should grant her wishes.
That's what real best friends do.
"Real best friends".
Thank you, Doctor.
AI KODAMA
Do your nipples feel good?
Yeah.
I'm so shy.
Just follow my lead.
Spread your legs.
Your pussy is so pretty.
I want to see yours.
So this is what your pussy looks like.
Are they alike?
Do our pussies look alike?
Yes.
That's because we're best friends.
Your clit looks like mine too.
That's so hot.
Lick my pussy too.
You bet.
Lick inside my hole.
Like this?
Yes. You're good.
You're dripping.
Drink it.
I Will.
It tastes so good.
Your pussy juice tastes so good.
Ai's pussy is delicious too.
Doctor.
Continue.
But...
I said continue.
Hikaru.
Ai, you too.
Relax.
You'll like it.
Go ahead.
Look at it.
It's awesome.
We're connected.
Yes.
One vibrator makes
your hearts and bodies as one.
This is real love.
Now, suck my cock.
Look at Hikaru's ecstatic face.
Let me try, Doctor.
Of course, you may.
Now take turns.
Hikaru,
I'm getting tingly all over.
I think I'm going to cum.
Am I going to cum?
I'm kind of scared.
Don't be scared.
I'm cumming too.
We'll cum together.
Did you enjoy it?
Thank you, Hikaru...
and Dr. Hirasaka.
If this is a dream,
I never want to wake up.
Ai!
Oh, no.
A seizure!
OPERATING
Next patient,
right this way.
My being the only happy one...
is unfair.
Your condition has improved.
We owe it to Hikaru's nursing.
Don't mention it.
Now, you can marry Dr. Hirasaka
without any worries.
When is the wedding?
We're not having a wedding.
Oh, just a reception?
No.
I'm not getting married.
- What?
- Huh?
How do you feel?
I'm fine now.
I had a funny dream.
Tell me.
It was awesome.
You and Dr. Hirasaka
were in it.
And the three of us...
I'm too embarrassed to say.