I can't hold it! I'm going to pee!
NIGHT SHIFT NURSES
HIKARU KODAMA
This thickness
only achieves the same timing
results as Hikaru Test Number 5.
Do you understand the implications, Hikaru?
Why don't you think before you answer?
It concerns yourself!
Doctor, stop it.
You have no patience.
It's your own body.
Why can't you hold it longer?
You pee every time.
I'm trying to achieve new
heights. How dare you drop it!
Hey, is that Ai?
What? What's the matter?
What a fortuitous event.
This is the first time I've seen your puke.
How could you!
It's because you don't listen.
That's enough for today.
You should open your asshole
more than your mouth.
Next time, your ass...
Don't bring up Ai's name
at a time like this!
Damn you!
Who do you think you are?
You're afraid of your little
sister hearing rumors!
Of her finding out that
you love bondage and dildos!
Am I right?
Doctor.
Ren, I need a favor.
Yes, Doctor. What do you want?
Go to the incinerator tomorrow and
get something before it's burned.
The incinerator?
Yeah.
Al KODAMA.
You mean that?
Quite an improvement. A miracle.
Ai, that's great!
Yes.
It's been a while.
What?
To go for a walk with my sister.
You're right.
I'm finished for the day
so I can be with you.
Really?
Yeah.
You're going to be tired.
You should go home and rest.
I'll be alright.
Don't worry, I'm young!
What are you talking about? I'm younger.
Oh, yeah.
Something smells.
Yeah, what's that?
Look at that.
Sister? Sister?
Hey, sister!
What?
Is it that smell?
Probably. I guess I'll clean it up.
Sister's got a tough job.
I'm done.
Are you sure? You'll get hungry tonight.
I'm full. Please finish it if you'd like.
No. Take another bite.
Open your mouth.
Come in.
Hi. How do you feel?
Hey, be careful.
You spilled the patient's soup.
I'm sorry.
I'm alright. Hikaru, is something wrong?
No. I just slipped.
It's as if...
you're cleaning your own waste.
Dr. Hirasaka, what do you want?
Oh yes, I forgot to introduce myself.
I personally supervise Hikaru
so that she can become a great nurse.
I'm Hirasaka, gynecologist.
I heard your condition
improved and wanted to say hello.
How do you do? I'm Ai,
Hikaru's younger sister.
Let's see.
Your pulse is good...
Hikaru.
She is not your responsibility.
Don't touch her.
What an introduction.
You two don't look alike.
What's that got to do with it?
Get out of here!
Hikaru, that's rude.
He needs to be told like this.
People have always said
we don't look alike.
Ls that so?
Do you think Hikaru
will become a good nurse?
Ai, stay out of it.
Be quiet.
This is a hospital.
Hikaru is remarkable.
Oh?
We found soiled sheets in the garden.
Hikaru picked it up and threw it away.
I would have ignored it.
That's commendable.
I'm sure your sister
will become a good nurse.
I look forward to it.
I didn't mean to intrude.
Ai, get well quick.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
What's the commotion?
It's open.
Oh, it's Hikaru.
Damn you.
You animal!
Die!
What are you doing?
You can...
you can go to hell!
Watch it! Stop it!
When I say, "stop it", have you ever...
stopped for me?
Stay away from Ai!
What's wrong with my seeing Ai?
What you're doing is harassment.
Harassment?
That's right.
Saying we don't look alike.
Making sure she saw those sheets.
You're not alike.
You are not related.
Don't say that!
You fool!
If that's what you want,
why don't you kill me?
You might feel better,
but what about Ai?
We can't keep the sister
of a murderer in this hospital.
Do you get it, stupid little nurse?
I know nothing about the sheets.
You carelessly threw it away.
The wind must have blown it.
Don't blame it on me.
No way was it the wind!
Shut up! Come.
No!
She's so cute.
Stop it. Stay away. You'll wake her up.
Her medicine keeps her in a deep sleep.
She won't wake up.
Stop it.
We'll experiment here.
No! Any place but here!
Be quiet, fool.
The experiment has already started.
What are you going to do?
Not much.
Let's see how you express
your orgasm without making any noise.
Don't raise your voice.
No! Not here!
Don't make a commotion!
No! Stop!
You say no, but your body says yes.
Do you know why?
You're heavy. Get off.
Ouch! I don't know why.
Then I'll tell you.
You're a natural born pervert.
Stop joking. I'm not like you.
Stop kidding yourself.
Your body is more truthful than your mind.
No.
See? You're wet.
This is your answer.
Your nipples are erect.
Aren't they usually inverted?
They are.
It hurts. It hurts.
Stop being childish.
Get up!
Put your hands there.
No. No.
Stop it.
This position is embarrassing.
But I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum, cum, cum.
Good. That's wet enough.
Now to Experiment Stage 2.
You're still not finished?
"Not finished"?
Fool, you must be tenacious.
I've said this before,
you should open your ass more.
You already forgot?
I'll do whatever you say.
But any place but here.
I beg you.
If you'll do whatever I say,
then don't tell me where!
Shut up,
and do as I say.
HONEY
Here it comes.
No.
Be quiet.
I'm using honey to be thoughtful.
Be grateful, you spoiled brat.
Thank you.
Oh?
You're welcome!
It hurts!
The asshole is where
I can measure body temperature.
Your body is stiff for your age.
Loosen up.
It hurts. It hurts.
Don't move around.
I said loosen up.
I can't stay standing.
Don't disobey.
Keep walking.
Go.
There. You're ass is stretching out.
Let's stop.
No. I'll stretch your asshole more.
Another experiment is
going to stuff even more.
I don't want to do that.
Stop sniveling, you stupid nurse.
This is great.
Like loosing your virginity again.
We're coming to the finale.
Show her.
Show your precious sister.
Show her this scene.
No. No. No.
I'm going to come.
Cum. Doctor, cum with me.
Hikaru...
Dr. Hirasaka...
How pretty!
Did you grow them?
Not all of them.
But it makes me happy that you like them.
Hikaru, don't you think they're pretty?
Yes.
Here, have one.
Decorate your room with it.
It's so cute. Thank you.
Look, Hikaru.
We're going.
I'll come again.
Sure, take care.
Hikaru, what's the matter?
Nothing at all.
I'm always peppy.
Hikaru...
Dr. Hirasaka...
Was that a dream?
Or was it...
This is...
The doctor's cock was in Hikaru's pussy.
Hikaru...
My stomach hurts.
This is a two stage experiment.
It might win the Nobel Prize.
HONEY
You're not using an egg today?
You've had enough eggs up your ass.
I learned the last time that honey works.
What's that?
Honey alone tastes boring,
so I'm going to use a lot of yogurt.
My ass...
isn't a blender.
Hey, that's funny.
I can't take any more.
I'm at my limit!
Well...
let's finish using Hikaru's blender.
Oh, what smooth penetration.
This is wonderful!
I'm going to...
gush out my ass!
Hold it as long as you can.
Isn't this also good for your skin?
No. I can't hold it.
What can't you hold?
My shit will come out.
Just shit?
The honey and yogurt will all come out!
Hold it a little longer. I'm cumming soon.
No. I have to shit!
I'm going to shoot!
No, no, no! Pull it out!
Got to catch it.
Hold it firmly.
Swallow it.
This is the important second stage.
Can people eat honey yogurt
that came out of their ass?
We must confront this huge question!
Swallow it!
It should have plenty of flavor!
Wow, that's good!
Good. How was it?
Not as bad as I thought.
That's good.
Doctor, I feel sick.
Incredible!
What a philosophical spectacle!
You did really good.
You're remarkable.
Doctor...
Al KODAMA.
You're in a good mood.
Really? I'm the same person.
Hikaru.
What?
What were you doing
with Dr. Hirasaka in this room?
What are you talking about?
You were having weird dreams.
I thought is was a dream.
But was it?
You're not a liar, so I can tell.
It's alright if it's true.
You're bright and
cheerful and everybody likes you.
Ai...
So it's alright.
If you love him, it's alright.
Hi, Ai.
You look well today.
Dr. Hirasaka.
Doctor, can I ask you something?
Sure. What is it?
Do you and Hikaru...
Listen!
I'm...
I'm going to...
get married...
with Dr. Hirasaka!
What?
Kodama-san, Doctor's making rounds.
Everybody please listen.
I'm marrying Dr. Hirasaka!
Hikaru...!