I just got a little curious. That was all.
Night Shift Nurses
Karte 10.5
Ok, I'm going to start!
No! No!
This is a simple, yet effective,
air expanding machine,
so it's ok, it's not dangerous at all.
Probably...
Doctor, can you stop please...?
This is embarrassing!
What are you doing?
If you'd let all your shit out it might
be a lot less uncomfortable.
It's going to rip...
it's going to rip open.
Please stop...
Then hurry and let everything out.
No!
Now I see! I understand now...
You keep holding it in because
it feels so good...
That's how Ren Nanase is...
just as I thought.
It must feel good.
No...
This is amazing!
I never knew it could fly this far!
It's almost time to start.
Yes, Doctor.
It's going in.
Keep your eyes open.
This is what true love is!
It hurts!
I'm coming! The eggs... The
shells are... breaking...
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't say anymore. It's ok.
I'm coming!
It hurts! It hurts!
You fucking idiot!
You're a dog, dogs don't
do the breaststroke!
You must do the doggy paddle! Get
it together you damn imbecile!
Woof...
It hurts!
Sensei, please stop it
already, stop it please!
You're telling me to stop while
moving your hips yourself?
You're telling me to stop
while feeling pleasure?
Well then shall we leave it
at that for today, then?
Well then?
No, more!
No not over there, over there isn't good!
Oh no! Oh no! Stop it! Don't!
What isn't good?
It stings! It stings! My vagina... no!
please stop it! Stop it!
No... don't do it! It'll
swell up! It'll all swell up!
Oh no! Oh no!
Let's go!
No! No! No! Nooo!
Don't cum in me!
NOOOoooo!
I found out that Sensei was doing the same
things he was doing to me to other people.
But... the thing that
really hit me was that...
he was doing it with
Chief Shinjyo for this long.
It hurts... It really hurts! My body's
going to be cut to pieces!
Please let me down! Please!
Shut the hell up!
Chew on this and bear it! BEAR IT!
Eat it!
It hurts!
How's that?
Well, how is it now? You like it don't you?
It hurts! Please let me down!
Stop fibbing...
You know you really like it!
It hurts!
Look at you piss! It's so good you
can't even hold it back can you?
Stop it! Please don't do it, it hurts!
What are you talking about?
You just came didn't you?
You liked it didn't you?
My body... My body's going to fall apart!
It hurts!
What a spoiled wretch of a woman!
You just want to take all the pleasure
for yourself and give none back!
Your father may be a big shot, but that's
no reason to be so impudent!
You really want to cum again,
don't you bitch!?
I think I'm about to cum...
Me too... I'm going to cum too..!
I'm going to cum I'm going
to cum! I'm coming!!
Alright!
No!! Stop it! Stop it!
It hurts... It hurts!!
Stop it please... stop it Hirasaka-kun!!
I'll do whatever you say so just...
Of course you will!
You will because you agreed to
participate in my experiment of course!
And this is my experiment!
While we're conducting this experiment
you'll do whatever I say!
That's ridiculous!
Shut it! Keep quiet and cooperate in
my experiment as you promised!
Stop it, it hurts!
It feels like it's
going to split open!
It may hurt or it may split open...
but that won't change the fact
that a promise is a promise!
All you need to think about
is fulfilling that promise!
It hurts!
I think it's about time I came!
No Stop it! Stop messing around!
Shut your face!
Oh, you had this much elasticity
after all eh? I had no idea...
An experiment should be frightening!
This is rather amusing isn't it? It's
almost like I'm milking a cow!
That should have made it a lot softer.
Ow!
Relax your muscle! Relax it!!
I told you to fucking relax
your muscle dammit!
Chief Jinguji!
I thought I finally knew why he
was being friendly with me...
No! Don't move it around!
No! It'll come out... It's coming out!
I guess we'll leave it at that for today.
This time we'll be using the special
chocolate egg which I developed myself!
I'm going to insert this in the front way.
We'll start with the first one.
It's gonna come out...
I thought you had become more docile,
but it appears you're still rather willful.
It's no good, you can't fit anymore in!
Hey now, we can't be forgetting the most
fundamental instrument can we?
I didn't forget... but...
we can't do it here!
As long as you're
well prepared...
you can easily lay eggs
even in a place such as this!
Ahh... I'm gonna cum... my front
and my back's gonna cum...
Ah my stomach hurts... The eggs are gonna
break... Ah, I'm gonna let loose...
Shut it! Someone might come in here!
That's good... you've got the
hang of it now, don't you?
When you do this yourself, don't forget
that this will make you leak faster!
Let's go! Let's go! Lets go! Let's go!
Sensei! It's gonna come out!
Hikaru, what are you up to?
Hurry up and come in here!
I don't want to! Open air bathing
is too embarrassing!
You fool! What crap are you talking
after coming all this way?
So you can do it in the train
but not in the open bath?
That's pretty contradictory.
It doesn't even make sense!
Hurry up and get the hell in here!
Eh? But...
Don't give me that crap!
Just come in dressed like that!
Idiot!
What's your problem? You don't
have to yell at me you know!
Sorry about that.
What the hell are you doing?!
Shut your mouth!
Stop with the violence already!
Just shut it! All you need
to do is follow my orders!
I'm going home!
Hey... what are you talking about... wait!
What? You still aren't satisfied?
No, I'm not. I need you Hikaru!
Don't!
Do it whenever, wherever,
in whatever situation.
That's my policy.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
That's good Hikaru. You're getting
better and better, aren't you?
Ah! If you pull that it'll let it all out!
It's alright, you already let out
a load in the train, didn't you?
Are you saying there's still more left?
There is! Don't do it, don't do it!
I see,
we've come all this way to the open baths
after all, we can't shit it all up can we?
So instead we'll have to play "Hot Spring
Eggs" so hang in there Hikaru!
What's the point in
coming to the hot spring
spring if you're going
to do that? Stop it!
Relax your anus!
If I relax then they'll all come out!
Where's your fighting spirit Hikaru?
Ahh no good no good... they're
gonna come out!
No they won't, because I'm going
to plug them up now!
Oh no! It's slipping! It feels so goood...
Oh no... my stomach hurts... it
hurts... but it feels gooood...
Don't! Don't take it out!
This time I'll do the front!
Maintain the pressure on your asshole.
Oh no!! They're slipping!
Senseiiii!
I'm gonna cum, Hikaru!
Me too! I'm gonna cum
too! Cum inside of me!
It's gonna come out!
It all came out!
You really did well.
It makes me really happy when
you praise me Sensei.
Oh... one came out without breaking.
I think I'll eat it.
Oh! This is quite scrumptious indeed!
There are some things in this world that
you're better off not knowing about.
This is definitely one of them.
I'm in love with Hirasaka-sensei.
My body and my heart are
both maintained by him.
And they will be...
always.