Congratulations!
This is wonderful!
Beautiful!
NIGHT SHIFT NURSES
KRANKE, REN NANASE
RYUJI AND REN HIRASAKA
Good morning, Ryuji.
Where have you been?
Oh.
I'll see you later.
Darling, breakfast will be ready.
The economy is looking upbeat.
Hmmmmm.
Ouch!
That's bad manners.
Please eat properly.
Uh, yeah.
What are you doing today?
As planned: examinations in the morning,
house calls in the afternoon.
After that, an overnight conference trip.
You'll need a taxi
to get to the train station.
Off we go.
- Here we go!
- Weeee!
- This feels great!
- Yeah.
Hello.
- Good morning.
HIRASAKA MEDICAL CLINIC
GYNECOLOGY,
INTERNAL MEDICINE...
Hey!
Watch it!
Alright.
Thank you for your patience.
Good morning.
Please watch your step.
- Like I said...
- What?
Say ahhhh.
- Ahhhh.
NO EXAMINATIONS
THIS AFTERNOON
Say ahhhh.
Ahhhh.
There. Is it good?
Huh? Yes.
Oh?
Why, all of a sudden?
After lunch I want to experiment.
Alright.
I've developed a new drug.
A drug?
That's the drug?
Yes.
It's special.
Yeah.
You're turning me on.
What are you talking about?
This is an experiment.
Be serious.
Yes.
What does this drug do?
It's supposed to radically accelerate
a women's pheromone secretion.
That's why we have
to rub a lot on your pussy.
Darling.
Yes?
Stick it in.
INITIAL EXAMINATIONS
NO EXAMINATIONS
THIS AFTERNOON
Breath in deep.
Have some tea.
Please eat.
BUS STOP
TO TOWN
The weather report is unreliable.
They should be made responsible
for what they report.
If this was from a doctor,
it would be a daily misdiagnosis.
What's wrong?
My body feels ﬂush.
The drug may be taking effect.
And...
my stomach is starting to ache.
That's not good.
Come here.
Does this feel better?
Yes, but I feel so hot inside.
What's happening to me?
What?
I need your fat cock.
Doesn't your stomach hurt?
Yes it hurts.
But I have to suck your big thick dick.
I need to fuck.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming too!
Let's cum together.
Ouch!
Is it aching again?
Yes.
Let's hurry.
It hurts.
I have to pooh.
Then do it in the bushes.
I won't do that.
That's stupid.
Holding it in is bad for you.
- Yes, but...
- I know a good place.
It's coming out!
What do you think you're doing?
This is your personal toilet.
Take a look.
Look at this magnificent toilet.
This is no time to be joking!
I'm not joking.
Let it all out here.
I can't.
I'm concerned about your health.
I have to force your excretion.
I'll pump your ass.
Deeper.
This will take care of it.
I have to pooh.
I can't hold it.
This is ecstasy.
I can't hold it!
It's coming out.
I'm going to pooh!
My stomach is so full.
I can't hold it.
Pull your cock out.
Pull it out.
We're husband and wife.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Darling.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
You should of listened
to me in the first place.
Yes.
So the experiment was a success.
This was a success?
Yes.
There was a scatological side effect,
but your horniness
was your pheromones gone wild.
It was far more effective than anticipated.
I am so happy to be of use.
Huh?
Ifs that fish.
I call him Ryuji.
The same name as mine?
Isn't he cute?
That's silly.
Ryuji.
See. He knows his name.
It's just expecting to be fed.
- Oh, no.
- What?
He's eating it.
It's your poop. It must be tasty.
Let me see.
This is pretty good.
Don't do that.
Ryuji, stop it.
Stop it.
Ewe.
Ewe!
Unbelievable.
The fish are getting horny
by eating the pheromones in Ren's poop.
Ewe!
This is the fate of the males that achieved
the height of arousal by Ren's pheromones.
Women are dangerous.
Let me taste it.
It's great!
You should try a bite.
No. How could you eat that?
It's soaked with your secretions.
Are you sure you don't want any?
No, thank you.
Here.
Remember to change your underwear.
Thanks. What about the taxi?
I called for one.
What are you pouting about?
I'm not pouting.
Are you angry about the experiment?
No.
Then what's with the attitude?
Hurry.
The taxi will be here.
Don't change the subject.
It's here.
If you don't catch the last train,
you won't make tomorrow's conference.
Huh.
NO EXAMINATIONS TODAY
They're not open.
Hey.
Ryuji, you're alive.
I'm glad.
You have the same name as my husband.
You won't give in that easily.
You're quick like him.
Come again, Ryuji.
ORACLES AND FORTUNES
This dildo is made from his cock.
It has the same length,
girth, and hardness.
That's why I can be
away from him for a day.
With this dildo,
I can always feel his cock up my pink slit.
Yesterday's argument was stupid.
I didn't see him off properly.
I failed as a wife.
Darling, I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I'll never talk back again.
Ren, it's alright.
There's no need to worry.
But...
I plan to experiment
again in the near future.
Will you cooperate with me again?
Yes.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum.
Cum, baby.
Cum.
Don't hold back.
Cum hard, baby.
I'm cumming!
You also...
...must cum.
Yes, darling.
I'm so wet.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming again.
Ren, I'm home.
Huh?
What's this smell?
Hey, Ren...
Ren!
Ren.
Ren, wake up.
What happened?
Welcome home, darling.
Ren, you...
Would you like dinner?
Or would you prefer a bath first?
Or would you like to...
...experiment?