Night Shift Nurses
Yakin Byoutou: Night Shift Ward
They're all here, aren't they?
It's like they're all tempting me
to fantasize about them...
Hmm, that's OK, but it's not quite right...
That's it! That's the figure
of a true human being!
Humans are born naked
and die naked, you see...
Those stupid women
who put on an air of importance,
and those who try to gloss everything over,
to me you're nothing but female slaves!
Ren, I want you to sit on this.
Yes, Doctor.
It's cold!
Now, get those juices flowing.
Doctor, I want you!
Yes, Nanase here.
I'm sorry.
Yes. A lot is coming out.
I have a favor to ask.
I want you to listen while you masturbate.
Fujisawa-san...
The basement, right?
I understand...
Doctor! You're not supposed to
use cell phones in the hospital!
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Well, I'll talk to you later.
What a lovely view!
Did you wear the garters
so that the male doctors
and hospitalized patients
can get a good look at you?
That's not so!
Don't film this!
What are you trying to do?!
What am I trying to do...
I'm trying to make you repent.
No...
No!
Untie me now!
If you resist too much,
the ropes will really hurt.
Stop it.
No!
What's the matter? Does that feel good?
It hurts!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Considering that you killed a person!
At least recognize the position you're in.
What are you going to do to me?!
Be sincere and think about what you did.
You should accept what's coming to you.
It's because you're wearing underwear
like this that you're not repenting!
You're all wet.
You've got an erogenous zone
in an interesting place.
Doctor, I beg you!
Really!
Please stop!
You can't!
No!
It looks like you're really wet.
Stop it! Stop it!
Don't ever go against me again.
Yes, Doctor.
No, no... I can't take this.
Now, Ren! Show the people of this town
the embarrassing sight of your peeing!
However, I can't be
satisfied at just this...
No! Stop it!
Please! Let me go!
Naoya-san!
NOOOooo!
No, no, no...
Naoya-san, Naoya-san...!
No...
Ren, you were a virgin?
As I thought, you are my woman!
Naoya-san...
Stop it!
It hurts, it hurts...
Don't move!
Father!
Mother!
What is it? I can't understand
a thing you're saying.
No! Stop it! Help me! Someone!
Are you sure you want to yell?
Imagine if someone came in
and saw this embarrassing view...
...and your sister heard about this.
No, such a thing... no... nooo...
Then, settle down!
That way, we can both enjoy ourselves.
It's so tight...
Come, I'm about to enter your inside!
Nice and tight!
Stop, it hurts... Don't move!
Does it hurt that much?
Just as I thought, you were still a virgin!
Enyjoy it! I'm going to show you
what it means to be an adult!
It hurts!
All right! I'm about to cum!
You can't! Stop! Please! Please stop it!
I'll use my cock to mash it up.
No! It's going further in!
But that's okay.
Doctor, I'm scared!
It's moving inside of me!
The egg is moving inside of me!
That's my Ren.
Good. Good.
Ren.
Yes, Doctor...!
I'm coming!
I'm about to cum.
Let me see it.
I'm about to cum!
Everyone's made splendid
experiment subject matter.
Being a doctor is my life's calling.
I'm so glad I became a doctor.
What's this?
Stop! Don't look!
I'd say that you managed
to get yourself quite wet.
Well? How about I take it out?
Looks like you had
quite a bit of fun with this.
Take a look, Hikaru.
This will enter your inside next.
No! N-No! Help!
Move your hands!
You don't care what happens to your sister?
If you try to resist me
or try to run away again...
I'll really show those
pictures to Ai-kun, you know.
O-O-Ow!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Seems you're not wet enough.
Yes...
Do you know what I'm
going to do with this, hmm?
It seems that your erogenous
zone lies in your anus.
Yesterday I explored your virgin pussy,
today I'm squeezing in
through the back door!
Stop it!
No! Stop...
No...
My stomach!
My stomach is going to explode!
Is it painful?
Is it embarrassing?
But it feels good, right?
It's turning you on, isn't it?
N-No, you're wrong!
Don't move or you'll get hurt.
Well, as I thought, this suits you better.
So you're not really a virgin, are you?
Being a nurse is a very
active job, so I just...
So then you're telling me you are a virgin?
Yes.
What a wonderful fragrance!
What a thing to do for a doctor!
The criminal heiress of
a pharmaceutical fortune
isn't in a position to judge
the ethics of a doctor.
No! It hurts!
What?!
It's an air pump.
No, no...
Release me!
Toilet...
Let me go to the toilet.
All right, I take it out now, OK?
Geez, talk about naive and gullible!
I-It hurts!
What are you...?!
Have you forgotten already?
I asked you to help me with an experiment!
What're you doing?
What're you going to do with that?
Isn't this nice?
This is what I'm going to do.
I've got to do something
about lubrication, after all.
With proper lubrication...
even a brat like you can
take a big thing like this.
Nice and cold.
No...
Don't worry. These eggs
are only half-boiled.
And I took off the shell.
One...
D-Doctor...
That went in pretty smoothly.
Maybe from all the work we've done so far?
Two...
Doctor, i-inside my stomach
it feels kind of funny.
I can't fit anymore.
Impossible, Doctor. No more.
You always give up so easily!
Always telling me, "You can't!",
"Impossible!" or "No way!"
Just keep your mouth shut!
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
All right. Now, relax
those abdominal muscles.
Yes, sir.
Good!
Good! All ready to go!
Hikaru, let's start your
practice! Start giving birth!
Yes, sir.
It's coming out!
Excellent! Just a little more!
Ahh! I can't stop it!
What new experiments will I try next?
You can't! Stop it! I'm going to go crazy!
I can't take it!
No more! It's coming out! It's coming out!
All right,
here goes!
It's coming out!
I can't anymore!
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
I want you to blow everything
you've got out in front of me!
Beautiful!
What a wonderful sound!
I'm going to untie you right now!
No, I'm almost there!
I think you're misunderstanding
something, Shinjo-kun.
Like you, Hikaru is doing
this because she wants to.
I don't want such a thing!
Of course you do!
Then, why did you come here?
Well...
Never mind. Let's just hold that thought
while we watch Hikaru do her thing.
I'm coming!
Just thinking about it makes
me want to take out my penis.
However, I'm going to need more than
this if I want to complete my experiments.
One day I'll create my own
special hospital ward...
And then my ideal will
finally become reality!
By day I'll attend to those
big shot drug producers,
but by night those bodies
will be consecrated to me.
How magnificent!
In order to obtain those
which are colored
like a rose, those
large 'front gates',
I will have to begin an
altogether new experiment!