I am in love with you.
Ever since we met and up until now.
D-Didn't I say I love you?!
I love you!
Jeez, don't make me repeat myself!
I cherish you, master!
What, are you perhaps enthralled?
As long as you're with me, I won't need anything else.
I love you with all my heart...
My adorable little brother!
U-Umm...
Nakamaru-kun!
Soushirou!
Master!
Little brother!
I-I...
I...
I-I can't choose one among them!
New Wife Calendar
Niizuma Koyomi The Animation!
So it was a dream...
My name is Nakamaru Soushirou.
I am the number one disciple
of the potter Tsukidate Takaakira.
I've been living in this town for a few years now.
I had various encounters when I look back on it.
A folklore major college student from the city
who came here as a fieldworker, Koyomi-san
Tsukidate-sensei's daughter, Tamaki-chan.
A daughter from a noble family of tea ceremony
practitioners and my childhood friend, Shino-neesama.
A fox girl deity residing at the mountain, Kuzunoha-san.
And now, it turned out that...
They all gave me marriage proposals!
Soushirou, good morning!
Good morning, Tamaki-chan.
Today is my turn, okay.
I'm looking forward to it, my dear husband.
O-Okay...
In the end, I couldn't choose one among
the four women that proposed to me.
At that time, what they suggested was...
Let's each have our turns as newlyweds!
He'll be able to have a taste of our affection
if we have the chance to be alone with him, right?
We'll each have a turn to be with him as newlyweds
and he'll choose one of us after that, okay?
Then, let's make the turns a whole day long for each.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won! I'll be first!
Let's get along, my dear!
Tamaki-chan is good on household chores,
cheerful and also good in cooking.
Moreover...
She's usually a pushy girl,
but she can also be pure and innocent like this.
Jeez, you're sucking like a baby!
Are you not ashamed of yourself?
Wait! Are you listening? You keep
on teasing my nipple...
No, the stimulation on my nipples is too much!
Soushirou...
Your tongue keeps on stroking them!
You keep on licking me frantically like that...
Don't dig up for my nipple!
Don't do that!
No! Don't do that! My nipples...
I can't... It feels so good...
No... No...
I'm coming...
My dear husband...
Are you really okay with this?
Yeah...
I'm longing for your thing down here.
I want you to fill me up inside.
You should start moving, Tamaki.
O-Okay...
You're reaching deep inside me!
I'm gonna pamper your cock a lot!
Don't twist and grind it against me!
Your cock keeps on ramming itself up my womb!
Your cock is overwhelming
my body into submission!
Dear, you're using my pussy too much!
But I like that part of you!
Rub your cock to me a lot enough...
So that my heart won't be able to go against you!
No... No! Coming, it's coming!
I want your semen inside me!
Please, give it to me! Give it to me!
My dear husband...
I love you!
How is it?
This time, I boiled some medicinal herbs
that I picked up and tried blending them.
Hmm, it's delicious.
Just as I expected from a mountain goddess.
Despite living for around two centuries
already, you still get the best of me!
I want to please you, master.
I want to shower you with my love!
Look forward to bedtime tonight!
How does my tail feel?
It's twitching like it wants to copulate already!
What a cock of such imposing presence!
And another thing...
You just brush it off without realizing
anything whenever I tease you.
You never looked at me.
Alright then, you'll have to let me have fun too!
How is it? Does it feel good inside me?
Master?! Not that, you can't do that!
Then, how about here?
Master...
It's like I'm being mounted on
by a beast in this position...
This way of copulation is against the norms of sex!
No, you can't! Any more than this and...
Whenever you move, your cock is...
The contour of your cock
gets entangled with my pussy!
Master, this is bad! I am... I'm...
O-Oh! Master, master!
Master...
Looks like you quite worn yourself out, little brother.
Nee-sama...
It's alright.
It's all for choosing your lifetime partner.
You can take your time.
Yeah...
Of course, choosing me will make me happy the most.
But I will be happy enough as long as
my dear little brother finds happiness.
Nee-sama...
I've always been thinking about it.
Aware of my family, no one dared
taking a step approaching me.
But you are different.
You took my hand without any concern.
You stayed so close with me.
That was a lot of happiness for me.
That's why it's my turn to wish
for your happiness this time.
Shino-neesama, I'm...
You don't have to rush yourself.
Find your own happiness...
Let yourself feel good, little brother.
It's coming out!
Alright, let's both feel good even a lot more!
N-Nee-sama...
Let your sister handle this, little brother.
Ouch!
My little brother...
My little brother's dick is filling me inside!
Your sister will move a lot
and make you feel good, okay?
Forgive me for being a lewd sister.
But this is all for the sake of your dick.
That's why you shouldn't worry about me.
You can do as you wish. If you wish to shoot it out...
It's okay for you to come a lot.
No way... That's...
You're being so rough!
Your dick is so robust!
It feels like it's reaching deep inside my belly!
No... No!
Huh?
N-No way, I just came a while ago...
Little brother, you can't!
If you start moving now, I am... I'm...
I can't take it anymore!
I'm pushing this incredible dick
of yours inside me on my own...
Nothing can make me happier!
Your cock is leaking with precum!
My pussy is making you feel good, right?
Let's keep shoving it in, okay?
Do you still remember? When we're kids, we played house
and you said that you want us to be parents.
We even tried to do lewd stuff as well, right?
And now, I've become one with you...
Ram your cock inside
and I'll wrap it up tightly in my womb!
That's why...
I love you.
Niizuma Koyomi!
Come on! Here, over here!
You're being sluggish, Nakamaru-kun.
You're just so fast, Koyomi-san!
Do you still remember the first time that we met?
I came here for a fieldwork, and you approached me.
You told me "What might be
the reason for you to come here?"
The next time we met was at that shrine, right?
That's where we get to properly
introduce ourselves. It's so nostalgic!
I wonder why.
Strangely enough, we always
end up running into each other.
And after that, I couldn't take you off my mind.
Me too...
It might have been the same for me.
I thought that it was our fate to meet each other...
I'm sorry...
I'm not being fair, am I? Even when
I know that everyone loves you a lot.
No matter which one of us you choose,
I'll accept it if you will at least remember about me.
Nakamaru-kun?
For being indecisive like this...
Yeah...
I really am sorry.
But...
I love you just the way you are.
Koyomi-san?
Did you just come?
When I thought that the one I love went inside me...
Huh?
It felt like you got harder...
Forgive me, Koyomi-san!
Huh?!
It's your fault for being so cute, Koyomi-san!
No way, you're suddenly being rough!
No, your dick is so big!
Your dick is impatiently pushing
up and down inside me!
Koyomi-san, you're so lewd!
L-Lewd, you say... I only wanted to become
a fine housewife that is appropriate for you!
This is too much!
It'll definitely take the shape of your dick this way!
I-I'm begging you! Make me your...
Make my pussy into your
exclusive newlywed pussy!
So deep... It's rapidly plunging deep inside me!
Coming... Coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Darling, I love you!
— Several Months Later —
At the end of deciding which one to marry...
I ended up marrying all of them instead,
who are all beautiful in their own ways.
I couldn't choose one and I didn't want
to see anyone of them sad.
All of them accepted that selfishness of mine.
You requested to have me and Tamaki
give you a double fellatio, master.
Isn't this fun? Our allotted time is almost up though!
Here are your favorite tits, little brother!
We'll have all of the sperm in these balls
out up to the last one and relieve you, okay?
There are tits whether you look to the left or right!
Here you go! We'll massage your dick!
My dear husband!
My master!
My little brother!
Darling!
My dear husband!
Master!
Little brother!
Darling!
Bring happiness to all of us, okay?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization