Oh yes, my nipples...
Yes...
You've already made it this big.
Will my breasts be enough to satisfy you?
Well?
Feels good, right?
If you put this dick inside my wet and tender pussy,
it'll feel even better than this.
I'm going to lactate!
If you're going to throw away your virginity anyway,
don't just do it with me.
Invite lots of other women to have sex with you too.
Sex Animal
~ Whores drowned in their carnal desires ~
[Please make me... a lot more sluttier]
There...
What?
What is this?
You're still a virgin, yet you're already this good.
Does it feel good here?
No... that kind of movement is...
Yuriko-san, is it okay?
We're almost like mother and son.
Doing this will be...
My, you're still beng quite persistent about this, aren't you?
No, don't play with my insides like that...
Rub my dick more.
Your hands are stopping.
I'm sorry... but I...
No, please don't stir it up...
Your pussy's already drenched.
Are you about to cum?
No way, why?
This is just...
No, no... I'm going to cum...
No, don't...
I'm going to cum... already...!
I'm cumming!
Something's coming out!
Amazing.
Yuriko, you didn't do enough, so I just came by myself.
Are we really going to do this, Naoki?
What? Can't we do it?
I-I didn't mean it that way.
But licking the asshole is just...
You can't be thinking that I'll just throw away my virginity
just because you're my childhood
friend and happen to be a virgin?
T-That's... not true...
If you really want my virginity,
then at least arouse me.
I get it already.
I just have to do it, right?
I just have to lick it, right?
Hey, rub my other thing too.
Don't get too cocky, you pervert.
Oh no...
His dick is getting hotter, and it's starting to twitch.
Naoki, are you getting aroused by this?
Good, keep it up.
The tip of his dick is starting to get wet.
He's really feeling pleasure from this.
What should I do? I'm starting to feel excited.
Suzuka, lick my balls next.
B-But, but that's...
No way...
If you perform well until the end,
then I'll give you my virginity.
Really? Are you really telling the truth?
Only if you can do it until the end.
I understand.
I-I'll do my best.
I think I'll be able to cum if you keep this up, Suzuka.
Okay, just cum.
Make yourself feel good with my tongue and hand.
I'm at my limit.
O-Oh wow, so this is cum?
Suzuka, you're quite good.
Naoki, you have to keep your promise.
You have to give your virginity to me now.
No, please remove my blindfold!
If you don't follow along, we'll keep this up all night!
No way... no...!
N-Naoki...
Where are you, Naoki?
Eh?!
Naoki...!
He got away from me!
My apologies.
If I'd known you were about to arrive, Sensei,
I wouldn't have let Suzuka do it.
Now, now, don't call me Sensei here.
Well, you were my home instructor from middle to high school.
I'm the vice president of your father's company right now, though.
S-Sensei...
The president and the vice president are supposed to be rivals,
but if we're put in a position where cooperation is beneficial,
then you won't have to worry about doing this with me.
This is quite the amazing day, Sensei.
W-Well, it is the day that I'll be receiving your virginity.
Sorry, but I'll have to do my best.
It's getting even bigger.
You have to put this inside me.
Sensei, can I take off your panties?
Y-Yes, it's all right.
Just do whatever you want.
It's already this wet,
and it looks really beautiful.
N-Naoki-san!
Sensei, please continue.
I'll cry if you don't.
I know...
But Naoki-san, you're just too good,
so I'm... oh no...!
You're getting horny already.
I'll make it feel even better for you, then.
Wait, just...
Now, now, you gotta work hard now.
You want to have sex with me, right?
That's right.
He's absolutely right.
Today, I shall definitely....
If we're going to have sex, then we
need to loosen this up a bit more.
No, no more...!
I'm... about to cum!
Naoki-san!
It's alright Sensei.
This isn't fair, I'm...!
That's no good, Sensei.
Cumming before me...
We're done with this part already, right, Naoki-san?
Indeed, we are.
Naoki-sama, congratulations on your 30th birthday.
Allow me to give you my blessings again.
The day has finally arrived, and it's good that
I have protected my virginity thus far.
Aya.
Yes, your precious part is indeed important.
I have been taught many techniques, just
so I can penetrate the likes of you.
In any case, you've really surprised the former president.
One of the conditions of the will for your inheritance
was to safeguard your virginity until the age of 30.
Then, this is my last chance, since I've
been a shut-in for such a long time...
To turn everything to my side,
you were able to conquer all temptations placed before you.
Once your birthday party comes to a close today,
you shall finally be the master of the entire conglomerate.
Aya, are the preparations for the birthday festivities done?
Yes, everything is complete.
Please, unleash all your pent up frustrations today, Naoki-sama.
I shall emerge victorious,
because no one else in this world can!
Everyone, thank you for waiting.
Mr. Teshirogi Naoki's 30th birthday banquet is about to begin.
Please turn your attention to the stage.
N-Naoki...
I'm...
The master's orders are absolute.
You understand this, don't you?
Everyone,
right now, I'm going to widen my pussy.
And I shall start masturbating.
I'm so embarrassed I could die.
And yet why...?
Amazing, Suzuka.
You seem to be really wet.
What should I do?
My body is starting to feel really hot.
It's starting to feel really good.
But my hand just won't stop.
It looks like I'm about to let loose as well.
Naoki is also feeling aroused.
His dick is getting really stiff after seeing
me make a fool of myself on stage.
Now, due to your sincere efforts,
I shall now give you the one thing you most desire as a gift.
It hurts...!
It hurts!
Pull it out, please!
Please pull it out!
How is it, Suzuka?
You wanted my virginity all this time, right?
But right now it's already...!
Stop...
Oh no, everyone's watching us.
Our very first sexual act.
Even my pussy that's being violated by a dick for the first time.
All of it.
So it is true, sex is indeed wonderful.
I can see why everyone is so obsessed with it.
Please stop, or I'll...
Suzuka.
I'm at my limit now.
I'm going to cum.
Oh no, oh no...
I'm cumming, it's coming out!
I'm cumming with your dick...!
That was one great orgasm.
We have prepared many more forms
of entertainment for everyone.
Please, enjoy them in any way you can.
Sex Animals R30
I'm going to lactate!
I am the remarried wife of the former president.
Being forced to do something this humiliating...
Now, now, Yuriko-san,
you have to squirt lots more milk.
Okay, I understand.
Please wait a moment.
You seem to be in pain, should I assist you?
I-I'm all right.
My nipples already hurt from all this squirting.
But, this is the only way I can survive.
You have an admirable attitude, Yuriko-san,
but I really want to help.
W-What!
No, don't just put it in like that...
They say that lactation is easier when you stimulate the vagina.
That's not...
You-have-nothing-to-hide.
I see, from the beginning my sole purpose
was to serve these people.
Your pussy is starting to get wet.
Does it feel good?
You're lactating now.
I'm going to go crazy if you stir it up like that.
Just hold on for a bit.
I'm squeezing your tits raw.
I can't hold it in anymore...
My mind's going blank.
It's okay, just cum.
Cum while you squirt your precious milk!
Oh no, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Wow, this is amazing!
So you had this much built up inside you, Yuriko-san?
Your pussy is still wide open.
I bet any guy will quickly ditch you with this loose hole.
It feels...
It feels great...
E-Everyone, let me introduce to you our company's latest product.
It's a new health care and sex tool for females,
and I shall now demonstrate how it works.
Oh? A health care tool, eh?
Can we test it now?
What's wrong? Letting out a voice like that?
Do you feel unwell or something?
M-My apologies.
T-The sensation given by this tool is just so stimulating.
Does it really feel that good?
Yes, it has a wonderful calming effect.
It helps the user relax using pleasurable sensations,
which provides a real soothing feeling.
In that case, let's jack it up.
I-It also has several intensity modes.
Users can try different settings to match their preferences.
Since we're already using it, why don't
we test it on your asshole as well?
D-Don't...!
N-No, no way...
My insides are being rubbed hard.
This is amazing.
Your entire body is twitching wildly.
No, it's just too intense, I...
Please, please, gentlemen!
Stop this!
I'm going to break!
This is good. Then show us how you cum until the very end!
N-No way, no please...
Turn it off.
Turn it off, please!
I-I'm going crazy!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
This is really wonderful.
Shall we arrange negotiations for the purchase
of this health care machine?
Ah...
Thank you very much.
I am very pleased.
Man, I can't hold back any longer after watching this.
I understand.
Then I shall give you the appropriate service.
Naoki-sama,
at this rate, everyone will be taken down by your guests.
Is this all right with you?
Of course, I do not mind at all.
This was my plan from the very beginning.
I beg of you...
I won't be able to stop myself anymore.
I won t be able to hold back.
Please push your dick inside me more!
Amazing, you were just a virgin awhile ago.
Please don't say that.
My pussy feels so good that I can't stop.
Please continue, go all the way inside!
Put it all In!
Everyone's watching us.
Are you okay with that?
Yes.
My body is getting more excited as they watch me,
and I'm getting really aroused.
My breasts, ass, and my pussy, everything!
Please watch!
Watch every bit of my lewd self!
Please, violate me more intensely!
Make a complete mess of my asshole and pussy!
Make a complete mess of it!
Oh crap, my dick feels like it's gonna melt from this hot sensation!
I've already been stirred up hard,
yet my pussy, my slutty pussy
still keeps on twitching.
Sucking it in happily like that...
Yes, all of our honored guests,
just use my body as you wish.
Please make me your toy!
I can't hold it in anymore.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Please don't stop now!
Release lots of cum!
Your dicks are starting to feel hot.
Please cum.
Cum it all inside me.
Pour it all on me!
I want your cum!
Something's coming!
Please, let's cum together!
Fuck my ass and pussy real good!
It feels great.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum inside of you!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
My breasts... I'm going to cum!
Wonderful, it's this exact sensation which melts in your mouth.
The true taste of a mother!
I'll take it all, so please cum lots!
Cum it all.
Oh wow, it's all coming out.
Oh yes, it feels really great.
You can push it in harder.
I want you to make a mess of me more.
With this, your revenge is now complete, right, Naoki-sama?
What are you saying?
Aya, I am now the master.
So I shall retrieve everything that I lost,
during those thirty years!
Master.
We are forever your slaves, your sex animals.
So please, tease and take care of us, okay?