You're working hard, young man.
Yes, but it feels good.
That's good.
Master, are you turned on?
Yeah, it's good. Do it harder.
Your breasts, use your breasts!
Master, like this?
That's right, continue.
That's good. Harder!
That was close.
l totally forgot about cleaning the bathtub.
Maria's sensation is still there.
The power of the dolls is real.
Man, it's not the time to be doing such a thing!
That's the newcomer.
H-Hey!
What crazy thing am l thinking about?
Mr. Sagara...
What!
l finished cleaning over here already.
Also, the hose was left out in the yard, so l put it away.
l-l'm sorry. lt slipped my mind.
Thank you for that.
lf Miss Saeka found it, she would have yelled at me so much.
No, it's my job.
Mr. Sagara.
Huh?
l don't think you are suitable for this job.
What?
What? Just because she can do her job really well...
She's so conceited.
Even though she's a newcomer...
This is...
...a doll of that girl!
Hey...
Who am l?
You are my master.
Okay, then what l say is absolute.
Hey, Shion!
Yes?
Answer me right.
l'm very sorry, Master.
Okay, that's good.
How is it? Are you turned on, huh?
Don't you have a pretty good body...
What's the matter? Your pussy is already soaked.
Suck it.
What's up with that sucking? Put it in deeper!
How about it? Didn't you want to try it out?
Keep on comforting yourself just like that.
That's good. More. Harder!
More! More!
Now, put your hands on that desk and stick your butt out this way!
Good, look this way.
Let's see, is it your first time here?
How is it? Are you turned on? Does it hurt?
This feels so good!
What's wrong, Nanami?
You don't seem too happy.
Really?
Oh, is it...
What?
Lovesickness?
N-No it's not.
Hey, l was right!
Who's this person?
l know, it's Takashi!
What!
Bull's eye!
Maria!
You can't hide it from me.
l saw you washing Takashi's underwear with these eyes.
Th-That is...
Why is it...
Last night, with Shion and with Maria...
l had no intention to use the dolls...
But before l knew it, l had the dolls in my hand.
Am l being manipulated by the dolls?
No, there's no way...
l-l'm sorry.
l-l'm okay.
l'm really sorry.
l was in a hurry.
lt's fine, plus...
...if l get more delusional than this, it'll be bad.
Huh?
No, nothing.
See you!
This is...
There it is! This is it!
Mr. Sagara.
Miss Yuasa.
l kind of just escaped for a little.
This is a little gift.
l made it. Please eat it later.
Th-Thank you.
Wow, so this is what it's like in here.
This is my first time coming here.
This is Sae, Miss Saeka's horse, huh?
The truth is l came here to consult with you on something, Mr. Sagara.
Me?
Yes.
Recently l've had this strange dream.
A strange dream?
A certain person makes me do really embarrassing things.
But l like to...
l'm very happy.
U-Um, this is only a dream.
Y-Yeah.
lt's really mysterious. l was thinking why is it...
U-Um...
Mr. Sagara, the truth is l...
Nanami! Where are you?
Oh no, it's Miss Saeka!
l must go back to work.
Miss Yuasa...
Nanami!
See you. Because Miss Saeka'll yell me at...
So that's what it was.
Miss Yuasa remembered that happening as a dream.
Master, does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
Okay, now it's my turn to make you feel good.
What?
Master, it feels so good.
Don't spit it out! Drink it all up!
What?
Yes, Master.
l decided that l wouldn't use those dolls ever again.
For her definitely...
So with this hammer...
lt's gone!
What's the meaning of this?
Why did the dollhouse disappear all of a sudden?
Boo!
M-Maria?
Why are you here?
l don't remember using the doll!
What doll?
What?
Oh, l got it. Maria, who am l? Say my name.
You are Takashi.
l'm glad, l didn't know what to do if you called me Master...
Hey, hey, hey.
Wh-What?
Speaking of, why are you here?
Did she confess to you?
What?
Did Nanami confess her feelings to you?
What are you talking about?
Man, she didn't confess yet, huh?
She's so stupid. lt's almost good-bye.
Wh-What do you mean by good-bye?
Nanami's quitting this place.
What!
Mother, is there no way to cancel this?
We have no choice.
This is the master's orders. We cannot do anything about it.
But, sending off Nanami to a horrible man like Gouda is just...
Regardless of the fact that it's Father's orders, it's horrible!
Miss Saeka! You have said enough.
lt's rude to Mr. Gouda.
But it's the truth!
Plus that man...there's something wrong with him recently.
Those eyes... lt's like he's not human.
As if he is...
Nanami was a childhood friend with Miss Saeka back in the day.
Hey, that looks good!
None for you!
Hogger!
Just one.
Thank you for the food!
Then?
Nanami used to be a daughter of a wealthy family too...
...but apparently she had a lot happen to her.
So good.
Also, apparently this trading with Shion was decided a while ago.
That perverted old man was eyeing Nanami for a while now apparently.
Then Madam, please give my regards to your husband when he returns.
Please take good care of Nanami.
Don't be worried. l will take good care of her.
Nanami...
Sae...
Good-bye, Mr. Sagara.
Miss Yuasa...
l'm sure you are tired. Why don't you rest here for a while?
No, l will get to work right away.
ls that so? Before that l have a present ready for you.
lt's the new maid outfit. Please take it.
That's a problem! l can't wear such an embarrassing thing!
l can't!
Oh? You don't like it?
That is troubling. Then l have no choice.
Help this lady with changing.
Be courteous.
No, let me go!
Please stop!
No!
lt's here.
lt's pretty run-down.
lt's like there are no signs of people living here.
Excuse me!
ls anyone home?
This is Mr. Gouda's residence, right?
This place is...
Do you like it?
M-Mr. Gouda!
l'm sorry l just barged in on my own.
l seriously wanted to see Nanami, l mean Miss Yuasa...
...one more time, so that's why...
You don't have to hold back.
You have the right to be a part of this ceremony too.
Ceremony?
What are you talking about?
Did you enjoy the dolls enough?
What!
My servants are also happy that they are going to gain another member.
The regret is that l wasn't supposed to meet you in this way.
Your heart and body were supposed to fully break down in a couple of days.
Just like them.
But it seems that Shion has failed.
lt's okay.
l was able to gain a wonderful collection.
Miss Yuasa!
Let go of Miss Yuasa!
How is it? lsn't it beautiful?
l've always wanted her.
What are you going to do to her?
She will replace Shion and become my new servant.
A servant?
That's right.
They will seduce humans one after the other and make them break down.
We will make this world into a dollhouse!
Stop it!
Miss Takamura?
Master, please do whatever makes you content.
That's a present from me.
Master!
This woman rudely tried to break my precious doll house.
She held a grudge against the dolls for her family falling apart.
But the first one that opened up that dollhouse was your family!
Well, time to get to work.
No, no, you cannot take that out.
This is a punishment...
Miss Yuasa...
Mr. Sagara...
Move! Get away!
Miss Yuasa!
You still don't understand?
This is my piece of art.
l can't let someone like you that doesn't know real beauty to touch it!
Nanami, the ceremony is at its climax right now.
You have to take my blood.
And be reborn as a new servant of the dollhouse!
Mr. Sagara!
M-Miss Yuasa...
Sh-Shion, what is the meaning of this?
The abominable doll curse will end here.
Mr. Sagara...
Miss Yuasa...
lt's all okay now.
What was l...
Watch out!
l won't let you escape...
Monster! Just what are you?
Run! Hurry outside!
With this, everything is over.
Miss Shion...
Who are you?
lt's something from a while ago.
A doll maker took a commission from a royal family and created a doll.
The model was their cherished daughter, and that doll held her perfect beauty.
That royalty fell in love with the doll and made the doll maker make more.
One time, that royalty...
...had the idea of having those dolls only for themselves.
They could not tolerate the fact that people other than them...
...could have the same doll.
The royalty lit the doll maker's house on fire.
The doll maker, along with his cherished daughter, burned to death.
From that time, the curse of the doll started.
First the royalty went crazy and died, and every time the owner changes...
...the dollhouse kept on sucking the life out of the people.
l was going to seal the dollhouse in the Katsuragi household forever.
So that was why l made the door to the attic doubled.
But Mr. Sagara, you opened that door.
l was not able to let you just be part of it.
That's why l weakened the power of the doll.
Do you remember?
A while ago, you and l met here in this place.
You don't say!
You were the girl from that time.
That event was making me suffer inside my heart for a while.
l thought it was a dream.
l wanted to forget.
You were my first love.
l am the servant of the dollhouse.
l'm an abominable existence born from the curse of the dolls.
But l was able to have the heart of a person for a little while.
Mr. Sagara, that's thanks to you.
Miss Shion...
l took the dollhouse in the attic away while Mr. Gouda wasn't watching.
What?
Now everything is in the fire, so my existence will soon disappear.
Along with the memories made with you...
Miss Shion!
Miss Shion, don't go!
Good-bye...
Miss Nanami, thank you for protecting me.
Good-bye, Mr. Takashi...
Shion!
Thank you, Miss Nanami. Mr. Takashi...
A day l can see you will come.
Someday...