l didn't actually remember where this place was or when it was exactly.
Takashi!
Hey, Takashi! Come on, wake up!
What are you slacking off for?
Maria!
N-No, l became a little sleepy by mistake...
Come on, l am the one that is working my butt off getting all sweaty!
You want me to tell Mr. Kashiwagi the butler?
Hold on, hold on!
lf you did such a thing, l'd be fired from this place!
Yeah, that's true.
Then help me with my job.
But l still have to mow the lawn...
Here are the sheets. Please take care of the laundry.
Why this many?
Because it's too much work to bring each one individually.
lf you do it all at once, it'll be done in one go, right?
What?
Well, please take care of it.
Gosh, it's so hot. l want to take a shower!
For my summer job...
...l was working under the Katsuragi millionaire family as a servant.
lt having a good hourly rate plus room and board was the main reason...
...but the reality wasn't that easygoing.
From the morning, cleaning up the backyard...
...helping to maintain the potted plants...
...throwing the garbage out, and mowing the lawn...
The reason why l fell asleep was because l was so tired l collapsed.
H-Huh? Where is the laundry room?
Oh, it's the tutor, Juri Takamura.
We're both part-timers, but she's in the air conditioning...
...and l'm in this scorching hot hell.
l can't agree with this!
Anyway, it's such an amazing mansion.
There's too much of a difference from my raggedy apartment.
Hey, you there, what are you doing here?
Oh, l-l'm sorry...
l didn't know where the laundry room was...
The laundry room is in the back!
Plus, servants cannot come in here!
l-l'm sorry.
l just started here, so l...
And also, what's with your clothes?
You're covered in dirt!
''Katsuragi family servants are supposed to...
...keep their personal appearance clean at all times!''
You should have heard this from the beginning!
B-But this is because of work...
Don't talk back to me!
Brother!
E-Excuse me...
lt's nothing!
Watch out from now on.
That girl...
She was seriously going to do it all in one shot, huh?
Could this one be that person's from before?
Her name was Miss Saeka or something...
...but she didn't have to say it like that.
Excuse me...
Would you like me to help you?
Ah, y-yes please.
Ah! No, this is...well...
l'll put it in the wash, so please give it to me.
Yes.
Have you gotten used to it already?
No, not at all.
Weren't you surprised?
This place makes people work really hard.
Seriously.
l don't get how things are working around here at all yet.
lf something is troubling you, please feel free to tell me.
Thank you.
Well...
Yes?
Your work clothes are pretty dirty.
lf you like, do you want me to wash it for you?
But...
Because you were being yelled at before, so...
Then l'll take up your offer.
Oh, l'm sorry! A change of clothes...
There are some in the back equipment warehouse.
l'm going to go and get it!
Um...
Change of clothes, change of clothes...
ls it over there? Let's see.
They're still small...
Well, l'm not saying as much as Maria...
...but l want to at least have as much as Nanami.
What?
ls it that small?
For some reason the horse was acting so violently l'm covered in sweat.
lt even dug in a little, so it kind of hurts.
lf l get caught like this, it won't end with just getting fired.
Takashi, what are you doing!
Maria?
Ah, th-there are many reasons for this...
You were trying to take a bath without telling me, huh?
Okay, l'll keep my mouth shut.
But in exchange...
...l want to take one too.
Come on, let's go! l'll wash your back for you!
W-Wait, right now isn't a good time!
Come on, hurry.
l'm covered in sweat.
Damn it...
lt's such a great chance too.
What?
Oh no, it's Madam.
Ah, it's that guy again.
Who's that guy?
That's the art dealer, Gouda.
l hate him!
Why?
He's such a pervert!
He touches my butt all the time.
That girl is?
She's not a familiar face. Maybe she's new?
l feel like l've met her somewhere.
l did such a horrible thing to her.
Nanami Yuasa, huh?
Where did she go? She was so cute.
Right now, there definitely was someone...
Putting that aside for now, l need to finish my job fast!
l'm finally finished.
Man, what a huge yard...
This is the cleaning equipment storage, but is there something...?
lt's nothing.
Excuse me.
What kind of business did she have in a place like this?
lf l remember correctly, the attic is up there.
Speaking of which, the human figure l saw that time.
Oh, it's an ordinary storage room.
What was that woman doing here?
An antique doll?
Where did it fall from?
There's a hidden room in a place like this?
That's an...
...antique dollhouse...
lt's really well made.
l'm sure it's a very expensive item.
Huh?
This doll looks exactly like her.
Wh-What?
What happened?
Wh-What's going on?
This is...
Excuse me.
Oh, M-Miss Yuasa...
Please call me Nanami, Master.
What did you just say?
Yes, you are my master.
So please tell me to do anything.
What are you saying?
The master of this house is the head of the household, lsao Katsuragi.
Stop joking around.
You don't like me?
What?
Okay, Nanami, make me feel good.
What am l trying to do?
Yes, Master.
M-Miss Yuasa!
Okay, suck it.
Yes.
Master, does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
Okay, now it's my turn to make you feel good.
What!
l-l did such a horrible...
Miss Yuasa's pussy is...
...totally exposed!
Master, it feels so good...
What am l doing?
lt feels so good.
l can't. l can't hold myself down.
Don't spit it out! Drink it all up!
Yes, Master.
That was a...dream?
No, it wasn't.
l can still feel the warmth from that girl's mouth.
Man, just remembering makes it react.
Did l do such a horrible thing?
This is bad.
This won't just be sexual harassment.
This is a total crime...
But why did she call me Master?
That's why l...
Yes!
Um...
M-Miss Yuasa!
l washed this for you.
l'm sorry!
l know it's not something that can be forgiven with just an apology...
...but there was something wrong with me!
Huh?
Well, you won't forgive me, right?
Come on, Mr. Sagara.
l just did the laundry for you. You are exaggerating.
What?
But if you feel that bad about it, then maybe...
...l should get you to help me with my job next time.
Good night.
H-Hey...
What is going on?
Okay, okay! l know, so please get away from there for a little!
l can't make it clean!
The horse that Miss Saeka is always straddling...
Oh man! What am l imagining?
Got to work, got to work.
Move away from there!
Can't you listen to what l say?
l am the master of this dog that bit me!
l have to punish it!
l'm very...
...sorry.
Okay.
So you're saying that you're going to take the punishment instead.
That's fine!
lt's that new maid!
Regardless of the fact that she's the daughter of the master, that's horrible!
Please stop it!
l understand your feelings, but we can't do anything about it.
But no matter how you look at it, that is way too much!
Maids are not slaves!
ln this mansion, what the master says is absolute.
While the headmaster is absent...
...Madame Towako and the daughter Miss Saeka are the masters...
...but even those two cannot go against the headmaster's commands.
That's the custom of the Katsuragi family.
Man, that hysteric daughter is so annoying.
She says l do my job too slow and it's not well done.
She's just playing around riding horses and playing instruments.
But l want to do it with her once.
l'm sure it would feel awesome to make that arrogant face moan.
By the way, do you guys...
...know about the strange rumor that is passed down in this mansion?
Apparently, somewhere in this mansion there is a thing...
...that lets you manipulate anyone to your liking.
Amazing! Then you can do her as much as you want!
Not just that girl.
lf you had that thing...
...you would be able to make all the women in the mansion be on your side.
Well, it is only a rumor though.
lf that servant's story is true...
This isn't for the purpose of doing perverted things to Miss Saeka.
lt's to get an apology for Miss Nanami and that new maid named Shion.
This is...
...the stable?
Miss Saeka!
Hurry and hit me please, Brother.
What? Brother?
You finally got in the mood?
Very well. l'll let you enjoy it very much.
But before that...
They're big enough, aren't they?
You don't have to worry about them being too small.
But they're smaller than Nanami's.
Don't worry about it. lf you do this, they'll get bigger.
lt's about time for the enjoyment.
lt hurts!
Stop it...
Looking good.
With that you are definitely the Katsuragi family's daughter.
l'm embarrassed.
Next, you're going to make me enjoy it.
Further to the back...
That's right.
l-lt's coming out!
No!
Brother, l'm embarrassed.
Look. That horse is totally excited.
No...
How about it?
You think you want to try it out?
l-lt's impossible.
l can't, Brother.
Then what about this?
No, don't pull it out!
Now...with mine...
No!
lt's so hard...
lt's tight...
lt's hot!
lt's hot! lt's hot!
l'm going to come! l'm going to come!
Damn it.
What have l done?
lt wasn't supposed to be like this, but why did l...
Young miss didn't remember anything.
But it was certain that what happened was because of the dolls.
That was when l knew something inside me was starting to change for sure.
That was like a premonition of destruction.