English Preparation Room
English club members use the English
Prep Room only three times a week.
I'm glad that there's one room that
we could freely use, Ayano-sensei.
Wait, stop...
There are still students,
walking in the hallway.
It's okay, as long as you don't let out your moans.
At least...
At least wait until the students leave.
Nope.
There are only 90 shots left for the seed I planted in your clitoris.
I'm going to give you every last bit of juice,
in order to let you make it for your dear Yui-chan's birthday.
Female Teacher
Chuuzenji Ayano's Slutty Future
Part Two
As expected,
you started moaning as soon as I drilled my big thing inside of you.
I thought maybe you'd like it slithering slowly and deeply,
so I'll just push this all the way in.
Bye bye!
See you tomorrow, Yui.
Hey, let's go already.
I haven't seen Ayano-chan around here today.
When I tried to do it more intensely for a quicker shot,
she started moaning even louder.
Okay, I'll be more gentle next time.
Th-This kid...
Morizumi Kouki...
What's with that kid?!
Always using Yui's name to coax me...
How unfair!
Damn, how did he find out?
I was really careful and wary of other people before.
Yui...
Right now, I have no choice but to heed his demands,
until I reach the required 100 cumshots.
Don't loiter around and go home as soon as you can, okay?
Okay.
Sensei, do you have a moment?
At the gym storage.
About one month, I suppose.
I've wanted to do this at least once,
with a female teacher, at the gym storage.
Idiot.
I can't go back anymore, I have to put up with it.
Three years after working as a teacher here,
and now I have to endure this absurd month.
Hey, just cum already.
Sensei, if you try to put more effort into moving your hips,
I'd cum in no time.
Sensei, you're such a pervert.
Getting wet in the middle of the hallway...
Idiot, you're the pervert here!
You're now so good at blowjobs,
that it's hard to imagine you're a lesbian.
But,
you'll still need to keep doing this to make
me cum even during lunch breaks.
Fifth period will start soon if you don't work harder.
I'll allow you to do this lunchtime blowjob service every single day.
I can endure all these embarrassing things.
Come on already!
Why's he such an expert in making this feel good despite being a brat?
My cum gets more potent the wetter you get.
But, instead of me using it to fuck you with,
I want you to enjoy this as well.
Of course I can't!
He got my pussy all wet with that hot thing.
And he just keeps on fucking me as it gets more aroused.
You seem sluttier than usual, Yui.
Why are you suddenly on the offensive?
Well, you seem to be a lot more sensitive lately,
as if your body is screaming for me to do it.
But you know,
I'll still love you, no matter how much you change, Ayano-chan.
Yui...
Come now, spread your legs.
I'm going to lick this sensitive clitoris.
C-Can we at least do it in a closed room?
Nope.
While all the other students are working their assess off in class,
here we are working our assess off having sex,
and it feels so good.
We're even doing this during class time!
I'll be cumming lots even during class.
I wonder what happened to sensei?
They say she's resting at the infirmary.
Hey, Morizumi.
Is your class on self-study, too?
No, not really.
Chuuzenji-sensei's supposed to be at our class during this period,
but now we're doing self study.
Oh, I see.
But man, I envy Chuuzenji.
This is just...
For that entire month,
our carnal lifestyle continued.
I'm going to cum inside again, Ayano-sensei.
No, no....
That's good...
Just keep on sucking...
It won't stop!
In my mouth, and in my womb...
He just kept cumming inside me.
Then we'll do it at your place this time.
Okay.
Man,
we're finally at our last round.
It went so fast after we started enjoying it.
We just blazed through Yui-chan’s birthday.
Fo-Forget that.
What's the meaning of this?
Those clothes were in you dresser.
These are Yui's change of clothes.
It fits you quite nicely though.
She just bought this.
She wants me to wear it while we're on dates.
What?
You're cute, Ayano.
What's with that all of a sudden?
Now, now, sensei.
Don't be so shy.
This will be our last time having sex after I cum inside you, right?
I kind of wanted us to act like lovers just this last time.
Can't we?
Is this really going to be the last time?
Really?
Of course.
I promise,
that this will be the last time.
Well, I can make amends, if you insist
on still wanting my cum after this.
I won't ask for that!.
I can really feel the way you rub it in your mouth, Ayano.
Feels like you're really putting a lot of effort into this last session.
What is it now? Jeez.
I'm not doing this out of love.
Of course, it's not passion for me,
but passion for my dick.
Guess I'll call it passion for my dick.
Ayano...
Your blowjob feels so good.
Alright.
Shall I cum it all inside your mouth this time?
Just kidding.
I'll be sure to fuck you and cum inside your pussy.
I'd feel quite sorry for your wet pussy if I didn't.
It's not wet!
Not wet, Ayano?
But it's making this really sloppy sound.
N-No...
Somehow...
today feels even more amazing than before.
I knew my dick was your pussy's favorite.
What a nice view.
It's completely exposed.
Oh no, oh no...
Not there!
The way my dick feels in your pussy changes
as I change the position of your legs.
I really love it.
My legs?
But if you position it like that, its thickness will be more apparent.
Don't pinch them hard like that.
Oh, seems like you still can't be true to yourself, Ayano.
It actually feels really great for you, I know.
You liar.
Th-This is not good.
If this keeps up...
Maybe you still got some fight left in you?
How about opening up yourself more?
Will you? How about it? Ayano-chan?
Here goes.
Whoa, and she just came.
That was quite effective.
You even sounded like Yui-chan earlier.
So, Ayano, how does my dick feel?
It feels good...
Amazing,
your pussy just keeps on pulsating.
That's because...
This dick feels really amazing.
You really have a great body, Ayano.
I'm almost at my 100th shot.
But it feels like I'm still not satisfied with it.
My pussy... it's like I'm being skewered.
Alright, I'll cum lots until I pierce myself deeper inside you.
Do it do it, do it, do it!
Congratulations on your 100th shot, sensei.
Sensei, look.
That's your own dick.
This can't be real...
The dick will normally be a clit.
Just say 'Zip my Clit', stroke it for a while,
and then it will become a dick.
If you don't touch it for about 30 minutes,
it will turn back into your clit.
So, you'll only need to say the chant to-
Are you listening?
Amazing.
Really amazing.
Oh no, oh no.
S-So... how do I cum with this?
Huh?
You can't.
Eh?
If you want to cum with that dick,
you need to release the white stuff first.
But you don't have the testicles to do so, sensei.
That log alone isn't enough for you to ejaculate.
And if you can't cum well... you can't cum.
That, can't be...
How terrible!
No way... no way!
Well, there is another way.
If you can't produce your own cum,
Then the only method is to obtain it externally.
One shot can be stocked as a single ejaculation so...
If you take in some of mine, you'll be able to do it.
Morizumi-kun...
Though, if you want it to regularly cum, then...
This guy, is the worst.
What are you going to do, sensei?
No, not in this place...
Jeez, you're such a pushover.
Ayano-chan, it's the birthday schedule that we planned, right?
I don't care if you treat me like a toy or anything else.
Please, turn me into a woman.
I love you, Yui.
Yes.
Five shots yesterday, and two today,
with a grand total of seven shots.
I suppose that's going to be enough for their first night.
Make lots of love with that new dick, okay?
For our Yui-chan's sake.