Oh, another love letter.
Another?
What should I do, Ayano-sensei?
Hey, you can't do that!
Jeez, you always do stuff like that, Ayano-chan.
Just let me be.
No, Ayano-chan...
Female Teacher Chuuzenji Ayano's
Upcoming Sexual Frustrations
Part One
During her third year as an student here at Saint Joni Academy,
she became "reborn" as a lesbian, and I became her third girlfriend.
It's her first time dating someone so mature,
and I 'm even her teacher!
Also, we're...
No, not there...
Ayano-chan, if you keep that up I'll cum again with my ass.
Oh no...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Ayano-chan...
We're happy, even if this is a secret relationship...
But the contents of this memory stick are bothering me.
One week earlier, the old second school building
that housed all the unofficial dubs was due to be rebuilt.
I was supervising the transfer of items and
equipment from clubrooms at the time.
After scouring the building again after the items were transferred,
I found a memory stick tucked away in a container
in one of the abandoned clubrooms.
The contents of the stick were image files from a digital camera.
Pictures of girls who were having sex, with their own dicks...
Do you remember the words we said before, Yui?
Now this is unusual,
calling me out to a place like this at this time.
I want to ask you something, Tomoka.
This picture,
this is you right, the one with her penis right here.
You never had this thing before when we were dating.
Tell me, Tomoka, what's the meaning of this?
There's no turning back once I tell you all about it.
Are you prepared?
Alright, tell me then.
If you want to know more,
you'll have to visit a certain guy.
He's actually one of your students.
His name is...
Morizumi Kouki,
the president of the unofficial Black Magic
club, which had five active members.
Morizumi-kun, huh?
Well, he does have a reputation for being
one of the weirder students, but...
He's the one who gave a dick to Tomoka?
Students guidance room
So, why did you call me here, Chuuzenji Ayano-sensei?
How scary.
Did I do something bad?
Open the envelope.
Oh, this.
I was wondering where these went after we cleaned up the room.
So it was you, sensei...
So, is there a problem with this?
Sensei, do you...
Do you want to have a dick?
I want one.
Oh...
Anyway, even if we're the Black Magic club,
none of us can really use any magic.
We do our activities by using magical items
that we procure from a certain source.
The one we're about to use for you is this.
A magic root.
Let's just say it's a penis seed.
We'll then start a ritual that will make this
seed become a part of your clitoris.
You'll then let the seed grow until it becomes a fully grown dick.
It's the best experience you can have.
The sensation is really good,
and it's basically still a clit.
It only becomes like that when you want to use it.
Now, let's prepare.
Okay.
Like this, right?
I see, you're a lesbian, so you're totally
okay baring yourself in front of a male.
Of course I'm not fine with it!
Exposing myself in front of a guy, in front of my student, even.
Okay, shall we begin, sensei?
*unintelligible chant*
We're done, sensei.
The ritual was a success.
Everything went according to plan.
I'd like to ask who she is, for you to be so desperate to have a dick,
that you'd be willing to expose your pussy to your own student.
I'm sure she's one lucky girl.
J-Just forget about that, okay?
S-So, when will it grow enough for me to use it?
Well, that's...
Cum? You tricked me!
No, I didn't.
I told you earlier, right?
That it's a seed of sorts.
A seed requires water to grow, right?
We're trying to grow a dick here,
so its water has to be semen.
Until this magic root grows and becomes a dick,
we'll need to constantly pump cum into you.
As long as you meet the required amount, Ayano-sensei,
it'll grow into a full sized dick.
Morizumi-kun, you...
Oh, and I'll let you know that I've used my own cum for the rituals.
It's not going to work if it's not mine.
You're the worst.
Who the hell would do what you've said?
Stop fucking with me!
If the magic root doesn't receive nourishment within three days,
it'll disappear.
You have three days, sensei.
The number you just dialed may not be available, or is out of reach.
Jeez, what's with that Tomoka?
Why did I impulsively make that choice?
I let myself be swayed by her story and
blindly exposed myself to my student!
I lost myself when I saw her with a real dick.
Cum... so that means I need to have sex with him?
I just can't do that.
Wow, this is really flattering, inviting me over for this.
Umm, Morizumi-kun.
Yes, sensei?
Will this really make me grow a dick?
I promise it will.
Doing it once isn't enough,
but as long as it regularly receives cum,
then it will eventually be yours.
I swear this on my name, and my own life.
Then... this may be too late, but...
What happens today, and in the coming days,
don't tell this to...
I promise.
Okay, then.
I'm sorry, Yui.
Well then, I'll be glad to do it.
Don't you want a kiss, sensei?
Though it's still okay even if you're not too cooperative.
No...!
Wow, their size sure is amazing.
You're rumored to have the biggest tits in school, you know?
Oh? It feels even softer around the areola.
No, not there...
It's okay, it actually tastes good, sensei.
Don't!
No, I've been the one doing this for her, so my resistance to this is...
Also, what's with this guy?
He's just a student, and yet he's very good at caressing me.
So this is sensei’s... a female teacher's taste.
Your fingers,
no, not the fingers...
I won't stop.
I won't let him have his way with me...
Okay then, next is...
Here, sensei.
Sorry for the wait.
No way, what's with this dick?
It's too big!
I'll take on those bombastic tits first.
Oh, as I expected, it's like they were made for me.
It feels great.
The pressure feels just right.
It feels good.
I'll keep this up until I cum, okay?
What? W-Wait...!
How about the cum?
Please drink it.
You need to take it inside your body.
That's right, drink it.
Just keep drinking it.
That's good, sensei, suck it.
Suck it all.
Good work.
Oh, your body feels tender, sensei.
It's great.
Wait, I really... I really don't want this.
I don't want it inside me.
No...
I'll completely savor your pussy, Ayano-sensei.
Please enjoy my dick as well.
I said no!
This is good,
very good, sensei!
I never thought your body would be this good at fucking!
No...
It's really a waste that you've never been fucked with a dick before.
I'm going to have to use it for quite some time, though.
Don't...
Your moans sound really great, sensei.
But... oh no...
No use trying to hold it in.
Your pussy is making your womb touch my dick.
It's starting to hit me as I push.
I'll pour all my cum into this 'friendly' pussy.
Please take it all in, okay?
No, don't...
Not inside!
Yes, like this, sensei...
My insides, feel hot with his cum.
I'm sorry, Yui, I...
We'll need to do it at least one hundred times before it fully grows,
so that means we still have ninety-eight left.
Th-That much?
Then I won't make it.
Are you in some kind of rush?
Well, my dong here is quite special,
so I can fuck you or I can cum in your mouth several times a day.
But, do you have a plan or something?
Oh, I know!
It's going to be your lover's, Wada Yui's, birthday.
It's already next month, huh?
How did you...?