No · zo · ki · A · na
SubDESU Presents:
This spring, in order to get admitted to the design arts vocational school,
I headed to the big city.
Well, it's not like I wanted to pursue design arts seriously.
Okay, done.
All I wanted was an ordinary school life
in this peaceful city, but...
A hole?
She found me!
Damn...!
The neighbors weren't home when I went to greet them.
That was a woman, right?
Is it bad for me to drop by so suddenly?
In any case, I should at least calmly tell her about the hole in the wall.
I have to be firm in my honesty...
Be firm...
She's cute.
Umm... I'm your new neighbor, Kido.
Can we talk for a moment?
Hey, wait!
Ow!
Crap, this could make me look like an offender...
Hey...
What are you doing?
That's my line.
What are you  doing in a lone girl's room?
Give me that!
I'm going to scream.
I just came here to tell you about the hole!
So you found out.
You know, I'm very interested in naked bodies.
I can erase this photo.
However, I have one condition.
My name is Ikuno Emiru.
If it's okay with you,
would you like for us to show our bodies to each other?
Show our bodies to each other?
Wh–What do you mean?
We'll take turns peeping.
Let's see...
It's your turn during Mondays, Wednesdays and Fridays.
It'll be mine on Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays.
The one who gets peeped on has to act normal.
We'll show our bare selves to each other.
Do you understand how weird what you just said is?
Is it?
I don't want any part of this.
I'm going to seal up that hole.
Kido-san.
Kido Tatsuhiko-san.
Why is it that she knows my first name...?
Keep the hole the way it is, okay?
Do whatever you want!
We'll start at dawn.
I don't care,
this has nothing to do with me.
Anyway, I just have to show that I'm unfazed.
We'll take turns peeping.
According to the rule,
today's my turn to peep.
I'm just going to see how things are going.
Because my neighbor's a perverted woman, after all.
If you know you're being peeped at, you can't just calmly...
I'm never going to peep!
Never!
Ever!
I thought I had already decided on it, but...
Now let's head to the karaoke!
Let's go, everyone!
You're coming as well, Ikuno-san.
Let's go, let's go!
Is this for real?
Okay!
Did you all exchange numbers?
Oh, so you came to Tokyo from your hometown.
Y-Yeah.
Yoneyama-kun is from Tokyo, right?
You're his friend so I thought both of you attended the same high school.
I exchanged numbers with Tatsuhiko during the last summer school trip.
And, by the way,
I haven't known these people for that long.
Going on with introductions, my name's Kotobiki Yuri.
And that's...
Terakado Makiko,
pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Aren't you feeling lonely being so far from home?
Not at all.
Then, let's totally hang out
so that you won't ever feel lonely.
F-Full volume!
I'm going to have a nosebleed.
What's that?
And then it goes like...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm heading to the toilet for a bit.
So you won't sing, Tatsuhiko-san.
You knew, didn't you?
If you asked whether I knew that we were in the same school and same class,
then my answer would be "No".
If my neighbor is also my classmate, then I don't want to argue about it.
Would you at least treat it as if nothing happened?
I wouldn't like that.
However,
it's true that it'd be hard to continue it this way...
That's why I've thought about it.
About what?
We won't stop exhibiting ourselves to each other,
but we won't be involved any more than that.
How about that?
Do whatever you want!
I've got some shopping to do actually.
I'm also going to shop for a while.
Well then!
See ya tomorrow!
Okay, see you then.
You're staring too much.
No, it's not like that!
It's okay.
Ikuno-san's cute.
You were checking her out a lot today, weren't you?
The thought of you getting snagged by her was making me so jealous.
What does that...?
You're living alone, right?
Can I come over to your place?
I'm coming in!
You haven't eaten anything proper yet, have you?
I'm going to make something for you.
Honestly,
Kotobiki-san's absolutely my type.
The fact that she come to this place,
is enough to make my heart soar in delight.
If only that hole weren't there...
Kido-kun, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't have one.
I have a girl neighbor who likes peeping, though.
Emiru's probably still awake.
It's her turn to peep today.
No, no.
If I think about it carefully,
as long as nothing happens, it'll be fine.
Kotobiki-san probably doesn't want to do it so soon.
Your eyes are so honest that they dazzle me.
She's watching.
I knew it.
What's wrong, Tatsuhiko-kun?
If you're not going on the offensive,
then I will.
Hey...!
Wait, Kotobiki-san.
What was this called... voyeur sex?
It looks painful.
I'll pull out the poor thing.
Kotobiki-san, wait.
It's a bit rough on the floor,
do you want to place a futon on it first?
Okay.
Now we're out of Emiru's sight.
Now, let's continue.
This seems a bit weird.
That bitch...
So she really wants to see it!
What's wrong?
Well, I thought we'd have too little space after all.
I'm not letting you get away now.
Quite big, aren't they?
I usually have stiff shoulders because of these.
Hey, Tatsuhikio-kun,
do you like big breasts?
Yeah, of course.
The situation however isn't the best.
That's good.
I don't want to be splashed with water again.
What should I do?
Think.
Is there a way to break out of this?
You seem restless.
Thinking about your girlfriend back home?
T-That's not it.
It's okay.
You don't have to force yourself.
I have a sharp intuition you know.
Kotobiki-san.
If you don't call me Yuri-chan,
I'm going to tease you even more.
Yuri-chan...
Trapped by this helpless feeling of delight,
I'm starting to forget about the fact that Emiru is watching us.
Yuri-chan, I'm about to...
You found it this time, right?
Sorry, I don't have one with me.
I'm really sorry.
Geez, you need to be on top of these things.
Here we go.
I-I'll be more careful in the future.
I kinda feel extremely aroused with just the tip hitting me.
Yuri-chan...
It's insi–
Sorry about that.
Yes?
Yeah.
I already told you that I'm at my friend's place.
A girl.
I get it already.
Bye then.
It was my Dad.
I'll be heading home now.
Sorry.
Yo-Your Da–?
I'll accompany you there.
It's fine.
My place is nearby actually so don't worry.
But it's already late.
It's really fine.
If you treat me too gently,
I might fall for you.
Are you ready for that?
Go ahead.
You think I'm just joking, aren't you?
Good night.
Kotobiki-san.
Yes?
Stop fooling around already.
I know that you were peeping.
This is a serious matter!
It's the rule.
Yea a rule that you  made on your own!
But you were the one who told me to do whatever I wanted.
In other words, you accept anything I decide, right?
W-Well, that's because you took one crazy picture back then...
Why isn't she wearing any undies?
Anyway, just don't peep anymore.
Kido-san, you know,
I was masturbating while I was peeping.
When I imagine seeing your raw skin like that,
I feel drenched in the waves of ecstasy.
I've had it!
If you wanna squander that picture in public, then go right ahead with it!
Kido-san.
Keeping secrets from a woman is quite an awful thing you know.
Especially so if you hold deep feelings for her.
Imagine if she found out that instead of genuine love she was subjected to voyeuristic lust.
How do you think Kotobiki Yuri-san will handle it?
You can't seal up the hole.
This is the first time that I've wanted to hit a woman with these fists.
Me too, it's the first time that a man has shown me such a scary face.
And because she had yet again found another weakness to grasp,
I couldn't quell my anger.
I thought of sealing up the hole every now and then.
But eventually daily life caught up with me, and soon I found myself with less and less time,
to the point that I gradually became used to the situation.
Because of my part time job, I was only home after midnight.
And even in school I did not associate myself with Emiru.
Kotobiki-san, this is bad.
It's okay.
No one comes into this room.
Don't want to?
That's not it...
It's bad for your health to stay like this.
If you're fine with me, shall I squeeze it out?
Wait! I'm really glad, but it would be dangerous to do it here.
Then when do you plan on continuing what we couldn't finish that time?
Actually, I have my part-time job tonight...
A part-time job again?
How lonesome.
Then, if you get some free time, be sure to tell me, okay?
I can't tell her that I'm working hard so I can afford to take her to a love hotel.
For Emiru the rule is absolute.
For me, it's like the rule doesn't exist at all.
In other words,
I just have to keep myself from bringing people to my place.
Kido-kun.
Horii.
Seems like you're always checking Ikuno-san out.
Do you have a thing for her?
No way!
Then no matter how close I get to her,
you have no problem with it,
right?
Why are you concerned about me?
Ikuno Emiru-san is really charming.
I don't like it.
Makiko.
He really seems to be such a player.
Why?
He's good with people, and he's also good-looking.
That is exactly why.
That kind of person would definitely have an ulterior motive.
I kind of understand those things quickly.
Feels gross.
Then I'll ask you since you are good at observing people,
what do you think of Ikuno Emiru?
Are you going for her?
No, that's not it.
Really.
Absolutely.
Don't get too worked up.
Let's see...
I don't understand Ikuno Emiru.
That's it?
She's a cute girl on the outside but,
there are also parts of her that I don't understand,
even though she isn't really someone who usually holds ulterior motives.
It feels like she doesn't hide her own self.
Bullseye more or less.
But if you ask what's bothering me about her,
if I were to say one thing,
it would probably be the fact that you just can't ignore her presence.
Now I have my earnings for the day...
Today's my turn to peep.
She's inviting me.
She's trying to make me peep on her.
Damn!
Don't be fooled.
No matter what happens in there,
I'd instantly lose the moment I peep!
And if I do that,
I'd never be able to hold my ground against her!
You said that you wanted to discuss something about Kido-san.
I am quite curious, Hoorii-san.
You really have a soft spot for Kido-kun.
And you even let me into your place without any objection the moment I mentioned his name.
I'm a bit jealous.
I'm not fond of beating around the bush.
That's strict of you.
Actually, there's a huge rumor going around about Kido-kun.
They said that Kido-kun raped Kotobiki-san and made her his woman.
Seems like they're having fun.
That's a masterpiece!
Was it that funny?
Normally, people don't actually laugh after hearing stuff like this.
Might you be mirthful by nature, Ikuno-san?
You're really the worst.
That's something you'd do to beguile a person.
I'm not really in the position to say this,
but there's one thing that I really can't stand.
Horii Makoto-san, you're a bag full of lies
and you've never shown your true self.
You're the type that I hate the most.
What happened?
I did it.
Damnnit.
And here I decided I'd never peep through that hole again, yet...
Are you surprised?
This is my real hidden face.
Do you like me now?
How beautiful.
I wonder how sensitive this is.
I should have just gone out until they were done.
I just hate myself...
It has nothing to do with me...
I'm not going to peep in there again!
When the cup was broken, it made a really loud sound,
but the city is cruel, isn't it?
People don't care about anyone but themselves.
Oh, so you can cry?
Your arrogant attitude seems nothing but a farce.
It's a shame that I can't kiss you like this.
I really wanted to kiss those really tender lips.
What is this?
It looks like rape.
What? You're not even wet?
It's going to hurt when I do it.
What should I do?
I should already be saving her at this point.
But it's Emiru...
It might just be an act to fool me.
Damn!
I don't know what to do!
Still not giving up?
What a bothersome woman.
It's difficult to undress you with just one hand, you know.
You bitch...
So those were just crocodile tears after all?
The thought of bowing down to someone like you
was so pathetic that it made me cry.
You're really arrogant.
But heading for the window instead of the door,
shows that you're actually flustered, despite your calmness.
Are you prepared already?
I won't escape.
Just do it if you can.
You won't be able to act like that anymore.
Once I make a woman mine, they become submissive.
Make me yours?
You sure can boast even though it's so small.
Kido-san's thing is far more magnificent.
Stop saying Kido's name!
Shut up!
Hey you, could this be...
your first time?
What was that?
What was that sound?
Is it the neighbor's house?
Damn.
I'm going home for today.
But now I've really taken a liking to you, Emiru-chan.
See you again.
Would there be another time for us to talk?
There will be.
It hurts.
Hey, are you alright?
Come in.
I'm coming in.
Umm...
Here, you can't wake up if you don't have this.
To be honest, you really saved me.
I tried acting strong,
but my heart was about to break.
So you were watching me after all, weren't you?
That's the thing that I really didn't want to hear.
I lost my resolve and ended up peeping, so I'm pissed at myself.
So, is that part safe?
That part?
Yeah "that part"!
You get it, right?
This is bad!
The things that I shouldn't be saying are flowing out of my mouth.
Confirm it for yourself.
If you weren't here,
this body would have been violated anyway.
Think of it as a token of my gratitude.
Go ahead.
That's what I hate about you.
That's what I like about you, Kido-san.
I should go home now.
Kotobiki-san.
Hey, call me Yuri.
Wait...Kotobiki-san, we can't...
Why so suddenly...
She drank it.
I'll remember your taste now.
Let's continue it tonight.
I wonder why...
I'm feeling this cold.
Earlier, when Kotobiki-san was sucking it,
it reacted intensely.
I know the cause.
It's Emiru.
After witnessing how Horii tried to rape Emiru,
it clearly showed me how sex can easily turn into violence.
Oh crap.
It has become a kind of trauma.
It's not responding at all.
If it doesn't get up,
she might get sick of me
and finally dump me.
Call
Ikuno Emiru
Oh yeah, Yoneyama made us all exchange our numbers at the karaoke.
Yes?
Kido-san?
You haven't returned to your room.
Are you at a love hotel with Kotobiki Yuri-san?
Maybe I'm interrupting you?
If that was the case, I wouldn't be answering your call.
That is true.
If you don't have anything more to say, I'm hanging up.
Ikuno Emiru
Thanks for saving me yesterday.
I just wanted to show you my gratitude again.
I didn't really...
If you think that I saved you back then,
you are welcome.
She's unexpectedly gentle.
So she can be polite at times.
I've been fantasizing about it.
If you were the one trying to do me at that time...
... I think I would've happily accepted your advances.
As I thought about that,
while playing with myself,
I climaxed three times!
Stop fucking with me!
I'm hanging up.
Kido-san.
I'll reserve "my hole" and keep it open for you.
If you want to peep at it, you may do so anytime.
I really hate you after all, idiot!
Who are you talking to?
The one you hate... It can't be me, right?
Hey, wait!
What happened to you?
It was so intense that I was a bit surprised.
Kotobiki-san,
I like you.
Kotobiki-san.
No, Yuri-chan.
I like you.
I'm going to take good care of you.
Please go out with me.
We kissed and you put your tip inside me,
then you came in my mouth and we kissed again.
And now a confession?
You're too serious.
It's the first time I've met someone like you.
Yuri-chan.
Now I'm really struck emotionally,
because you said something so weird, Tatsuhiko-kun.
Sorry.
I need you inside me right now.
Let's feel good together.
It's really getting big.
I'm happy.
I noticed it then.
That my manhood had completely recovered before I even realized.
The fragment of sympathy that I had for Emiru,
had turned into anger because of her phone call.
I wasn't able to hold my desire for Kotobiki-san
and now I'm about to burst out.
From now on, I will think of this girl only, Yuri-chan,
and fill my mind with her.
What a beautiful moon.
It's like a peeping hole pierced out from the sky.
If only I could peep through it to where Kido-san is...
Shouko-sensei, thanks for the meal!
It must be a lot of work to have treated all of us here.
Sorry if it was too cheap for a treat.
It's a feast as long as sensei is here!
But is it okay for you to be here with your students?
Well, it is specified that teachers aren't supposed to get too close to the students,
but wouldn't that be a bit too unfriendly?
I know, right?
Besides, it's rather difficult to go into these kinds of places alone.
Sensei, you're still quite young, so why don't you come with a boyfriend?
Oh, so your boyfriend looks really mature then.
That's right, he's quite a grown man...
Just kidding!
It's actually quite tough to always have middle-aged men fall for you.
How Cool!
Shouko-sensei seemed like a grown-up woman earlier.
Not "seemed", I am  a grown-up woman!
Even though Shouko-sensei's older, she still radiates an aura of loveliness.
Getting worked up like that is just indecent.
When can we be alone together again?
How about later today, after this?
Okay, got it.
Here, look at this.
Eh? But I don't like stuff like that.
I'm sure it would look good.
Excuse me, I'll buy this please.
Okay, please bring the item here.
See, it does  look good!
Really? Thanks then.
I'll be going home now then.
My Dad's been bugging me about spending time with my family this weekend, sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'll look forward to next time.
See you after the weekend!
I remember she was also like this last week.
Kido-san, are you on your way home?
What have you been doing up until this time?
I can do whatever I want, right?
Kido-san hurry, the signal's going to change.
Why do I have to go home with you?
What's the matter so suddenly?
Shh.
What do you mean by that?
You understand, right?
How can I understand?
Stop fooling around already!
More of your bad habits?
Put a leash on your peeping already
Eh? Shouko-sensei.
Kido-kun, and Ikuno-san?
Good evening.
And so, she told us about the adulterous affair
while trying to keep herself composed.
I understood that my partner already has a spouse and a child.
But I just couldn't help myself.
I just reaped what I sowed.
After putting on make-up and donning a formal suit,
I was determined to be how a woman in her 28th year should be.
But in romance its different.
Complications are slowly piling up
And I'm getting a lot worse.
God sure is cruel.
He never seems to choose a perfect match for me.
But...
The Shouko-sensei in front of us speaking sorrowfully
already looked very mature to me.
Sorry for making you hang out with me.
Sensei, if it's okay, would you like to exchange numbers?
Just in case anything happens.
You too, Kido-san.
Huh...You're just rude, aren't you?
While I'm not capable of giving advice,
I can at least listen to whatever you have to say.
Well, I guess I can't simply act tough anymore, eh?
Here.
Why did things escalate to this?
I don't understand at all.
She is still a child.
Perhaps even more than me or Kotobiki-san.
Huh?
I'm sure she'll try to call you.
And I assume that it will happen within the next three days.
Are you stupid?
That won't happen.
No one wants to show their weak side to the same gender, right?
Stop saying random stuff.
So you don't understand anything at all.
You might be the one who's the most child-like.
Child-like...
At that time, I thought
that it was just her usual bluffs or remarks.
Until the end of my part-time job the very next day...
I'll leave ahead now!
This ringtone is for calls, then its...
Yuri-chan?
It's Yuri-chan!
No it's not you idiot!
Makiko?
It's Makiko! No it's not either!
You're quite popular, eh?
Is this a prank call?
Honnami Shouko
Shouko-sensei?
That's right! It's Shouko!
I'm on my way now,
so fetch me at the station.
In 10 minutes, okay? 10 minutes!
Shouko-sensei?
What's with her?
I'm sure she'll try to call you.
And I assume that it will happen within the next three days.
In the end, I just couldn't hand her over to the police and get away.
So I brought her to my apartment.
She really reeks of alchohol!
Just in case, I tried to consult Emiru about this, but...
As I thought, she's totally ignoring me.
Well, it's a good chance for her to peek anyway.
I guess it can't be helped.
It's Saturday today.
It's her day to peek.
Her eyes are there.
And just this time, its a relief that she's there.
Kotobiki-san, I'm sorry!
This is not cheating, right?
So this is Kido-chan's room.
It reeks of alcohol, right?
Sorry about that.
I already have Kotobiki-san and yet,
I'm doing this with sensei, this is really bad!
Emiru.
She's there, watching...
Oh, my stockings have been ripped.
It's such a pain so I'll just rip it all off.
I'll rip all of it.
Even an adult's emptiness,
and the walls between her and a student, okay?
Shouko-sensei, you're too drunk.
I was a fool for being relieved
thinking that Emiru is in there.
She's my enemy after all!
What's wrong, Kido-kun?
Sensei, I said you're too drunk!
I'm sober. you know.
She stinks of alcohol!
I even remember how to do it.
How to do it?
How to please a man!
Here's some boobies!
Huh, you won't suck it?
Just suck it already!
Just wait up!
Oh, escaping eh? Gotcha!
Good boy.
Now let's do some really good things.
Good boy, good boy.
What a huge mushroom!
It feels good...
But what is this mood?
Shall I eat the mushroom now?
Oh yeah
She's a child.
Just like what Emiru said.
That Emiru,
So she  is peeping right now.
You just laughed earlier!
That wasn't me!
Okay, let's put it in!
I'm already prepared for this today!
No, we really can't do this!
Ouch!
That hurts.
Now I've got a cut.
How bad of you.
I'm sorry.
How very bad of you.
Everything really ended earlier.
What kind of world is this?
God really has made the wrong match after all.
I'll never fall in love again.
Now I understand.
She's been having meaningless sex
with a meaningless partner.
And she wanted something to fill those lonely nights.
That's not true!
Kido-kun?
I'm sure, there is still next time!
If god is even unwilling to give opportunities
to someone who is willing to truly like another person just like you sensei,
I'll smack a few words out of that ass god.
I don't have that kind of willpower anymore.
Then I'll go in your stead!
So sensei...
Sensei?
Shouko-sensei?
Hey, you kidding me, right?
Awake already?
Where am I?
I remember being drunk, and then...
Good morning, Shouko-sensei.
Ikuno-san?
Why am I here?
Didn't you call me on the phone?
I was a bit surprised.
Here, have some coffee.
Thank you.
You were quite something last night.
You got really drunk.
Thanks to that, I was able to witness different sides to you.
Seems like I have imposed myself here.
Sorry about that.
No, it was fun.
Oh yes, the ripped stocking,
it was already unusable so I disposed of it.
Shall I go with you to the station?
No, I'll just take the taxi.
See you then.
See you.
Tanabe
Was this alright?
Yes.
She would have been guilty of her own actions if she were to wake up at your place.
She didn't remember a thing?
Even if she did, you can just put it aside with a little lie.
As long as we don't say anything,
that will be the truth.
This is uncommon of you.
I thought you were the type that hate lies and fabrications.
I hate them.
But a sweet lie that would not hurt anyone,
it wouldn't be bad to have one of those once in a while.
That's what I thought when I saw you.
I did call Ikuno-san, but...
What's this?
Okay, let's go Tatsuhiko!
Here it goes!
You jerk!
You sure are bad at this!
Sorry bout that!
Don't throw it back at me!
Crumpled papers aren't balls you know!
Here.
Thank you, sensei.
Thank you too.
Huh?
And to God as well.
I'll just smack him with my own words!
The relieved smile on Shouko-sensei
looked even more mature than before.
Did she find out already?
After that, I became confused.
Ikuno Emiru, the one who told the "sweet lie" for sensei's sake.
I have always thought of her as a demon,
but I wonder what kind of girl she really is.
I can't endure anymore...
Let's do it already...
I can't wait either!
Seriously? These guys are getting it on in a place like this!
Hey, hey, hey.
This one's getting turned on already.
Yoneyama invited all of us during the summer vacation, to the beach.
It's the summer sea where everyone comes to play.
You're not going in, Yuri-chan?
My skin turns red when I'm under the sun.
Hey...
...don't you think I'm the best one on this beach?
Wow, those are some amazing breasts.
That's a great woman.
That would be natural of course!
Do you really mean that?
Emiru?
Where is she going all alone?
I'm going to buy some drinks.
O-Okay.
I'm certain she went this way.
Storage
What are you looking for?
Don't surprise me like that!
No one called you here.
I was just tired of the sun and the stares from the people.
Are you worried about me?
Well, since everyone came here.
It'd ruin the mood if someone suddenly got sick.
Wait...
Hey, are we really going to do it here?
What? I want to enjoy this summer!
You're a man, yet why are you acting like a wimp?
Y-You idiot!
Who's getting hesitant here, huh?
Not only are we hiding in this locker, we are also peeping at the same time.
What the heck is this situation?
Aunt! One Blue Hawaii, please!
I want a Red Bean Milk!
It's hot.
How hot is it inside this locker?
We're going to faint here before they even finish.
Yes!
But it feels really arousing to watch other people having sex...
Wait, what am I thinking?!
I just synced my mind with Emiru's!
This is bad.
When did it start to grow stiff?
Wait, wait.
Just how close are you planning to cling on to me?
You idiot, stop that!
Try doing it from behind...
I'm... I'm... I'm about to...
Hey! Don't use someone else's cock to masturbate!
Ouch!
Did you say something?
Nope, I didn't.
It's just my imagination then.
Yep, just your imagination.
Let's go swim!
Yeah!
How about we do it in the sea next time?
I don't want to!
That wasn't your imagination...
This feels great!
Kido-san?
I'm sorry.
I ended up biting you in the shoulder.
So apparently I gave you a hickey.
It was the first time I felt that good.
My mind was so blank I was about to faint.
I'm sure that it was because I was in your arms.
You really have a large strike zone when it comes to sexually satisfying yourself, don't ya?
Are you not going to get angry like you always do?
It's hot so I don't care.
It was hot...
Really, so much that we could've died...
It was so hot that even I didn't want to keep peeping.
This is the first time I've heard you whine at something.
What's that for?
Geez.
Stop it, I said!
Take this!
It's cold.
Should we head back to the hotel?
Y-Yeah.
This guy...
He was the one who wanted to tell ghost stories...
We haven't even started and he's already asleep.
He's tired from swimming.
He was playing around since morning.
That's right.
I'm also tired too.
I'm going to sleep now.
Me too.
Then I'll carry Yoneyama and head back to our room.
Isn't it alright just sleeping here?
Eh?
Let's just huddle together.
So many things happened today,
that I could fall asleep at any time...
It kinda smells good...
Yuri-chan...
This is bad!
I can't hear you~
You thought that my bikini was irresistible, right?
I knew.
L-Let's use an empty room if we're going to do it.
No.
I want to do it here.
Tada!
It's my first time doing it in a situation like this.
My heart is beating really fast!
It'd be bad if someone notices us.
We have to finish this quickly.
Hey, you're too intense.
My voice is going to get us noticed.
S-Sorry.
Are you trying to finish quickly?
It's okay.
Everyone's so tired that they're fast asleep.
Besides, they already know about us.
If we're seen, then so be it.
I saw it earlier.
You were having a good time with Ikuno-san.
So... So she saw us...
No, that's...
No escaping!
I'm not letting you go until you cum so hard that you rip the condom apart.
I-I understand.
Yoneyama won't be a problem, and Makiko is also fast asleep.
The problem would be Emiru...
Oh man, we are totally putting up a show for someone...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
Damn, I was so conscious when she peeped from a hole,
but being stared at directly is an intense pressure in it's own league!
Peeping seems to be a really arousing experience.
When we peeped at that couple earlier,
I was totally dazed and was rock hard.
And now, when someone is watching us...
This can't be!
My mind is becoming more like Emiru's!
I won't be able to call her a pervert anymore!
Emiru?
Did you cum?
My insides are really the best after all, right?
I'm sorry, Kotobiki-san.
I'm the worst.
Tada!
I bought new clothes!
Yuri-chan! Those clothes are really cute!
That's good, that's good!
Hey, what do you think Tatsuhiko-kun?
Yep, it looks really cute.
It must be nice to look cute in that kind of dresses... I'm jealous!
I came while fantasizing about Emiru.
It's because I started pondering over something weird in the middle of sex.
I don't really think of Emiru as someone special,
and I'm definitely not interested in peeping...
... or at least that's what I want to believe.
But the image of Emiru, who I had been trying to remove from my mind,
started to appear unconsciously before me.