I moved to the city this spring to attend design college.
It's not because I have any real passion for design.
There, done.
I just wanted to move to the city
and live like a normal college student.
A hole?
She saw me!
Shit!
Ikuno
There was no one home when
I tried introducing myself earlier.
Ikuno
So my neighbor is a woman?
I guess I can't just go off on her.
I'll just tell her politely that there's a hole in the wall.
I must remain firm. Firm.
Sh... She's cute.
Uh, I'm Kido and I live next door.
Is it all right if we talk?
Uh, wait!
Yow!
Crap...
this now makes me an assailant.
Wh-What are you doing?
What are you doing barging into a woman's apartment?
Give me that!
I'll scream.
I only came to warn you about the hole!
Guess you caught me.
I really like seeing people in their candid state.
I'm willing to erase the photo
on one condition.
My name is Ikuno Emiru.
How would you like to expose ourselves to each other?
Expose ourselves? What?
We each take turns peeping on each other, so...
you take Mondays, Wednesdays, and Fridays,
and I take Tuesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays.
We must both ignore the fact we're being watched and expose who we really are.
Look, do you have any idea
how crazy you're sounding?
Is it crazy?
Count me out!
I'm covering up that hole!
Kido-san?
Kido Tatsuhiko-san?
How does she know my first name?
Don't cover up the hole.
F... Fine, whatever!
We'll start first thing in the morning.
I don't care. She can do what she wants.
All I have to do is act casual.
We each take turns peeping in on each other.
According to the rules, it's my turn today.
I'm just checking in on her.
I am living next to some freaky girl.
I can't rest easy thinking I'm being watched—
No more peeping!
Never! Not for anything!
Suga Design School
At least that's what I swore off.
Let's do some karaoke! Let's make it a mixer!
Come with us, Ikuno-san!
Yeah, come!
Are you kidding me?
Great! We've officially exchanged contact info!
So you came to Tokyo from the countryside?
Uh, yeah.
But Yoneyama-kun lives in Tokyo!
I thought you two went to the same school since you're pals.
Me and Tatsuhiko exchanged contacts during a field trip one summer.
But me and Horii met just today!
So you remember me, Kotobiki Yuri.
And she's...
Terakado Makiko. Glad to meet.
Same here.
Still, don't you feel homesick here in Tokyo?
No way.
Well, I'll make sure you never feel lonely here, okay?
Sh... She's stacked!
How about we start off with something easy? Can we?
My nose is bleeding...
Then what about Nikugori's "Charan"?
What?
You know the one that goes
"Pururun! Pururun! Pu-ru-ru-run!"
Is something wrong?
Never heard of it.
Uh, nah.
What, you haven't?
It's everywhere, man! Like in commercials and stuff!
I need to use the restroom.
Yeah!
I guess I'll list—
You're not singing, Tatsuhiko-san.
So you knew.
If you're saying I knew we shared the same class at the same school,
the answer is "no."
If my neighbor is also my classmate, then I don't want any trouble.
Can't we just forget the whole thing?
Sorry, can't do that!
This does make things awkward, though...
So I've been thinking.
About what?
We won't stop exposing ourselves to each other.
However, that's where we'll draw the line.
So, what do you think?
Fine! Whatever!
I need to do some shopping.
Me too!
All right, see you tomorrow!
You do? Okay, see you later!
Now you're staring.
No, I wasn't!
I don't mind. Ikuno-san's cute.
I've been thinking about her the whole day,
wondering if she's going to beat me to the punch.
Uh, what do you mean?
You live by yourself, don't you?
Can I come over?
Coming through!
Are you even eating right?
I'll cook us a light supper.
Uh, sure.
Honestly speaking,
Kotobiki-san is just my type of girl.
I would be dancing for joy
knowing that she came over,
if it weren't for that damn hole.
Do you have a girlfriend, Kido-kun?
No, I don't!
But I do have a girl next door who's a damn voyeur.
Emiru is probably awake.
Today's her turn to peep.
No, get a grip!
I can just assume nothing's going to happen.
Kotobiki-san's probably not here for that anyway.
Your eyes are so honest and bright.
Sh... She's watching...
She has to be!
What's wrong, Tatsuhiko-kun?
If you won't make the move, then I will.
Uh, wait... Kotobiki-san?
Th... This is turning into a peepshow!
Oh, something's happening down here.
I'll relieve the stress and let it out.
Kotobiki-san, wait!
I don't like doing it on the floor.
Let's spread a futon, okay?
Sure.
This should be in Emiru's blind spot.
Okay, let's resume.
This is kind of weird.
That bitch!
"All we're doing is peeping" huh?
What's wrong now?
Yeah, um... I feel cramped over here.
This time you're not getting away!
Big, aren't they?
They make my shoulders stiff.
So, Tatsuhiko-kun, do you like them big?
Uh, yes... of course.
I'm not liking the situation, though.
That's great!
But I don't want to get hit with water again.
What should I do? Think!
Think!
There must be something I can do...
You're not really into this.
Were you thinking about an old girlfriend?
O-Of course not.
It's fine, you don't have to lie.
I can tell.
Kotobiki-san...
Call me Yuri-chan.
Or else I'll mess with you more.
Y-Yuri-chan...
What she was doing felt so fucking good,
I began to forget that Emiru was even watching.
Yuri-chan... I'm gonna...
Are you wearing a condom?
Sorry, I don't have any.
I apologize.
What were you thinking? God...
Here.
I-I'll be careful next time.
Just feeling your tip is turning me on.
Yuri-chan...
It's coming...
Sorry.
Hello?
Yeah.
I'm at a friend's place.
A girl friend.
I know!
I'll see you.
It's my dad.
Sorry, I have to leave.
Y-Your dad?
I-I'll take you.
Don't worry.
I live around here, so I'll be fine.
But it's late.
I'll be fine.
Besides, I might fall in love with you if you're too nice to me.
Do you want that?
Go ahead.
You think I'm joking, aren't you?
Good night.
Kotobiki-san...
Yes?
That's it, I've had enough!
I know you were watching! I can't deal with this crap!
Those are the rules.
Rules that you made up!
But you said I can do whatever.
That means you accepted the rules.
Th-That's because you still have that photo...
Why isn't she wearing underwear?
A-Anyway, no more peeping.
Kido-san, while I was watching,
I was fingering myself.
Just knowing I was watching you live was very arousing.
Fuck this, I'm done!
Show that photo to whoever the hell you want!
Kido-san...
Girls hate it when people keep secrets from them.
Especially if that girl has a thing for you.
If she knows that you let me peep in, however unwillingly...
I wonder what Kotobiki Yuri-san would say.
Don't cover the hole.
Th...
This is the first time I've wanted to raise my fist to a girl.
And that's the first time a guy's
given me such a threatening look.
I couldn't contain my anger knowing that Emiru had me by the balls again.
I told myself repeatedly that I'd cover up that hole.
But since we humans are such fickle creatures, my anger soon subsided with time,
and I actually became used to the situation.
I began working part-time, and never got off until late.
Emiru and I never talked, not even at school.
Kotobiki-san... this isn't right!
Don't worry. Almost nobody comes in here anyway.
Don't you want to?
It's not that I don't...
Your poor thing's practically suffocating.
Maybe I should let it out for some air.
Th-Thanks, but we really shouldn't do it here.
Then when can we continue where we left off?
Sorry, but I got work tonight...
What? Again?
That blows!
Be sure to tell me when you're free!
Too bad I can't tell you I took that job so I can afford a hotel with you.
Emiru still thinks the rules are the rules.
However, those rules no longer affect me.
That means I'm no longer inviting girls over.
Kido-kun.
Horii!
Ikuno-san's always on your mind,
isn't she? Are you in love with her?
Hell no!
So that means you have no problem if I make my move on her. Right?
Why are you even warning me?
Ikuno Emiru-san is a stunning girl.
I don't like him.
Makiko?
I think he's too much of a frat boy.
Why's that? I think he's sociable and good looking.
There you go. His kind always has a hidden side.
He just gives off that feeling, and it creeps me out.
Okay, since you can read people so well, what do you think of Ikuno Emiru?
You want her too?
No way! Honest! I swear!
Calm down, tiger. Let's see...
I don't get her.
Why?
She looks cute, but sometimes you don't know what she's thinking.
But she doesn't seem like someone who hides stuff from people,
heck, it's almost like she
doesn't want to hide anything.
Yeah, that's her all right.
But there's definitely something about her.
It's like you can't really ignore her.
I sure earned my pay today.
Today's my turn to peep.
She let him in just so I can watch!
Shit! Don't fall for her trap!
It doesn't matter what they're doing
next door, one look and I'm done for!
If that happens, I'll have no right to criticize her!
So you want to talk about Kido-san?
You have no idea how curious that makes me.
You seem to be pretty infatuated with him.
After I said that, you immediately let me in.
I'm a little jealous, actually.
I don't like beating around the bush.
You're harsh.
Actually, I heard some very bad stuff about Kido-kun.
Rumor has it he raped Kotobiki-san and now has a hold on her.
Sounds like she's having fun.
That's priceless!
Is that so hard to believe?
I don't think it's something to laugh at.
Are you a laughing drunk?
You really are a scumbag.
I'm not talking about how you're trying to trick me.
I can't really throw any stones myself.
But there's one thing I can't stand.
Horii Makoto-san, you're full of lies.
You never show your true self.
You're the type of guy I hate the most.
What the?
What did I just do? Fuck!
I thought I said I wouldn't look!
Surprised? This is who I really am.
Are you starting to like me?
Very nice.
I wonder how sensitive they are?
I should have just taken a walk till she was done.
God, I hate myself.
None of my business. None of my business.
I'm not peeping in again.
You almost scared me off by breaking that cup.
But thank god we live in a city where nobody looks out for each other.
Oh? Is this you crying?
Guess all that haughtiness earlier was just a bluff!
Too bad I can't kiss you
on those soft, pouty lips of yours.
What is this? Is he raping her?
What the hell? You aren't even wet!
It's gonna hurt when we get it on.
Wh-What should I do?
I know I should save her!
But maybe this is all an act she's putting on.
Fuck, what should I do?
Still struggling? God, you're a chore.
It's not easy stripping you with one hand you know.
You cunt!
So you weren't really crying?
I was only crying at the thought that you are pathetic enough
to think you could take advantage of me.
So you are a goddamn brat.
But you still went for the window instead of the door,
meaning you're not actually thinking straight.
Are you gonna shut up and take it?
I won't run.
If you think you can do it, go ahead and try.
You'll be singing a different tune real soon.
You girls always learn your place once I own you!
How can you "own" me when you don't even own much down there?
Kido-san was much bigger.
Stop talking about him!
Now shut up!
Wait, don't tell me...
Is this your first time?
Wh-What the?
Who made that sound? Is that from a neighbor?
Shit!
I'm leaving, for now!
But you've only made me want you more, Emiru-chan.
Catch you later.
Do you think I'll have anything to do with you anymore?
Oh yeah.
He hurt me.
Hey.
Hey, you all right?
Come in.
Thanks.
So, um...
Here.
You'll need this to wake up tomorrow.
You really did save me back there.
I know I put up a front, but I was actually glad.
You were watching me, weren't you?
That was the last thing I wanted to hear from her.
I was pissed off at myself for giving in and peeking.
I hope he didn't take your... you know.
My what?
You know what I'm talking about! God!
Crap! I didn't even have to say any of that!
You can check for yourself.
I would have been raped anyway if it weren't for you.
Think of it as a "thank you."
Go ahead.
I really hate it when you do that!
Well I really like this side of you, Kido-san.
Dammit.
I'll head home.
Kotobiki-san!
It's "Yuri," remember?
God... Kotobiki-san, what's...
with you?
She swallowed... my load!
I remembered how you taste like.
Let's finish off where we started.
God, why am I not all that into this?
Kotobiki-san gave me great head, but...
Who am I kidding?
It's Emiru.
I witnessed her almost getting raped by Horii,
and saw vividly that sex can be pretty damn violent.
Fuck. That actually traumatized me.
Now I can't get it up for the life of me.
If I can't get hard, she's going to get up and walk out on me!
Calling
Ikuno Emiru
Emiru?
Calling
Ikuno Emiru
Oh yeah. Yoneyama had us exchange contacts at the karaoke bar.
Yeah?
Kido-san? You're not back home.
Are you at a love hotel with Kotobiki Yuri-san?
Are you two going at it?
I wouldn't pick up if we were.
I suppose you're right.
Tell me what you want or I'm hanging up!
Thank you for what you did last night.
BBBBBBBB
Ikuno Emiru
I wanted to say that again.
Don't worry, as long as you think I helped.
That was pretty nice of her.
I guess she would be after that.
I've been imagining if you were the rapist that night.
I would have gladly let you have your way with me.
That's making me touch myself...
and I came three times!
Don't fuck with me! I'm hanging up!
Kido-san,
I'll always have my hole open for you.
If you want to see what's inside, by all means.
I fucking hate your guts! Go to hell!
Who are you talking to?
I hope it's not my guts you hate.
H-Hey!
What's with you all of a sudden?
You're so rough you caught me off guard.
Kotobiki-san,
I love you.
Kotobiki-san...
I mean, Yuri-chan... I love you.
I'll treasure you forever.
Be my woman.
So you kissed me, inserted the tip,
got sucked off, then kissed me again, and now you love me?
You're such a boy scout.
I've never met anyone like you.
Yuri-chan?
That actually made me super hot.
God, why did you have to say that?
Sorry.
Hurry up and stick it in. Let's sex each other up.
That's... really big!
Oh god!
That's when I realized,
that I fully regained my functions as a man.
Whatever sympathy I had for Emiru
turned into rage after that phone call.
And I...
was filled with an uncontrollable primal lust for Kotobiki-san.
From now on, she'll be the only girl...
Yuri-chan will be the only girl I'll think about.
The moon looks beautiful.
It's like one big peephole in the night sky.
I only wish I could peep in on Kido-san out there.
Burgers
Thanks for the food, Shouko-sensei!
Sorry you had to pick up the entire tab.
Burgers
I'm sorry I took you to such a cheap place.
It's always a treat to be with you!
Are you sure you it's okay to eat here with your students?
Officially, us professors are told not to be too chummy with our students.
But I think that's too strict of a rule.
Yeah, you got that right!
I also find it hard to come to these places alone at my age anyway.
But you're still young, Sensei.
Can't you just go with a boyfriend?
I bet your boyfriend is a real man!
Yeah, he's a... real man.
Yeah right!
I only attract middle-aged men, it's not even funny!
Wow! That's cool!
Shouko-sensei, you sounded
like a grown woman just now!
That's because I am a grown woman!
Shouko-sensei's pretty cute for an older woman.
Ugh. She's acting cute around children.
When's the next time we can get together, alone?
Okay, how about today, after we're done here?
Sure, sounds like a plan.
Hey, how about this?
What? I've never worn that!
I'll look great on you!
Excuse me, can we have this?
Oh, that one, eh?
I told you it'd look good!
You think so? Thanks.
I think I'll be heading home.
My dad's been bugging me to spend the weekend with the family. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine, really.
I'll be looking forward to
the next time we hook up.
See you next week!
Uh, right.
This was the same thing that happened last week.
Kido-san? Are you going home?
What were you doing so late into the night?
None of your business!
Oh, Kido-san! Hurry, the light's about to change!
Why do I have to go home with you?!
God, what now?
Shh!
Food & Fun
Come on!
I don't wanna hear it!
You know what this is!
No, I don't!
Please, be reasonable!
You gotta learn to quit. This is no time for snooping.
Save it, jerk!
Huh?
Shouko-sensei?
Food & Fun
Kido-kun? Ikuno-san?
Good evening.
Sensei told us about her affair while
struggling to maintain a cheery disposition.
I knew he had a wife and children.
But I couldn't stop myself.
I guess I deserve it.
I know how to wear makeup and I wear suits.
At 28, I should have no problem knowing how to conduct myself as an adult.
But when it comes to romance...
it seems like everything gets
complicated and I make it worse.
The gods sure are cruel.
They never seem to give me
someone that'll make me happy.
However, the way Shouko-sensei talked with that pained look on her face
made her seem pretty adult to me.
Sorry you had to keep me company.
Sensei, how would you like to exchange numbers?
Just in case anything happens.
You too, Kido-san.
H-Hey, you're being rude!
I won't be able to give you any advice, but I can lend an ear.
You're right. I can't keep up that facade anymore.
Here.
Why is this happening? I don't get it!
She was such a child.
She's probably more of a child than Kotobiki-san or me.
What?
I'm sure she'll be calling you soon.
Yeah, I'd give it about three days.
Get real. She'll never do that.
She wouldn't want to show her weakest moments to another woman, would she?
Now you're just being random.
You're so clueless.
You might be the most immature out of us.
Immature?
At the time, I thought Emiru was just talking shit like she always had.
That is, until I got off work the next night.
I'll see you!
That ring tone's for a phone call! Could it be...
Yuri-chan?
Yes, this is Yuri-chan!
Not! Who the hell's that?
Makiko?
Yes, it's Makiko! No it's not!
You're quite the ladies' man!
What the? A prank call?
Honnami Shouko
Shouko-sensei?
Got it in three! It's Shouko!
I'm heading out right now. Meet me at the station.
I'll be there in ten, you hear me?
Shouko-sensei?
What happened to her?
I'm sure she'll be calling you soon.
Yeah, I'd give it about three days.
I decided not to let the police handle it...
and took her to my apartment.
You really reek of alcohol.
I tried seeing if Emiru could help.
So she's blowing me off?
Guess she doesn't wanna miss this chance to peep.
Fuck it.
Today's Saturday, Emiru's turn to peep.
That's where she's looking through.
This time, I'm actually glad she's seeing this.
Kotobiki-san, forgive me!
This doesn't count as cheating, does it?
So this is your apartment, eh?
I must reek of booze, right?
I'm sorry.
Kotobiki-san is my girlfriend.
I can't do this with Sensei!
Emiru?
She's there! She's looking!
Aww, my pantyhose ripped.
I'll just tear them off since they're in the way.
I'll just strip it all off.
Both my grown-up mask, and the pretence of a student-teacher relationship, ‘kay?
Sh... Shouko-sensei, you're too drunk.
I was a dumbass thinking having Emiru as an eyewitness would be my lifeline.
I mean, she's the enemy!
What's wrong, Kido-kun?
Like I said, Sensei, you're too drunk!
I'm totally thinking clearly!
There's that beer breath!
I know everything a girl can do.
To do what?
To please her man, silly!
Hi, see these boobs?
Aren't you gonna suck on them?
Come on, suck ‘em!
Hey, time out!
Hey, come back here!
Whoo-hoo!
Gotcha!
Good boy! You deserve a reward!
Good boy, good boy...
Looks like I found a huge mushroom!
This feels awesome.
But what's with this foreplay?
Maybe I should eat Kido-tan's mushroom.
That's right, she's a kid.
Just like Emiru said she was.
Emiru must be watching the whole thing!
Hey, you're laughing!
That wasn't me!
All right, I'm putting it in!
I don't need protection today!
D-Don't do it! I mean it!
Ow!
That hurt!
You scratched me, you meanie!
I... I'm sorry.
You're mean... you're mean...
We officially ended it just a while ago.
Four and a half years, all for nothing.
The gods gave me the wrong person.
I'm sure they don't want me to find love.
I finally got it.
Sensei wanted to drown her
sorrows she suffered tonight
with meaningless sex with a random guy.
You're wrong!
Kido-kun?
I'm sure... I'm sure you'll find someone!
You'll find someone who'll love you just as much as you love him!
If the gods don't want to give you that chance, then curse those damn gods!
But I don't have the strength to.
Then I'll curse them for you!
So Sensei...
Sensei?
Shouko-sensei?
Come on...
Are you shitting me?
Are you awake?
Where am I?
Was I drunk?
Good morning, Shouko-sensei.
Ikuno-san? Why am I here?
You were the one who called me. It kind of surprised me.
Here's some coffee.
Uh, thanks.
You should have seen yourself last night. You were really drunk.
Thanks to that, I saw a lot of your hidden sides.
I must have put you through a lot of trouble. Forgive me.
Oh no. I had fun.
Ugh...
Oh yes, your pantyhose were ripped beyond repair, so I disposed of them for you.
Should I take you to the station?
No, I'll take a cab.
I'll see you.
Bye.
Tanabe
Do you think it worked?
Yeah, but I wonder if she'll eventually figure out what she did last night.
Tanabe
Kido
She said she doesn't remember a thing?
Even if she remembers a little, we can just wave it off.
If we both keep our mouths shut, that lie will become real to her.
This is new.
I sort of thought you hated lies and deceit.
I still do.
But now I think a white lie that spares people from getting hurt is permissible sometimes.
I began to accept that after witnessing you.
I did indeed call Ikuno-san...
What's that?
Here I go, Tatsuhiko!
Suga Design School
There!
Ah, stupid!
You suck!
My bad! My bad!
Don't throw it back!
Putty rubbers are not balls!
Here.
Uh, thanks, Sensei.
No, thank you.
Excuse me?
As for the gods...
I gave them a good cursing!
Shouko-sensei's refreshed smile made her look a lot more grownup than before.
I guess she found out.
That day forward, I didn't get her at all.
Ikuno Emiru told Sensei a white lie to spare her feelings.
I used to think of her as pure evil, but now I don't know what to think.
God, I can't control myself!
Hurry...
M-Me neither...
Are you shitting me?
They're picking that spot to do it?
Hana... can I put it in?
Oh crap...
Yes, please!
it's turning her on!
Yoneyama invited us to go to the beach during summer break.
A summer trip to the beach with everyone.
Aren't you going to swim, Yuri-chan?
My skin turns red under the sun.
Hey...
Do you think I'm the hottest babe on the beach?
Whoa, look at that rack!
She's gorgeous!
You know you are!
Are you just saying that?
Emiru?
Where's she going off by herself?
I'll go get us some drinks.
Uh, sure.
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
I know she went somewhere here...
Storage Shed
Why are you looking for me?
Hey, don't scare me like that!
You're the one who came in the first place.
I got tired of the rays and the crowds.
Were you worried about me?
It's only because we came here to have fun.
It would suck if anyone got sick.
Hey—
Wait, you wanna do it here?
Come on, I want to enjoy my summer!
Why are you so scared? I thought you were a man!
Screw you! Who are you calling scared!
Here we are hiding ourselves in a locker, peeking in on them.
How the hell did this happen?
Ma'am, can I have a Blue Hawaii?
Shaved
Ice
IceACream
Rentals
Parasols
Beach Chairs
I'll have an adzuki milk.
So hot.
I wonder what the temperature is inside this locker.
I'm probably going to keel over before those two finish.
Oh... Oh yeah!
Still, watching them have sex is making me really hot...
God, what am I thinking!
I'm in tune with Emiru!
Fuck, and I got a hard-on too!
Hey! Why is she pressing so hard against me?
Stop it, you moron!
Are you getting sore from the hard surface?
I'm fine.
But it'll get more comfortable if you hit me from the back.
I... I'm... gonna...
Hey! Stop using my johnson as your sextoy!
Ow...
Did you say something?
Nope, not a thing.
I must be hearing things.
Yeah, it's all in your imagination.
Let's go for a swim.
Mm-hmm!
How about we do it in the water?
No way!
I swear, you can be pervy sometimes!
They weren't hearing things.
That felt good!
Kido-san?
I'm sorry.
I bit your shoulder, remember?
I left a mark.
I never felt that much pleasure in my life.
My mind went blank and I completely lost myself.
I sure it's because you were holding me.
You sure can attack from all corners, can't you?
Aren't you going to get angry again?
It's too hot for that!
It sure was hot.
Got that right! I almost died from the heat!
I'll admit a part of me didn't want to watch them from that hot locker.
That's the first time I heard you complain about anything!
What was that?
Geez!
Stop that!
Hey! That's freezing!
Hey!
Should we head for the hotel?
Uh, yeah.
God, look at him!
He's the one who suggested we tell scary ghost stories,
but here he is sleeping before we even started.
He's tired from all that swimming.
We did hit the beach since morning.
Yeah, I'm also beat.
I'm going to sleep.
Me too.
Okay, I'll take Yoneyama to our room.
You can always sleep here.
Yeah, let's sleep together.
So much happened today, and I'm so wiped I wanna go to sleep.
Hmm, something smells good.
Yuri-chan?
This is nuts!
I can't hear you!
My swimsuit turned you on. Believe me, I know.
I-If that's what you want, let's use another room.
No way.
I want to do it here.
Tada.
This is my first time doing this, so my heart is beating like crazy.
It'll be a disaster if someone else sees this.
I gotta get this over with.
Hey, you're too rough! I won't control my voice!
S-Sorry.
Are you trying to make this quick?
Relax! Everyone's too tired to wake up.
Besides, they all know about us. Who cares if they see us?
I know.
You bonded with Ikuno-san earlier today, didn't you?
Sh-She saw us.
Uh, no, we were just...
You're not getting away.
I'm keeping you here until you come so hard inside me it breaks the condom.
Y... You got it.
I don't have to worry about Yoneyama, and Makiko's also asleep.
The only problem is Emiru.
She's fucking fixated on us!
What's wrong?
N-Nothing.
Dammit! It was hard enough
being watched from that hole!
But now I can feel her direct stares piercing through me!
But this peeping thing is pretty damn arousing.
Watching that couple at noon made me so hot I popped a huge boner.
And now that I know I'm being watched...
Fuck! I'm starting to turn into Emiru!
Now I can't think of her as some freak.
Emiru?
Did you come?
You love how it feels inside me, don't you?
Sorry, Kotobiki-san. I think I'm going to be sick.
Tada!
I bought a new dress!
Yuri-chan, that looks totally cute!
Looking good! Looking good!
What do you think, Tatsuhiko-kun?
Yeah, you look really cute.
You're so lucky you look good in cute clothes. I'm jealous!
I came thinking about Emiru.
Some weird thoughts entered my mind during sex.
She doesn't mean anything to me,
and I'm not into that voyeurism stuff.
At least I thought so.
But while I was trying to avoid thinking about her, somewhere along the way,
I became more obsessed with her than I'd care to admit.
AAAAAAAAA
Our
dream
ne
Our dream will never die
ver
die
Our
dream
ne
ver
die
As
long
as
As long as you believe
you
be
lieve
As
long
as
you
be
lieve
Take
my
hand,
Take my hand, let's take off
let's
take
off
Take
my
hand,
let's
take
off
Change
the
bar
Change the bar
Change
When you're all alone hiding who you are
You will spend all your day bored and restless
It's
It's
On the other hand, if you want to change
tion
tion
ka
e
te
Your imagination to something you want...
Yesterday I didn't receive an answer
Nobody can expose their limits
Drop your excuses
and break away from those days
Break
Break
Let's head for the stars in the night sky
There we will transcend time and space
I'm expecting big things,
so I'm counting on our future
Stand up and rise, over again
gain
gain
Surrender to your feelings, we're going to ride
ride
ride
We
Go
ing
We're going to ride
To
Ride
We
Go
ing
To
Ride