Excuse me, I'll be Naotatsu-kun's support!
School Trip to the Nudist Beach 02
School Trip to the Nudist Beach: The Animation.
Suemori-san?
U-Um, this might sound a bit random,
but I have something I want to ask you.
Naotatsu-kun, I... I...
Am I a slut?!
Uh... come again?
U-Um, sorry.
U-Uh, well you see, a little while back,
I saw you changing for gym.
You're in really good shape.
Ever since I saw your body, my heart just won't stop racing.
Since then, I haven't been able to take
my eyes off your muscles or veins.
During class or break... I can't take my eyes off of you.
I never even noticed you before,
but now I have! Does that make me a slut?
So basically... you're interested in my body... my muscles?
Yeah!
I don't see a problem.
If you're a slut, you're a slut.
Just look at me. I've been bursting at the seams
with sexual desire this whole time.
That's why I don't think there's a problem.
You could call me a slut for getting
aroused over any woman's body.
Yeah, you're right! Being a slut isn't a bad thing, right?
O-Of course not! Having an interest
in each others' bodies is perfectly healthy.
Then how about we touch each other?
They're so hard and yet so soft.
So this is what boys are like?
Wow, your back is so broad!
Boys' butts are so bouncy.
Sorry.
Wow.
Is this a muscle too?
N-Not exactly.
It's the male genitalia. It's primarily tissue
that grows in size due to an influx of blood...
Oh, that's right. We came into this
tent to get this back down in size.
R-Right.
Um, so... do you wanna have sex?
U-Uh... can we?
W-Well, I'm a virgin, but I guess we can.
V-Virgin?!
Naotatsu-kun, that feels so good!
It feels good for me too. You're so soft!
No, that's so embarrassing!
I'm putting it in. We're gonna have sex.
Okay.
Oh, right, I need to put a condom on.
Come on!
U-Um, it's my safe day, so it's okay.
It went in! It's in!
It's in now, how do you feel?
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine, but this is kind of amazing, isn't it?
This is amazing.
You're so cute, Suemori-san.
You just make me so hot.
Your flesh is wrapping around me
so tightly that it's hard to move.
I'll try moving to loosen it tip.
Suemori-san! Suemori-san!
So big! It's so big!
My vagina feels like it's gonna break!
Naotatsu-kun, your huge tip is knocking
on parts so deep inside me!
Suemori-san, your voice is so erotic, it's getting me so hot.
Let me hear more of it!
Na-Naotatsu-kun!
Suemori-san!
Your pussy's gotten so wet.
I think I can move my dick around harder inside of you.
No, wait! Wait, Naotatsu-kun!
I'm gonna break! I'm gonna break!
My dick's gonna melt! I'm gonna cum, Suemori-san!
Okay, do it.
Do it. You can cum.
I want to see it.
I want to see you cum because of me so badly.
I'm cumming!
I... I...
Yay! Your dick is finally soft again.
It's so soft now. It's hard to believe
that it was so big and hard before.
This is so interesting.
O-Oh no.
It got big again.
I-If you keep sucking the tip like that, I'm gonna...
M-Maria?!
It sounded like fun when I was outside.
Let me in on the fun.
Sayaka and Maria's tongues are...
Naotatsu, could you lay down for me?
S-Sure.
Your dick's so cute when it's hard.
You want this? You want to put it in my pussy?
That's fine. Let's do it.
Let's have sex, Naotatsu.
Naotatsu!
Maria!
Naotatsu's dick is so hard!
I've never had a dick this hard before!
Oh, god! Oh god, oh god, oh god!
Naotatsu's dick is too good!
Sex with that other guy didn't even
feel close to as good as this.
Naotatsu, you're amazing!
Maria, your pussy's so wet... it feels good!
I can't stop thrusting my dick inside you!
No!
Oh, god, I'm gonna cum from doing it from behind!
I'm not done yet!
W-Wait, Naotatsu!
It went so deep! This is so good!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming. I'm gonna cum, Maria!
Do it.
I'm cumming!
It doesn't look like it's ready to stop yet.
You can see it going in perfectly from this position, right?
Y-Yeah.
Your entire dick is going inside me!
Y-You sure about this?
Yeah.
I'll lick this for you too.
Feels good, doesn't it?
I-If you keep licking it like that, I'm gonna...
Not yet.
If you're gonna cum, you need to cum in here.
It's hitting all my weak spots!
Doesn't it feel good to not have to do any of the work?
So good! It feels so good!
It's so big that it won't fall out even if I try.
I felt it get bigger. You can cum whenever.
It's pouring out inside of me!
Maria?
Hm?
Sorry.
Huh?
It still isn't going down!
Still not satisfied?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: akin
quality control: paynes, fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч