Those are boobs... Boobs!
We seriously came to a nude beach!
Yeah.
You boys can't keep your
eyes off of them, can you?
Holy crap!
The beach is amazing today!
Hey! How long are you guys going
to hide? The boys are waiting!
Akiho, what should we do?
I'll go out first, so follow me!
Our class rep, Taniguchi Akiho,
is naked right in front of us!
Come out already!
Oh man, this is crazy!
'Kay, everyone! Before we start
having fun, let's gather 'round!
School Trip to the Nudist Beach: The Animation.
That's about it!
Oh, one last thing. Sex is not allowed.
No erections, okay?
Sensei said that, but...
How could we not get
an erection in a place like this?
It's impossible not to...
Huh? All of your dicks are still small.
Wha... Nagahama?!
I thought all guys get hard when they see boobs.
N-No...
Come on, don't they?
Now that I think about it, how come
nobody is getting a boner in this paradi...
Someone did!
My apologies. I, the class rep,
am putting on such a shameful display.
Hey, Naotatsu, having an erection
at a nudist beach is bad manners!
Sensei came prepared for something like this.
Come in here and turn it back into a normal cock!
The goal of this school trip is to shorten
the distance between the girls and boys,
so the girls should help
the boys in their time of need.
Wow, it's really big. It's my first time
seeing one, so I'm surprised.
Taniguchi, I'm sorry about this. It's all my fault.
It's because I'm a pervert that I got like this!
I couldn't take my eyes off the girls, and became like this!
I think it's fine. I think that it's okay
you got hard because of that.
We're class reps, so let's work together
and go back to everyone else!
All I have to do is close
my eyes and stand still, right?
Yeah, I'll take care of the rest.
Naotatsu!
He can't just sit back and look?
He's sucking on my nipples!
Thank you. I think I can cum now!
Okay.
Naotatsu, you can kiss me while you're cumming.
Are you sure? Is it really okay?
You're already doing it, aren't you?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Your dick is rubbing against
my stomach! It's so hard and hot!
I'm cumming!
Your dick got smaller, which means
my body was able to help you, right?
Yes, definitely.
Naotatsu...
Do you two have a moment?
Huh?
Ai!
School Trip to the Nudist Beach: The Animation.
What are you doing in here, Onose-san?
Sensei said that one time would probably
not be enough to make it go down.
Naotatsu-kun...
Onose-san, is this okay?
It's fine. Touch my body too.
No, I mean, would you mind doing
it with me? In front of Akiho, too...
It's fine. I'm not being forced or anything.
I want to have sex with you, Naotatsu-kun.
It's so slippery... Can I lick it a little?
S-Sure.
This is amazing. It's so big.
Onose-san, let me lick you too.
Sure... Thank you.
Onose-san, you're really wet.
You don't have to tell me that.
Naotatsu-kun...
No!
I'm gonna put it in, Onose-san.
It's so tight!
Naotatsu-kun, do me more!
Naotatsu-kun...
Onose-san, your moans are so cute!
Don't be embarrassed, it really turns me on!
That's it!
No!
Your voice is so hot!
I'm gonna cum!
Here I come. I'm cumming, Onose-san!
I'm sorry that I made you wear a condom.
Today's not a safe day for me.
Let's do it bareback another day, okay?
A-Ai?!
Sex with Naotatsu-kun is insane.
My lower half is done for!
Are you okay?!
Yeah. I'm sorry, Akiho. Sensei asked me
to do something during this trip.
Huh?
You two wouldn't get any closer
if we don't do something like this.
I'm sorry for having sex with him before you did.
It's okay, though.
It looks like he can go another round.
Go get 'em!
N-Naotatsu...
Akiho...
Sorry. This is all happening because I'm a pervert.
I'm perverted too!
I wanted to have sex with you, too.
Watching you have sex with Ai really hurt.
Even so, I couldn't look away!
That's how perverted I am!
That's how much I love you!
So, please! Give me all of your cum!
Akiho!
Naotatsu!
It went in, Akiho!
It's inside me!
Akiho, your pussy's so amazing!
Your pussy fits perfectly,
it's like it was made for me!
Here I go, Akiho! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
It's flowing into me...
His dick is pumping cum into me,
and it's twitching so much!
The pleasure of being cummed inside... It's amazing!
Akiho, I'm sorry, but I'm not done yet! I can't stop now!
That's fine. Let's keep having
rough sex until you're satisfied.
You're so rough!
I love you!
I love you, Naotatsu!
Akiho!
I don't know what our relationship should be
now that we're doing this. I don't know!
What my heart is telling me right now,
though, is that it's beating for you.
I-I-I can't... anymore...
Akiho...
What? We don't get to have sex?
Why were we even shown in the first place?
It's a shame, but time's up!
It's the end, bye-bye!
What?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч