hanime.tv Presents
Yama-chan, if you didn't crash land
and break our tricycle
we would have been there already!
It just keep getting bigger...
What kept getting bigger?
W-Well
Original Animation Disk: Nuki Doki Revolution
Angels & Demons: "Make Them Cum" Battle
I-I'm sorry about my tail.
Well, we can't help it now.
Your superpowers haven't
worn off yet, so let's hurry.
Wow, Sera-chan is so nice!
She's so cute too!
And...
her style...
Uh- Uh oh!
My cock's getting so excited! I
don't know if I can handle it!
If Sera-chan doesn't help me with this,
it might poke a hole in Nonoa's panties.
Time to use my acting skills...
M-My tail!
Y-Yama-chan, are you OK?
It's gotten so swollen!
It's this swolilen!?
Could this be from the tricycle accident earlier?
Y-Yeah that's what it must be
I was trying my hardest to get you to
the devil's hideout as fast as I could.
I guess I tried too hard.
So that's what happened...
I didn't realize, so I got upset and
said some terrible things.
I'm sorry.
N-No, Sera-chan, don't cry!
H-Honestly, this isn't a tail, it's my-
Yama-chan,
Let me know if there's anything I can do, OK?
I'll do whatever you say.
Really?
Y-Yama-chan, are you feeling better already?
Oh, the pain... the pain!
Woe is me!
"Chinchin" - Cock
My cock hurts!
It hurts!
Wait, that's not what I mean!
"Chinchin ni" - hot (temperature)
It's a pun.
My tail's burning hot!
It hurts, and it's swelling!
So how about I take my hot tail and
put it inside your special place to cool it?
I... can only show that place to
the person I love the most.
She gave a boob job before, no problem!
I thought she'd be easy!
I guess nothing's getting through those "gates".
That's right...
It's a girl's special place, after all.
I'm sorry for asking something like that.
No, don't worry about it.
Instead, you can use this hole instead.
I don't mind, so give it a try.
Yama-chan, are you OK?
Ass!
Y-Yama-chan! Be more gentle!
My ass is going to break!
No! Y-Yama-chan, gentle! Be more gentle!
I'm going to break!
l-lt hurts, Yama-chan!
Stop, stop, stop!
Be just a little more gentle!
Your tail is too big!
My ass is stretching wider!
It's hot! It's so hot!
I'm burning up!
It feels like this isn't my own body anymore!
It's hot! It's so hot!
It's coming.
It's coming!
Something's coming!
Deep inside my body, something's coming!
My head is feeling strange!
Yama-chan, save me!
I'm going crazy!
It's coming! Coming, coming, coming!
I'm coming!
It's so hot.
Yama-chan,
your hot stuff is inside me.
Whew!
That felt good!
Sera-chan, thanks.
My hot tail's all better now.
Eh?
What? Nonoa?
What's with that outfit?
Oh, this... isn't what it looks like.
I just tripped and fell.
And before that, Sera-chan tripped on her skirt.
And unluckily my cock, which was hard because of
a bee sting, just happened to penetrate her ass.
Those eyes-
Nonoa, what's with the superhuman strength?
She can't hear you.
Devil girl?
What have you done to Nonoa?
Huh?
You're always fooling around,
But that girl's special for you, isn't she?
Looks like I hit a nerve.
I'm asking you a question!
What have you done to Nonoa?
And what have you done to my body?
You're trying to seem tough,
but it just makes you look more pathetic.
Shut up! I can't move my body, so I can't help it!
She's going to milk you for your semen.
I performed a ritual that allows her to
use some of my demonly powers.
It's similar to the halo Sera gave you
that's floating above your head.
Oh, OK. That makes sense.
Wait, Nonoa's going to milk me for my semen!
My power has you paralyzed like that.
However,
that your member is fully erect
is not due to my power at all!
l-lt's just...
My M tendencies unintentionally kicked
in when Nonoa hit me before.
As expected from the amazingly
talented girl I found!
You best give her all the semen you have.
What did you say!!
Sex with Nonoa when she can't give consent...
I, uh... Don't kid around like that!
There's no need to act brave.
Just sit back and enjoy this.
I've implanted some of my egg cells inside her.
Knowing how pathetic you are,
I bet you'll cum and get her pregnant
in five seconds flat.
In a mere hour, my beautiful child will
ravage her insides, grow and develop
then it'll fly right out!
What?!
Now, woman, milk this pervert for
his semen. Don't leave a drop.
W-Wait, Nonoa.
Don't come near me!
When I look at her like this, I
can't help but get aroused!
What should I do?
If she takes me inside her, I'll last only three
seconds before I cum. I'm sure of it!
That said, I can't contain my cock when
she's masturbating right in front of me!
Wait a second...
If this angel's halo doubles my sense of smell...
maybe it doubles my already-potent
ability to fantasize!
Hurry! Hurry up and give it to me!
Yamato!
I can't wait any longer!
Nonoa! You've gotten your pussy so wet!
Well, it can't be helped. Wait a second for me, OK?
I'll turn my whole body into a cock
and plunge it inside you!
Yamato, I want your massive cock inside me!
Quickly, shove it in me!
Nonoa-chwon!
Open the pussy!
Yes!
It's twitching!
It's soaring through the air!
I'm сimming!
Yama-chan, your semen is filling my pussy-
It's making me cum!
That was close!
I came in the nick of time!
I didn't have to cum inside you, Nonoa!
Th-This can't be! He came without touching
it, with only his fantasies!
Filika!
I finally caught you!
Filika, you stupid, stupid, stupid!
Why did you vanish without telling anyone!
Sera-chan, you're confronting her?
What's going on?
For you and me, an angel and
a devil, to be together...
We can't have children.
This was the only way. Forgive us.
enough to make me happy.
Filika, having you by my side is
Promise you'll never leave me.
Very well, I promise.
What a day!
What was the point of all this?
Yamato-san?
Answer my three questions without turning around, would you?
One:
Why am I naked?
Two:
Why are you wearing my panties?
Three:
Why am I covered in semen?
Th-This isn't what you think, Nonoa!
I can explain!
You filth!
I'm gonna kill you 10^26 times,
so prepare yourself!
I'm blasting off after just one hit!
I can't do this again!
Filika, kiss me, kiss me!
Kiss me!
W-Wait! We can't do it here...
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
Visit us at hanime.tv
softsub: Asuka_Langley