I messed up.
I can't believe that someone like
myself could forget that way back.
And because I've been dragging this
around all night, I'm just about at my limit.
But actually, how is she still not waking up?
Humans might be more durable creatures than I thought.
~The milking battle of angels and demons~
Getting silky smooth skin from the steamy bath!
Sex with Nonoa and Firika!? Arc
Who's doing that? Who's being
so loud this early in the morning?
Could you quiet down a lit...
That was so close.
What happened to my clothes?!
Where am I?!
Oh yeah, me and Yamato were...
Finally awake?
As sudden as this may be, use this
device to guide me to my base.
I've put the address into this map.
Give me back my phone!
This is from yesterday...
Who in the world are you?!
Why are you cosplaying as a demon?
Полноразмерная SD карта в телефоне в 2017? Серьёзно?! Дайте два!
You're smart enough to know what's on this, right?
That's dirty.
Crap, she's already found me?
There's no time. We're leaving.
Hey, wait a second!
We're here, but are you sure this is the right place?
Indeed. There's no mistake.
Um, can you not read a map, Firika-san?
I'm simply unaccustomed to it.
Don't be so embarrassed
I thought you might have been a dangerous
person, but you're a lot cuter than I thought.
Save that for later. We don't have the time for this.
Get in the shower already and clean your body.
Okay.
But if the ritual succeeds, give me the memory
card with all those dirty pictures of me, okay?
Very well.
Sera-chan? Sera-chan?! Stop! Stop!!
Yama-chan, focus your strength
into your center and try to stop!
R-Roger!
Very good. Servants who have sworn fealty
to me, once again offer your lives to me.
Wow, just because of this halo you put
on top of my head, I can float in the sky!
Not everyone's halo can do the same thing.
Halos produced by an angel as highly skilled
as myself, inherit their producer's abilities.
Wow, you really are an angel, aren't you, Sera-chan?
I've been saying that since the start!
But that's not important right now. Did you
find a clue as to where those two went?
Oh, right.
I've been able to track Nonoa by her scent thanks to
your halo, but it just suddenly disappears around here.
That Firika might have casted a spell to erase her scent.
I wanted to save this for a special occasion, but...
Equip!
Yama-chan, I can't believe you had such an amazing power!
This might be our chance at catching Firika!
You're twitching so much. Are you about at your limit?
The sour smell and thickness of it is truly wonderful.
Who's next?
Impressive virility you have.
You seem like you have a lot built up.
Don't disappoint me.
Your dick is swelling so much. You
really aren't holding anything back, huh?
I think I can expect something great to come out of you.
It's going all the way inside me!
Are you about to cum?
It's alright. Give it to me inside.
Don't even leave a single drop!
That's less than you produced
last time, but it's still sufficient.
Who's next?
I want more! Give me more of that thick liquid!
Do it! Give me your thick liquid!
Pour your thick cum inside me!
Good! So good!
It feels so good!
More! More!!
More!!
It feels so good!
More! More!!
Cum!
Hurry!
Give me more of your thick cum! More!
More! I want so much more of it!
That's good. My stomach feels like it's about to burst.
So good!
You're the last one I'll be using for this ritual.
Make it something to remember!
So good!
Wow, that felt great.
Well now both my body and mind are cleansed.
Firika-chan?
S-Stop!
Firika-san, what are you doing...
Sniff Sniff.
Nonoa's scent has grown stronger.
Sera-chan, it's really likely that Nonoa
and the other girl are around here!
Really?
Okay, just you wait, Firika Mia Shatana!
Firika-sama, it's so hot! So hot!
My body feels like it's on fire!
My nipples are so hard right now that
they feel like they could cut glass.
And it's even hotter down there! I feel like
my clitoris is getting as big as my earlobe!
I can't wait any longer!
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Please hurry and cleanse me with your liquid, Firika-sama!
Don't be so impatient.
I'll promptly fill this bathtub with all the
liquid that I've purified inside myself.
It'll be enough for you to drown in.
It feels so good.
Firika-sama, my body feels like it's about to melt!
I feel like my mind and heart... every part of me is melting!
Excellent. I think I'll be able to use you well.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4c4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч