www.SubDESU-H.net
Geez, just how did things turn out that way...?
Yamato, Yamato!
This isn't funny!
Me, the Great Filica, submitting to some lowly servant like him?
Besides, he's currently...
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Yamato-san, you don't need to force yourself to do things for now, okay?
Just stay right there.
I'll do everything for you.
Your thing is twitching.
It's hot.
Does it feel good?
You can cum anytime you want to.
Wow, and it's still stiff.
Yamato-san, I'm...
I'm already itching for it, my pussy already wants it badly.
I'm going to insert it.
So just stay put, okay?
It's going in.
Your cock is going deep inside me.
It feels good.
My pussy is being filled by your cock.
Yamato, does it feel good inside my pussy?
Does your cock feel good in it?
I want you to feel great with it.
Your thing's tip is touching my very insides.
Yamato-san, I'm...
I'm already filled inside.
Yamato-san, let's cum together.
Lots of cum is being poured inside.
If I keep making him feel good, it'll be the Angel's victory.
Huh?
Thank goodness.
Your wounds have healed already.
It seems that you're fine now.
Yamato-san, that was not good.
You almost died back there.
And if you do, our battle will be all over.
We are Angels, so there is no need for you human to save us.
Your death would only be wasted.
Please don't think about saving me again, okay?
W-W-What did you just do, Filica-san?
Slapping an Angel like me just like that.
Do you intend to do things by force?
That's against the rules!
Umm... well...
Then...then...
This would mean the Angels win, you know?
Is that okay with you?
Oh, just shut up will you.
Stop joking around!
Angels winning against Demons is just absurd!
Besides, before you try to reprimand my servant like that...
You have to go through me first!
What servant are you talking about?
Yamato-san will choose the Angel's side!
Come on, I won't be able to move if they suddenly have sex like that.
W
Nuki
doki!
~Semen Squirt Battle Between An Angel and A Demon~
Original Animation
Big-Breasted Innocent Angel Sera~ Clumsy Girl's Pure Train Sex
What could this be?
I can't look straight into his face.
I wonder if this can fix it.
Ya-Yamato-san.
It feels good when touched this way, right?
Perhaps this feeling will disappear if I do this.
Yamato-san, it's really hot.
Yamato-san, I don't think we should,
do it here...
Yamato-san!
Yamato-san, we can't do this...
This isn't good.
We'll be seen.
Oh no, Yamato-san is inside me, in this place...
We're inside the train, and he's entering my pussy.
He's thrusting this hard already?
His thrusting is even better than before.
If this keeps up I...
Oh no...
If this carries on...
No way...
F-Filica-san...
Geez.
And when I was thinking of saying hi to them,
they just started doing it.
This nymphomaniac Angel...
Umm... I...
Hey, what's with that innocent look?!
What you were doing earlier was quite perverted, you know?
H-Hey!
Are you okay?
I already said it earlier, Yamato-san.
I'm an Angel, so...
Please only think about yourself.
No need for you to be concerned about me...
Anyway, you can't just do this okay?
Why is she getting all embarrassed?
Umm, I...
Geez.
Well, I guess it's about time that I get serious.
That goes for you as well.
Let's go.
And so,
here!
These kinds of things are also quite good, right?
Don't just stare like that.
These clothes are already used, so you can make me dirty whichever way you want to.
Your tongue is licking it...
Stimulating my sensitive spots...
Oh crap...
No...
Oh no...
I think I drank too much of the stuff earlier.
Hey, j-just wait for a moment.
Stop for a moment.
Yamato!
I said stop!
Wait...
Pause!
Stop!
You...
Making me do something embarrassing like this.
I'm definitely going to make this my win!
If I don’t—
Yamato...
Oh no.
Hey!
Yamato!
You're too sudden!
Your cock is amazing!
It's stirring up the insides of my pussy!
It's thrusting intensely deep inside.
Oh crap, let's hide somewhere.
Huh?
Why is it locked at this time?
Yeah, I wonder why.
That's weird.
I thought I was right on schedule.
That was close.
I somehow managed to hide us using magic.
I lowered my guard.
It's not cumming yet so it's probably still itching to continue.
Hey...!
I said you can't do it!
I'm going to moan!
Just hold on for a moment will you?!
Hey!
Huh?
I can't find my uniform.
Didn't you put it in the laundry?
I already took it out of the laundry.
It should be somewhere here, but...
Seems we have to hide really well.
Could I have misplaced it somewhere?
Well, it'd be difficult for you if you don't cum, right?
This is just perfect, right?
I'm going to squeeze it all out with these breasts.
Cum if you want to.
Would you have wanted it inside my pussy instead?
Oh wow, this is...
Just try and make yourself feel good.
You just soiled me like this.
Geez, not my problem if something happens, okay?
www.SubDESU-H.net
I was careless.
She just had sex right off the bat.
He's currently doing it with Filica-san, huh?
My, my.
Seems my warning was of no use.
Enka-sama?
I already told you to be careful.
So, I just need to squeeze the human's semen,
make him sway our way,
and make him feel good, is that correct?
W-Well, I suppose that's right, but...
Sera-chan, you've always been a diligent girl, albeit a bit weird.
What do you mean?
Angels aren't capable of serving others at the same level.
Yes, I am well aware of that.
This will be a good opportunity,
so I want you to do your best so that you may understand it properly, okay?
I... see...
It is indeed difficult to find someone like Yamato-kun,
so I guess it can't be helped.
No way...
Then as an Angel I'm...
That's not true.
It's better that you were able to realize it.
You now know what you need to do next.
Yes.
Yamato, I'm feeling weak.
My, Filica-chan, that's such a slovenly expression.
Sera-chan seems to be looking more feminine now too.
We just need to leave the real fights up to our partners,
and just have some fun with this.
Though it's been a few thousand years since I last met mine.
Oh, but we can probably feel more at ease without them.
Now then,
I wonder what Sera-chan will do now.
I can't wait to see.
We've arrived, but it really feels tiring whenever we finally finish.
Yamato-san.
I can't just stay like this.
What are you doing here all of a sudden?
I need to become an Angel.
That's why I need you to...
... choose me!
What did you say?
Stop messing around already.
Please be silent!
I am an Angel...
... but things can't just stay like this.
This is...
This can't be just for the sake of one person.
What's with you now?
So you're starting to love Yamato for real now, eh?
That's not true.
I'm an Angel!
Well, even if you are one,
I wonder how you'll be able to go all the way, if you don't even understand how it feels.
For us Demons, we only have to get to the person and snuff out their souls.
It'd be a cinch for us.
So this is what Enka-sama was talking about.
T-Then Yamato-san.
Right now can you...
Hey, why is it getting all stiff now?
That cock of yours!
Hey!
Yamato-san, umm....
I want to be embraced by you!
How can you just shout out those embarrassing things?
Hey, wait a—
My breasts are being sucked...
If you suck strongly like that...
It feels good.
Being sucked by you...
What the... Hey!
I... can't...
Yamato-san, please enter me.
No way! Hey, stop that!
Hey!
Your cock's getting suddenly intense, Yamato-san.
My pussy feels good.
Please stir my insides a lot.
Please thrust deep inside me with your cock.
Please do it until I lose myself with it.
Yamato-san, I love you.
Let me go crazy with your cock!
No way.
I don't want him to do it with anyone else but me!
I don't want this!
My, my, I wonder what will happen?
Filica-chan doesn't look so good.
I think it's about time.
Filica-chan, do your best.
Do my best?
Huh? What's happening?
So you love Yamato-kun that much, eh?
I-I don't know what you're talking about!
Well, he is my servant so that's just...
Hmph.
You're not being honest.
Should I make it so you're unable to move again?
Sera-chan has already realized it.
She's now more formidable than ever.
If you don't keep up...
I'm sorry.
I'm being teased by your cock,
and it's continuously rubbing inside me.
Please completely fill my pussy with your cock.
His cock is filling me.
It feels good.
This is just too good for some useless Angel.
Filica-san!
That's unfair, give that back!
Shut up!
Something wrong with it?
It still feels good for Yamato, you know?
Geez, Yamato-san.
Your cock is inside Filica-san's pussy!
Yamato... oh yes...
Let it out.
Cum a lot inside my pussy!
Let it all out inside me, Yamato!
I...!
What in the world was that?
Yamato will choose me.
Filica-san, you discreetly got in the way!
Please try and take notice of it for once, Yamato-san!
He came a lot inside me...
Filica-san, return his cock already!
I want his cum too!
It's my win already, right?
Yamato also said that it felt good.
He did not.
He felt a whole lot better in me.
Right, Yamato-san?
Hey, Yamato!
W-What is this getting stiff for?!
Hey!
Geez, Filica-san.
I'm the one who'll make him feel good.
I already told you that he's my servant,
so he's mine!
No, he's mine.
You're getting cheeky again you useless Angel.
Though, it'd be better if you decide on one of us already.
That's right.
I can't just let you keep us both.
An Angel, or a Demon?
Which of us are you going to choose?
www.SubDESU-H.net