Geez, why was I so...
Yamato... Yamato!
Stop joking around! Why would I, Filika-sama
fall for such a filthy human...
Besides, by now, he's probably...
How... is it?
Does it... feel good?
Yamato-san, you shouldn't push yourself anymore, okay?
Please stay still.
I'll do it all for you.
Yamato-san's is... twitching...
It's hot...
Does it feel good?
You can let it out any time you want.
It's amazing... so much is coming out.
Yamato-san... my body feels so
lonely that my pussy is crying...
I'll put it in so... please stay still like that, Yamato-san.
It's going in...
Yamato-san's penis is going deep inside!
This is wonderful... your penis is filling up my pussy...
Yamato-san... does Sera's pussy feel good?
Does your penis feel good from this?
I want Yamato-san to feel really good!
The tip of the penis is rubbing Sera deep inside...
Yamato-san! I... So much...
Together please, Yamato-san!
Inside... there's so much sperm flowing in...
If I make Yamato-san feel good,
I can bring victory to the Angels.
Ugh... Huh?
That's good to see.
Your wounds have healed properly
as well. Seems like you'll be okay.
But you can't do that, Yamato-san.
You could have died there.
If that happens we won't be able
to get a winner out of this.
I'm an Angel, so not someone
who needs help from humans.
It's pointless, so please don't
think about saving me, okay?
Wh-wh-wha-what was that about, Filika-san!?
To raise hands against an Angel...
Who do you think you are!?
That was against the rules!
Uh... Err...
Well, then, this means victory for the Angels, right?
Shut up! Stop joking around!
It's ridiculous to even think that a mere
Angel can win against Demons!
Besides, before you start lecturing my servant,
you should ask for permission from his master first!
What do you mean "servant"?
Yamato-san will definitely choose us Angels!
Geez, having sex so suddenly... I can't move now.
Nuki Doki! ~A Demon and an Angel's Cum-Pumping Battle~
The Busty and Pure Angel Sera Erotic Train with the Clumsy Girl
What's happening?
I can't look at Yamato-san's face...
Would doing this help?
Ya-Yamato-san...
This feels good, right?
Doing this will help with this strange feeling, right?
Yamato-san's thing is so hot...
Yamato-san! Not... Not here...
Ya-Yamato-san...
Yamato-san, um, you can't go... that far...
We'll be noticed...
It's inside... Yamato-san is inside
me in this kind of place...
Although we're inside the train,
his penis is going in my pussy!
You're so rough so suddenly, Yamato-san!
Yamato-san is even more amazing than before...
So much... I...
No... if this keeps going on I'll... inside the train...
No way! Not like this...
Fi-Filika-san...
Geez... I'd thought I'd say Hi, and suddenly
you're having sex, you slutty angel!
Um... that's not...
Hey, what's with that innocent lovely
atmosphere you're giving off!
Even though you're doing such perverted things...
Hey!
Are you okay?
Yamato-san I've um said this before right?
I'm an Angel so...
Please only think of yourself, Yamato-san.
I'm not... um...
Anyways, stop doing things like this, okay?
What was that about? That shy,
lovey dovey atmosphere!?
No... I...
Geez.
Well, it's about time a proper decision is made.
You should think about it seriously, too.
We're leaving.
And since that's the case...
Something like this is good too, right?
Stop just staring like that.
This outfit is disposable so you can stain it if you want.
My pussy... is being lick by his tongue...
My sensitive parts are being stimulated...
No... it's amazing...
This is bad, I might have drunken too much juice earlier...
No, wait, wait a moment! Time out!
Y-Yamato!
I said wait! Hey! Time-out! Stop!
How dare you... make me go through
such embarrassing things!
You're definitely going to make me win! Or else...
Yamato...
Yama...
Hey! Yamato... not so sudden...
Yamato... your penis is amazing...
It's stirring up... my pussy...
Yamato...
So rough... all the way inside!
Damn. Hey Yamato, hide!
Huh? Why is it occupied that this time?
Yeah, I thought we found a time slot
where it was vacant. That's strange.
That was close.
I hid it with my magic, but I was careless for a moment...
He hasn't cum yet, must be painful...
Hey! Y-Yamato, not yet!
My voice will come out! C'mon...
Hey, I said wait!
Hey!
My uniform isn't here...
Huh? Did you send it for cleaning?
I did that not long ago.
I remember putting it here... hmm...
We have to hide properly.
Geez, where could it be...
Well, guess it'll be hard for you if you don't cum.
You can't hold back, can you? Filika-sama will
squeeze it out for you with her breasts.
You'd better... cum soon...
Did you want to cum in my pussy?
I guess that's... for next time...
Go ahead and feet good...
You stained it so much... Geez, I don't know anymore.
I was too thoughtless.
They're having sex right away...
Sex with...
Filika-san...
Oh dear, looks like my warning didn't work.
Elka-sama?
Even though I told you to be careful...
So, I squeeze out the semen of the human
so he turns in our favor, right?
Well, that's true... Sera-chan is hard-working,
but you're slightly dull sometimes...
What does that mean?
Angels must enforce equality, so we
can't do things for one's own will.
Yes, I understand that well enough.
Well, um, this is a good chance for you to
learn the meaning of it, so do your best.
I see...
There aren't many people like Yamato-kun, so I guess
it can't be helped if things turn out like this.
That's... so then, as an Angel I'm...
That's not true.
Understanding this kind of feeling is a gain for you.
On top of that, think about the things that you should do.
Yes.
Yamato... I've lost my strength...
Oh my, Filika-chan is making such a lewd face...
Sera-chan has finally started to look like a girl, too.
Let's leave the deciding to the
men, and just enjoy ourselves.
I haven't seen him in a few thousand years though...
Well, guess it just means that things
are better without the husbands.
Well then, what will Sera-chan do?
There's so much to look forward to!
Coming back is tiring every time, isn't it?
Since it's after we do it...
Ya-Yamato-san!
If this goes on I'll be in trouble.
What's with you all of a sudden!?
I have to become an Angel.
So I have to get Yamato-san...
to choose me!
What's that?
Stop saying such irresponsible things!
You are too noisy!
I'm an Angel,
but, I can't let this go on...
Something like this... doing things for one's
own will... this shouldn't be happening!
What's that? Are you actually in love with Yamato?
That's not true! I'm, I'm an Angel after all!
Well, being an Angel and stuff, how do you plan
to protect him without any of those feelings?
On the other hand, Demons can just possess
and take away the soul. Neat, right?
So this was what Elka-sama was talking about...
Well then, Yamato-san,
will you, from now... with me...
Hey Yamato what's that getting hard!?
I see a penis don't I!? Hey!
Yamato-san... I... want to be... loved by Yamato-san!
How do you manage to say such cheesy things... hey!
You'll soak my breasts...
If you suck that hard...
It feels good... being touched lots by Yamato-san...
Hey, no!
I...
Yamato-san, please come...
No way, c'mon, stop it!
Hey...
Yamato-san's penis... so suddenly...
My pussy feels good!
Please stir up my inside a lot!
Please thrust your penis deep inside...
Please do it so rough that I'll go crazy!
Yamato-san, I love you!
Please make me go crazy with your penis!
Why... I don't want anyone other than me with Yamato!
No more!
Oh my, how will this turn out?
Filika-chan looks like she could fall ill from this.
About time he's cumming.
Good luck, Filika-chan.
Something like this...
Huh? What's happening?
So you love Yamato-kun this much now...
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Well, he is my servant so...
You're not very honest aren't you?
Well, I guess I'll restraint you again.
Sera-chan has noticed her feelings.
She's a tough opponent.
You have to work hard as well.
I'm sorry...
I'm being teased by Yamato-san's penis!
I'm being complete messed up!
Yamato-san, please fill up my pussy with your penis...
So much cock... it feels so good!
This goes... to waste on that failure... of an Angel...
Filika-san!
That's cheating! Please give it back!
Shut up! Yamato... feels better...
inside... me, anyways!
Geez, Yamato-san...
Your penis is inside Filika-san's pussy!
Yes! Yamato!
Let it out! Give my womb lots of your sperm!
Cum lots! Yamato!
Inside... me!
He came in buckets...
Yamato chose me.
Filika-san, why did you do that!?
Geez! And Yamato-san should pay more attention!
I got creampied so much by Yamato...
Filika-san! Please return the penis to Yamato-san already!
I want his sperm, too!
Eh? Can't we just make it my victory?
Yamato says it felt good, too.
He hasn't said that.
I definitely feel better.
Right, Yamato-san?
Hey, Yamato... why are you getting hard again, hey!
Geez, Filika-san.
I'm the one going to make him feel good.
Yamato is my servant! So he's mine.
Yamato-san belongs to me.
You're too cocky for a failure of an Angel!
Well if only you'd hurry up and decide.
That's right. You should stop saying "both" all the time.
Angel or Demon, which one?