I made a wrong turn. To think a being
as dignified as me has become lost!
Dragging this girl around all night has put
me near my limits of physical strength.
And why doesn't she wake up from
being dragged around like this?
Humans might be tougher
creatures than I thought.
Original Animation Disk: Nuki Doki Revolution
Angels & Demons: The "Make Them Cum" Battle
In this episode: Silky soft skin in a steamy
bath! Nonoa and Filika have sex!?
Who's making all that noise
so early in the morning?
Keep it down a little, would y...
That was close!
Why am I dressed like this, in a place like this?
That's right, Yamato and I...
Finally awake, are we?
This may seem sudden, but use this device to
guide me back to my base of operations.
I've inputted the address.
Give my phone back!
Th-This is from yesterday's.
More importantly, who are you?
Why are you cosplaying as a devil?
I take it you understand what
I've stored on this card.
How cowardly!
They're onto us already.
We're out of time. Come with me.
H-Hey, wait a minute!
We've arrived, but are you
sure this is the right place?
Yes, I'm sure.
Fi-Filika-san, can you read maps?
I'm just not very skilled at it.
You're blushing!
Filika-san, you seemed like kind of a scary person,
but you have your a cute side as well, don't you?
More importantly, we don't have much time.
Shower and cleanse yourself.
Roger that.
B-But once we finish that ritual, you have to give
me that SD card with those pictures on it.
I understand.
Sera-chan, Sera-chan, stop!
Yama-chan, put some effort
into it and hang in there!
Eh? Roger!
O servants who have sworn me your loyalty!
Offer me your lifeblood once again!
Wow! Thanks to Sera-chan's halo, I can fly now!
It's not like every angel's halo
can do this, your know.
Only haloes created by highly-skilled
angels like me have that ability.
So you really are an angel after all, Sera-chan.
That's what I keep telling you!
More importantly, Yama-chan, did you find
any clues as to their whereabouts?
Oh, right. The angel's halo let me
track Nonoa's scent this far, but.
Her smell disappears right about here...
Filika might have concealed her scent with magic.
I was saving this to masturbate to, but...
I'm equipping them!
To think Yama-chan had such an ability!
This gives me a chance to beat Filika!
I can feel it.
You're almost at your limit, aren't you?
That's good. That has a wonderful taste and scent.
Next.
What vigor!
You're quite pent up, aren't you?
Don't disappoint me.
Y-You're really quite girthy.
This penis really gets your expectations up.
It's going all the way in!
Y-Yes!
A-Are you going to cum?
D-Do it. Cum inside me.
Give me all of it!
You came less than last time, but
your technique has improved.
Next.
I want it! Give me more cum!
Y-Yes!
Give me more of you strong-smelling cum!
Cum inside me!
Yes, yes!
That feels good!
More, more!
More!
Yes! That feels so good!
More, more!
Cum!
Quickly!
Your cum, give me more!
More, more, more!
Yes!
It feels like I could burst!
That's good!
I need just one more of you to cum inside me.
Then I'll have enough liquid for the ritual.
You best give it to me.
Yes!
That felt so nice!
Now my body and mind are clean and refreshed.
Hey!
Filika-san, what are you doing all of a sudden?
Sniff sniff. Nonoa's scent is getting stronger!
Sera-chan, Nonoa and Filika are probably
hiding out in this area!
Really? Just you wait, Filika Mia Shatana!
Filika-sama, I feel hot! It's so hot!
My body feels so hot. It's like I'm on fire!
My nipples are so completely erect!
My pussy is itching with desire! It's so engorged!
I can't hold back any longer!
Quickly, quickly, quickly!
Quickly, use your liquid to cleanse me!
Don't be in such a hurry.
The fluid I've purified inside me.
I'll give you enough to completely envelop you!
It... It feels so good!
Filika-sama, it feels like my body could melt!
It's like my body, my mind, all
of me... it's all melting away!
Very good.
Have a nice long soak.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч