We already would've been there if you didn't
fall and break my tricycle, Yama-chan!
I didn't know that I would get even bigger than that!
What exactly got bigger?
U-Uh...
~The milking battle of angels and demons~
Explosion of Yamato's Fantasies!
Why don't you try being a demon, Nonoa? Arc
S-Sorry about my "tail".
I guess that's that.
It didn't look like you knew how to control your
new power too well, so let's just keep moving.
Man, Sera-chan is so nice.
And she's so cute.
And her body's... pretty hot.
No, not good.
If my nether regions get any more heated than this...
If I don't get Sera-chan's help, Nonoa
might end up in some real trouble.
But let me just try one last trick...
Oh god, my tail!
Yama-chan, are you okay?
My tail is swelling up so much!!
Why's it so swollen?!
Wait, is it because of the accident we just had?
U-Uh, oh, yeah, that's exactly it.
It might've overworked itself because it just really
wanted to save Nonoa from the demons.
Oh, I see.
I said all those mean things to you
without even knowing that!
I'm so sorry.
U-Uh, Sera-chan, don't cry!
Actually, this isn't a tail, it's a...
Yama-chan,
if there's anything I can do, just let me know.
I'll do anything you ask me to.
Really?!
Are you serious?
Yama-chan, does it not hurt anymore?
O-Oh god the pain! Ow!
My dick hurts! It hurts!
What I meant was that my tail's getting
as hard and swollen like a dick is.
So what I need is for my tail that's now like a
dick to go in you down there to cool down.
Down here?!
I'm not supposed to show it to anyone
but the person I love the most.
She gave me a tit fuck like it was nothing, so I
just thought she'd be easy to have sex with!
But I guess the last fortress was impenetrable.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It's a girl's most important place after
all. Sorry for being weird like that.
No, don't worry about it.
But instead of that hole, you can use this one.
Why don't you try it?
Yama-chan, are you okay?
A-Ass!
Y-Yama-chan, do it slower!
You're gonna make it rip!
No! I told you to go slowly!
Move slower!
You're gonna break me!
Th-That hurt, Yama-chan!
Stop! Stop! Stop!!
Be a little more gentle!
Your tail's too big, Yama-chan!
You're spreading out my butthole so much!
It's so hot!
It's so hot!!
My body's getting so hot, it feels like
it's not even my own body anymore!
It's hot! It's so hot!
It's coming! It's coming!!
Something's coming!
Something's going to come inside me!
It's coming! It's coming!!
I'm losing my mind!
Yama-chan, help me!
It's coming! It's coming! It's coming!!
So hot...
Yama-chan's...
Your hot stuff is inside me...
Faint.
Damn, that felt so good.
Thank you, Sera-chan.
My dick... I mean, my tail is back to normal.
Huh? Nonoa?!
Why are you dressed like that?!
Wait, this isn't what it looks like.
I just kinda fell over and for some reason.
Sera-chan was just there with her skirt
flipped up, lying there on the ground.
And then my dick, which was swollen from
a bee sting, just fell right into her asshole.
What's with your eyes...
Nonoa, what happened to you?
Your voice won't reach this girl.
Aren't you that demon?
What did you do to Nonoa?!
I guess even a wimp like yourself can get angry
when it's over a girl he cares about.
I said, "What did you do to Nonoa?!"
And what did you do to my body?!
If you're trying to act cool right now,
you chose the wrong outfit and pose.
Shut up, my body won't move. It's not like I have a choice!
The girl has undergone a ritual and
obtained a fraction of my power
so that she can extract the sperm from within you.
It's just like how that angel gave you her halo.
Oh, okay that makes sense.
Wait, what's Nonoa gonna do?!
She's gonna extract my sperm?!
The reason your body is unable to
move is due to my own power.
But I cannot control that large, hulking piece of meat there.
Y-Yeah, my masochism kicked in when
Nonoa hit me and this is the result.
I really did find the perfect specimen.
Now, flood this woman with your
sperm to your heart's content.
What?!
There's no way I could seriously bring
myself to have sex with Nonoa!
D-Don't joke around.
Just say you were forced to do it and enjoy it to the fullest.
She has my eggs within her.
With my genes inside her, she'll be able to bear my
children within give seconds of being inseminated.
Within the next hour, my wonderful children will feed
off her insides, grow, and then burst out of her.
What'd you say?!
Now then, woman, drain all the sperm from
within him. Don't leave a single drop.
Wait, Nonoa! Don't come any closer!
You can't keep showing this to me.
This is turning me on too much.
What should I do?
If she puts me inside her, I'm confident
I'd cum in three seconds.
But there's no other way for me to calm this
down with her masturbating in front of me.
Huh? Wait a second...
Wait, if this halo can amplify my memories,
then that means my specialty masturbating with
my imagination, should be strengthened as well.
Hurry! Hurry up and give it to me!
Yamato!
I... I can't wait any longer!
Nonoa, look at how wet you are. You poor thing.
Just wait.
The amazing all-dick, all-cum Yamato-chan
is coming to go inside you right now!
Yamato hurry and give me your big dick!
Hurry and shove it inside me!
Nonoa-chan!
Time to go inside your pussy!
Yes sir!
Welcome to the beautiful world!
I'm cumming!!
Yamato's hot milk is inside my pussy!
I'm gonna cum!!
That was close!
I was so close to cumming inside Nonoa!
Th-This isn't possible!
He was able to ejaculate just with the
power of his own imagination?!
Firika!
I finally caught you!
Geez, Firika, you dummy! You big dummy!
Why'd you disappear without saying anything?!
Huh?!
Wait, Sera-chan, I thought you were
here to eliminate demons!
There was no other way for the two
of us, an angel and a demon,
to come together unless we had children.
Forgive me.
As long as I could be with you, Firika-chan,
that's good enough for me.
Promise me that you'll never leave my side.
Very well. I promise.
What about me?
Why did I even try so hard?
Hey, Yamato?
Gulp!
You mind answering three questions
for me without turning around?
First, why am I completely naked right now?
Second, why are you wearing my panties?
Gulp!
Third, why am I covered in semen right now?
Th-This is a big misunderstanding, Nonoa!
There's a perfectly good explanation for this...
You bastard! You better be prepared to die right now!
I can't accept any of this at all!
Firika...
– Kiss. Kiss. Kiss!
– Wait, not here!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч