I-I can't.
I can't cum anymore! S-So...
You're a man aren't you? How are you such a wuss?
But I guess I did target you because you're like that.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?!
Looks like your mental processing and
stamina are below that of an average person.
With the cum from a human who's far from perfect...
And with an inhabitant from the demon
realm... When the two of those combine,
Apparently the resulting child will be...
An elite demon like I am.
Fuck that! Why did you choose me?!
Last week on the train, you masturbated
in front of a sleeping high school girl.
You knew that she was fast asleep and wouldn't wake up.
So you shoved your dick into her mouth.
And then took pictures, so you could
blackmail her into keeping her mouth shut.
And then...
You came a large amount into her mouth, did you not?
Does that really pass as something a good
person would do in the human world?
Thank you for choosing me.
Alright, please continue.
Very well.
Alright then, let's pump number
twenty-eight out of you right now.
And then move onto the next one!
I'm cumming!!
~The Milking Battle of Angels and Demons~
The demon warrior appears on a moonlit night.
Firika's target is a loser guy's cum!? Arc.
What's so fun about rolling a ball back and forth like that?
Are you here to just watch from the sidelines again?!
Why don't you try actually playing for once?
If you keep doing this, you're going
to lose all your friends except me.
Everyone hates a girl who's too nosy.
Also, this is the first time I'm hearing that we're friends.
Momose, watch out!
Yamato?
Hey, are you okay, Yamato?
Hey, Yamato!
Yamato? Yamato! Hey, Yamato! Answer me!
So that's a human? So pitifully frail.
Yamato, sorry.
You're hurt, but you came all this way with me.
You have nothing to apologize for, Nonoa.
Also, it's been ages since I've been to your house.
Yeah, you haven't been here since you got
caught peeking in on me taking a bath
and got thrown out of the house.
So it's been about a year, I guess?
I completely forgot.
Boobs!
Yamato, you perv!
You get so full of yourself if I show
you even a second of kindness.
You just wait there, perv.
I-I couldn't help it.
Ow, that hurts.
Her punch hit harder than that basketball ever did.
But seriously, when did Nonoa get so...
Yamato?
Lady Momose, please excuse my behavior earlier!
But looking at your boobs was
seriously beyond my power to stop!
I swear on my life that I wasn't purposely staring at them!
You don't have to force yourself to apologize like this.
Yamato, how do I look?
So, Yamato, isn't this outfit great?
Mom sewed it for me after the design I gave her.
So, Yamato, does it look good on me?
Nonoa, I...
Y-Yamato, what's the matter all of a sudden?
For a while now, Nonoa, I...
I guess I have no choice if you're so insistent, Yamato.
I thought you had a flat chest.
Sorry about that.
But looking up close, you've really become an adult woman.
Are those your final words?
– Lady Nonoa, are you perhaps embarrassed?
– I'm mad! Yamato, you perv!
Please, not the face!
Huh, what?
What was that sound?
Yamato, what happened to your pants?!
Yamato, you pervy demon!
He may just be a human, but he has quite the fine package.
He passes.
This really wasn't on purpose!
My pants were down before I even knew it!
Fine, I get it, so put that dirty thing away already!
R-Right.
Huh?
Why are you still showing it to me, you perv!
Huh? Why can't I move my body?
I'll make it so you feel good too.
See? See what I mean?!
I can't move my body all of a sudden.
So I'm not a pervy demon!
I get that, but...
But why is it standing up like that?
This is because the way you're wearing your
clothes, how am I supposed to help myself?
Wh-What happened to my clothes?!
How long are you gonna stare at me, Yamato?!
Look the other way!
But I can t do anything about this, Ms. Nonoa.
Remember, I can't move my body at all.
It's not even like my dick's that hard right now.
I'm not even looking at your amazing boobs...
M-Ms. Nonoa?
Seeing as we both can no longer move our bodies,
I feel as if we need to work together
to find a way to improve our situation.
W-Wait, my body's just moving on its own!
N-Nonoa, are you okay?
L-Let me just say that my dick moving is
involuntary and has nothing to do with my mind.
B-Basically, it's against my will!
What are you saying at a time like this, Yamato?!
My left hand is moving on its own!
Why is my hand going to my nipple?
Your body is mine.
And so is your package...
That's mine as well.
Nonoa
Hey, Yamato!
Don't get any weird ideas from this!
I'm not!
My dick is experiencing pleasures
that it's never felt before right now...
Oh god, this might be bad.
If you cum now, I won't be able to harvest it.
No! My body's moving on its own again!
Yamato, seriously, look away!
I think I can move my head, but
this chance doesn't come every day!
I-I don't want to do anything that
you don't want me to do, Nonoa!
But I can't control my head. It's forcing me to look at your butt!
Really?
A-Again?
It's time to get close and personal.
I wanted to wait until I was married!
W-What is it this time?
What? My right hand is moving on its own.
Wait, does this mean that...
I'm the pervy demon now?!
Are you trying to kill me?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч