Nonoa, are you okay?
For the record, my dick moving is not of my own accord.
Th-Th-This is completely out of my control!
What are you saying at a time like this, Yamato?!
My left hand is moving by itself!
Why are my fingers going to my nipples?
Your body is mine.
And...
So is your package.
That's mine too.
Nonoa
Hey, Yamato!
Don't get any weird ideas from.
I'm not!
My dick... It's experiencing pleasures that it's never felt before...
Oh god, this might be bad.
If you cum now, I won't be able to harvest it.
No! My body's moving on its own again!
Yamato, seriously, look away!
I think I can move my head, but this
chance doesn't come every day!
I-I don't want to do anything that
you don't want me to do, Nonoa!
But I can't control my head. It's forcing me to look at your butt!
Really?
A-Again?!
It's time to get close and personal.
I wanted to wait until I was married!
What? My right hand is moving on its own.
Wait, does this mean that...
Am I the pervy demon now?!
Are you trying to kill me?!
~The Milking Battle of Angels and Demons~
The angel descends during the sunset!
You can do whatever you want to Sera's boobs ♡ arc
Oh, it's this sensation again...
It's like somebody's licking my dick!
No! I can't give into the sweet bliss of
the visual and pleasure before me!
I'm about to blow!
Wh-What's going on...
O-Ow! It's gonna break! It's gonna break!
Nonoa
Yamato?
What's going on? My legs won't stop moving!
Stop! Stop!!
Yamato, if you get any closer then th-that's gonna hit me!
You've got it backwards, you're the
one moving! I haven't moved at all!
Stop being stupid! J-Just lower it or something!
I told you already, I can't control it at all.
And anyway,
I think part of the reason why my dick
is so out of control right now,
is because of your provocative pose, Nonoa.
Huh?! Try saying that again!
Stop flapping your mouth and put your hard dick away already!
Huh? I've never heard a maiden speak so vulgarly.
Maidens have times like that!
My chastity is at risk!
Just cut it off or something!
What do you think my dick is?! A lizard's tail or something!?
Oh god, they're gonna touch.
Nonoa, we're already this far, how about
we just sit back and enjoy the ride.
I don't want it to happen like this!
Th-This is...
Does this mean I'm saved or...
Nonoa!
Nonoa! Hey, are you okay!
Pull it together!
How did I mess that up?
That was such an amateur's mistake.
Boobies...
a beautiful older lady's boobs...
W-Why are you dressed up like a demon?
Oh? I guess you're young and quick to rebound.
Oh, right!
S-Sorry! Even I'm not sure why my
lower half is like this right now.
The unconscious girl over there is my friend.
A-And what I'm trying to say is that what's
happening here is completely consensual.
I-I'm definitely not committing a crime or anything...
I just need to directly harvest your semen myself.
My semen? Harvest it?!
My body's moving on its own again!
I shouldn't have relied on that girl and
instead done this from the start.
Hey!
Wait!
Slump.
W-Wait, that's...
A pure white dress.
An angel's halo floating above her head.
And huge wings on her back!
The tips of her hair are curled into hearts!
She's such a cute girl!
And she's riding in on a gallant... tricycle?!
What the hell are you doing on a tricycle
if you're cosplaying as an angel?!
I'm an angel so of course I'd wear angel's clothing.
And other angels like myself personally like having
a halo floating above our heads like this.
What, you really think you're a real angel?
А это кто должен переводить? Пушкин?
Well, that aside...
wouldn't a bike or a motorcycle or even a car be better?
Well, let me explain.
When I rode a bike, the front wheel came off and I fell over.
When I rode a motorcycle, I could only keep
going straight, so I fell into the ocean.
And when I rode a car I kept getting the
acceleration and brakes mixed up
and I crashed into a convenience store!
What...
I almost had to change my profession to being a demon.
And that's why when I met this splendid vehicle
that can only move by the force of one's will,
I felt like fate had intervened!
Oh my.
Poke. Poke.
W-W-W-W-Wait!
So that's where human's have their tails, huh?
That's so weird!
What's up with her weird aloof idol personality?
I don't care how much of her character
is supposed to try and be surprising...
I've never heard of a girl who doesn't even know what a dick is...
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
What's wrong with her?!
She's coming after my dick without even a moment's hesitation.
How crazy is this chick?!
Sheesh, you can just let me have a little peek, can't you?!
What do you have to lose?
I have a sense of shame, you know?!
If she insists on pretending to be
an angel, we can play dumb too.
I bet it'll lead to a very delicious situation.
Ahem.
Well, Ms. Angel?
What's your name?
My name?
My name is Sera Mitra Airun.
She's so thorough with her cosplay she even made a name.
I bet she'd even say that she's billions of years old.
That's a mouthful, can I just call you Sera-chan?
Yeah, sure.
What's your name?
M-Me?
My name's Hitsuhara Yamato.
You can call me Yama-chan.
Okie-dokie, Yama-chan!
We shouldn't try and trick such a pure and sincere girl...
Okay, I'm gonna show you my tail.
You ready?
Sure am!
When a human's tail gets angry, it can
bite you, so keep your distance, okay?
Oh, really?
Yama-chan, that... Does that mean
that your tail is in a bad mood?
Sera-chan, it looks like it's mad at you for poking it earlier.
It's my fault?
Yeah, sorry to break it to you.
The only way to appease it is to take something...
soft and put it in between that and then rub it.
Something... something like...
Boobs, maybe?
Boobs?
Crap, did I go too fast?
I've never heard of an idol who would ever just straight
up give a guy a tit fuck in this situation.
How do I get out of this?
By boobs do you mean these boobs?
Are you okay, Yama-chan?!
If I can make your tail's mood get better with my boobs, then...
Here we go.
I can't move them that well.
Oh, I know!
Sorry I just went in without introducing myself.
My name is Sera Mitra Airun.
Pleased to meet you.
I'll do my best, so feel better, okay?
Huh? It's getting kind of slimy.
It's easier to move around it now.
Such a good girl!
I've never met anyone as kind as her!
She's a real angel!
But, you know...
I've met so many people today... angels, demons...
Nonoa?!
Where's Nonoa?!
I don't see her anywhere!
That girl cosplaying as a demon's gone too!
Demon?
Oh, right!
Firika?! Where are you Firika Mia Shatana?!
Where are you, Nonoa?
And Firika...
Just what is... Firika Mia Shatana?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: jordan
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч