Why is that guy the representative?
I guess humans are like that.
Seriously.
I can't believe there's a human
who won't listen to what I say.
Geez.
I-Isn't this a bathroom!?
What the hell?
Damn it! Why did I have to
materialize in this kind of place!?
Sheesh... This is why I hate the human world.
Nuki Doki ~A Demon and an Angel's Cum-Pumping Battle~
Love-Struck Succubus - The Cum-Sucking 9 Straddling Devil Filika
Huh? Why do I have to go?
On top of that, humans...
As you already know, Filika-chan,
Heaven and Hell have been fighting for
a long time about who's the best.
It's obvious. We demons are better!
But the fight isn't over yet.
That's why we're going to let humans, a
third party, decide which of us is better.
But they're so vulgar.
It's already been decided.
So Filika-chan, as a representative of the demon
world, you can't let the angels win.
You're the human who's been chosen, right?
Here, sign a contract with me immediately.
Huh? What the hell? Why?
I'm getting seriously sick of this.
Who are you?
I'm Filika-sama, the first daughter
of the Queen of the demon world.
Queen... of the demon world?
Who cares about the details? Just
hurry up and sign this already!
What is it?
It's a contract, obviously.
There's no way I'd sign such a suspicious piece of paper!
You, a mere human, dare to brush me off?
Now, sign the contract!
No way!
More importantly, just let me go!
I, the most elite devil in the demon world, have
to go to such great lengths for a mere human?
H-Hey, stop.
So this is a cock.
Stop! Put it back in my pants!
Don't you dare order me around, you filthy human.
Ouch.
I've heard that it usually feels good when you do this.
So it hurts, huh?
It's getting hard.
Wow, this is amazing! It's pulsing!
It's so hard!
That's enough.
Oh, come on, just be honest.
Your cock is enjoying this.
Making that face is only gonna make
me want to tease you more.
I wonder...
Will feeling this good make you cum?
Oh, but you mustn't.
I won't forgive you if you cum without my permission.
If only you would sign the contract...
Who'd do that?
So you're gonna tough it out, huh?
Here goes, then.
This is only the beginning.
Wow! I didn't know so much cum would come out.
Why did you cum without my permission?
Are you gonna sign the contract?
No! Never!
Oh yeah?
Then I guess I have no choice.
All right, let's get it on.
You have to take responsibility for this,
because you're making me do it.
Wai...
Are you ready?
Ouch.
It hurts.
Is this your first time?
What are you saying?
I'm fine. It doesn't hurt.
Oh my God...
It's even bigger than before!
It's better to show my tits like this, right?
My insides are getting torn apart.
It hurts!
No, it hurts.
Because it's your first time.
It's not!
This is...
This is nothing.
What is this? This is amazing!
I, the daughter of the Queen of the demon
world, am enjoying sex with a filthy human.
What is this?
The friction on my pussy...
Your cock is clinging to my pussy.
It's gonna turn me inside out.
Your cock is reaching deep inside my pussy.
Oh my God.
I'm...
Obviously, it's not my first time. I wouldn't
waste that on a human like you.
You can't hold it, right?
You can cum now.
Go ahead and cum deep inside me, as much as you can.
You came.
You came inside me.
There's so much.
Even if you don't sign, this pretty much seals the deal.
All you have to do is simply choose me.
I've had enough. I just want to go home.
I don't want to stay in the human world.
Huh? What?
She's the representative of the angel world?
Geez, give me a break.
What is this?
What... is this?
Why? This can't be happening!
Filika-chan.
Mother?
The battle has begun.
We decided in the angel world that you guys
should not interfere with one another.
That's why you can't move.
What is this? You never told me about this!
If you interfere any more than
this, you will forfeit the battle.
Which means we lose.
Could we actually lose because of that?
Yes. Just deal with it.
I understand.
This is enough. Let me loose.
You're staying like this until they finish.
Seriously?
Queen Elka-sama told me that when I was
with you, I should light this incense.
Oh, really?
Huh?
Y-Yamato-san, I'm feeling weird.
For some reason, my body's getting hot.
It's hot.
Go ahead. Do as you please.
You've seen my breasts.
Yamato-san, you're touching my breasts.
Your hands are so... warm.
I'm getting touched in such a sensitive place.
Your tongue...
Even though this is my first time, I'm feeling really good.
No.
You're licking my most sensitive spot.
It's inside!
No!
It feels so good.
You haven't cum yet, right?
N-No.
I'm finally ready.
So pleases...
Come, Yamato-san.
Get inside me.
It's going in!
My pussy is so tight around your cock.
It's okay. You can move.
Yamato-san... slow down!
Sorry.
It's okay. I have to get used to it, so it's okay.
I'm feeling you, Yamato-san.
So much!
I'm feeling so much of you inside me.
Yamato-san, you can thrust harder if you wish.
Yamato-san, you're satisfying my pussy.
I'm feeling you so much.
I'm getting hot!
You're so intense.
Yamato-san, it's okay!
Go ahead and cum inside me!
You're amazing.
Yamato-san, you came so much inside of me.
Even though this was my first time, it felt really good!
So now we have a deal.
The hell was that!?
Time flies, doesn't it?
It's already been two weeks.
It's about time to decide.
Our victory, that is.
Say whatever you want.
Come on, Yamato, hurry up and choose me.
If you do that, it will all be over.
F-Filika-san, please get off Yamato-san.
Hell no. How dare you order me around?
No matter how much you like Yamato-san,
our fight is a different story.
We need to decide this properly.
Why does it have to be like that?
I get it.
You're avoiding the fight not because
you're afraid of losing,
but because you're afraid of losing Yamato-san, right?
Gimme a break.
It's obvious I'm gonna win.
Fighting would be a waste of time.
How would you know?
Yamato-san's been nice to me these past few days.
That's...
We'll see about that.
This isn't the best place, but it'll do.
Yamato?
Yamato-san, this is something
you have to decide by yourself.
We will accept your decision.
It's just...
Yamato-san, what's wrong?
Funny it turned out this way.
It's as if it's connected.
It's getting harder by the minute.
Yes indeed.
I don't want anyone to see me this way.
Y-Yamato-san?
This much...
It's so big.
It's pulsing.
You're feeling good.
I'm gonna squeeze your cum out.
There's so much cum.
You better have chosen me by now.
It looks so limp.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm feeling better now.
What's that loose expression on your face?
Boring.
It can't be helped.
Yamato-san's at school.
I'm gonna go interrupt him.
You shouldn't do that. You'll bother him.
Pitiful. You angels are way too serious.
But we demons aren't like that.
Filika-san!
Huh? Where am I?
Geez, human guys like those kinda girls?
Yamato, you meanie.
It's okay to hang with me too, you know?
We're in the middle of class!
Don't say things like that, Yamato.
That's enough.
Yamato?
Is there something there?
Huh? Yamato?
Putting your head in a place like that.
So this is what guys like, huh?
What are you doing? I'm in the middle of class.
Don't talk while your head is there.
Geez.
Guys like this, right?
Your cock has already gotten so big.
It feels good when I squeeze
your cock with my tits, right?
There's no way I'd lose to Sera.
Yamato, you're twitching.
It's flowing down.
Your naughty cock deserves this.
Your cock is being so naughty.
I won't go easy on you.
It's twitching this much.
You're feeling it too much.
Is it coming out?
You can cum.
Wow...
You poured so much cum into my mouth.
Did it feel good?
Yamato...
You want to put it in, right?
It's okay. I want it too.
Your cock is plunging into my pussy.
Yes, thrust your cock deep inside of me.
Yamato, make me feel good!
Poke my sensitive spots with your cock!
It's deep inside of me.
Fuck me harder!
Yes, Yamato. Harder!
Move your cock a bit higher. Rub it harder!
No, not there. Higher.
It feels good there.
Sheesh, is this what I should be doing?
It's still too soon for you to make love to me like a man.
Your cock is inside.
Yes! I knew it was better to look down at you like this.
This suits me.
Your cock is touching all my sensitive spots.
Yes!
Your cock is feeling it.
Looks like you're about to cum.
You want to cum inside of me?
Amazing!
Yes!
I'm going to cum, Yamato.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
There's so much cum in my pussy. So deep inside of me.
You came so much! You're way too horny.
You'd better choose me now.
Filika-san...
I still can't move.
Filika-san, you don't have to do it.
I'll take Yamato-san home.
That's what you say, but you're
actually gonna fuck him, right?
Huh? Yamato?
Hey, Hitsuhara, you bastard!
That's dangerous!
Sera!
Yamato!
Yamato-san!
No, this can't be happening!
Yamato!
Filika-san, leave this to me.
If you touch this light...
Shut up. He's my manservant.
I can't let him go just because of this.
Geez, don't mess with me!
What the hell?
Stop. Just wait for now.
Mother?
Don't you dare touch that light!
Yamato...