Why is that guy the representative?
Are humans really like this?
Geez.
Besides, just the fact that there is a human
who can defy the likes of me...
Good grief.
This is the toilet!
What is this?
Geez, why did I have to come out through this thing?
Man, that's why I hate the human world.
~Semen Squirt Battle Between An Angel and A Demon~
Tsundere Succubus ~Filica~ The Demon sucks a straddled kid
What? Why do I have to go?
And to a human...
I think you already know, Filica,
but for a long time now the heaven and the demon realm
are competing to see which one is the best.
/
Of course our demon realm is the best one!
But it has yet to be actually settled.
That's why after an agreement by both realms,
we've decided to let a human act as the third party.
But that doesn't mean I have to put up with such vulgar...
It's already been decided.
That's why Filica-chan,
as a representative of the demon realm,
you will not be allowed to suffer defeat from a angel.
So you're the chosen human, eh?
Here, just sign this and form a contract with me already.
Eh? What is this?
Why?
Geez, I'm starting to really hate this...
Who are you?
I am one of the most elite within the demon realm.
The Great Demon Lord's eldest daughter, Mistress Filica.
Demon realm? Great Demon Lord?
Just forget about that and sign this already!
What's this?
A contract of course.
There's now way I'm going to sign that suspicious
looking broken piece of paper!
I can't believe that a human has just made a fool out of me.
Now, sign the contract.
I don't want to.
More importantly, bring me down!
You're still acting tough in front of a super
elite member of the demon realm?
Hey, stop that.
Oh, so this is a cock.
Stop, zip it back!
Don't you dare order me around like that, human.
Ouch!
Eh? I heard that it feels good when it's touched like this.
It hurts?
It's getting hard.
Wow, it's twitching.
And it's getting even harder.
This is nothing...
Just be honest about it already.
Your cock likes it, right?
If you show me an expression like that
I'll feel like teasing you even more.
I wonder if you're about to cum.
Does it feel so good that you're almost about to cum?
But I won't allow it.
I won't just let you cum.
Oh, but it's okay if you sign it though.
Who in the world world...
Quite the stubborn one, eh?
Well, a little challenge is not bad.
We're just getting...
Wow, so semen gets ejaculated like that.
Hey, what are you cumming suddenly for?
Does that mean you'll sign the contract?
No, I won't!
I see.
It can't be helped then.
Well now...
Let's get to the serious part.
You've pushed me up to this point.
You'll have to take responsibility for this.
Hey...!
Are you ready?
Ouch...
It hurts...
Is this your first time?
What are you talking about?
It doesn't hurt... I'm just fine!
This big thing is in me, and its touching my womb.
Its better if I show my breasts like this, right?
Your cock is getting wet all the way inside.
Ouch...
It's because it's your first time.
I said it's not...!
This is nothing...
This is...
What's this?
On no...
A demon lord's daughter having sex with
a human doesn't feel the slightest...
What am I saying?
My pussy is being completely rubbed.
This is...!
His cock feels hot.
My pussy feels like it's going to melt.
Your cock is entering deep inside me.
This feels good...
I...
Wow...
Of course it's amazing.
It's more than what you deserve, human.
You can't hold it in anymore, right?
Then...
It's okay.
Cum all the way...
Cum all the way inside me.
It's coming out...
It's coming out inside...
Lots of it...
That was close!
Even without signing, this seals the contract.
You just need to choose me afterwards.
I want to go home already.
I just can't stay forever in the human realm you know!
What?
Is she the heaven realm's representative?
Geez, stop kidding me.
What is this?
What in the world is this?
Why?
No way!
Filica-chan?
Mother?
The battle has already begun.
The decision will be made by the partner.
So it has been decreed that none of you can interrupt each other.
You won't be able to move an inch there.
What kind of crap is that?
I never knew that!
If you intend to resist, the battle will be over
and it will be the demon realm's loss.
Eh? We can lose because of that?
That's right.
So just stay put there.
I understand.
Hey, just make it a bit more loose!
You're staying that way until they finish.
No way.
I've been told by Elca-sama to stay like this
when we are together, Yamato-san.
I see, umm...
Huh? Yamato-san, I feel weird.
Somehow my body feels warm and hot.
Please, do what you want.
Yamato-san is looking at my breasts.
It's getting caressed...
And your hands feel hot.
If you stroke that sensitive part...
Yamato-san's tongue...
It's my first time, and yet I...
No...
My most sensitive part is being licked...
It's inside...
Wow.
Yamato-san it's your turn next, right?
Yeah.
I'm ready now, so... please.
Come to me, Yamato-san.
Come inside me.
Ouch, it's going in...
Yamato-san, your cock feels tight.
It's okay, please move.
Yamato-san, be a bit more gentle.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'll be fine once I get used to it.
I can feel you Yamato-san...
...fully inside of me.
My insides are full...
Yamato-san.
You can try pushing more intensely now.
You're really filling my insides, Yamato-san.
I'm becoming horny because of you, and its getting hotter.
So intense...
It's okay, Yamato-san.
Release it all the way in me.
This is amazing.
Your liquids are pouring and filling me.
Yamato-san, that was my first time,
but it felt very good.
With this the contract is settled.
Eh?
What was that about?
Things sure went by quickly.
It's been two weeks already,
so it's about time that a decision is made.
As our victory.
Just say what you want.
Come on, Yamato,
just choose me already.
So that everything will be settled.
Filica-san, get away from Yamato-san!
No can do.
And don't you try to order me around like that.
No matter how much you like Yamato-san,
our battle is a different story.
So we must do it fair and square.
Why would think its like that?
I just know.
It's because he's going to be taken from you
if you lose our battle, right?
Stop kidding me.
Victory is already mine so your efforts are useless.
That's not true.
Yamato-san has been really kind to me lately, so...
Oh, let's see then.
Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Not exactly my spot, but I guess it's fine.
Huh?
Yamato?
It's all about your own decision,
so we can't do anything but respect it.
However...
Yamato-san, what's wrong?
What an interesting situation we have here.
It looks like it's still connected somehow.
And it's already getting stiff.
Oh yeah!
I don't want to be seen like this.
Yamato-san?
It's become like this...
It's big...
and it's twitching... He's really feeling it.
I'm going to squeeze it out all the way.
It's pumping this much?
He could have just come to me you know.
Now you're finished, huh?
Are you really okay?
I feel relieved now.
Hmph, looking as if nothing happened.
This is so boring.
We can't do anything about it.
Yamato's at school anyway.
Let's go and visit him then!
You can't do that!
You'll be disturbing Yamato-san.
You poor goodie angel.
That's nothing to us demons.
Filica-san?
Huh? Where in the world am I?
Geez, so human males like that kinda thing, huh?
Geez, Yamato you're so mean!
Notice me even for a bit will you?
We're in class!
Please don't be like that, Yamato!
Geez, stop fooling ar...
Yamato?
Something over there?
Huh? Yamato?
Digging your face like that in my thing...
So guys really like this.
What are trying to do?
I'm in the middle of class!
Don't talk while your face is in there!
Geez.
Guys like this, right?
Yamato, you're cock's already gotten this big.
Feels good to have your cock between these, right?
I'm not going to lose to Sera!
Yamato, you're thing is getting twitchy, and its going wild.
And wild boys deserve this.
Your cock is still going wild.
Just don't move...
It's twitching, almost as if its going to burst.
Are you about to cum?
It's okay.
Wow, you released this much.
Did it feel good?
Yamato...?
You want to put in, right?
Okay.
I also want it in me.
Your cock is rubbing inside my pussy.
Yes.
It's penetrating inside me.
Yamato, let me get horny.
Your thing is getting stiff inside, and its thrusting in.
Go deeper in me... be more rough.
Yes.
Be more intense, rub it all inside.
Not there...
Higher...
Where it feels good...
I think I need to put some effort into this after all.
You're still too green to lead me like that.
Your cock's coming inside.
Yes.
It's really better for me if I'm the one who's looking down on you.
It's now rubbing in where it feels great.
Wow...
Your cock is getting really stiff.
So you're about to cum?
You want to release it in me?
Wow...
This feels great...
I'm about to cum, Yamato.
I'm cumming!
Lots of cum are pouring inside.
I'm getting filled inside.
For you to release this much...
This is too much for copulation you know.
Just do it to me for real already.
Filica-san, you...!
I still can't move!
Forget it Filica-san, I'm the one who will send him home!
Send? You just plan on sending him somewhere
else so you can do it, right?
Huh, Yamato?
Hitsuhara, you...!
Watch out!
Sera!
Yamato!
Yamato-san!
No way...
No way!
Yamato!
Filica-san, leave this to me.
If a demon like you touches this light...
Shut up!
He's my servant!
This is nothing!
Geez, stop kidding me!
What?
No, you must wait for now.
Mother!
Even for you that light is dangerous!
Yamato...