Our demon king's army has been invading the human realm.
The holy knight Ruvyrias stood in our way.
On top of her power being such a joke,
she fell into the hands of us demons.
She's apparently top-notch down there.
Jeez, master!
Don't forget about the former
demon king Shout's seal!
Of course, don't forget about me too.
The Fallen RPG: Holy Knight Ruvyrias
Episode 2: The Advance of Demons - Gang Rape of Ruvyrias, Semen Bath of Iris and Lifulia
Stop, I'm right here!
Y-You took a while.
Won't all of the women in this town end up
getting raped if you came here any later?
Don't mess with me!
I'll never ever forgive you
after doing such a thing to me!
A woman can't live without having cocks.
You who made love with my master
should know that by now.
Take a look! You were making
the same face last time.
A fine lady like you is worthy
of becoming my personal fuckhole.
Scoundrel! You dare speak such words!
I'll gladly take that provocation of yours!
What's wrong? Did tasting womanly
pleasures muddle up your sword skills?
Sh-Shut up!
I'll end you with this!
Your attacks are unusually lighter!
Do you want to make love with me that much?
D-Don't mess with me! Who would want you to...
I can't get enough of that prideful face of yours!
It was just about time,
and I was thinking of rewarding these fellows.
Your eyes will be opened, just like mine.
Stop!
Don't touch me, you brutes!
N-No, don't put it in!
Don't put that thing in me!
I-It can't go in further!
My belly will be ruptured!
I can't do this! It'll get torn!
I'll get torn apart down there!
My belly...
She's amazing.
She's still alive despite having monsters as partners.
Will she keep it up, or else...
I-I'm begging you...
Let me go home, your highness demon king...
Very well!
But if you'll take my sperm in after getting raped,
will you ever think about going back home?
No! Not that cock!
It feels so good!
Even after getting fucked that much, this tightness...
You're fucking my brains out!
Your cock is scraping me inside!
I can't hold back anymore!
Ruvyrias, be mine!
I-I don't want to come!
I can't stop coming! I'm coming again!
Coming... I'm gonna come!
No! I'll lose it if you shoot your sperm in me!
I'm gonna come already!
I'm coming—!
It's coming out! It's your raw cock juice!
Huh? I somehow am getting filled with mana...
Oh... That's right.
After getting creampied by this cock...
It's gushing out
My pussy is gushing out because of your cock!
Coming... I'm coming!
I'm coming while gushing semen out!
What's up? You should be able to go home now.
Or maybe you finally came to like
the life of a woman for mating.
H-Huh? I'm going home...
Oh...
She channeled all of her remaining power.
She's quite something.
Isn't she amusing?
No matter how many times Ruvyrias
challenges me, I'll rape her every time!
I wonder how long she'll endure it.
Wh-What the...
This isn't any good!
I-I want to come!
A-Anybody will do! Make this settle down!
Demon king... Put it inside me!
Your...
...cock!
H-Huh!?
Th-This is...
I-It's inside!
It's in my pussy!
It feels good!
How is it, milady? Weren't you lonely?
I'm having my master's cock that you long for
reach you through a sensory link!
Fully savor it!
Wh-Why is it inside?
B-But...
This certainly is that man's...
Between that girl and me,
whose pussy feels better?
Don't ask odd questions.
It'll be decided at the end!
Whether it's you or her...
Jeez! You're such a tease, master!
I'll end up coming if you do that!
Shoot a lot of it! Let it all out!
I'll savor your thick semen using my pussy!
After all, you'll imagine her pussy
while dumping your semen in me!
Almost there! You're about to come.
Let's come! Your semen will meld us together!
Coming... I'm coming!
His cock is rock hard and swelling!
I-I'm scared!
I'll die if he comes in me right now!
I'll die in ecstasy! No—!
It's coming!
His cock milk is really pouring into my pussy!
I'm coming! Coming!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
It's the best...
I love the demon king's cock...
Th-This is how much I want...
...that man's cock.
Huh!? Did she escape from you again?
Are you stupid, onii-chan?
Yeah, yeah! I get it.
Now your goal is only that holy
knight and using her pussy.
Or rather, are you a monkey?
A demon king like you still hasn't made
a human female knight fall from grace?
Hmm?
But even after going through that much,
she still kept her sanity.
She's truly a woman worth raping.
What, aren't you glad that you'll still be fucking her?
The troops are also doing their jobs well...
I mean, this is the first time
for me to see the demon king
not making love with a woman and not nude.
Thanks to both of your diversion efforts
that this worked out. I'm grateful!
That's only because our pussies
will distract him if we're with him.
He's just keeping us away from him.
You two... Is it one of those days?
Your promise to quickly end the war
and use my pussy for one whole night...
That's out of the question now.
Am I right, your highness?
Don't tell me that you forgot about that!
Can't you do anything about our father anymore?
I've kept proposing brilliant ideas
but you never listen, you stupid cock!
You bitches!
I told you not to suddenly plunge it in!
She'll fall for me soon!
There's no way for humans
to win against a demon king!
That's right.
You surely are a walking cock with
nothing else in mind but pussies.
Beneath your majestic aura, you live
an easygoing life with a happy attitude.
I love all of those about you...
Are you mocking me, you bitch!?
No!
Your cock is horrible!
Don't shove it in my pussy!
No... No!
What, are you stopping midway?
A demon king like you is already giving up?
Just how much did Tia and that
holy knight milk you dry?
What a weakling!
Who said that, is it this mouth?
Did this mouth say something?
It seems that I end up satisfying both
of you too much when I do you two!
U-Umm, your highness...
Huh!?
See? If you want onii-chan
to make love with you, it'll be easy.
That felt great!
Now we can work hard on
our separate mission again!
Ah, wait for a moment. I have to relieve myself.
Now I feel like doing it too.
Why did you go here?
You should do it over there.
It's what they call as being "washroommates".
I'm in a good mood today.
What's "shroommate"?
Huh? Why are these orcs...
Hey, stop!
Hey, what are you doing? Let me go!
Could it be that father's power
can reach even here?
They totally went berserk! They're dangerous!
I can't put any strength to move...
We got carried away and made onii-chan...
...fuck us too much, didn't we?
I-I'm still not wet... It still hurts!
You can't do this! Only the demon king
is allowed to use my pussy!
W-Wow! It really is an orc!
They're all too big!
It hurts! The one in me is too hard!
You two, let go! Let go of us!
Y-You're gonna come? Stop, if you
come inside me right now...
I won't forgive you if you come inside me!
I'll turn you into char!
He's eating me out! This is bad! This is bad!
This cock is so hard! I can't breathe!
O-On top of forcing his cock in my mouth,
he's lapping up my groin with his tongue!
To think that I'm gonna come
from being eaten out by an orc...
I can't take this!
This is gross!
He's shaking his hips while coming!
This is weird!
They have such strong sex drive!
No, don't put it in!
This feels...
This feels disgusting!
They release such thick semen!
Huh? Did they just turn into a crowd?
Wait, any more than that will be...
I can't take any more orc cocks!
The orc's sperm won't stop
pouring out of my pussy!
An orc ejaculates by squirting too much amount!
You'll tear it up! It'll get torn apart!
Don't do that!
What are you two doing?
Even my head turned into orc sperm inside...
Ugh, this feels gross...
I prefer the demon king's after all...
To think that the former demon king's seal
has weakened up to this extent...
I need to hurry up.
That's right, and you two truly are erotic!
Ahh! Onii-chan's cock is the best!
Ahh, that's not fair!
Your highness, give it to me as well!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji