This peaceful world which is abundant
enough to provide for all living things
was suddenly attacked by demons.
I won't forgive them!
My name is...
Did something happen today?
Your cock is way stiffer than usual, master!
Did seeing female humans being
indiscriminately raped arouse you?
I'm glad that my first move was taking you away
from the range of my former
demon king father's power.
You would've been a formidable enemy otherwise.
If I stayed under the effects
of Shout-sama's power
and fought against you instead,
you'll never stand a chance.
I certainly can't win against this pussy.
It's the best cunt around.
I'm gonna come again!
Master, your diabolical cock feels good!
The head is ramming and rubbing against my womb!
You're about to shoot your
impregnating semen into me!
Knock me up! Knock me up!
My pussy is ready to take
your sperm in as well!
It's coming out!
Your piping hot semen is
forcing me into submission!
You're spraying your thick
cock juice into my womb pussy!
Are you the demon king?
So, you've already been resurrected.
Your ruthless invasion in the human world
is unforgivable, so prepare yourself!
So you're that female knight who's been
giving us trouble all over the place.
Oh... She's a nice woman.
Master?
Do you think that a mere human
like you can win against me?
Shut up! I'll end your schemes
even if I have to pay with my life!
Your well-stacked ass and ample bust are both nice.
It's a waste for you to end up
becoming a swordswoman.
How about serving under me?
I'll teach you a lot about the
pleasures of being a woman!
V-Villain! Just how lowly can you be?
I'll slay you right here!
The Fallen RPG: Holy Knight Ruvyrias
Episode 1: Stolen Purity - The Resolve of Ruvyrias
Master?
For me to run away from her...
I'll rape you!
I swear that I'll rape you!
You're pounding my pussy all of a sudden!
A loss is a loss!
What the hell! Are you saying that I lost?
I should've at least rammed that pussy of hers!
Th-There's nothing we can do about it!
Us demons are naturally weak against holy knights!
What's this? Are you enjoying
getting forcefully fucked?
You're being reckless!
Your burly cock is mashing up and
scraping my womb more than usual!
Oh, no! I can't take it anymore!
It's gonna spill out of me...
Both my pussy and my baby room
are gonna melt into a sloppy mess!
A holy woman's power is
necessary to seal my father.
If I can use that female knight, then...
So, you intentionally showed yourself to me.
Have you already forgotten?
You fled pathetically back then.
I just didn't know that you are a holy knight.
Go back to the demon realm
if you still value your life!
Her holy sword certainly is troublesome.
If you're going against a holy knight,
shall this evil deity lend you her powers, then?
What... Are you saying
that you're an evil deity?
Alright! Lend it to me, Tia!
How's that, female knight?
Make my death swift.
Stop! Don't touch me!
What are you doing?
S-Stop!
Stop! That place is...
Stop! Stop!
What's this? Aren't you a virgin?
It's a waste to keep such a fine hole to yourself.
What's up with that?
Don't tell me that... Anything but that!
Stop, Listen to me! Stop this!
S-Something that huge won't fit inside!
No... I don't want to!
No way! Pull it out... Pull it out...
Take that thing out of me!
Are you giving me orders?
Is that the way to speak
when pleading to someone?
Th-That was inappropriate of me.
I apologize for offending you.
Stop this.
Stop this?
Please stop already...
P-Please, I'm begging you!
No—!
N-No way, it went inside me...
I'd hate it if you underestimate me down there.
The whole thing hasn't got in yet.
Huh?
O-Ouch!
How is it? This makes you
a full-fledged woman now!
Ouch! It hurts!
Stop moving! Stop moving!
I-I'll kill you! I will kill you!
Ouch! Stop...
Stop!
Don't you look lovely while teary-faced?
What's wrong? That pain will
soon turn into pleasure!
No... D-Don't tell me...
No, you can't! Anything but that!
Forgive me...
Please... I'm begging you!
Don't shoot it out! Don't come!
Th-This can't be... It's coming out...
A man's stuff is pouring...
...into me.
Wh-What's happening?
My body, my head, and down there...
They're all feeling numb...
Wh-What? What is this?
Th-This is weird!
So, how does the Demon King Voice's
semen of pleasure feel like?
He can dominate any life form using his semen.
This makes your pussy a cum dumpster now!
I-I'm...
I can't get enough of your face warped in agony
and that defiant look in your eyes!
You're beautiful, Ruvyrias!
When female humans take
a demon's sperm in their bodies,
they end up producing breast milk!
Your breast milk is delicious!
It has a fantastic flavor!
Okay, let the orcs have a taste as well!
Yes, let's do that.
Wh-What was that?
That is teleportation magic, your highness.
Hmm?
Should I accompany you, onii-chan?
Iris...
Aren't you having a hard time?
It can't be helped...
Huh?
D-Don't suddenly plunge it in!
Wait...
To think that you're using your cute little sister
as a pussy cum dumpster...
Teleportation magic?
Are you saying that the female knight
possesses that much mana?
Didn't you give her a creampie?
Then it can be done using your vast
mana pool as a demon king.
So, does it mean that she was able to escape
because I gave her a creampie?
I wasn't able to cover such
a top-notch woman with my semen!
That's so sudden!
Your piping hot semen is gushing into me!
Yes—!
Is her pussy that great?
Onii-chan, your head is filled
with nothing but pussies!
Is that how much you want to impregnate
your blood-related little sister?
Onii-chan, your cock is swelling up inside me!
You're hammering my pussy!
This perverted cock is forcefully penetrating me!
Coming! Coming! Coming!
Your sperm is about to come out!
Here comes your thick stuff!
Your sperm is flowing in! It's pouring in!
Your creamy and raw cock milk is spurting!
Your semen is making me piss in orgasm...
You're mesmerizing!
I'm certainly making you mine, Ruvyrias!
Lifulia! Are you in there, Lifulia?
Hey, forget about that girl and do me
in my pussy one more time!
You wait here outside.
Uhh...
Your highness...
She's the same sleepyhead as always.
Isn't this the demon king's? Yummy!
If it's the demon king's cock,
I can lick it as much as you want!
You're such a cutie!
It's delicious!
I can't take it anymore!
A cock went inside me!
Wow... This thickness and hardness...
This is the demon king's cock for sure!
Yes, it's making squelching sounds!
I'm happy! It feels good, your highness!
Live here with me,
and then you can use my pussy
as much as you please!
That might be great too.
Here it is... You're about to come...
Am I right, your highness?
Please pump my womb full
with your piping hot and impregnating semen!
It's squirting and spurting into me!
I love your raw and creamy semen!
There's plenty deep inside me!
There's so much of your thick semen pouring inside!
I love you so much, your highness!
Please kiss me!
I am your woman!
Huh, your highness?
Good morning!
I somehow had an amazing dream!
Why did you come here?
Could it be that you went here for my pussy?
Yes, you're right. I won't forget
how sexy you are when asleep.
You suddenly shoved it in!
My pussy is soaking wet for some reason.
Why are you fucking her pussy!?
Oh... So you're here as well, Iris-san?
You're still the same musclebrain meathead.
Jeez! Stop going into heat whenever
you see onii-chan, you tits in vain!
May the slut who only joined
for inquiry please shut up!
I am fully devoted to the demon king!
A wimp like you won't amount
to any military might!
I can jack him off as many times as he wants too!
Well, I never knew that a public
cum dumpster is capable of speech!
Then you can hear too, right?
The exit is that way!
Onii-chan is tired of the pussy
you're proud of in particular!
Did your stupidity worsen from your tits
hogging too much nourishment?
Jeez!
Wh-What's up with you two!?
You can't stop me!
I'm always around for your sexual relief!
Don't underestimate the times that I spent
together with the demon king!
Y-You two! Hey, wait...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji