The Flawless President: Mira Campbell
She is not only top of the class in both academics and athletics,
but also in beauty as well, making her the flawless President.
But given her high specs reputation, she's seen as out
of anyone's league. Her cool and lone wolf demeanor
have earned her the moniker, "Snow White".
Because of that, no boy even attempts to get close
to her and instead just admire her from afar. As a
result, she's still a beautiful virgin, high school girl.
The prodigy who skipped grades Kujo Shizuryuu
She's a girl who's recognized for not only having
skipped grades and her beauty but also for her iconic
bob cut that's easy to see when she's studying.
As the youngest in her class, she's very reserved
and quiet especially due to her intense fear of men.
Because of that, she's been given the name "Iron Maiden".
However, underneath her skirt lies an unbelievable secret...
The only one who's noticed is Shousuke...
The Legendary Meat Stick
Yabuki Shousuke
A completely average male student.
However, as soon as every student in the school
began enjoying having sex with each other.
He turned the other way and disregarded this golden opportunity.
However, the unused meat stick that he’s packing is very special...
The Seika Academy used to be a normal private
school, but after the previous headmaster retired.
His daughter, Yarima Keiko took over and to
everyone's surprise, turned it into a sex academy
as her first move after being inaugurated.
Stating that this was a way to combat the declining population,
the threw away all sense of virtue and spread the idea that sex should be enjoyed as much as one enjoys eating.
She aggressively implemented the rule that all
students had to have sex and even offered financial
assistance for students who got pregnant.
By now all the students have acclimated to their
new sex filled school lives and there are barely
any students who aren't participating...
Despite that, Shousuke continued to kill time
in the same place while he let the chance to sate
his healthy desires as a boy, slip away from him.
He ended up meeting the Flawless President,
Mira and ended up giving heir first times to each
other on the top of the roof in plain sight.
Further, he was hunted down by the school's Queen of
sluts, Nana, and ended up having a three way with her
and Mira in the empty Nurse’s Office. From that moment
on, his life began to revolve completely around sex...
Shousuke tried to escape from being reduced to a sex doll for Mira
and ended up bumping into Shizuryuu... truly, a fateful encounter.
Because during class she became drenched in the fluid that she
was trying to hold inside her urethra, she ran to the old school
building, the liquid that she had expelled soaked in the diaper.
After reaching her destination, a feeling of relief welled
up wit her, so she flipped up her skirt and began to
once again let the built up liquid come out of her.
Little did she realize that while she was
doing that, there was someone in front of her.
Previously on Yarimakuri Academy
Wh-What is this?
Oh, you're awake.
S-Souma-san?
We're classmates, not strangers. Call me by my first name.
Call my Nana.
It's so huge, it's hard to fit into my mouth!
Your dick... I can barely fit half of it inside me!
So good! Your tongue...
It's twirling around in my pussy!
I can't wait anymore!
Please take my dripping wet pussy's
first time today with your cock!
Oh my god, it's so hard!
Actually having it inside me is just too good!
It feels like my body's getting
raped by your cock in this position!
Oh god, it's coming!
I've had a lot of big cocks in me up until now, but...
I want you to fill my pussy up with
a huge serving of your sticky cum!
Hey, watch it. I haven't kissed him there yet.
I can't live without his cock too!
Kissing his cock before kissing his lips? I
expected nothing less from you, Snow White.
But sorry, Shou-kun's mine.
Don't get so full of yourself. We
were each others' first times.
This is my dick!
Shou-kun, your dick is slamming itself against my womb!
It feels so good!
Your tongue is moving inside my
pussy! It's making my pussy overflow!
I can't hold on anymore!
I want you to stick it in me so bad!
No! I'm not done yet!
I want more of your cock!
So good! Your dick...
It's hitting all of my soft spots!
No! I'm gonna become even more perverted.
I can't think of anything but your dick anymore!
Come on over! Private Sex School
Diaper High School Girl: Shizuryuu ~ Peeing and a Loose Ass with Anal Beads ♥
Ow!
Sorry, I was in a bit of a rush. Later.
Shousuke?!
Wait, huh?
Oh, you're the girl who skipped
grades, Kujo Shizuryuu-san, right?
Are you alright?
Yes.
You wouldn't happen to know if
a guy ran past here, would you?
Geez, he's fast.
I have high hopes for you.
I'd be glad to have you as the
next student council president.
I didn't even get to thank him for
flipping my skirt back down for me.
Toilet
It took in so much so it's pretty heavy now...
It's starting to feel weird again.
Is it because I peed myself in class?
Nobody's gonna have sex with a freak like me.
I-It's coming out!
Is it because I put in more than usual?
Oh god, it feels too good!
And now I'm peeing again...
It just feels too good!
Mira influences those close to her way too easily...
Ah! I-I'm so sorry!
Don't hurt me!
Don't make me into your cum dumpster!
You got it wrong.
More importantly, you should cover up.
Y-You're not here to rape me?
But you've already raped Snow
White and the Queen of Sluts.
Kids your age shouldn't say "rape".
D-Don't treat me like a child!
And what? You're just going to ignore
the embarrassing sight before you?
D-Do you not like girls who wear diapers?
Are you going to... clean me up down there?
O-Onii-sama, your tongue is...
I-It's twirling around inside me!
It's so good!
I-I've never felt this before!
If you keep playing with me like that I'm gonna pee again.
I'm really going to pee if you keep doing that!
I know I shouldn't, but you're not stopping!
Now that I peed on you, aren't you
going to punish me, onii-sama?
If that's what you want, then...
Up you go.
You're going to take my virginity away
as a punishment, aren't you, onii-sama?
It's so big! You're really going to rip me apart!
This is because you've been a bad girl, Shizuryuu.
Shizuryuu's been a bad girl...
Please punish her pussy with your huge dick.
You're inside me, onii-sama.
I can feel you really deep inside me!
Punish me more!
Onii-sama, your dick...
It's making my stomach so full!
It's so full!
It's so deep! Go deeper!
Onii-sama, that's...
My pussy's gonna cum for the
first time after losing its virginity!
Onii-sama, are you also going to punish my ass?
You're a smart girl.
My ass feels so weird!
M-My ass is being punished!
Onii-sama, your dick is reaching
all the way to the back of my ass!
Being punished like this while somebody's watching...
I-It's making me go crazy!
Onii-sama, your dick is jumping around inside me!
I'll let you punish me for the rest of my life, onii-sama.
Shower Room
How could you make me leave in the middle of
class to come here? You're so mean, onii-sama.
You're going to turn me into a delinquent.
You wanted this though, didn't you?
I-I have class...
I'll be waiting at the shower room
You're so pushy...
I know you want it, Shizuryuu.
Y-You're wrong.
I-I just didn't want to be yelled at by you, so I came...
Onii-sama... you're such a pervert.
Th-That's...
Y-Your tongue is as amazing as ever.
You can't wait any longer either can you, onii-sama?
Your dick is so hard, onii-sama.
And it's so big.
Let me use my mouth on it.
So this is what your dick tastes like, huh, onii-sama?
I-It's so big, I don't think it'll fit.
Don't push yourself.
It feels good.
That makes me happy. I'm so glad I can make you happy!
It makes all the punishment, worth it.
O-Onii-sama's semen...
There's so much!
Onii-sama, I want it really bad.
Please punish me with your dick, onii-sama.
My ass is being punished by your dick, onii-sama!
It's thrusting so deep inside me...
I'm losing my mind!
Wasn't it worth training your asshole with anal beads?
But your dick is so much thicker and
bigger than the beads. It's so much better!
Oh my god...
If you keep doing me like this, I'm gonna...
Onii-sama, there's so much of your
cum, pumping into my stomach!
You're even punishing my pussy!
Your dick is going to break me apart!
So rough!
Your dick's rubbing around inside me...
you're making my insides go wild!
Your dick keeps knocking so deep inside me!
It's coming so deep!
Oh my god, that feels so good!
Both my ass and pussy are...
They're breaking!
Please give me your semen, onii-sama!
I want you to punish my insides...
all the way to my stomach!
I'm being completely filled with your cum, onii-sama!
Both my ass and my pussy are
being filled with onii-sama's...
Wh-What's going on there?!
W-Was Shousuke's dick just in her ass?!
So what I saw back then was definitely...
H-How could you use that hole like that?
But it kinda looks like it feels good... I think.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч