Good evening, everyone!
At a popular spot of the sex paradise Mizuryuu Kei Land,
is an event stage where "Bitch Ranking" takes place.
Extreme idol performances are held in here everyday.
That's it for this week's introduction!
Everyone!
Are you horny?
We're your lower body idols,
"Horny Sentry"
Here! Look! Over here!
Can you see it?
Our pussies are so wet!
I want to fuck somebody. I can't take it anymore!
It's entering my pussy!
Look at me! Look at me more!
Okay, this time let's all get hyped up!
The dick twitches...
Oh, dicks are the best! It's so hot and twitching!
Good! It feels good!
My pussy is getting stirred up violently!
N-No... No good!
My body's trembling, I can't take anymore!
Oh, I'm think I'm going crazy!
Coming! I'm coming!
W-With everyone! Together!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Let's go! Mizuryuu Kei Land
#2  Lower Body Idol☆Horny Sentry
Take a look!
I've been creampied this much!
Me too, my belly is filled up.
Nice working with you. I'll be going.
Yuka-chan, are you going home?
Sorry, I have training today.
Yuka is good at performance,
but she obviously isn't as passionate on sex.
You said it.
She never even made a single
audience member come today.
Maybe Yuka-san isn't particularly fond of having sex.
Everyone's horny all the time,
always thinking about sex...
How stupid.
Please keep your handshake ticket
ready, and form two lines!
A handshake is limited to 1 minute per customer!
Hey, come on, do it already!
Plunge your dick into my pussy!
A-At last! I met you!
I always wanted to meet you!
Amazing! How big, go on!
You can move as you like! Fuck me hard!
Y-Your pussy is the best, Tsubaki-chan!
I'll be rooting for you from now on!
It's an honor to me!
C-Can we kiss?
Okay, help yourself.
Let's lick each other's tongues.
This ain't good! I'm gonna come soon!
Okay! Pour it out!
Make my pussy more dripping wet!
It's pouring in! Hot stuff keeps pouring inside!
My pussy feels sticky, it's disgusting.
Why is everyone enjoying doing this?
Err... pleased to meet you.
Please go ahead.
Are you alright?
Sorry... I'm fine.
What is this! It feels totally different from all others!
My womb is tingling and it feels good!
Hey, let's kiss!
Kiss me!
I'm... gonna come! I'm coming!
Come! Shoot it inside!
Shoot it all in me!
Okay! Time is up!
Switch with the next in line!
I guess 1 minute isn't long enough at all.
I'll be rooting for you.
Please keep doing your best!
Ah... wait!
Yuka-chan
Even when it felt so good...
In the end neither of us came!
I hate this...
I want that boy's semen!
Hey, you there.
You're the boy from the
handshake event earlier, right?
Oh no!
Horny Sentry's Yuka—
Shhh!
You see... I've been always busy with live shows,
so I don't know much about the park yet...
If you got some time, do you want
to take a walk around with me?
O-Of course! I'd be glad to if you're fine with me.
I've been your fan for a long time now!
Really?!
You bet! I especially loved that Petal Dance of yours!
I love those moves that seemed like a wild beast!
Is that so? Thank you!
That dance...
I hated it and never did well on it.
If only I knew someone will praise me like this,
I should have tried doing better.
Wait...
It's okay, shoot it out!
Come!
If you do it that rough, I'm...
You don't have to hold back,
Shoot it out with all your strength!
This feels great!
The dildo is.. rubbing... in and out!
How is it?
Does it look like I'm gonna lick the dick fountain?
Yes!
Hey, isn't it hard to walk like this?
Walking together while
holding a dick is a trend in here.
You got this hard again.
Hey, want to do it? Let's have sex.
This isn't good.
You have so many fans.
It's not fair that only I get a special treatment.
That's not...
And also, people said that you absolutely won't spread your legs outside of work.
I love that stoic part of you. Yuka-chan.
I see... So that's how people see me.
No wonder, since I always hated giving fan service.
To have sex only on fans that I like...
That would be selfishly convenient for me...
Yuka-chan?
But I want it. I want to have sex!
I want to be creampied!
My pussy is stupidly feeling horny.
I want it! I want it! I want it!
Please! I can't wait anymore!
I'm not really stoic!
Your dick felt so good,
that I can't think of anything but lewd thoughts!
So please, fuck me!
It's the Bitch Dance of Obedience.
It's a pose from their show
when they beg for a creampie.
Hey, could she be that girl...
Yuka from Horny Sentry?
You're kidding? In this place?
If you keep doing that, I won't be able to resist...
It's okay! Rape me! Rape me!
Screw my pussy!
It's inside. I fucked Yuka-chan!
I'm fucking my idol's pussy in private!
This is sex!
This is the best!
Your dick is reaching my deepest parts!
And I feel better and better every time you thrust!
That couple is so intense.
D-Do you want to do it with me?
Okay!
Excuse me, may I borrow this dick?
If you're fine with me...
Fuck me more! More!
So hot! I feel so hot!
My pussy is being ravaged,
it feels like it's melting!
It feels good! Wonderful!
Doing it together with everyone makes me feel excited!
Forgive me, Yuuta-kun!
I'm doing it again... I'm fucking someone else again!
Your dick is twitching!
I can feel it, it's getting bigger!
What should I do? You're coming inside again!
Yuka-chan, I'm coming!
I'm coming inside you!
Okay! Come, shoot it inside!
I want your seed inside me!
Cum as many times you want inside me!
I'm coming!
The warmth is gradually spreading. It feels good!
I never know that creampies can feel this good!
I'm sorry, for forcing you like that.
You're disillusioned now, aren't you?
No, that was incredible!
To think that the usually stoic Yuka-chan has a lewd side,
This gap in your personality is so adorable!
I-Is that so?
I'd love to see more of your lewd side on stage!
I'm sure all of your fans will love it!
Okay... If that's how you put it,
I will try to work harder!
Yay!
Are you horny, everyone?
We're the very lewd idols, "Horny Sentry"!
We'll have a kinky performance today!
Enjoy it as always!
For today, I will... be fucking 6 men at the same time!
Come up on stage, crazy monkeys!
Ehh?
Hey... Hey...
Wow! There's a lot of amazing dicks!
I love this. What a lewd scent!
Which should I choose first? I can't decide!
There, right there! Feels good!
Dicks! Dicks are the best!
Eh? Just one dick isn't enough!
Look at me! Everyone look at me!
I'm gonna come from both my pussy and asshole!
Dicks are going inside!
Inside my belly! Like that!
Yuka-chan!
Oh no! I'm coming!
I'm coming again!
Everyone... please spray it on me!
Make my lewd naked body sticky with sperm!
Coming! Coming! I'm coming!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project