Stand.
Bow.
Sex!
That feels good.
Geez, aren't you a little too hard?
My pussy's starting to overflow, plug it up with your dick!
Your dick's amazing!
Okay now, no need to rush.
Which dick shall I have today?
Don't worry, I'll make sure that you all get a turn.
Oh, wow.
It has so much energy! It must be a morning dick.
This is too good.
I swear, it's been nothing but this
ever since they changed the school's rules.
Our school will be ridding ourselves
of our restrictive guidelines
and will be introducing a new system
where sex will be held constantly.
It goes without saying that there will be
financial aid for those who get pregnant
and national aid for any damages you might incur.
I can't believe it. Now everyone's just going at it.
Mira-san, I'd like to thank you for yesterday.
Mira-senpai, please use this!
They're just doing it in plain sight and it's driving me crazy.
I need to find somewhere to kill some time.
The sun's out and it's pretty good weather,
so I guess here should be a nice change of pace.
Wh-Wh-What is that?!
More importantly, who is that?!
Wh-Why's he sleeping with a boner?!
I've seen some of the guy's things,
but I've never seen one like this.
Huh, aren't you the student council president?
You're in my spot.
Mind moving?
Your panties...
Y-Y-You saw them, did you?!
How dare you look at my panties!
Aren't you the one who forced me to look at them?
Y-You're just imagining things.
Anyway, that's my spot.
It's not meant to be a spot for a brute like you.
Brute? I was honestly just looking for a place to be alone.
Oh, I just assumed you were a brute because
of that monstrous thing you have there.
What thing of mine is making you call me a brute?
Why is it...
Don't you think it's a little rude to be putting that brutish
thing away after leaving it out for the world to see?
Huh?
This will be your punishment for ruining my view.
Wha... Pres...
I think this is appropriate since
you got in the way of my relaxation time.
Oh? Why is it getting like this?
It's because you're touching it. Also, I can see your panties.
Because I'm touching it? I see.
So you're just going to take it?
You're a wonderful woman and the worlds
we live in are just too different...
Everyone builds a wall to distance
themselves from me because of that.
Don't you think that's just awful?
Or perhaps you are the same as them?
Pres...
Stop calling me that.
O-Okay then, Campbell-senpai.
That doesn't sound cute at all.
Cute?
Mira-san?
That sounds even worse.
Mi-Mira?
You pass.
I think your dick's gotten even bigger.
You are so wet, Mira.
Every time you say something, I can feel your breath.
Also, you need to speak more casually to me.
We're birds of a feather, huh?
We both came here because we wanted to be alone.
I wonder if we'll go all the way and you'll take my first time.
Would that be okay with you, Mira?
Don't you think it'd feel better
if we did it while being watched?
This is the first time that someone's fondled my boobs.
It feels better than when I touch myself!
Your pussy's soaking wet, Mira.
With everyone watching me and you touching me, I...
That feels so good!
Your dick looks like it's about to burst.
It's okay, you can take my first time.
Ow! Ow! What is this?! It hurts so much!
Mira, you're tensing up too much. Loosen up your hips.
I can't! I can't! What's going on? Why's it hurt so much?!
Everyone's looking at you, Mira.
Huh? When did they...
No, why is this happening?
So you get turned on by people watching you?
You're a pretty big pervert, aren't you, Mira?
I'm not! I'm not getting turned on
by everyone looking at me.
Mira, I'm going to do it.
It's coming inside me!
Shousuke, your dick is coming inside me! It's so tight inside!
Here I go.
This is so good!
You're moving me so wildly inside me
while stirring up my insides!
Everyone can see your perverted face too.
No! If everyone sees the face I'm making right now,
I'm gonna die of embarrassment!
But I just keep getting wetter!
So you're a dirty exhibitionist, Mira?
I'm not!
There's mo way that I'm getting
turned bn from being looked at!
Maybe if we changed positions, you will.
No! They can see everything! This is too embarrassing!
It feels so good! Your dick is making me feel so good!
If that's so, then you should tell everyone just
how good you're feeling by making a peace sign.
What kind of idea is that?
Is that all you want me to do?
My mind's going blank, I can't think straight!
My body's...
No, I... I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming even though it's my first time!
I'm cumming while people are looking at me!
No, don't! Stop!
No!
No! No! Stop! I can't stop peeing! It's not stopping!
It's falling to the ground!
Your pee is like a reward, Mira.
What? No, that's just for you.
No! This is so embarrassing! Everyone's watching!
I'm peeing everywhere!
Geez, you knew it was my first time and you still
made me go through something that embarrassing!
But, I'm glad you were my first time.
You're like my prince.
Yeah, and to me, you're even better than a princess.
That makes me happy.
If you're happy, then let's go again?
Huh?
This feels even better than before!
Your dick is stirring me up so deep inside!
It feels so good!
You're making me feel so good,
I can't stop my juices from coming out!
If I knew sex felt this good,
I would've done it much sooner!
I'm happy that I was your first time, Mira.
I didn't even want to at first, but for some reason, I just...
You're not gonna have it easy.
You've got to protect me from now on, okay?
I'm yours and yours only!
As you wish, m'lady.
That thing that felt good is happening again!
Be more rough!
Okay, here I go.
Do it! Shoot your load inside me!
Flood my pussy with your cum!
Fuck my pussy hard!
I'm cumming!
I can feel it pumping into me.
Your cum is spreading out inside of me.
I'm covered in cum now.
This is the thing that stole my first time yesterday, huh?
It doesn't taste too bad.
It feels really good, Mira.
After I got home last night, I really wanted
to make you feel good, so I did some studying.
You can cum whenever you want.
I said "whenever you want".
Cum.
Give it to me.
Hey...
There was so much.
You came so much yesterday, but there's still so much left.
That's impressive.
So you want me that badly?
I'm so happy.
Come here, give it to me.
Come here and fuck me with your dick.
Your dick is doing me so hard!
It's going to make my pussy soaking wet again!
If you keep doing me so hard like that,
you're going to make my pussy overflow!
Good! That feels so good!
It's so amazing, I'm gonna get hooked!
I want you in me all the time,
but class is starting soon, so don't take too long, okay?
So intense!
You're rubbing me... I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Let's cum together!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum with you
pouring your cum inside of me!
Even my boobs are cumming.
You poured so much inside me.
It feels so good, you're making my head spin.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hyakupercent
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч