Geez, why are you wearing such plain clothes?
It's fine. They're just gonna come off later anyway.
You nervous?
Y-Yeah...
This is your first time after all, Mai.
I'm... kinda scared.
Don't worry. There'll be lots of us there.
Alright, let's get going!
Geez, you're so impatient, Yuki.
Come on, time to go.
R-Right...
S-Sorry!
There are cute girls like her here too?
See? Aren't you glad you came?
Yeah.
Come here! Mizuryuu Kei Land
First time at Mizuryuu Kei Land
Come here! Mizuryuukei Land!
Welcome to the sex academy, Mizuryuukei Land!
All feelings of guilt that our visitors might have towards
sex are reshaped into respect and reverence.
Here, everyone returns to their primal,
original state as animals.
It's just like enjoying a pleasant meal.
Everyone can enjoy sex to their heart's content.
This is... a place of dreams.
Hey...
Are you sure this is okay to wear?
Wow, it looks so good on you!
You look very cute, Mai.
D-Don't look at me so much.
Oh right, don't forget to put this on.
What's that?
It's a sticker telling people what you're up for.
If you put this one on, you'll be able
to have sex with all kinds of people.
W-With all kinds of people?
Before we get started, we need to wash down there.
W-Washing down there?!
Y-Yeah.
Y-You know, diseases and all that.
Don't want any of those, do you?
B-But doesn't... this kinda feel good?
N-No...
D-Don't...
Th-That's...
We're finally in!
I'm ready to go!
I wanna fuck so bad.
Wow, they even check for STD's when you show your ID.
Yep.
They've really thought things through.
Fucky fucky here!
To make sure that everyone has fun sex while they're here...
We'll need all the men to wear condoms.
H-Hey!
I-I'll do it myself!
Your dick...
It's getting so big!
There.
Let's start fucking, okay?
W-Wait, uh...
God, that cleaning was just so good...
I'm so turned on right now.
My pussy's... soaking wet.
I just wanna fuck somebody, I don't care who!
Look. You see those guys over there?
They're fapping to us.
Why don't you give them something to work with, Mai?
Huh?
Just like this.
Your lewd smell is luring in.
Look, here they come.
Yuki, come on...
You're such a cutie.
Wanna have sex with us?
I-I, uh...
That's not right.
Mister, this girl's new to this, so...
So... would you like to have some fun with me instead?
H-Huh? Are you sure?
Oh my god...
This is what I wanted!
Thank you!
I don't care what you do, just fuck
my pussy as hard as you want!
Eri?
I'm gonna go with Mai to a place
more suited for newcomers.
Text me when you're done, 'kay?
A-Are you sure?
Yeah, she'll be fine.
Got it ♥
I'm not really into old guys anyway.
A Ferris wheel?
Fucking wheel
Yep, it's one on one sex.
And when you're with that special girl...
You can do anything you want for thirty minutes.
But you don't know who you'll be having
sex with until you get on, right?
What're you gonna do if they're crazy?
Everyone here is just another sex craved maniac.
Having sex here is basically a greeting.
Come on, you can go first.
Y-You're...
Y-You were on the same bus as earlier.
S-So...
Th-This is my first time here.
M-Me too...
Everyone here is just another sex craved maniac.
Y-You're okay with this, right?
G-Go ahead.
I-I...
I'm actually really dirty, but I have trouble showing it.
I know all my friends are having sex
and that makes me jealous, but I can't
bring myself to tell them that.
That's why...
I-I'd like you to fuck me.
It feels so good!
Fucking feels so good!
More! More! Fuck me more!
I... I've wanted to fuck you since I first saw you on the bus!
That makes me so happy!
Please, please make yourself feel really good with my pussy!
My boobs... You're touching my boobs too!
It feels good!
So good!
Crap, I'm about to...
I'm about to cum!
Go ahead.
I'm going to cum too. I'm cumming!
That felt... so good...
Hey...
Looks like you had a good time too.
Yuki?
Oh, what?
You two are friends?
This is perfect.
Let's all go to the rest cottage together.
Oh my god, your dick is just too amazing!
More! More! Do me more!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm... cumming again!
Wow. So when Yuki's having sex, she
makes those kinds of sounds, huh?
Hey, how about we switch partners?
I want to take him for a spin.
Huh?
So?
You good with that?
Y-Yeah...
I don't think I'm good with playboys like him.
O-Oh my god!
It's so good!
I'm... I'm so happy! So good!
I love your dick!
It feels so good.
It feels so good!
Your friend's pretty amazing, huh?
It looks like he's about to break her pussy.
Me too! I don't think I can hold back!
Mess me up!
Did I make you mad? It's okay, you can rough me up a bit!
Y-Yeah! That's good!
Keep it up! You can do it!
I-It's hitting me! It's hitting me right in my womb!
It's so hot! Your dick's so hot!
Does sex with me... not feel good?
No, of course it does.
Your friend was really rough, but
you're just so gentle that...
I-It just makes me feel so happy for some reason.
Make that girl happy too, okay?
Oh god, I'm gonna cum!
My pussy's gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
Sorry.
I was just hit on so many times while trying to get here.
And because of that I got really held up.
You came at a good time.
The parade's starting soon anyway.
You should come too.
Yeah!
Huh?
Hm? What about them?
They're fine, don't worry.
She came a lot.
She's better off resting for a little, don't you think?
You're not going with them?
Oh... Yeah, not yet...
You weirdo.
Did you know?
Normally you can have sex as much as you want
here, but no one's supposed to have sex tonight.
All the people who come here might seem reserved, but...
They're all extremely horny people.
It's tough for them.
Yeah, even I get that, but...
How do I put this, having sex with you feels special.
It's like...
Like I want you to be with me all the time or something...
I'm a lot dirtier than you think I am.
That's fine.
I'm actually always thinking about dirty things.
I'm always ready to have sex with anyone.
Even then, I don't care.
And, uh, what else is there...
I'm really shy and not really honest, and really dirty.
Wait, I said that already, didn't I?
Please go out with me.
Sure.
Hm? What?
We don't even know each other's names.
So, let's do this right.
My name's...
This is Mizuryuukei Land.
A place separated from the rules of human society.
A place just for adults.
A theme park of lust and desires!
Everyone who visits forgets reality
and acts upon their desires.
You can have as much sex with the
person you like as you want!
Now then, I welcome you to this wonderful
place of dreams as well!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч