The Peerless President: Mira Campball
Academice, athletice, beauty... Mira Campball is a triple threat wortly of her position of student council president. Perfection comes at a price, however – all the boys are too intimidated to get close to her. They just admire their "Show White" from a distance. Because of this, she remains a virgin despite her beauty and charm.
The Prodigy: Kujo Shizuru
A genius whose knowledge has allowed her to skip grades. She is equally beautiful as she is intelligent. Since she is the youngest in her class, she tends to be shy and reserved, but it's also due to her fear of men. Her silence is seen as coldness, earning her the title of "Iron Maiden". However, underneath her skirt lies an unbelievable secret... A secret only known by Shousuke.
The Legendary Meat Stick: Yabuki Shousuke
Your average male student. Everyone in his school has started having sex with one another. While most boys his age would revel at this golden opportunity, he seems disinterested by it all. Quite the shame, considering what he's packing in his pants...
Seike Academy used to be a normal private school until Yarime Kaiko, the previous headmaster's daughter, took over. Her first inagurel change was to turn Seike into a sex academy, much to everyone's surprise.
Her reasoning for the change was the declining birth rate. She ineieted that virtue be ignored and that sex is no different than eating. She was aggresseive in enforcing this new policy, and eve offered financial aid to students who got pregnant. Most students are now acclimeted to their new sex-filled school lives, but few have managed to avoid it.
Deepite the school's call to intercourse, Shousuke continued life as normal, killing time in his usual spot rather then eating his teenage lust. That soon came to an an end, however, when he ran into Mira, the Peerless President, and fucked her publicly on the school roof. He was then hunted down by Nana, the Queen of Sluts, and anded up having a three-way with her and Mira. From that moment on, his life became a revolving door of sex.
Shousuke kept getting raped time and time again into having sex – even once with Shizuru in the bathroom. Mira secretly watched him every time, getting more excited until she couldn't handle it anymore. Watching the small Shizuru's asshoe get skewered by Shousuke's mighty cock filled her with anal beads but was caught by Shousuke. Desperately, she tried removing them from her anus, but to no avail.
Previously on Private Sex School
Nobody's gonna have sex with a freak like me.
Up you go.
You're going to take my virginity away as
a punishment, aren't you, onii-sama?
Onii-sama, your dick... It's making my stomach so full!
It's so full!
It's so deep! Go deeper!
Onii-sama, that's...
My ass feels so weird!
So this is what your dick tastes like, huh, onii-sama?
I-It's so big, I don't think it'll fit.
Don't push yourself too hard. It feds good.
That makes me happy.
I'm so glad I can make you happy!
It makes all the punishment, worth it.
O-Onii-samas semen...
There's so much!
Oh my god that feels so good!
Both my ass and pussy are...
They're breaking!
Please give me your semen, onii-sama!
I want your punishment to go deep inside me...
all the way to my stomach!
I'm being filled so deep with your cum, onii-sama!
Both my ass and my pussy are
being filled with onii-sama's...
Wh-What's going on there?!
W-Was Shousuke's dick just in her ass?!
So what I saw back then was definitely...
H-How could you use that hole like that?
But it kinda looks like it feels good... I think.
Come on Over! Sex Academy
The Pure Student Council President: Mira ~ Pouting,
Embarrassed with a Plowable Pink Asshole
Mira?
Wh-What?! Wh-Why?!
Why are you here?!
I was looking for you and thought I saw you come in here.
Should I not have come in?
O-Of course you shouldn't have!
I made this room off limits for a reason!
Hey! Get back!
What are you doing?
Just some light stretching.
I've been studying all day, so I'm trying to loosen...
H-Hey what are you... Stop!
Do you know where you're licking?!
I said stop!
Hey!
No way! It's going in!
My ass is spreading out...
That's one down...
What is this? My ass is...
Shousuke... That feels...
You're rolling your tongue around!
Getting turned on by your first anal experience? Dirty girl.
It's not like that!
My butt hurts so much!
But when you lick me like that...
Why does it feel so much better than normal?
What's going on? Your dick and the beads
are rubbing against each other.
Why does it feel so good?
This is so intense!
Both my ass and my pussy are so full!
No way!
It's coming out of my ass!
Oh, no!
You're being too rough!
They're coming out, you idiot!
Wait, don't...!
Why does it feel so good?
Ramming your cock into my pussy while my ass
is stuffed is going to make me lose my mind!
I'm gonna cum... I'm really gonna cum!
I'm cumming so hard!
This feels way too good!
Having both your dick and those beads
inside me felt way too good!
Your dick is as unrelenting as ever.
What?!
Shousuke?!
Huh?
You?!
You're that slut in the bathroom yesterday!
Huh? You were watching?
What do you want? You're interrupting
my precious time with Shousuke.
Do you mind?
Hey! Ow, ow, ow...
Just that little hurts?
I guess you're not ready for onii-sama, then.
Onii-sama?
You perv!
Senpai told me that she wanted me to succeed her,
so I guess that means it's my turn, right?
Hold your horses, bitch.
You know that's not what I meant.
Shousuke's mine!
Please fuck me, onii-sama.
Hey, don't get ahead of yourself just because
you skipped a few grades! Shousuke is...
My asshole can't wait, onii-sama!
Your body's not ready yet, Prez.
Be a good girl and watch.
Onii-sama, please slay my ass with your dick.
Your dick is skewering me!
No way! How can she fit his huge thing in her butt like that?
It's so deep!
You're so deep inside me!
It feels so good!
It's so long and thick!
I want your dick to destroy my ass forever!
Onii-sama!
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm cumming with my ass!
I can feel your hot cum pouring inside me!
I can't wait any longer.
And now you're inside my pussy!
Onii-sama...
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy that I turn you on so much!
Please use my body as you please!
Cum for me!
Pour it into my tiny pussy!
Onii-sama's cum is inside me!
My ass and pussy are filled with your seed!
You went too far.
She's just a kid.
That was too much.
Um, Shousuke?
Um, so, uh... Yeah...
My butt's still sore, so...
You're already going this hard?!
It hurts!
Be more gentle!
I told you... I'm not ready there yet!
What the heck, Shousuke?!
I'll help you train your cute butt.
Happy to hear that, but maybe some other time?
I want you in my pussy!
This shouldn't feel good...
No way! My body is...
You say one thing, but your body says another.
No! This doesn't...
I like doing it normally!
There's no way I like this!
No way!
From my ass...
I really came from my ass?
This is so embarrassing.
Did I really just cum that hard from my butt?
I'll prove it to you.
This position makes me look like a dog peeing!
No!
Your cum leaks out every time you thrust!
Your dick keeps moving around inside me! It feels so good!
But I can't forget about my ass!
Am I a slut?
I'm cumming with your dick shoved into me,
and semen spilling out of my ass...
I'm cumming like some kind of slut!
Oh, no... I'm peeing.
But it feels too good...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч