Previously on Sex Academy
W-What is that?!
No, more importantly, who is that?!
W-Why's he sleeping with a boner?!
I've seen some of the guys' things,
but I've never seen one like this.
Huh, aren't you the student council president?
You're in my spot.
Do you mind getting out of it?
Your panties...
Y-You saw them, didn't you?!
How dare you look at my panties!
Aren't you the one who forced me to look at them?
This will be your punishment for ruining my view.
Wha... Pres...
Mira...
That's better.
I think your dick's gotten even bigger.
Ow! Ow! What is this?! It hurts so much!
Mira, you're tensing up too much. Loosen up a little.
I can't! I can't! What's going on? Why does it hurt so much?!
No, why is this happening?
Everyone's looking at you, Mira.
No! If everyone sees the way I look
right now, I'll die of embarrassment!
But I just keep getting wetter!
So you're a dirty exhibitionist, Mira?
I'm not!
There's no way that I'm getting turned on from being looked at!
Maybe changing positions will help.
This is the thing that took my first time yesterday, huh?
It doesn't taste too bad.
It feels really good, Mira.
After I got home last night, I really wanted to
make you feel good, so I did some studying,
You can cum whenever you want.
Your dick is doing me so hard!
It's going to make my pussy a wet mess again!
If you keep doing me so hard like that,
you're going to make my pussy overflow!
Nurse's Office
I heard he made the Snow White fall for him!
I wonder what kind of technique he used to do that?
I came here to get away from all that,
but it's probably even worse for Mira right now.
Wh-What is this?
Oh, you're awake.
S-Souma-san?
We're classmates, not strangers. Call me by my first name.
Call me Nana.
Now I think it's time for me to get a hands-on
taste of how you made Snow White fall for you.
I didn't do anything special. It just kind of
happened in the natural flow of things.
So in the natural flow of things, you put this inside, huh?
It's gotten so big.
Wow, I didn't know you were packing something like this.
You already refused to have sex so I just assumed the worst.
I've never seen anything like this.
What a surprise.
You might have the biggest one in class, no, in the entire school.
So this is how you made her fall for you. Makes sense.
I might want you to make me fall for you too.
It's so huge, it's hard to fit into my mouth!
I can only fit half of it inside!
Shou-kun, could you make me feel good too?
I'm still a virgin today.
Virgin?
That's right a "one day virgin".
So good! Your tongue is twirling around in my pussy!
I can't believe you were hiding such an amazing thing.
Your tongue feels so good!
This is my first time today, so I'm really sensitive right now!
Not good. If this keeps up, I think I'm gonna cum first.
So...
I'll make you cum first.
You're the first person I've done this for.
Even if you can only cum once,
you made Snow White fall for you, so it should be okay.
I'll squeeze all the cum out of your amazing dick with my mouth.
There's so much!
Not only is its size great, the amount
of cum you let out is amazing too!
I can see how somebody would get
hooked on this when it's their first time.
Next, could you give me your fat cock in my wet pussy?
I can't wait anymore!
Please take my first time today with your cock!
What is this?! It's so big!!
It's filling me up!
Having it inside me for real is just too good!
Good! It's coming so deep inside me!
Your cock is too amazing, Shou-kun!
It feels like my body is getting
raped by your cock in this position!
It's... pushing itself deep inside me again!
What's going on? I know the taste of cock so well,
but I feel like I'm already gonna cum!
You're going so deep! You're startling
my womb with how deep you're going!
So good! You're messing up my pussy
so hard, it's making me lose my mind!
Oh, god! I've had a lot of big cocks in me up until now, but...
I want you to fill my pussy up with
a huge serving of your sticky cum!
Pump it into the deepest part of my womb!!
It's coming!
It's shooting all the way into my womb!
I'm cumming too!
I've never felt anything this amazing.
Your cock is too wild.
Wait, what? Your cock is getting...
Are you serious?!
Your pussy feels really amazing, Nana.
How?! You came so much, but you're still this big?!
How is it this amazing?!
You're gonna break my mind!
No! I'm gonna cum again!
My womb's already eaten up so much of your
cum, it's gonna get addicted to your milk!
Your cum is shooting all over inside me!
You came so much that it's flowing out of me!
I seriously can't handle this!
This isn't fair.
I've had so many cocks but now I
can't think of any of them but yours.
So this is where you were?!
After tasting your cock, I just can't be satisfied by anybody else's.
Sorry everyone.
Hey, watch it. I haven't kissed him there yet.
I can't live without his cock too!
Kissing his cock before kissing his lips? I
expected nothing less from you, Snow White.
But sorry, Shou-kun's mine.
Yeah? Well we were each other's first times.
This is my dick!
But you know, doing it here is kind of embarrassing.
Could we go somewhere else?
Huh? I'm fine with here though.
I wanna show everyone just how good I'm feeling.
That's a slut for you.
This isn't where you're supposed
to be kissing, but it feels so good!
Yeah, your cock is amazing, Shou-kun!
I want it inside me forever! Come on!
I'll let the slut have it for right now
as long as you stick it in me last.
My pussy feels better, doesn't it?
Shou-kun's cock is mine.
Your cock is thrusting against my womb so hard!
It feels too good!
Your tongue is moving inside my
pussy! It's making my pussy overflow!
I can't hold on anymore!
I want you to stick it in me so bad!
No! I'm not done yet!
I want more of your cock!
No! I'm gonna cum!
I want to stay on your cock longer, but I can't... no!
You came so hard in me again!
There's so much cum inside me!
Oh no, your cock fell out of me.
I'm cumming too!
Oh, it's your dick.
You were waiting for me, huh?
It's so tight inside me! It's a perfect fit!
Your dick's amazing!
I'm getting pushed in so hard, it
feels like I'm hanging from your dick.
This feels amazing!
Your dick's pushing in me so hard!
No! I'm gonna become even more perverted.
I can't think of anything but your dick anymore!
Your dick is pushing all the way to my womb!
It feels so good!
Your dick's rubbing me so hard! It feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
My head is going blank!
I'm cumming!
So good! This amazing thing is for me only, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч