You're wearing plain clothes again.
It's fine. We're all gonna take them off anyway.
Are you nervous?
Y-Yeah.
It's your first time here, right Mai?
I'm... somehow getting scared.
It's gonna be fine. Many people like us are coming too.
Okay, Let's get going already!
You're so impatient, Yuki.
Come on, we gotta go too.
O-Okay.
I-I'm sorry!
Someone that cute also went here...
See? Glad that we came here?
Yeah.
#1 First time in Mizuryuu Kei Land
Let's go! Mizuryuu Kei Land
Welcome to the sex paradise, Mizuryuu Kei Land!
Where all feelings of guilt and aversion against sex are swept away,
where you can revert as original form as a living being.
and savor it like how you enjoy a meal.
Anyone has the freedom to safely enjoy sex as their instinct dictates.
This is a place where such dreams come true.
Umm... Is it really okay for me wear this outfit?
Oh! You look good in it.
You're cute, Mai.
D-Don't stare so much.
Ah, we need to have these attached.
What's that?
These are called "Declaration of Will" stickers.
If you attach this in your body, you can have sex with anyone.
W-With anyone?
And the last would be vaginal washing, right?
V-Vaginal washing?
Y-Yeah... better do this to avoid something... like STD spreading, right?
This... feels kind of... good though...
Ahh... no... don't...
That's... ahh—
Inside at last. I can't wait anymore.
I want to fuck someone already.
STD Check-up to ID card presentation
Huh?
They're more strict than I expected.
Pakopakorin!
For the sake of safe enjoyment in the park,
we must make all men put on our exclusive condoms~!
W-Wait! I can do it myself!
Let's get your penis hard like this...
Here you go!
Want a good fuck with me?
N-No, I'm g—
What should I do? That vaginal cleaning... umm... felt so good!
My pussy is... soaking wet.
I don't care whoever it is, I want to have sex!
Look at that old man.
He's rubbing one out while looking on us.
Mai should give them some eye candy.
Eh?
Here we go! Let's lure them with Mai's lewd scent.
They're already craving for it!
Jeez, Yuki!
You're cute!
Want to have sex with me?
It's my first—
No, you can't, oji-san.
It's her first time in here.
How about relieving yourself with me instead?
Ehh?! Can I?
P-put.. i-it... i-i-in!
My pussy is waiting for this!
Feels good... so much...
I love it...
I feel great, everyone.
Don't hold back and use my pussy!
Eri, we're gonna go to the beginner's area.
Text me when you're done, okay?
I-Is that okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
Sign: Roger
I'm not into old men.
Sex-o-wheel?
Yeah. They make sure to always pair a boy and girl in every car.
You can do anything inside with whoever you end up with for half an hour.
But, doesn't that mean that you won't know who you're ending up with until you get in?
What if we get paired up with a weirdo?
All the visitors who come in this place are sex-craving nuts.
Sex is just like a greeting in here.
Hey, you should go first!
You are...
You are... from the same bus we took earlier.
U-Uhm... It's my first time in here...
So am I.
All the visitors who come in this place are sex-craving nuts.
I-It's okay, right?
N-No problem.
I am actually naughty, despite trying to hide it.
I'm really jealous when my friends fool around with men, but couldn't say it.
So can you...
bang me please?
Good! Being humped feels good!
More... more... screw me more!
From the time I saw you in the bus, I wanted to fuck you.
I'm glad!
Please make my pussy feel very very good.
My tits, touch my tits as well...
That's it... feels good!
I'm... gonna cum... soon!
It's okay... cum!
I'm also close...
Being creampied feels good!
Seems like it went well for you too.
Yuki!
Oh, so you two are friends.
Ain't that good? Let's all go to the rest cottage.
Y-Your dick feels so amazing!
More, do it more! Give me more!
Cumming, I'm cumming... again!
I'm cumming!
W-wow! That looks amazing.
Yuki makes moans like that when having sex.
Hey, let's try swapping partners this time.
I want to have a taste of that boy too!
It's fine, right?
Yes.
Flirty guys like him aren't really for me.
Oh no, don't, don't, don't! I can't take anymore!
Oh no, rough sex feels so great!
I love your dick!
S-So good! Feels so good!
Your friend is amazing.
Oh, her pussy is gonna break.
Let's... let's do the same!
D-did it ignite your competitive spirit?
It's okay, you can be rougher on me!
J-Just like that. Go, go, do your best!
So deep! It's hitting me deep inside!
It... feels hot! Your dick feels so hot!
Does having sex with me not feel good?
That's not true!
Your friend does rough sex,
but yours is gentle...
Somehow it makes me feel heavenly!
Please make her feel happy too, okay?
I can't anymore... cumming... My pussy is cumming, Ahh!
Cumming... cumming... I'm cumming!
Sorry!
I got hit on many times while on my way here.
I did it with all of them so I came late.
You're just in time.
It's almost time for the parade.
You're going with us!
'Kay!
Eh?
Wait, how about them?
No, they're staying.
Mai still needs to catch her breath.
It's better to let her take a break.
Are you not going?
Ahh... yeah. I'm still...
You're a weird one.
Did you know?
You are allowed to do anything in this place,
but falling in love is one thing you shouldn't do.
Everyone who comes here are easy to get slut and studs,
no matter how timid they might look at first.
You'll only hurt yourself.
I know that at least,
Even so, I feel that sex with you is something special.
I don't know how to say it. I feel like I want you to be by my side, or something
I'm way more of a slut than you might think.
I'm fine with that.
The truth is, my mind is always filled with lewd stuffs.
And I'd readily have sex with anyone.
Even so, I don't mind.
And.. what else... I'm an introvert, not honest with my feelings, and a lewd.
not honest with my feelings, and a lewd girl.
Wait, I already told you that.
Please go out with me.
Okay.
What's wrong?
We still don't know each other's names.
Uhm... Please take care of me from now on.
My name is—
This place is called Mizuryuu Kei Land.
A place where the societal rules derived from morals don't apply.
A theme park of lust for the adults!
Everyone here escapes from reality,
to let themselves be engulfed with lust.
and be able to indulge in sex the way they want with someone they want.
And to you as well,
welcome to this lovely dream land!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project