Hello everyone! Good evening!
Here we are at a hot spot in our
sex paradise, Mizuryuukei Land.
This is the Sex Party Ranking, coming
to you live from the event stage.
We'll be choosing one idol from their
stunning performance yesterday and...
Performing this week is...
Hey everyone, are you all limp?
We're the idols of your private parts...
We're the Horny Sentries!
Hey!
Hey, come on.
Can you see?
Can you see our pussies?
They're so wet and ready to have sex! I'm
so horny, I can barely hold back right now!
It's going inside my pussy!
Look. Look at me more!
Okay, let's all have fun together now!
Dick... Dick...
Your dick's amazing! It's so hot and lively!
Good... So good!
You're making such a mess of my pussy!
No... I can't... My body's getting so hot, I want more!
I think I'm losing my mind!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
Everyone... Everyone, let's do it together!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Welcome to the Kingdom of Dreams!
Come here! Mizuryuu Kei Land
#2 The Horny Sentries
Come here! Mizuryuu Kei Land!
Look. I got cummed in so much!
I know what you mean. My stomach is really full too.
Good night. Later.
Yuka-chan, you're leaving already?
Sorry, I have lessons today.
Yuka's performing fine, but when it comes
to sex, it feels like she's not giving it her all.
Yeah, good point. She didn't even have
sex with a single customer today.
I wonder if Yuka-san just doesn't like sex that much?
Everyone here... Their heads are filled with nothing but sex.
What idiots!
GenitalShaking Event – Celebration of Horny Sentries 3rd Single "Horny Onahole Girl"
We've distributed tickets beforehand,
so please form two single-file lines.
We ask for only one minute per "Handshake".
Hurry, come here. Shove your cock into my pussy!
R-Ryouko-tan! I've wanted to meet you!
I've wanted to meet you so bad!
So good! You're so big!
It's okay. Move inside me however you want.
Just keep pounding it inside me!
Ts-Tsubaki-chan, your pussy is the best!
I'll keep supporting you forever!
Wow, I'm so honored.
C-Can I... Can I kiss you?
Sure, go ahead.
Let's lick each other.
N-No, I think I'm already gonna cum!
That's okay. Cum! Cum a lot!
Make my pussy, a slopping wet mess!
It's coming! Your hot stuff is shooting out inside me!
There's cum running out of me... It feels so disgusting.
How do they all look like they're enjoying this?!
U-Um, thank you for having me.
Oh, go ahead.
Are you alright?
Sorry, I'm fine.
What's with him? He's completely
different than the other guys!
He keeps thrusting against my womb... it feels so good!
It feels so good!
H-Hey...
Let's kiss.
Kiss...
I'm... gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Do it! Cum inside me!
Cum everything you have inside me!
Okay, time's up!
Next person in line, please.
I guess one minute isn't enough time to cum.
You have my support.
Please keep up the good work!
Hey! Wait!
Yuka-chan?
It felt so good, but none of us even got to cum in the end...
I don't want it to end like that!
I want that boy's cum!
Hey, you.
You're... You're the kid who came to
the handshake event today, right?
No way!
You're Yuka-chan from Horny Sentri...
Shh!!
Listen, I don't really know anything about
this place except the performance stage.
Would you like to go around the park with me?
O-Of course!
If you're okay with me, then I'll gladly go!
I've been your fan for soooo long, Yuka-chan!
Really?
Yeah, really!
I especially loved the Flower Petal Dance!
Those captivating movements of yours really
made the dance come to life... it was amazing!
Oh, I see.
Thanks.
That dance... I really hated it, so I
didn't even try to get it right, but...
Now that there's someone praising
me for it with so much vigor...
It makes me wish that I tried harder.
Semen Shot
Shooting Range
Wait...
It's okay, just cum.
Cum!
If you're that rough, I'm gonna...
Don't hold back.
Just cum with everything you have!
Oh my god, this is so good!
This dick just keeps... just keeps thrusting into me!
How's it look? Does it look like I'm
licking the dick water fountain?
Yeah!
U-Um, it's a little difficult to walk like this.
Walking around like this is pretty popular nowadays.
Look at how energetic it is again.
Hey, should we do it?
Sex, I mean.
W-We can't.
You have so many fans. It wouldn't be fair to
them if I'm the only one to get special treatment.
That's not...
Also you said that you'd never
spread your legs on your time off.
I like that stoic part of you too, Yuka-chan.
Oh, I see. So that's how everyone's been seeing me.
I guess that makes sense. I hated our fan-service so much.
It wouldn't be right for me to suddenly
only have sex with the fan that I like.
That wouldn't be fair.
Yuka-chan?
But I want to!
I want to have sex!
I want to be cummed in!
My pussy is horny like crazy right now!
I want to fuck! I want to fuck!
Please! I can't wait any longer!
I'm not really stoic at all!
Your dick felt so good that I can't
think of anything but sex with it!
So please, have sex with me!
That's the Submission Dance of the Slut!
It's the pose that signals that
she wants to be cummed inside!
Hey, isn't that...
She's Yuka from Horny Sentries, right?
No way! All the way out here?
E-Even I can't hold back if you keep doing this!
That's fine! Do it! Fuck me!
Mess up my pussy!
I'm doing Yuka-chan!
I'm having a private sex session with my favorite idol!
Sex! Sex!!
I love it! It's the best!
Your dick's reaching all the way inside me!
It's making me feel good... so good!!
Wow.
That position...
Um, if you're alright with it, would you have sex with me?
Sure.
Excuse me, could you lend me your dick?
I-If you're good with me.
Do me harder!
Harder!
Hot... It's so hot!
My pussy's so wet! It feels like it's gonna melt!
It feels so good! This feels so amazing!
It feels so good doing this with everyone!
Yuuto-kun, sorry! I'm fucking... I'm fucking someone again!
Your dick... It's starting to twitch and it's getting bigger!
Oh my god, I think I'm gonna cum!
Yuka-chan, I'm cumming.
I'm gonna cum inside!
That's fine. Cum!
Cum inside me!
I want your sperm inside me!
Cum as much as you want inside me!
His cum is so warm, it feels so good!
I never knew being cummed in felt so good!
S-Sorry, I forced you into that.
I broke your image of me, didn't I?
No, that was amazing!
You act stoic, but you're actually a downright, pervert!
I love that reversal!
R-Really?
I'd love it if you showed me more
of your dirty side on the stage!
I bet the other fans would love it too!
Hm, well if you say so then maybe I'll try a little harder.
Yay! Everyone in the crowd limp right now?
We're the downright perverted idols, the Horny Sentries!
Please enjoy our...
...perverted performance.
I'm ready to take on six people at once right now!
Now come on stage, all you sex obsessed monkeys!
Huh?
Hey, now...
There are so many great looking dicks!
Wow, they all have such a dirty smell.
I don't know where to start!
I-I like it! I like it when you do me like that!
Dicks! Dicks are the best!
But one's not nearly enough!
Look! Everyone look!
Look at both my pussy and my ass...
They both have a dick inside them!
My stomach's so full!
Yuka-chan!
Oh no! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Please, everyone! Shoot your cum inside me!
Make my body sticky with your semen!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I'm gonna cum!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч