Tamaki, you haven't been to my house since we were kids.
Geez. You're already an idiot, and you go and catch cold on top of that?
Just hold still.
Hmm, you're running a pretty high fever.
Uh, Tamaki...
A-anyway, why'd you show up in a swimsuit?
My sister told me that it makes men excited.
If you've got a cold the best thing is to sweat it out, right?
Okay, get horny and start sweating!
H-hey Tamaki, you're acting weird-
Tamaki, wait!
FAKKU! Presents
Milady is crazy about making love
Episode 2: "Doctors, Maids, and group sex"
Tamaki...
That's bitter.
The hell did you make me drink, Tamaki?
Medicine.
I swiped it from my sister's place.
"Mystery Medicine"
Are you sure that's actually medicine?
It's a secret medicine my family uses.
It'll cure any sickness in no time flat!
I'll let you drink it mouth to mouth.
Could it be this stuff that's got her acting weird?
Drink this and get well soon, 'kay?
Tatsuya.
Tamaki, wai-
What's the rush?
It's just a common cold-
But if you don't get well soon, I won't be able to stand it!
Miss Tamaki's kinda strange today!
There must be something in that medicine, huh?
There sure is.
Mistaking "energy" drinks for cold medicine...How very like her.
Mistress!
Come on, drink up and satisfy me already!
M-Mistress!
Here, I'll suck out the virus through your dick.
C'mon Tamaki, I'm sick you know?
Huh? It's all flaccid.
Just forget it! It's impossible in my condition!
Why? How come it won't get bigger?
Even though I'm trying my very hardest to please him!
Tamaki, it feels great, but it's just not gonna happen today!
Maybe some other time!
But but but...
Your dick hasn't been in here for a week!
T-tamaki...
Incredible. All soaked in love juices...
It's totally transparent!
Oh yay, it's up!
The power of the swimsuit, I guess?
I'm also starting to get...kinda hot.
Because of the swimsuit, perhaps?
My first time with your hard dick in a week!
My head's spinning, starting to go blank...
Tatsuya, Tastuya!
It's weird! Something's strange!
My body and my pussy are really hot!
Probably cause of my fever.
Tatsuya! Cum, Tatsuya!
Blow your hot stuff, cum with me!
All of it! Everything!
W-well? Don't you feel better now?
I can't really tell.
Bounce, Bounce
Well then, how about one more round?
Huh? What!?
It's fine. You're still so hard.
Ahh, whatever, I give.
Yeah, more!
How is it? You're hornier than usual, right?
Y-yeah, you're so sexy.
Tatsuya.
My breasts too...You've gotta fondle them a little too!
Tamaki!
Tatsuya, does the swimsuit really make you this horny?
I've learned something new!
You're one to talk, Tamaki.
This is the first time I've seen this side of you!
It's a first for me too!
Your hot dick's gonna burn my pussy!
My breasts too...
Tamaki!
Tatsuya!
Your dick's throbbing. Are you gonna cum again?
Me too! It feels so good!
Here it comes! I'm going to cum!
Together, Together!
After cumming this much, you'll recover real soon.
Alright, one last time!
Come on! You'll feel better if you cum more!
H-hold on now...
Ooohh, I'm done for...
Goodness, Mistress is being so rough on her patient.
At this rate, Master Tatsuya will die!
No choice then. In that case, we'll have to do something too!
Yeah!
TRANSFORMATION!
At a time like this, he needs to be hospitalized!
Yeah!
Pardon me, Mistress!
Huh? What happened to me?
Doctor! He's awake now!
I see.
How are you feeling, Tatsuya?
You've been asleep this whole time.
We were so worried!
Hold it! What's with the swimsuits!?
Eri, Mari, you may begin.
Yes ma'am!
W-what on earth are you doing!?
What do you mean "what"? I'm checking you body for any abnormalities.
Huh? Doctor, it's even less responsive than when he was asleep.
What do you think you're doing!?
Mari, Eri, I can't perform a diagnosis like this, so get it erect, okay?
Sure!
This is a messed up situation...
Good, good. Keep it up!
It's really hot, Doctor.
The tip's gotten big too!
Alright, almost ready then!
Doing this is kinda making us feel good too!
My pussy's already soaked. I'm so turned on!
I see. I get it now.
This is all a dream!
A dream cause by my swimsuit-induced lust!
Don't worry. Don't hold back and cum whenever you like.
Make our faces and tits drip with cum!
Mari, you're nipples are erect!
You too, Eri!
I'm can't go on!
Harder!
His dick is pulsing!
Mr.Tatsuya's cumming!
He came!
He came so much!
Hmm, 1 minute 6 seconds. Still plenty healthy.
Yep, this is a dream alright. There's no way this would actually-
Now then...
Let's begin your physical.
It's a dream, damn it!
Mr. Tatsuya, has the fever clouded your perception?
Can you attribute this sensation to a mere dream?
Good. Heartbeat is healthy.
Almost too much so!
So then if we do this, maybe it'll speed up!
Oh dear, you're beet red.
At this rate, your heart just might burst.
Wait, could this actually be real?
You're the picture of health, Mr. Tatsuya!
Wonderful! You're so hard already!
Doctor, you're amazing!
You too, Mr. Tatsuya!
Move your hips! Thrust all the way!
Doctor!
You're wonderful! It's hitting my womb!
How could you Mr. Tatsuya!
You're only paying attention to the doctor. Have you forgotten us already?
Okay then, how's this?
Amazing! He's even shoving the swimsuit in too!
You're both completely wet.
Well that's 'cause we've just been servicing you, so our pussies are all sloppy and wet!
Tease it! Wiggle your fingers deep inside me!
The swimsuit's rubbing against my insides! I've never felt like this before!
It's so good!
Doctor, I'm going to cum!
No wait! Cum together with me!
Good, you're great! Mess up my tits!
Doctor, your pussy's tightening up!
I've never felt this good before!
I can feel it! Your dick's so hot!
Doctor, your nipples are all hard and erect!
O-oh no...I think I'm about to cum!
My hips won't stop! I'm gonna lose my mind!
Me too, I'm gonna cum!
It's okay, cum for me! I'll collect your sperm sample!
We can't hold on either! Cumming!
Everyone, all together now!
Here it comes! I'm cumming!
Huh?
So it was a dream. I knew it...
Tamaki...Have you been there this whole time?
J-just one more time, and your fever will go down...
Hey, my fever's gone!
Move out!
Yes ma'am!
Our Mistress Loves Being Naughty
Hmmm...This place really is empty.
The rest of my family's at our Caribbean villa.
The Caribbean, huh?
You know, Tatsuya...
In that case, it's fine if you wanna spend the night...
N-nah, I couldn't impose like that-
Besides, I'm still recovering.
Okay then.
Just wait here in the bath, okay?
Oh, hi Tamaki.
Sister Leira! What on earth are you doing?
You're supposed to be with Father in the Caribbean!
S-sister?
Oh, about that...
I just didn't go.
Why!?
It's not really any of your business.
I guess so, but...
No, I guess it's not.
Our apologies, Miss Tamaki.
It seems our plan's been exposed.
Ah, well monitoring our Mistress' actions is but another task of the head maid.
Goodness. This all happened because of your amorous amusements, you know.
I wouldn't really call it that...
Well I guess a simple guy like that's just perfect for a simple girl like you.
*clash*
Ohh? Did you think I was oblivious?
You're having relations with that butler, aren't you?
What?
This is nothing but a toy.
I've no "relations" or anything with him.
How unsightly.
Sister, everyone in this mansion is aware.
W-well...
She's correct...
The master's pretty much the only one who doesn't...
Uhh, hey now...
Let's just simmer down now...
SILENCE, IMPOTENT BOY!
Tatsuya is NOT impotent, Sister!
Oh, then premature, perhaps?
P-p-premature...?
You've got one standing right behind you!
Fine then. Care to prove it then?
Fine by me!
Whoa-
Huh!?
Mistress, pray tell, what is this?
Alright then. We pleasure each others partner, and whoever cums first loses.
You got it!
Here goes!
They're huge...
You won't last a second sandwiched between these!
Do try not to embarrass Tamaki too much now.
I've never seen a penis besides Tatsuya's.
Wow...Sister's already to that point.
I can't lose to her!
Mistress, please cease this silly contest!
Oh, just be quiet!
Alright...I can do those kinds of things too!
Mistress Tamakai!
Come on! Hurry up and cum!
Ehhh!? What's that?
Allow us to assist you, Miss Tamaki!
H-hey, that's-
You're adorable, Yuusuke.
Your nipples sure are sensitive!
H-hold it! That's my-
Well then, I shall provide assistance over here.
Huh? W-wait!
What are you doing?
T-that's my asshole!
Her anal tongue bath is quite intense.
Is this your first time being licked there?
It'll make you come in no time!
Oh shit, these two are really good!
But I can endure it for Tamaki!
I'm not going to lose here!
I'm going to prove he's the premature one!
I-if you keep that up I'm gonna-
Miss Tamaki, keep it up! He's about to cum any second now!
You're not good enough for Tamaki anyway.
Just give in and let yourself go!
I can't do that!
When you fight it that much, I just can't help wanting to tease you!
O-oh crap! Y-you're tongue's-
Jeez, would you just cum already?
How long do you plan on making us service you anyway?
Mistress Tamaki, any more and I'll-
Your dick is twitching!
You're gonna cum, right?
Go on! I'll take it all in my mouth!
Coming! It's coming!
Your huge load is coming out!
Mistreeeeessss!
T-there! He just came!
The exact same time?
Guess so...
This isn't over yet!
After all, Yuusuke can cum 5 times in a row, no sweat!
S-say whaaat!?
T-tatsuya can handle that no problem!
W-what the hell, Tamaki!?
Very well then.
Let us return our partners and continue.
Fine with me.
So good! You feel so good, Yuusuke!
Harder! Make a mess of my pussy!
But we're doing it right in front of Mistress Tamaki!
It's fine! I don't care!
If you don't cum soon, I'm gonna go crazy!
M-mistress! If you're that rough, I'll cum again!
Just cum whenever you feel like it!
Cum even more than you did in Tamaki's mouth!
My sister's right in front of me, but my pussy's soaking wet and I can't stop!
I'm such a pervert!
Tatsuya, be rougher! I wanna feel more of that dick!
Your pussy's burning up!
I know! Yours is the best!
It's way better than any others!
More! Keep stirring up my pussy!
Wow...they're so intense.
Do you think we should help out again?
Just stay put. They're busy making love, so we shouldn't get in between them.
I can't believe Tamaki's staring at me like that!
Speak for yourself, sister! You're so lewd!
Our love is far deeper than this!
Mistress Leira!
Yuusuke, put it in my ass this time.
M-mistress!
Mistress, this is such a depraved position!
Yes it is! My asshole feels so good!
I'll show you all of my naughty sides!
It's deep! It's so deep!
Sister...
Tatsuya, I wanna try anal too.
There's no reason to be that stubborn now.
That's not it!
I mean, sister looks like she's in heaven...
O-okay then. I've never done this either though...
It's in! It's going in!
Tamaki!
This feels so strange!
It's my first time, but my asshole's so hot!
Oh no! Tamaki, if you stare like that, I'll get even more turned on!
Sister, Father, I'm so sorry!
My asshole, it...it feels so good I can't stand it!
And here as well, Mistress!
Idiot! If you tease me there, I-
Oh God, sooo good! It feels sooooooooo good!
Me too sister! I'm going to cum too!
So hot!
Inside! Do it inside!
Mistress!
Sisterrr!!!
Tamakiii!!!
Oh my...Everybody just came.
I wonder what will happen to the contest?
That's not important. All's well that ends well!
Now I know why you didn't go on vacation, sister.
Oh, just shut up.
Yuusuke sure does treasure you, doesn't he?
Yours is a decent, honest boyfriend too I guess.
Oh, sister!
Goodness, what's the matter?
Sister, what are we going to do next?
Oh dear, there's no way I'd let it end with just that!
Come on! Let's have another match!
Right, sister!