Disgusting! So disgusting!
I just wanted to go shopping!
This had to happen when my gun's at maintenance!
Damn you!
I can deal with this guy even without my gun!
I won't take any more--
What do you think you're doing?
That disgusting bastard!
Um... thank you!
You're... welcome.
She's really cute.
Her skin's fair and her hair's silver.
She must be half-Japanese.
His eyes are burning to my core!
Oh, I gotta get off at this station!
Sorry!
I knew at that time that it was a fated encounter!
The Princesses' Battle for Marriage
Episode Two:
Storm by Cinderella's Castle
I was lucky to get some tickets.
I'm glad I could come with you!
You invited me on a date! How could I possibly refuse?
This place is on the Black Rose's territory. It's their greatest source of income.
It's dangerous for me to come here.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing!
Sakura, let's ride that next!
Okay!
Looks like the intel was correct.
Why's Mamoru on a date with Sakura?
They dare flirt!
But choosing this place for your date was a fatal mistake!
Where am I?
A pip room inside Cinderella's castle.
Ageha?!
You should be grateful for being here! Only Mama and I can use this room.
Where's big si-- I mean, Sakura?
I'm here for you, yet you talk about other women?!
I didn't mean it like that...
What's that you don't like about me?
You can only get hard at cowtits like Sakura's?
No, it's nothing to do with your bodies...
I have manly responsibilities to her, so I can't do whatever I want.
Don't tell me you did it to the end!
Um... I'm... sorry.
Ageha?
Why? Why Sakura and not me?
You're the only one...
who treats me like a normal girl!
You too?
I haven't lost yet!
I'll make our bond a fact!
Hey, Ageha, are you seriously--
Huh?
My head's spinning.
There are love potions in this room that Mama often uses.
You gave me that with this kiss?
You can't control your lust now.
Ageha...
I'll do it to you.
This's Mamoru's cock!
It's already rock hard!
Stop that!
You can still say that? You're strong.
It's so big I can barely fit it in my mouth!
Ageha, if you do that...
Mamoru, you're finally in the mood...
Mamoru's licking my pussy!
Mamoru's tongue's inside me!
Continue, Ageha...
Ageha, that feels so good!
Your clit's erect too, Ageha.
This is semen?
But it's still hard!
Look, Mamoru!
I might be small, but I can become one with you!
That's quite small indeed.
Not that! Here!
Sorry!
I just end up saying whatever I think.
You have no restraint because of the love potion,
but you're being too straightforward...
Ageha... Are we really doing this?
You're still saying that?
How is it? Do you want to invade my pussy?
I want to put it in.
Then I'm giving you my virginity!
It's in!
You're so tight, Ageha!
I could finally become one with you!
I'll make you feel great!
Ageha...
I can feel you big and hard in me! It reaches all the way to my womb!
I haven't cummed yet...
I'm sorry, Mamoru...
Just call me "Big Bro".
Sakura's my big sister, so you'll be my little sister!
You mind?
Will you stay with me if  I become your little sister?
Of course!
Okay, I'll become your little sister then, Big Bro!
I can feel you getting big in me!
Ageha...
Big Bro, you're so wild!
It feels so good, my hips are moving on their own!
It's overwhelming me!
My pussy's so cute, be more gentle!
You said it might be small but it'll be okay!
Yeah, but you're so wild!
Ageha, is today a safe day?
Then I'll be cumming inside!
Cum! Your little sister's womb is waiting!
Cum in me!
I'm cumming!
It's over...
No, not yet!
You welcome a guy in your pussy already full of cum...
I didn't know my little sister was so lewd!
I'm sorry! Don't hate me for being lewd!
How could I hate a little sister so cute who makes me feel so good?
I'm happy!
Does it feel good, Ageha?
Your cock feels great, Big Bro!
I was a virgin until a few minutes ago, but it feels great how you're taking me!
Let's feel even better, us two siblings!
You're so wild!
Big Bro, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! Inside my little sister's pussy!
Twist my pussy and fill my womb with your semen, Big Bro!
Ageha!
Big Bro!
I started peeing...
It won't stop...
Big Bro, don't look at me now!
You're so cute, Ageha...
I'm sorry...
It's okay. I'm happy you were my first time, Mamoru.
Also that I found a wonderful Big Brother!
Ageha, are you really gonna become my little sister?
Of course!
I'll never leave your side, Big Bro!
I couldn't find Mamoru anywhere.
It must be Ageha's doing.
No way!
I'm moving in with you as of today!
I'll be living with you from today!
Isn't it natural for a little sister to live with her big brother?
It's a big sister's duty to look after her little brother!
Like cooking or fulfilling your sexual desires!
What's that lovely creature?
You've never met before?
She's my little sister, Kuu.
His real little sister?
I didn't expect a sister rival to show up now!
I should become his little sister too...
There's no need for any more little sisters!
What?!
Problem?!
Let's eat, Kuu.
The End