Is something the matter, Miss Tamaki?
Oh no, it's nothing.
Nothing, right?
My sister should have left for our Caribbean estate with Father this morning.
Okay, all finished Milady!
You look marvelous Miss Tamaki. Just wait till Master Tatsuya sees you!
Y-yeah, I know that!
Come everyone, let's get going.
Yes, Milady!
So she intends to bring all her servants along? Seems she's going to go for it tonight.
Milady, did you cancel your trip and remain here just to spy on Miss Tamaki?
Do you think I'm such a petty woman?
No, of course not!
You'll be waiting on me hand and foot today, remember?
Oh my, you're already hard. You were looking forward to this weren't you?
I-um...
Well then today, you're going to satisfy me with what you've been saving up.
Milady!
FAKKU! Presents
Milady is crazy about making love
Episode 1: "Yukatas, Swimsuits, and Bathtime too"
Look, you're already twitching.
Just relax and I'll make you cum a whole bunch.
But you're not free to choose when.
That's for me to decide.
You've gotten so huge!
This taste, this hotness! Your penis is simply filthy, Yuusuke.
Milady, I...!
You're not going to cum already, are you?
Well, I-
Goodness, you always have to have it your way. I can't have that.
Oh come on! M-milady?
Get on it! Im giving you special permission to lick it so start making yourself useful!
Yes, Excuse me, Milady.
Ohh, getting carried away, aren't you? I'm not going to sit back and do nothing!
My pussy's spread wide open! He can even see my asshole too!
Oh no! If he keeps this up, he's going to make me cum!
Milady?
Consider yourself lucky. I'm allowing your nasty dick inside me!
Well? Doesn't it feel great inside me?
Oh crap!
Your voice is adorable; Getting excited, hm? I'll take it up a notch.
My pussy's top class; the very best! I'll make you cum in no time!
Milady!
H-hey! Who said you could move on your own!? Stop right now!
Who the hell do you think I am?
I'm sorry, but I can't hold back anymore!
Stop it! How come it feels this good when you're so rough?
Milady, this is too much!
You won't get away with that! Father will hear about this!
Milady! I'm at my limit!
Me too! Just a little more...
Milady!!
Yuusuke!!!
You came inside without permission!
T-terribly sorry, Milady.
And I was so close too...
I-I didn't say anything!
Anyhow, thanks to you I'm all sticky. Help me clean myself up.
Y-you mean a bath?
We have to hurry before she comes back, right?
Milady...?
My Mistress Likes Being Naughty
Of course I do!
Oh good. Tamaki's not here yet.
We've been expecting you, Master Tatsuya!
Miss Tamaki's been waiting. Come now!
Tamaki!
There you are.
Hey, Tatsuya!
You're late! You invited me to this commoner's festival, and you make me wait 30 minutes.
You're unbelievable.
Sorry. I didn't think you'd get here so quickly.
Is something wrong?
Nah, I was just thinking you looked really good in that...
What a corny line.
No good, huh?
Tatsuya's head-over-heels for my Yukata look!
Thank you, oh adorable me!
Well, whatever.
Let's get going then.
Take care, Milady.
Hey, wait up Tamaki!
Master Tatsuya,
Isn't there something special about Miss Tamki today?
S-sure...
Like "She's radiating beauty"
Or "If I were a guy I'd be all over her!"
Or maybe "If those two are alone, it'd get pretty steamy!"
Come on, let's go!
W-well, see ya! Hang on, Tamaki!
Have a nice time!
I invited you, remember?
You can do it, Miss Tamaki!
Mari, Eri...
Today's the day! I'll show my childhood friend just how I feel!
Here goes nothing!
I said wait! Did you forget who invited who? At least let me be in charge for a day!
Not a chance!
Common folk festivals are rather fun!
I ended up getting sucked into her pace again...
Come on Tatsuya.
Let's go check that out next!
Hm? Something the matter?
Nah, I-its nothing.
Gosh, why won't you just fall over?
Tamaki's  way too into this.
Looks like Tatsuya's dying to see what's under my Yukata.
Okay...
Come on! I hit it dead-on...
Yeah, what a shame.
Mari and Eri's "no underwear plan" is working its magic. Just one more push!
When are they going to start the fireworks?
Uh, should be pretty soon I think.
H-hey Tamaki?
Is it just me or is the Yukata all you're wearing?
Maybe!
You got it.
What!? Seriously? Aren't you supposed to wear underwear with that?
Don't be silly. Yukata's are traditional clothing.
It'd be humiliating if you could see the lines.
Yeah, but still!
Oh? You mean to say you've been ogling me this whole time?
N-no, stupid, that's not-
It's okay. I don't mind...
If you're that interested, just see for yourself.
Y-you're really not wearing any.
Of course I'm not.
See? Without underwear, you can feel the curves of my bottom.
Yeah...
Come on, give me your other hand!
Feel my chest too...There...
Hey, Tamaki, you sure about this?
You're asking me that while touching me?
Tamaki's boobs are so soft!
Hold on! You're  getting carried away-
Tamaki, you're nipples are hard...
That's cause you're being so rough with them!
Tamaki!
And no panties either, huh?
That's what I've been saying!
And you're already wet...
Tatsuya, who said you could touch me there? Most people could only dream of touching that!
What about you Tamaki? What've you got your hand on?
You idiot! You should consider yourself lucky I'm doing that.
Oh dear, now what do I do? I'm rubbing Tatsuya's thing already...
What's the woman supposed to do next again? I should have had Mari and Eri explain it better.
Ta-da!
Mari, Eri!
Squeeze it, Milady! Squeeze!
Oh yeah, that's it! Nice assist, girls!
Here goes...
Whoa, Tamaki! That's my-
It's not fair if I'm the only one in such an embarrassing pose. Show me yours too Tatsuya!
See? Just look at how big you've gotten.
Tamaki, that's bad-
Well? Satisfied now?
Do it harder.
Bossy, aren't we?
Well then, I'll return the favor.
Y-you dummy! If you do it that hard I'll-
I'm feeling kind of strange...
I...I came, but I was able to make Tatsuya cum too.
Miladyyy!
Suck while he's still hard, Milady!
Mari, Eri!
Finally, time for a blow job!
Tamaki, what are you doing!?
Just hold still. I'm going to give you a blow job.
Where on earth did you learn this?
Doesn't this feel nice Tatsuya?
Y-yeah...
Oh shit! She's terrible at this, but because it's her doing it...
Now I'll use my breasts.
Tamaki, even that?
Gosh, you're so spoiled! Having me do this for you...
Look how hard my breasts are making you.
Crap! If you keep doing that...
Come on, cum! Cum all over me!
You came so much...I'm all sticky!
After coming this far, all that's left is...
You want to do it here next, don't you Tatsuya?
Are you serious?
Yay, finally!
You want to do it too?
You're still a virgin, aren't you? You sure you want me?
Just how much more do you want to embarrass me?
Tamaki
H-huh? What the-
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Sorry, I can't see too well.
Further down.
Noo! Don't spread it open!
No Tatsuya! Not there!
I said no! My knees are going to buckle!
I'm putting it in Tamaki.
Y-you okay?
..ss me
What?
I said it hurts, so kiss me!
I'm sorry, Tamaki.
Eri, Miss Tamaki's a woman now!
We must inform Miss Leila, Mari!
But
This feels too good!!
How is it?
It's starting to feel better. You can start moving now.
Tamaki...
HEY!
You want to do it like this?
You don't want to?
I didn't say that, it's just kind of embarrassing.
This is so embarrassing! Being in such a slutty position...
Tamaki, you're so dirty!
S-stupid! This is a special treat, doing such perverted things!
Today is special!
So you better make me feel good.
Tamaki, I lo-
You love me, right?
H-hey, let me say it!
Too bad.
I won't let you do as you please, Tatsuya!
Tamaki...
Satisfy me with actions, not words!
Miss Tamaki did it all on her own, how wonderful! Way to go, Milady!
Right, Eri?
Right, Mari!
Tamaki, I-
Don't you dare cum before me Tatsuya!
Just a little more, a little more and I'll-
Tatsuya, it's so hot inside me!
Tamaki, I'm cumming!
It's okay, cum!
Geez, this is so boring.
Shouldn't you be washing here?
R-right. Excuse me then.
You really are a perv, shoving your hands under my swimsuit all of a sudden.
You've been dying to do this, haven't you?
E-excuse me.
Aren't you being a little rough?
S-sorry!
My breasts are all slippery now.
Next...
Would you wash this for me too?
V-very well.
G-good. Very thorough...
Good, just like that.
Milady, your vagina's completely soaked!
You're making those noises on purpose! You're just hopelessly vulgar, aren't you?
Y-yuusuke, wait!
You're too rough!
I'm going to-
Cum!
You cheeky little-!
I want you to clean here too.
Get in there real deep with that thing of yours.
I've never washed here before...
Just do it.
Yes ma'am.
Shoving my swimsuit in too. You're quite the perverted servant.
My apologies
Good! Shove your thick rod all the way in!
M-milady, you're tightening up on me!
Come on, put that hand to use!
Right!
You're amazing Yuusuke! Doing it in my ass feels so good!
You're going to cum soon, aren't you? Go on, dump your nasty sperm into me!
Oh no!
E-excuse me!
It's fine. You haven't had enough yet, have you? Wash me with your dick here too.
Milady!
Doing it directly feels better, doesn't it?
Don't misunderstand! I wouldn't let just anyone do this!
Only you're allowed to do it directly!
Milady!
Ohh, you're getting carried away again!
Hang on! Just calm down!
It's so hot! I'm getting short of breath-
It's okay, do it harder.
It's hitting my womb!
M-milady, I can't hold on! Where should I come?
Wherever you want! Let's do it together!
E-excuse meee!
Moron! Where the heck are yo-
Honestly, inside my swimsuit? You're a freak.
Sorry...
Oh, the head maid.
Pardon me, Miss Leila. I have something to report.
I just received word from Tamaki's attendants.
Lend me your ear a moment.
Miss Tamaki...woman...
Oh that girl, how aggressive. I guess you can't fight your true nature, right father?
Good work, chief.
Thank you.
I have a feeling the fun's yet to come.
Hurry up, Yuusuke. It's time for my massage now.
Yes Milady!
Our Mistress Loves Being Naughty
See you next time!
Sindalf - Typesetting is bland because I have school finals to attend to and I really don't care about porn at a time like this
Jacob - Is still a fag
Waar - Actually did a good job this time
ACF - Picked up something good for once
TehMikuruSlave - Taught him how to time and he still won't help me out