Ageha Kurosaki.
Sakura Sumiyoi.
Why the heck are you here?
Mamoru!
Mamoru-sama!
Ageha, what did you just say?
You as well Sakura. How do you even know Mamoru?
Oh? I met you both at that time.
Then, this is...
To Amakawa
That's my letter...
My love letter...
To Amakawa
Don't tell me, Mamoru-sama is also someone you...
Do you intend on snatching Mamoru from me?
That's supposed to be my line!
What are you talking about?
So you want to die, huh?
Wanna die?
Sakura, the daughter of the Sumiyoi gang leader who owns the northern half of the city.
Ageha, the daughter of the Black Rose mafia leader who rules the southern half of the city.
Both of them are princesses of two very notorious gangs operating in this city.
However, since I was a transfer student, I wasn't aware of this little detail.
Ladies
Matrimony Rivalry
Volume One
Milady's Love sickness
A rare day-off for me...
I just wanted to spend it with my friends, like a normal girl.
Feels like everyone's avoiding me.
Hey, hey young lady.
Why don’t you come spend some time with us?
No thanks.
They are the worst.
And I don’t even have any bodyguards with me.
If only I had my katana at least,
these punks would be...
It’s all right. Come with us, okay?
That's it—
Found you at last, sis!
Why are you here?
Everyone's waiting already.
Hurry up and let's go.
I-I'm sorry. I got a little lost.
We have some family related business today,
so please excuse us.
Thank you very much.
You really helped me.
Y-You're welcome.
Umm... if it's okay, would you mind telling me your name?
Ah, I'm Mamoru Amakawa.
So you are addressed as Mamoru-sama?
A splendid name.
Ah, oh no!
Sorry, someone's waiting for me. I gotta go.
Ah! Mamoru-sama!
Mamoru-sama...
Not only are those two in the same school,
they also ended up sending me two love letters.
Mamoru, who will you choose?
Momoru-sama, who are you gonna choose?
Mamoru-sama won't like chopping boards, so he'll choose me!
Instead of the one with flabby boobs, he'll definitely choose me!
Erm... you both...
we just met, it's too soon to talk about love and...
I've already fallen for you even though we just met!
I, too, believe that it was a destined encounter!
I was happy they confessed to me but,
I just can't decide that fast...
Both of their parents are also big shots in this city...
Rejecting anyone is gonna be hard...
Mamoru will definitely become mine.
What should I do to get Mamoru-sama's attention?
If I don’t act quickly, he might fall into one of Ageha-san's selfishly treacherous schemes.
I will never allow that!
If it comes to it...
I'm going to stake everything for victory!
It's from Sakura-senpai.
"I am sleeping in the infirmary at the moment."
Did she fall sick or something?
Thank you for specially coming to see me.
Well, I...
By the way, where's the infirmary nurse?
I requested she leave me alone for a while.
So she took a break and went somewhere.
No way. That's one irresponsible nurse, leaving someone sick alone...
So they can even give orders to the teachers here?
I wonder if she feels lonely since she is usually alone.
Mamoru-sama.
Since I'm a daughter of a gang leader, are you not scared?
Eh, why?
You're an ordinary cute girl too, right?
Se...Senpai?
It's okay. I'm all right.
As I thought, Mamoru-sama is as kind as I had imagined after all.
Mamoru-sama, actually the illness that I have right now can only be cured by you.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Only by me?
That's right.
Would you have a look, doctor?
D-Doctor?
Yes, from this point on, you will be my doctor.
You will take the responsibility to cure me, right?
Err... responsibility?
Please, doctor.
My body has been feeling hot lately, and its throbbing.
Senpai, what happened to your bra?
My chest felt tight, so I took it off.
Doctor, would you continue the examination?
Senpai?
So? Can you feel it?
It's beating quite fast.
My heart's been beating very fast lately, and it won't stop.
It starts to happen when I'm around a certain person.
A certain person?
Who is it?
You're dull. You're too dull, doctor!
Geez...
Directly?
Making a woman do these things...
Doctor, you’re a jerk!
Could it be that, I'm the source of your illness?
It'd be painful if my heart continues to beat at such a pace.
Doctor, please cure me.
Mamoru-sama...
Was my treatment method incorrect?
No at all. Um... continue. Please continue the palpation.
Palpation? On your body?
I'm your patient, so please call me Sakura instead of Senpai.
But senpai is older than me...
Then how about big sis?
That doesn't sound weird, right?
W-Well, big sis is a bit embarrassing, so...
How about Sakura-nee?
Of-course. That sounds good.
You're my younger brother now.
Doctor, please continue.
Sakura-nee!
So these are your breasts...
Mamoru please be a bit more gentle...
Sakura nee's nipples...
Mamoru, you need to be gentle when caressing a girl's body...
S-Sorry, I got carried away.
Sakura-nee?
You lubricate it like this, and then do it gently.
Okay, I understand.
Doing it like tha—
Lubricate, then do it gently.
Mamoru!
Mamoru is caressing my breasts!
Sakura-nee, your breasts are really tasty!
Doctor, I also want you to examine the lower part next.
The stockings have already gotten dirty.
You can tear it if you want.
It's quite drenched.
I'm going to cum.
Sakura-nee...
Is it going to fit in this small hole?
It's okay.
A girl can accept it as long as it's from someone that they love.
So please, I request an injection in there.
Sakura-nee...
Sakura-nee, I-I...
So after all, you really are scared of my status?
N-No, it's not that!
I just want to take care of you properly.
But then I started wondering, that if I am even capable of doing that?
And I suddenly became anxious.
You are a gentle guy, aren't you Mamoru?
But if you really want to take good care of me,
you'll have to show more courage.
Because the most important thing is our feelings right now.
Okay.
I understand.
Sakura-nee?
I'm all right.
It's a bit painful because it's my first time,
but I'm really fine.
So it does hurt after all...
No, these are tears of joy.
I feel happy because I gave my virginity to you, Mamoru.
Then will it be cured? Your illness that is?
It should, so please start moving.
Okay.
Your insides are warm and soft. It feels good.
I'm happy.
If you feel that good, then I also feel good.
More! Please take more pleasure!
Sakura-nee!
Mamoru!
It really feels too good inside you.
I'm already at my limit.
I'm sorry, I wasn't able to hold it in at all.
And you haven't even climaxed yet.
You don't have to worry about that.
Can you still continue the examination?
I think I can.
Well,
you seem to like my breasts, so...
Your cock's very lively.
If you keep doing that, it'll release again.
Don't let it out yet.
The injection's supposed to be here.
This time please release it inside.
It's a safe day so do so without worries.
I understand.
It's still my first time yet I can already feel it.
Wait. It feels so good, I might die!
I'll die from your injection!
Mamoru!
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum!
Sakura-nee!
Injection's coming in,
and it's flowing into my womb
I feel like melting with your semen inside me.
Sakura-nee...
Mamoru...
Which means a person's gender will be determined by the chromosomes...
In return for giving you my virginity,
I'll be taking yours, Mamoru...
www.SubDESU-H.net
To be continued...