Kurosaki Ageha...
Sumiyoi Sakura...
What are you doing here?!
Mamoru!
Ageha, what did you just say?
Why do you know Mamoru?
Ah, you're from back then!
Did you write these?
That's my letter!
My love letter!
Don't tell me you set your eyes on Mamoru?!
You want to steal him from me?!
That's my line!
Get real!
You look so eager to die.
But I'll send you ahead.
The daughter of the Sumiyoi clan leader, who rules the north half of the city, Sakura.
The daughter of the Black Rose maffia leader, who rules the south half of the city, Ageha.
They are the two princesses of the town.
But I didn't know who they were when I transferred here.
The Princesses' Battle for Marriage
The Princesses'
Annoying Love
I wanted to spend this day off like a normal girl, with my friends...
They're all avoiding me, aren't they?
Hey babe, wanna hang out with us?
I'll pass.
Could this get any worse?
I've got no bodyguards with me
and I even left my sword at home, or I could deal with them...
Come on now!
I can't bear this...
Sis! I've been looking for you!
What are you doing here?
Everyone's waiting! We must hurry!
Sorry, I just got lost...
We've got a family event to attend. If you'll excuse us.
Thank you!
You really saved me back there.
You're welcome.
Would you be so kind as to tell me your name?
Ah, I'm Amakawa Mamoru.
So you are called Mamoru...
What a wonderful name.
Oh crap!
I'm late for a meeting. See you!
Mamoru!
Mamoru...
Who would've thought they're both my schoolmates and they'd give me love letters?
Mamoru! Who are you gonna choose?
Of course Mamoru will choose me over you, you flatchest!
It's obvious that he loves me more than your cowtits!
Uh, you know we just met...
Love isn't really--
I fell in love with you at first sight!
It was a fated encounter for me!
It feels good that they confessed to me, but having to choose like this doesn't...
Not to mention their fathers rule the town and no one can oppose them...
I'll take Mamoru for myself, no matter what!
What should I do to make Mamoru choose me?
I must hurry or that selfish Ageha might use force...
I can't allow that!
That way she'd win without a fight!
It's from Sakura...
"I'm in bed in the nurse's office."
Did she get sick or something?
Thank you for coming here just for me.
It's just natural.
By the way, where's the nurse?
I told her I wanted to be alone,
so she told me to rest well and left somewhere.
Huh? She left her patient alone?
That's so irresponsible.
She can even tell teachers what to do and she is always alone...
Mamoru?
Aren't you afraid of me because I'm the daughter of a ganglord?
Why would I be?
You're a normal, really cute girl.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I'm fine.
He's really the person I thought he is!
Actually you're the only one who can cure my sickness.
Only me?
Yes. Would you take a look, doctor?
Doctor?!
Yes. You're to become my doctor now.
Please cure me responsibly like a good doctor.
Responsibly?
Please, Doctor...
I've been feeling so hot and my heart's racing.
What happened to your bra?!
It squeezed my chest so much I took it off.
How are you going to examine me?
What--
Can you feel it?
It's racing hard.
It's been like that for a while now.
It happens whenever I'm around a certain someone.
A certain someone?
Who?
You're so dim! You're so dim, Doctor!
Directly?!
How dare you do this to a girl, Doctor! You dummy!
Am I the cause for your "sickness"?
I can't endure my heart beating so hard all the time.
Doctor, please cure me!
Mamoru...
Was that the wrong cure?
No...
But you should use palpation now.
Palpation? Of your body?
I'm your patient now, so please call me by my name.
But that'd be so awkward... You're older than me too.
Then how about Sister?
Huh?
That shouldn't be weird, right?
It's a bit embarrassing, so how about big sis Sakura?
That's great.
You're my one and only dear little brother.
Doctor, how will you continue the examination?
Big sis Sakura!
Your boobs are great!
Mamoru, be gentler with them!
And now her nipples!
Mamoru, you must be gentle with girls' bodies.
I'm sorry, I got carried away.
What?!
Wet like this... Gently...
I get it.
That's not what I meant!
Make it wet... then gently...
Mamoru! You're sucking on my tits!
Her boobs taste great...
Doctor, could you check me below too?
My stockings are already wet, so you can tear them.
It's so wet...
Shut up!
Big sis Sakura...
Will it fit in a hole this small?
It's fine. Girls are made in a way so we can accept the man we love.
So please, give me an injection!
Big sis Sakura...
I'm sorry, but I...
Are you afraid of me after all?
No, that's not it!
I want to take good care of you,
but then I got worried what if I couldn't do that...
You're so kind, Mamoru.
But if you really want to take care of me, you must be brave.
Our feelings matter the most now.
Okay.
Big sis Sakura...
I'm fine.
It's my first time, so it hurts a bit, but I'm fine.
But if it hurts...
No, these are the tears of joy.
I'm really happy that I could give you my virginity.
Then is this gonna cure your sickness, big sis Sakura?
I think it is, so start moving...
Inside you it's so hot and slippery! It feels great!
I'm so happy!
If you feel good, I feel good too!
So feel even better!
Big sis Sakura!
Mamoru!
Your pussy feels so good!
I'm at my limit!
Sorry, I couldn't hold it back...
You haven't cummed yet.
Don't worry about it.
Can you continue treatment?
I think I can do it.
Well then...
You seemed to like your big sister's boobs a lot.
Mamoru, it's so hard!
I'll cum again if you do that...
You can't do that just yet.
I'll have an injection here.
This time on the inside, please.
Today's a safe day, so I can't get pregnant.
Okay.
This is my first time, but it still feels so good!
Wait! It feels so good I feel like I'm gonna die!
Your injection's gonna kill me!
Mamoru! Mamoru!
I'm cu-cumm--- I'm cumming!
Big sis Sakura!
I can feel the injection in me!
It's filling up my womb!
I'm melting from your semen...
Big sis Sakura...
Mamoru...
And this chromosome is what decides the gender of people.
I'll give you my virginity, but then your cock will be mine alone!
To be continued...