This is the worst!
The worst!
The worst!!
I planned to do my shopping quickly,
so I left my gun at home for maintenance.
I've had enough.
Even if I don't have a gun...
If it's just this jerk...
I can't stand this anymore!
What do you think you're doing?
That's the worst type of guy.
Um...
Thank you.
Y-you're welcome.
What a really cute girl.
She has fair skin and silver hair.
Is she multi-ethnic?
He's staring at me so passionately...
Oh, I have to get off here.
Sorry!
At that time, I truly felt
that was a fated encounter.
Ladies
Matrimony
Rivalry
Distress!
Tsunderella
Castle
I got these tickets by chance,
but I'm glad you were able to come, Sahura-nee.
If you invite me on a date,
there's no way I'd refuse.
This is Black Rose's turf,
and their primary source of income.
To be honest, it's extremely dangerous
for me to be here.
Is something wrong?
No. It's nothing.
Let's ride that next, Sahura-nee!
Okay!
Seems like my intel was right on.
Why is Mamoru having a date with Sakura?
Getting all flirty like that!
Still,
choosing this place for your date
is like a mosquito flying right into a web.
Where am I?
This is the VIP room of the Tsunderella Castle.
Ageha?
Did you know that only my mother
and I are allowed in this room?
You better be grateful.
Sakura-nee... I mean, what about Sakura-senpai?
To say another woman's name
while I'm right in front of you...
No. Well, I didn't mean...
What do you find lacking in me?
Is it because I don't have big breasts like Sakura?
No. This has nothing to do with your body.
As a man, I have to take care of Sakura-nee.
I can't fool around with other girls.
Does that mean you did it with Sakura?
Well, um...
Sorry.
Ageha?
Why?
Why her and not me?
You were the only one...
who treated me like a regular girl.
Ageha, you too?
I haven't lost yet!
I'm also going to create a pact between us!
Wait a sec, Ageha.
Do you know what you're saying?
What?
I feel dizzy...
There's an aphrodisiac my mother keeps in this room.
So just now... in that kiss...
With this, you won't be able to resist your desires.
Ageha?
I'll do it for you.
So this is your cock?
It's already dripping...
Stop this...
You're still against this?
Such a stubborn fellow.
Your cock is so big that it might make me full!
Ageha, if you do that...
So you're finally up for it, Mamoru?
Mamoru is licking my pussy.
Mamoru's tongue is inside me!
Keep that up, Ageha.
Ageha...
It feels so good.
Your clitoris is also getting stiff.
So this is semen?
You still have more in you?
Look, Mamoru.
Even if I'm this small, I can still be one with you.
Even if it's that small?
Not there!
Here!
Sorry!
Sometimes, I just say what's on
my mind without thinking.
You can't seem to think straight
because of the aphrodisiac.
But still, you're a little too honest.
You're really going to do it, Ageha?
You're still asking?
How is it?
Don't you want to enter my pussy?
I want to.
Then, I'll be giving you my virginity, okay?
It's in.
Your insides are so tight.
I finally became one with Mamoru.
I'm going to make you feel good.
Ageha...
Your cock is stirring my inside up,
and it's even reaching my womb.
I haven't cummed yet.
I'm sorry, Mamoru.
Call me "Onii-chan".
Sakura-senpai is Onee-chan,
so you are my little sis.
You don't want it?
If I become your little sister, will
you always be by my side?
Of course!
Then I'll become your little sister!
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan is getting bigger inside me.
Ageha...
Onii-chan, this is intense...
It feels so good. I can't stop...
Your thing is really amazing!
But at this rate, my pussy will break.
You're the one who said it's fine even if it's small, right?
Yes, but...
For it to be so intense...
Are you safe today, Ageha?
I'll completely cum inside you.
Will you give it to me?
Onii-chan will release it inside little sister's pussy.
Cum! Cum!
It came!
It's finally over.
No. We're not finished yet.
Your pussy is still filled with semen,
and you're going for round two.
What a slutty little sister!
I'm sorry!
Please don't hate the slutty me!
It's impossible for me to hate
this delectable and cute little sister!
I'm happy!
Do you feel good too?
Onii-chan, your cock feels good!
For the little sister to be penetrated this good...
I was a virgin just a few minutes ago.
Now, it feels so good.
Let's feel good together, as siblings!
It's going in...
I can't keep up anymore...
I'm going to cum, Onii-chan!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to release it inside my little sister Ageha!
Cum.
Destroy your little sister's pussy,
and fill my womb with your semen, Onii-chan!
Ageha!
Onii-chan!
I peed.
It won't stop!
Don't look at me, Onii-chan!
You're cute Ageha...
Sorry...
It's okay.
I'm happy my first time was with you.
And I even got a wonderful new
Onii-chan, so I'm very glad.
You're really going to be my little sister?
Of course.
I'm never letting you go, Onii-chan.
I can't find Mamoru anywhere.
I guess this really is Ageha-san's...
No way!
From this day on, I will be living here.
Starting today, I will live in here with you.
I'm your little sister, so isn't it normal
for us to live together?
Onee-chan also has the responsibility
of looking after her little brother!
Like preparing dinner or taking care of sexual needs!
What's with this lovely little thing?
Oh, you haven't met her yet?
This is my little sister, Kuu.
A real little sister?!
So my greatest rival finally appear?
If it comes to this, I'll have to be a little sister too.
We don't need anymore little sisters!
What did you say?!
What?
Let's go eat, Kuu.
The end.