No Money!
ikiteku koto wa subarashii
生きてく事は素晴らしい
Living your life is a wonderful thing.
demo issun saki wa yami rashii
でも一寸先は闇らしい
But one step ahead,
I hear there's only darkness.
shounen gaku nari ga tashi
少年学成りがたし
Art is long. Life is short..
sugu ni susume
すぐに進め
Go forward without delay.
unmei kashikari wa nashi
運命、貸し借りはなし
Destiny always evens things up.
seishun koukai ya da shi
青春、後悔嫌だし
And you don't want
regrets in your youth.
saishuuheiki wa watashi
最終兵器は私
I can be your ultimate weapon.
yukuze YES YES
ゆくぜ yes yes
So come on... Yes, yes.
Don't hesitate
over holding this hand of mine.
sono te wo nigirishimeru no ni mayotten na yo
その手を握りしめるのに迷ってんなよ
kamisama ga tokubetsu kureta CHANCE dakara
神様が特別くれたチャンスだから
Because this is
a special God-given chance.
zettai ni ROMANCE
絶対にロマンス
It's romance for sure.
We're sexy men for sure.
zettai ni romensu
絶対色MENっす
yume mireba kanau mono
夢見れば　叶うもの
If you dare to dream,
it will come true.
dekkai na ROMANCE WAY
でっかいなロマンスウェー
After this great love of ours...
kimi wo nosete
君を乗せて
...I'm taking you along for the ride.
jissai ni ROMANCE
実際にロマンス
It truly is a romance.
The fact is we're sexy men.
jittai ni ROMANCE
実態にロマンス
kimi dake ni sasageru ai no sube
君だけに捧げる愛の末
After I've given you this love
that's meant only for you...
mou hitori ni shinai
もう一人にしない
...I'll never leave your side again.
A few weeks ago, I would
never have imagined...
...that because of a debt...
...I would be...
I'll pay you $5,000 every time.
You are mine until
the debt is paid off.
How long are you going to take?
Mr. Kanoh...
I should have gotten in with you.
When we did it in the
bath the other day...
...the way your voice
echoed turned me on.
Please let me go!
No, I'm not waiting any more!
What? Whose voice...
No...
Was that me?
Don't try to hide it.
You like this.
Just admit it.
No, that's not...
Then I'll prove it to you.
Don't let go.
Watch...
See what you look like
when I'm doing you.
No...
Sto...
No... This is... It's like...
Oh no...
I'm going to come!
No.
Who said you could come?
Let's hear you beg...
...like I taught you.
What are you going to do?
Please...
And?
Let me come...
I'm losing... I'm losing myself.
Very good.
It's okay.
I'll let you come.
I'm scared.
I don't want this.
Episode 3
Does it hurt?
Um... no...
Of course not.
I'm being gentle.
It seems like you're
getting used to this.
You saw it, right?
What you looked like...
Please stop!
There's no way!
I'm a man.
This isn't...
Please, let me get
a job to repay you!
I can't do this,
even if it's for money.
Do you have any idea
how well I'm paying you?
You can clean dead bodies
or work at a bathhouse...
...but you're not going to
make more than what I pay you!
But...
But... Not anymore...
I can't...
Fine.
Get ready.
We're going out.
I'm going to hook you up with a job.
A job?
Your call was so urgent, Mr. Kanoh.
What took you so long?
I expect you to be here
in 5 minutes when I call.
Oh, don't be so unreasonable.
Wow! What a cutie!
Did you get a new girlfriend?
Hi, hello, I'm Gion.
Uh...
Uh... I...
But my goodness, you've
changed your tastes.
You used to not be
into this petite type...
...but those hot chicks like ba-boom!
Balls!
They're small, but you're a guy!
Wh-what are you...
And that high-pitched voice!
A high school boy and
your voice is still...
I'm a college student.
Now, now, no lying.
Um... Mr. Kanoh... Hello...
You look even more scary than usual.
There's an aura...
Hello?
Hello...
This isn't good.
My life was too short.
My head is caved in.
My brains are leaking out.
This is the end for Gion.
It's not that bad.
Don't you know how to go easy?
A-are you okay?
Never mind him.
It's okay, come here.
But...
Y-yes.
Mr. Kanoh...
Um...
I don't mean to pry,
but what's your relationship?
He's repaying a debt with his body.
Huh?
I just bought a piece of him.
Didn't I, Ayase?
In other words, he belongs to me.
Next time you lay a hand
on him without permission...
...just know you'll wind up
at the bottom of Tokyo Bay.
I'll be sure to remember that.
But, if you're not careful,
you could be fish food too.
Hm?
Didn't you recently confiscate
a certain master-tape...
...for payback on a debt?
There's a problem.
Ever heard the name Yoshizumi?
He's an entrepreneur who runs
a club in Roppongi as a front.
It turns out that tape
was stolen from there.
They're going crazy trying
to get that tape back.
It's only a matter of time before...
Gion!
Listen...
You should be more concerned!
He has a beef with you too!
You've got good sources!
Then you knew where
the tape came from?
You got guts, man.
Yoshizumi....
He's gotten carried
away just because...
...he's got some
politicians as backers.
He was pretty arrogant
when he tried to hired me.
But I will hand it to
him for recognizing...
...my talents as a cameraman.
Cameraman?
What's his connection to Mr. Kanoh?
I don't like the way he operates.
So when I told him I only
work with subjects I like...
...he got nasty with me.
It was horrible.
But if the model they had
was as good-looking as Aya...
...I might have taken it.
Don't worry.
There are adult movies
that aren't that hard-core.
I'll make sure you look good.
S-stop kidding...
Gion...
Just kidding, just kidding!
I was just joking!
Go ahead.
What!
What did he...
You can shoot him.
That's why I called you.
You said you would do anything if
you didn't have to sleep with me.
I'm hooking you up...
...with a lucrative job.
Ask and you shall receive!
Being able to shoot
a cutie like this...
...is a cameraman's
dream come true, really!
...is what I'd like
to be saying, but...
I'm sorry, I have to decline, Bro.
What?
Aya doesn't seem
to be down with this.
I know it's an adult movie...
...but there has to be love in
the sex scenes. That's my policy.
Mr. Gion...
I don't quite understand
the situation, but...
...you should be nicer to Aya.
So, please excuse me.
Shut up you idiot!
Shut up and do as I
say before I lose it!
Y-yes!
I'll go right away to
get my equipment!
What should I do?
Oh no, is he serious?
Damn!
I'm kidding!
U-um...
Mr. Kanoh...
So you're the
Loan shark from Shinjuku.
You're just a kid.
I understand you have
something of mine.
What?
A master-tape.
This is him...
Ever heard the name Yoshizumi?
It turns out that tape
was stolen from there.
It would be in your best
interest to return it.
You'll be sorry if you
make an enemy of me.
Like Gion did...
I hear he's your kid brother.
He's a stupid kid.
If you don't want
to end up like him...
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Who are you anyway?
I don't remember meeting
a third rate club owner...
...from the outskirts of town.
Don't screw with me kid!
Watch where you're going!
I-I'm sorry!
What the hell is going on!
Are you hurt?
Um...no...
Please, I'm sorry!
I'll clean it right away!
You punk.
I can get your Loan shark
permit revoked in an instant...
Y-you!
Enough barking.
Why are you messing with
a kid like me, old man?
You came all this way from
Roppongi to make a fool of yourself.
I don't want to grow up
to be like you.
I-I'm going to kill you!
Let go of me!
Sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
But you're disturbing
the other customers.
Huh?
He's the perpetrator here!
Hey, are you listening to me?
I'm sorry, sir. We were remiss.
I'm very sorry.
No, I'm sorry to have
caused the trouble.
We're ready to go to our room.
Uh... um...
Hang on a second.
I...
Ayase...
Don't piss me off.
Let me go, damn it!
Enough!
Who do you think I am?
I know who you are...
...Yoshizumi, sir.
But don't forget, this is Shinjuku.
It is not wise to wage
a war against him here.
For your own sake, please, leave.
Yeah.
And?
Okay, fine.
Don't be so nervous.
It's no different than
any other time.
Besides...
It turns you on to be
watched, doesn't it?
Admit it.
You loved it when we had
sex in front of the mirror.
No...
No.
I was disgusted...
...by myself.
I...
Do you want me to
remind you what you said?
Please...
...let me come.
No!
I didn't...
...say it because I wanted to.
Then why don't you ask them.
The people who will be watching
this video we're about to shoot.
What?
Don't be so surprised.
That's what it means
to make an adult movie.
I'm eager to see who will watch
the numerous copies we circulate.
You might not be able
to go back to school.
It's all falling apart.
Because of this man,
it's all falling apart.
Even if you leave school...
...this video will haunt you
for the rest of your life.
My life, my morals...
...my self, my body, my soul...
How?
How did it come to this?
You can't escape.
How can I get out
of this situation?
How?
You'd still rather
not sleep with me?
Ayase.
I-I will do it.
Please...
Stop...
Please stop the video.
Please...
You...
I don't...
I don't want to...
I don't want to!
Please!
Stop!
What am I doing?
There's...
...nothing I can do.
I can't get away.
I wonder what's
wrong with Mr. Kanoh.
Why does he look so pained?
I don't get it.
After what he's said to me...
Why do I feel so
tender towards him?
The video's off.
I'll talk to Gion.
Huh?
You stay here tonight.
I'll come get you tomorrow.
See you.
Everything is coming
apart because of him.
My life, my morals,
my body, my soul...
But...
Why?
Why does he seem so kind to me?
Mr. Kanoh...
I'll come get you tomorrow!
Why couldn't...
...I tell him I wanted
to go home with him?
I can never find the words...
...and so I never say what I feel.
Am I going to lose him too?
He said he'd become my family.
He's awake.
Where am I?
I remember.
I must have...
Hey.
Thanks a lot for yesterday.
Yoshizumi! I told you
not to be rough.
Why are you kidnapping this kid?
Are you okay, Aya?
Mr. Gion...
You guys are my bait
to lure Kanoh out.
Blame it on Kanoh.
That's misplaced resentment.
If you've got a gripe,
tell it to the person...
...who stole the tape from you.
What?
You have no idea what he's like.
Somuku Kanoh is not the
kind of man who will...
...come running because
you have his girlfriend.
Wait all you want!
Shut up!
To be honest, he's not even
remotely concerned about you.
Do you want to die?
Huh? Do you get it!
Let it go, Yoshizumi.
M-Mr. Kudo!
I told you not to use my name.
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
This is nothing compared
to what Bro does.
In any case, a hostage
means nothing to him.
Let the kid go.
I can't do that.
I came to meet you.
Huh?
What a beautiful child.
I like him.
What?
Cut it out, you
pervert politician!
I'm going to tell your
daughter and your voters!
I'm going to need
your help, Gion.
Huh?
Kanoh's kid brother
is going to film...
...his little lover being violated.
Isn't it a great idea?
Give me a break, no way!
You can lick your wounds later.
Get ready to film!
Wait!
You! Come here!
Go ahead, sir.
As promised, we won't
show your face.
You're going to give
me the master-tape.
I'm looking forward to it.
It seems he's indeed his lover.
Wow.
He's already been broken in.
But his reaction is
so naive, it's great.
Is this...
...your first time with
someone other than him?
This feels horrible.
Even though it's
the same thing...
The same thing...
That was a surprise.
It's not the same.
Aya.
Sir, let me tend to that!
Don't bother.
I see you have no manners.
What are you doing?!
Shut up and film!
I like you even more.
It's going to be fun
to discipline you.
What?
Is this your first time
with drugs like this?
It's going to make you feel better.
You have no choice.
Excuse me, Yoshizumi.
I see!
It's easy to dominate with violence.
But with a boy with eyes
as innocent as yours...
...I want to totally
humiliate and violate you.
I'm scared.
Mr. Kanoh...
I'm scared!
Look, Gion.
You said he wouldn't come.
No way.
Our best customer is here.
Is that your master?
Did you bring the
money and the tape?
He shouldn't have come!
But...
He came.
Hey!
You!
You freak politician!
What!
How long are you going to
keep your filthy hands on him?
Let go!
What's with the attitude?
Don't you care what
happens to the kid?
On your knees, Kanoh!
Get on your knees and
apologize for yesterday!
What's the matter?
Didn't you hear me?
No! Mr. Kanoh! Don't do it!
Mr. Kanoh!
You're not finished.
Rub your head on the floor
and say that you're sorry!
Say it!
It's my fault.
If I had said that I wanted
to go home with him...
This wouldn't have...
Kanoh, was it?
I've heard about you.
You said my hands were filthy...
...but what about yours?
What did you to do to
this kid with those hands?
What's so different about us?
Yes, we're the same.
You and I...
You're not!
You're not...
Mr. Kanoh is...
I have to say it.
Now or never!
No...
Mr. Kanoh is...
See you...
Mr. Kanoh was kind to me.
He was...
What are you doing?
Why don't you check the goods?
Yoshizumi.
Fine.
But don't go
thinking this is over.
You will never
disobey me again.
Mr. Gion!
It's good, isn't it?
The weight of $6,300.
Just how stupid are you?
Now we have to re-discipline another idiot.
Yeah...
...and you'll be first, Yoshizumi.
And then you, you freak politician.
I'm going to show you...
Y-you...
Let my daughter...
...who you started a war with!
When I opened the window
and spoke to you...
mado o akehanashitara
窓を開け放したら
...I could see that the
wintry, night sky was sparkling.
fuyu no yozora ga kirameite ta
冬の夜空がきらめいてた
Could it be that the emotions
of all the people everywhere...
hitobito no omoi subete ga
人々の思いすべてが
...had turned into those stars?
ano hoshi tachi ni natta no ka na
あの星たちになったのかな？
toki o koeta ano yakusoku o
時を越えたあの約束を
That promise we made so long ago...
ima mou dakishimete iru yo
今もう抱きしめているよ
...is something I still
cling tightly to now.
On sleepless nights in my dreams...
nemureru yoru wa yume no naka de aa
眠れる夜は 夢の中で ああ
Even if a single tear falls...
namida hitotsu koborete mo
涙ひとつこぼれても
wasurenai hohoemi o
忘れない微笑を
...I'll never forget that smile.
itoshii hito yo
愛しい人よ
My beloved, just keep me warm forever.
eien ni nukumori o tsutaete
永遠に温もりを伝えて
kanashii ame ni utarete mo
悲しい雨に打たれても
Even if I'm caught
in a rainfall of grief...
...I want to become your love.
anata no ai ni naritai
あなたの愛になりたい