No Money
Living your life is a wonderful thing.
ikiteku koto wa subarashii
生きてく事は素晴らしい
But one step ahead,
I hear there's only darkness.
demo issun saki wa yami rashii
でも一寸先は闇らしい
Art is long. Life is short.
shounen gaku nari ga tashi
少年学成りがたし
Go forward without delay.
sugu ni susume
すぐに進め
Destiny always evens things up.
unmei kashikari wa nashi
運命、貸し借りはなし
And you don't want
regrets in your youth.
seishun koukai ya da shi
青春、後悔嫌だし
I can be your ultimate weapon.
saishuuheiki wa watashi
最終兵器は私
So come on... Yes, yes.
yukuze YES YES
ゆくぜ yes yes
Don't hesitate...
sono te wo nigirishimeru no ni mayotten na yo
その手を握りしめるのに迷ってんなよ
...over holding this hand of mine.
Because this is
a special God-given chance.
kamisama ga tokubetsu kureta CHANCE dakara
神様が特別くれたチャンスだから
It's romance for sure.
We're sexy men for sure.
zettai ni ROMANCE
絶対にロマンス
zettai ni romensu
絶対色MENっす
If you dare to dream, it will come true.
yume mireba kanau mono
夢見れば　叶うもの
After this great love of ours...
dekkai na ROMANCE WAY
でっかいなロマンスウェー
...I'm taking you along for the ride.
kimi wo nosete
君を乗せて
It truly is a romance.
The fact is we're sexy men.
jissai ni ROMANCE
実際にロマンス
jittai ni ROMANCE
実態にロマンス
After I've given you this love
that's meant only for you...
kimi dake ni sasageru ai no sube
君だけに捧げる愛の末
...I'll never leave your side again.
mou hitori ni shinai
もう一人にしない
We've been waiting
for you, Mr. Kanoh.
Welcome to Axi.
Episode 2
Te...
Tetsuo!
Y-You look well...
Better than I thought.
You too. I haven't seen you since
the day you came to borrow money.
Were you planning
to bilk us from the start?
N-No, of course not.
Why don't you let the boy
off the hook for now, Kanoh?
I didn't ask you to come all this way
to discuss trivial matters like that.
I wonder which is more trivial?
A crooked casino that strips amateur
gamblers of all they've got...
Well, Mr. Hayashida?
You bastard, how dare you...
Knock it off.
I'll be upfront about this... I just want
to do some business with you today.
In a peaceful way.
I'll get to the point.
I want you to hand
overyoung Ayase there.
Of course, you'll be compensated.
I'll pay you back your 120 million.
And I'll add another 10 million
to the total. What do you say?
I see...
You're planning to resell.
You've found
a higher bidder, haven't you?
Well, now that's a surprising scenario.
I don't want you
to misunderstand, Ayase.
Someone's appeared who heard of
your plight and decided to rescue you.
He's even offering to adopt.
Not only that, but he says
he'll pay off my debt too!
Tetsuo...
I'll finally be free again...
And you'll be rich.
Isn't that awesome?
It's settled, right, Yukiya?
Tetsuo...
It's no good after all.
You've got to get a job
and pay the debt off yourself.
If you do, I think your mindset
and life-style will both change.
You're the one who has to change.
Or you may end up in a vicious circle.
W-What are you doing, lecturing me?
Y-You're just Yukiya!
Let's do it that way,
Tetsuo. I'll help you too.
Shut up! Just do
what I say, you little...
Ishii is absolutely right. Ayase...
...reality isn't so nice.
I'm telling you for your
own good. Do as I suggested.
The patron has status and honor.
Quite the gentleman...
Outwardly.
He also has sexual propensities
that can't be made public, right?
As a sadist, he'll train
you till you're insane...
Or you'll be eaten alive
by hedonistic sexual gourmands...
Since this is a place where a corrupt
crowd comes to buy their next prey.
You can hardly expect them
to treat you like a human...
You know that and
still want to sell him off...
Right, lshii?
N-No... Of course not!
As long as you save yourself,
you don't care what happens to Ayase...
At any rate, it's too late.
I won the bid for Ayase...
That's invalid.
What's that?
That auction was restricted
to mem bers, you see...
It was a mistake
to hand over the product...
...to someone who entered
the premises under false pretenses.
Now then, take our money
like a good boy and go home.
Sorry to disappoint.
I was participating
on behalf of a certain member.
Since I've paid you and taken
possession, this kid belongs to me.
Then how about this?
Why don't we make a wager?
If you win, I'll contact my client
to tell him that the deal is off.
Not only that, I'll return your 120
million, along with an extra 50 million.
Not only does that mean
you'll get Ayase for free...
...you'll also earn a cool
50 million without lifting a finger.
And if you lose, you'll have
to give that kid back to me.
Naturally, I won't repay you.
Well?
If I win, I want you to add another
200 million as an "inconvenience fee."
Also, I want you to transfer
all of Tetsuo lshii's debt to me.
M-Me? W-Why?
If you can accept these
new terms, I'll take you on.
If there's nothing I can do
to rip lshii out of Ayase's heart...
...I have no choice
but to keep him close.
Then let me add another condition.
If you lose...
...you'll close your loan shark
business and leave Shinjuku.
You'll also apologize for insulting me.
I hope you don't think you
can make it out of here alive...
The deal's done.
Let's get this show on the road.
There's 320 million yen here,
and these are all of lshii's debts.
Satisfied?
Looks fine.
Then come overto this table.
Then come over to this table.
We've closed the place tonight
for you, but we're both busy men.
A speedy conclusion is best, right?
Let me explain the rules.
The trigger can't be pulled
if the cylinder can't rotate.
Boss, what should I do?
Let him go, Kuba.
That was just a demonstration.
Yes, sir.
The rules are quite simple.
We load the gun with one bullet,
then take turns pulling the trigger...
...and whoever's out of luck loses.
That said, it's just
loaded with red ink, of course.
I had these guns and bullets
made just for this game.
Of course, it's a real gun that can fire
live bullets like the ones from before.
Hey, hand him the gun.
And a new bullet too.
I wouldn't want you
to suspect me of conning you.
You'll feel safer
loading it yourself, right?
Why thank you.
Don't give me that.
You accepted my terms
because you're sure you'll win.
Which means...
It's got to be a con.
Like people could play fair here.
Serves you right, Kanoh, you bastard.
You'll get shut down and driven out.
I just can't wait to see him eat it!
All right, I'll go first.
May I ask something, Kanoh?
Why are you so
hung up on this kid's welfare?
It'd be far safer and beneficial for you
to take the money and hand him over.
What possible reason could
you have for taking such a risk?
I have a reason.
Though you don't seem
to remember anything about it, Ayase.
But this time around...
...I'm going to save you.
What's he talking about? Don't tell
me you knew him from before?
I don't know.
You must be out of your
mind from all the tension.
But...
We have one bullet left.
This will be settled in the next round.
Right.
It'll be all over in
this round! Your life, that is.
I have to stop him.
S-Stop him?
Leave them alone!
He's about to lose!
Doesn't that make you feel good?
He put you through hell too, right?
But...
You okay?
He was so good to me...
He was good to me.
Mr. Kanoh! You mustn't shoot!
Please stop! This gun is...
Idiot...
You...
...said it for the first time.
My name.
One more time...
No, what are you doing, Mr. Kanoh...
Mr. Kanoh...
I-I have to tell you...
Just sit back and watch.
I'm an extremely lucky guy.
I don't feel like I can lose today.
B-But...
Don't worry.
I'll protect you no matter what.
No...
Mr. Kanoh...
See? Lucky, right?
T-That's...
That's impossible!
There's no way that could happen!
Kanoh, how the hell...
There's no way?
You make it sound like
it was a done deal that I'd lose.
Right, Mr. Hayashida?
Sorry things didn't go as you planned.
Kuba, take this money to the car.
Yes, sir.
That means you too,
lshii. Don't run off.
I see... I get it.
You pretended to load it at the start,
but you didn't put any bullets in.
Trying such a petty trick...
Don't think you're leaving here alive...
W-What are you doing?
Just as I thought.
The chamber's empty after all.
Actually, you're wrong.
True, I didn't load this paint bullet, but
I did load something else in its place.
Do you know what that might be?
Four, five...
O-One bullet is missing...
D-Don't tell me it's a live bullet...
Right on the money.
As a reward for giving the correct
answer, I'll take you for a drive.
Hey, out of my way! Step aside!
K-Kanoh...
Well, now... If it makes you
that happy, it makes me happy too.
I can see it'll be a fun trip.
It finally went down, huh?
You nearly gave me a heart attack.
Collapsing as soon as we got home...
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
Ayase...
Yes?
About lshii...
Yes.
Considering what that bastard did,
selling his organs won't be enough.
U-Um...
But...
Just this once,
I'll forgive him for your sake.
Of course, I'll make
sure he pays me back in full.
By doing wholesome manual labor.
Thank you so much.
Damn, it pisses me off!
Oh, u-um...
I know.
For you, being family is on a different
level, with no bearing on like or dislike.
But it still pisses me off.
To see the person I love look so
damn happy over another man...
Say, Ayase...
Can't it be me?
Couldn't I ever be your family?
If we lived here together...
B-But...
Sure, you and I are total strangers.
But even your parents
started out as strangers.
That means you can become family
even when not tied by blood, right?
Yes.
Ayase...
Oh! Wait, um...
T-That's right.
There's something I wanted to ask...
What?
We've met before
somewhere, you and l, right?
Please tell me.
I can't remember, and l...
About that...
I'm not telling you.
There's no point unless you
recall these things on your own.
B-But...
No way. But on the other hand,
if you do, I'll make this go away.
What is that?
It's what you owe me.
Even if I make lshii pay
back what he owes me...
...I'll still be in the red for
the amount I bid on you.
But the repayment during
yesterday's showdown...
That's money I earned
putting my life on the line.
It has nothing to do
with your debt to me.
By the way,
I'm charging 10/10 interest.
10/10?
That means
10% interest every 10 days.
You start accruing interest
the day your loan begins...
...so if you borrow
the whole 120 million from me...
...that means you're really
132 million in the red.
In 10 days, the interest is 13 million.
It's 14.6 million after 20 days.
In otherwords, after 30 days, you'll
owe me 57.2 million just in interest.
I'd include interest when I close
the books every 10 days...
...but in your case,
I think I'll give you a break.
Be happy. I rounded off the total.
Understand, Ayase?
I-I can't do it. All that money...
Don't worry about it.
You know you have it.
An amazing potential to earn...
Like I told you before, I'll pay you
500,000 yen each time we have sex.
Wait... Let go of me...
You did a good job.
You even came so many times.
Stop it!
Y-You said we were
going to be family...
Why?
Even family members need to be
scrupulous about money matters.
I should let you know that
"500,000 yen a time"...
...means each time for me.
Just because I confessed my love,
had sex, and started living with you...
...doesn't mean I can ever rest easy.
Boss, Mr. Ayase is here to see you.
Come in.
Because in my case...
Sex
(Rape)
Living
Together
(lncarceration)
Confessed
Love
(I think
I did)
I did everything way, way out of order
Thanks for waiting, Ayase.
What do you want for lunch?
Um, anything's fine with me...
This won't do. He's about to...
Move! Kanoh, when are you...
So this is the young man...
Well... You certainly went for
a type you don't usually go for...
But I admit he's sweet.
U-Um...
Oh my! How rude of me
not to even introduce myself.
Here.
Kaoruko Someya?
Would you like to work at my place?
I've got a shop...
Shut up, you sick tranny!
Ow!
What's wrong?
Can't you just lend him?
I'm not lending him!
I'll seriously kick you off
a high-rise, you queer!
What? You're a homo yourself.
Who is?
You're not?
B-But then why'd you
do all those things to me?
What an intriguing young man...
I really must get my hands on him.
Kanoh here is a homo all right.
He's the kind of man who never
recognized the rights of transvestites.
But here he is with
a crush on a young man.
I really have an obligation
to worship that young man.
Shut the hell up! I'm still not a homo!
Then what are "all those things"?
He's special...
Boss.
What?
A call from Mr. Takanohashi.
You'd better get out, pervert.
You're scaring Ayase...
Oh, look at the time.
Unfortunately, I've got to go.
It was lovely chatting with you.
For me too. I enjoyed it.
Hold it, Someya!
How did I get him to warm
up to me? He's so friendly.
Friendly?
It's true he seems very quiet, so you
need to break the ice somehow...
If I could, I wouldn't
be having a hard time.
That's your punishment for breaking
so many women's hearts.
Faced with one immune to your looks,
body, and money... Serves you right.
Still, if you took away those three
things, I wonder what would be left...
Oh, I know! I'll send
something useful over later.
W-What? Hand it over now.
It's a secret. Later!
Hey!
What's useful about this?
Bastard... Messing with me...
How to Tame Small Animals
I guess I'm not the only one who sees
Ayase as a small creature like this.
Since he's got brown hair,
is small, and has big eyes.
The Smart Way
to Tame Your Pet, Day One.
It's stressful for an animal
to be in a new environment.
Don't touch them or go near them.
As they're very small and delicate,
never treat them with violence.
Day
One:
Rape
It's hopeless then.
Welcome home...
Damn this thing! How can this help?
You were there?
Never
treat
them
with
violence.
T-There was a roach...
I see. Such clean
apartments still have cockroaches...
Huh? This book...
That's from Someya.
Do you have some kind of pet?
Well, I guess.
I can't say it's to help
me get close to you...
Um... may I read this?
Sure.
So cute.
Damn it... He's so sweet looking...
I want to touch him...
kiss him... make love to him...
Ayase...
Don't
touch
them
or
go
near
them
on
the
first
day.
I'm going to the office.
You go on to bed.
Just go to bed, all right?
I can't be with him and not have sex.
Day two.
Your pet still hasn't gotten
used to his new environment.
Ayase...
Yes?
Call him by his name in a gentle voice.
I'll be late again tonight,
so eat without me.
O-Okay.
And in a few days...
Welcome home. You're early today.
No, I just came for a change
of clothes. I'll be heading right back.
I see...
Ayase...
Yes?
After a few days,
you'll be allowed to touch him.
Stroke him gently on
the head and develop affection.
See you.
U-Um...
It's important at this time
not to pursue him too hard.
If I touch him, I'll lose all reason...
The trick is to not ever scare him.
He seems to like
sake more than you'd think.
Hey, do mice and rabbits
drink sake nowadays?
What kind of nonsense is that?
And a few days later...
Welcome home.
Are you going to work again tonight?
No.
If you work hard at it,
your efforts will be rewarded.
I finished up at the office.
He'll start to display trust
and affection towards you.
True, my efforts have been rewarded.
But at a cost. The celibate life
I've been leading for the last few days.
Meaning if this goes on, I'll never...
...get to have a physical
relationship with him.
In which case, there'd be no point!
I could fix you something to eat.
Good idea. I'd like something
light to go with my sake.
Join me.
Um, then just for a little while.
I'll start making it now.
This isn't the time to become
a good-natured owner.
We'll do it tonight for sure.
All I have to do is make
sure I don't scare him.
Just a little more...
I can drink some more...
Hey, don't fall asleep on me yet.
Right there!
Does that feel good?
Yes.
It's hard to believe he normally
flinches from my touch.
Why are you laughing?
I'm so relieved.
He still thinks of me as a kind
owner, even when it comes to this.
I was starting to think that
you were avoiding me, Mr. Kanoh.
We never eat together,
and you always run off somewhere...
That was...
Say it again...
Remember the other day
when you said I was special?
What's he talking about?
That day?
He's special!
I was worried, but since
you said that about me...
Say it one more time...
Sure...
Words I unknowingly said worked
betterthan my efforts these few days?
You're special.
Say it again.
Sure... You're special, very special.
Seriously, you're special.
In more ways than one.
What does that mean?
Just what I said.
Anyway, I think I've seen the light.
What?
I'm done with elaborate
tricks and forced restraint.
It seems it's better to be
straightforward when expressing love.
You threw that book away?
So cruel! I was trying to help...
Don't give me that. You were
having fun messing with me.
There you go again,
taking it the wrong way.
Not that you were totally off the mark...
...but I'm going with the flow.
So you did read it? You fool.
I know what kind of man you are...
Could this also be because of him?
He's not to be sold short.
Say, where's Aya?
Still asleep.
He has a hangover.
When should I have him drink next?
"Going with the flow" is different
from "succumbing to instinct."
I'm never going
to drink alcohol again.
When I opened
the window and spoke to you...
mado o akehanashitara
窓を開け放したら
...I could see that the wintry
night sky was sparkling.
fuyu no yozora ga kirameite ta
冬の夜空がきらめいてた
Could it be that the emotions
of all the people everywhere...
hitobito no omoi subete ga
人々の思いすべてが
...had turned into those stars?
ano hoshi tachi ni natta no ka na
あの星たちになったのかな？
That promise we made so long ago...
toki o koeta ano yakusoku o
時を越えたあの約束を
ima mou dakishimete iru yo
今もう抱きしめているよ
...is something I still
cling tightly to now.
On sleepless nights in my dreams...
nemureru yoru wa yume no naka de aa
眠れる夜は 夢の中で ああ
Even if a single tear falls...
namida hitotsu koborete mo
涙ひとつこぼれても
...I'll never forget that smile.
wasurenai hohoemi o
忘れない微笑を
My beloved,
just keep me warm forever.
itoshii hito yo
愛しい人よ
eien ni nukumori o tsutaete
永遠に温もりを伝えて
Even if I'm caught in a rainfall of grief...
kanashii ame ni utarete mo
悲しい雨に打たれても
...I want to become your love.
anata no ai ni naritai
あなたの愛になりたい