No Money
Living your life is a wonderful thing.
ikiteku koto wa subarashii
生きてく事は素晴らしい
But one step ahead,
I hear there's only darkness.
demo issun saki wa yami rashii
でも一寸先は闇らしい
Art is long. Life is short..
shounen gaku nari ga tashi
少年学成りがたし
Go forward without delay.
sugu ni susume
すぐに進め
Destiny always evens things up.
unmei kashikari wa nashi
運命、貸し借りはなし
And you don't want
regrets in your youth.
seishun koukai ya da shi
青春、後悔嫌だし
I can be your ultimate weapon.
saishuuheiki wa watashi
最終兵器は私
So come on... Yes, yes.
yukuze YES YES
ゆくぜ yes yes
Don't hesitate
over holding this hand of mine.
sono te wo nigirishimeru no ni mayotten na yo
その手を握りしめるのに迷ってんなよ
Because this is
a special God-given chance.
kamisama ga tokubetsu kureta CHANCE dakara
神様が特別くれたチャンスだから
It's romance for sure.
We're sexy men for sure.
zettai ni ROMANCE
絶対にロマンス
zettai ni romensu
絶対色MENっす
If you dare to dream,
it will come true.
yume mireba kanau mono
夢見れば　叶うもの
After this great love of ours...
dekkai na ROMANCE WAY
でっかいなロマンスウェー
...I'm taking you along for the ride.
kimi wo nosete
君を乗せて
It truly is a romance.
The fact is we're sexy men.
jissai ni ROMANCE
実際にロマンス
jittai ni ROMANCE
実態にロマンス
After I've given you this love
that's meant only for you...
kimi dake ni sasageru ai no sube
君だけに捧げる愛の末
...I'll never leave your side again.
mou hitori ni shinai
もう一人にしない
Have you heard
the name Yoshizumi?
He runs a club in
Roppongi as a front.
The master-tape was
stolen from there.
They're desperately trying
to get the tape back.
Say you're sorry!
Mr. Gion!
I'm going to show you...
Y-you!
My daughter...
...who you started a war with!
Episode 4
Put your hands behind
your heads and get down.
Kanoh. You...
Let me tell you.
I don't have a lot of patience.
If you make me wait...
I'll start by cutting off her ear...
...then I'll chop her up till
she doesn't even look human.
No, stop!
Don't hurt my daughter.
What are you doing, you idiot!
Do as you're told!
Y-yes...
You too, hurry up!
Yes...
There, you happy now?
Now let Mika...
Let my daughter go!
She has nothing to do with thi...
Have you already
lost the plot, old man?
What?
Who's the one who got innocent
people involved to begin with?
This is good, Kanoh.
He's lost his mind to sex
and money, he can't remember.
So, Let's make this
a movie party.
Let's let your daughter see
you in all of your glory.
You can't see my face, can you?
You idiot!
Get real!
We have to do that
when we're editing.
You're all over the screen!
The image of you fondling
a boy and drooling.
I-I understand!
I don't care about the master-tape
or the money, so don't say anymore!
Damn you Yoshizumi,
this is all your fault.
What are you going
to do about it!
I was a fool to go along
with a dimwit's stupid plan.
You're useless!
You're just...
Shut up you worthless politician.
I don't care.
What I want to know is...
Ayase...
Y-yes?
Who hit you?
Um...
It's okay.
It didn't...
...really hurt...
So it was you!
Mr. Kanoh, wait!
Mika!
Please stop!
Why?
She has nothing to do with this.
I'm going to make
him suffer like I did.
But...
Have you forgotten
what he put us through!
Do you know what would've
happened if I didn't...
...get here when I did?
I...
But...
She...
...really doesn't...
...have anything to do with this.
And he...
Stop! Don't hurt my daughter!
To her...
...this is her precious father.
I'm sorry.
Please, Mr. Kanoh...
Just go...
Idiot!
This is our chance!
I'm going to kill all of you!
A politician, through and through.
I'll keep him alive
so long as he's useful.
Come and show some respect.
I guess this is
good enough for today.
Shall we go home?
Yes!
What's going on?
I feel so hot.
Ayase...
Are you okay?
The basement...
I see...
I made it out of there.
Yes...
I-I'm sorry...
So you don't like it?
Being touched by me...
Huh?
It's going to make you feel good.
You don't have a choice.
Fine...
No...
If you don't want me around, I'll leave.
I'm just going to take you home.
Okay?
I have to tell him...
The truth...
I can't...
If I say something now...
I have no idea what will come out.
Do you want something to drink?
I see.
If you need anything, call me.
I'll be up.
What!
What did you just say?
Ayase...
Don't go!
Please...
P-please...
I...
Ayase...
Is it that bad?
The drugs?
I'm sorry.
I dragged you into this.
Just now...
I...
What...
Drugs?
I don't think there'll
be any side effects.
Ayase.
I'm sorry, it's nothing.
I can't believe this.
I did something...
What was I trying
to say just now?
Really, it's nothing.
After all the rejections...
I can't bear it anymore.
Really...
I'm depending on him
because of the situation.
I'm sorry.
I'm the worst.
Listen, Ayase...
It's the drugs.
Nothing you said or did has
anything to do with who you are.
And when you wake up...
...know that this is all
because of a horrible man.
It's not your fault.
So...
There's no need to
feel bad or ashamed.
That's what you think, but...
Mr. Kanoh...
You don't dislike me?
Of course not,
what are you saying?
Even if you...
...see me at my worst?
Where's this coming from?
Come on, those are my lines!
Huh?
Huh nothing!
It may be a little
late for this, but...
I'm hundreds of times
worse than you!
But you just said
I wasn't like them.
Mr. Kanoh...
You were nice to me...
You were saved.
But back then...
I was mad at myself for not
being able to say it right.
With me beforehand...
Not even that...
Ayase...
Are you okay?
Because of him...
...everything is falling apart.
Even the shell
I've been hiding in...
Yes...
The pain goes with it, but...
It won't get rid of the
doubts or the confusion, but...
I think I can change.
Little by little...
Wow, that looks good!
Are you trying to pick
a fight with me, Gion?
Huh? You don't like sweets?
Oh, don't worry about it.
I bought them for you, Aya.
But you're in worse
shape than I am.
Don't worry about him, Ayase.
This idiot is a glutton for punishment.
Yep!
Otherwise I wouldn't
survive hanging out with...
...immoral, corrupt money lenders.
I bet they're really close.
Hello?
Sure.
Another cup?
Thank you.
I can't believe how
different things are.
Huh?
Mr. Kanoh.
In the past, it would
have been unimaginable.
It's like he's more humane.
I bet it's your influence.
Considering his
line of work, though...
...I'm not sure if
it's a good thing.
But I still like him
better this way.
Mr. Gion...
Hey!
You were talking
about me, weren't you?
Um... er...
We were! We were!
About how much you like Aya!
M-Mr. Gion!
Huh?
You're just getting it?
Little late, isn't it?
I had no idea.
To be told in front
of other people...
Hey!
You didn't just
get it too, did you?
I'm so embarrassed.
Hey!
Why are you looking away!
I had no idea...
My eyes were blind.
I am as sorry as the
ocean is deep for saying...
...I didn't want to film
Loveless hanky-panky.
And so, you two,
here's one more chance.
This time, let me capture
some loving hanky-panky.
What are you going to do?
Oh, come on, Aya!
I'll make it look really nice.
I swear it won't
get out there.
It's only for the personal
pursuit of beautiful aesthetics.
What are you doing, Bro?
You could knock this
door down in one kick.
I bet you'd do it for
three hundred million yen.
I won't do it!
Aya, open up!
Open the door!
No Money
Side Story
And?
What's with the get up?
What are you talking
about, President Kanoh?
I'm dressed up, that's all.
I'm proving how serious I am. Yep!
I've come again to request
that you be in my video!
Wait, Aya!
Please, just take a
glance at the proposal.
If I may say so myself,
it's a good, heart-felt story!
I admit, I don't have
three million to pay you, but...
Money isn't everything, Aya.
I don't want it anyway!
What?
Really, you'll do it for free?
You're such a man, Aya!
That's not what I mean.
The time period is
the Taisho-era?
Yes, the Taisho-era.
A cold-hearted banker and a young
man whose nobility is crumbling.
It's their tragic love story.
Wow, look at this mansion!
Damn that Loan shark.
With money he swindled...
Hey, don't dawdle! Hurry up!
You're so useless.
No, there were things
you were good at.
There's no accounting
for people's tastes.
To think he will erase
our debt in exchange for...
...a part barbarian mutt like you.
Come on, Let's go.
You're happy too, right?
You've been a weight
around the family's neck...
...and now you get to pay
us back for bringing you up.
Right, Yukia?
Are they here?
Yes, they are waiting
for you in the back room.
I see.
Um...
I'm Ayase Yukia.
It's nice to...
Don't be so nervous.
You're not here
as an employee.
There was a time
when they connected...
...because of the trap
that Kanoh set.
Hang on, Ayase,
where are you going?
I-I have to save everyone!
What are you talking about?
They sold you to
pay back their debt!
That may be, but
this is too horrible!
It was always your
intention to ruin the Ishii's!
Because Ken Ishii was
forced into filing bankruptcy.
And so what?
They all deserve to die!
B-but...
Their relationship took a turn.
The rest of it is about breaking him in!
What's so heartfelt about this?
It's a story that hits the heart
and the groin. It's a good story.
Isn't it?
Besides, how are you going
to shoot a period piece?
You don't have a cent.
Lend it to me.
No.
Rejection
Proposal
And this storyline is awfully familiar.
Come on, you love it!
Edo-style confinement, obi's, woo!
I could do that
whenever I wanted to.
Oh, so you prefer something
that is totally fantastical?
Fine, leave it to me!
If you let me film you,
I'll do anything!
Tell me what you want, in detail.
In detail?
Let's see...
Welcome home.
I'll make some dinner.
Sure.
You've had a long day.
This is a scene from
your fantastical scenario?
Are you okay, Mr. Kanoh?
How about this for an
unrealistic situation?
Money, money, money, money...
And all of these Aya's...
...love Mr. Kanoh!
Mr. Kanoh, Mr. Kanoh,
Mr. Kanoh, Mr. Kanoh...
What, is it that unlikely
that Ayase would like me?
It was totally wrong right
from the "Money, money!" part.
I-I thought it was cute.
W-well, let me hear
what you want, Aya.
But I...
It's not necessarily
going to get made.
Just tell me what you'd want.
It can be anything.
Uh... er...
I'm home!
It's cold out there.
You were at school late!
Youngest Brother
Toranosuke
Welcome home.
Middle Brother Homare
Eldest Brother
Misao
What nice brothers.
Welcome home.
Tonight we're having
your favorite, hot pot.
Mother
Someya
A loving mother.
Go wash your hands.
Oh, and get your father.
Okay!
Dinner's ready!
I'll be right there.
Kitty
$250,000.
Father
Somuku Kanoh
Hey, who's the father, huh?
Fine then, I'll break
you in the old school way!
Hang on!
What a turn of events!
This is good, Bro!
Huh?
The father sexually
abuses the fourth son!
And the oldest and
second sons join in!
The mother is a transvestite!
This is an adult film that
cuts to the heart of...
...societal issues
surrounding the modern family!
And the title!
Daddy's Sex Ed
Daddy's Sex Ed!
No!
Rejection
The End
When I opened the window
and spoke to you...
mado o akehanashitara
窓を開け放したら
...I could see that the
wintry, night sky was sparkling.
fuyu no yozora ga kirameite ta
冬の夜空がきらめいてた
Could it be that the emotions
of all the people everywhere...
hitobito no omoi subete ga
人々の思いすべてが
...had turned into those stars?
ano hoshi tachi ni natta no ka na
あの星たちになったのかな？
toki o koeta ano yakusoku o
時を越えたあの約束を
That promise we made so long ago...
ima mou dakishimete iru yo
今もう抱きしめているよ
...is something I still
cling tightly to now.
On sleepless nights in my dreams...
nemureru yoru wa yume no naka de aa
眠れる夜は 夢の中で ああ
Even if a single tear falls...
namida hitotsu koborete mo
涙ひとつこぼれても
wasurenai hohoemi o
忘れない微笑を
...I'll never forget that smile.
itoshii hito yo
愛しい人よ
My beloved, just keep me warm forever.
eien ni nukumori o tsutaete
永遠に温もりを伝えて
Even if I'm caught
in a rainfall of grief...
kanashii ame ni utarete mo
悲しい雨に打たれても
...I want to become your love.
anata no ai ni naritai
あなたの愛になりたい