No Money!
ikiteku koto wa subarashii
生きてく事は素晴らしい
Living your life is a wonderful thing.
demo issun saki wa yami rashii
でも一寸先は闇らしい
But one step ahead,
I hear there's only darkness.
shounen gaku nari ga tashi
少年学成りがたし
Art is long. Life is short.
Go forward without delay.
sugu ni susume
すぐに進め
Destiny always evens things up.
unmei kashikari wa nashi
運命、貸し借りはなし
And you don't want
regrets in your youth.
seishun koukai ya da shi
青春、後悔嫌だし
saishuuheiki wa watashi
最終兵器は私
I can be your ultimate weapon.
So come on... Yes, yes.
yukuze YES YES
ゆくぜ yes yes
Don't hesitate...
sono te wo nigirishimeru no ni mayotten na yo
その手を握りしめるのに迷ってんなよ
...over holding this hand of mine.
Because this is
a special God-given chance.
kamisama ga tokubetsu kureta CHANCE dakara
神様が特別くれたチャンスだから
It's romance for sure.
We're sexy men for sure.
zettai ni ROMANCE
絶対にロマンス
zettai ni romensu
絶対色MENっす
yume mireba kanau mono
夢見れば　叶うもの
If you dare to dream, it will come true.
After this great love of ours...
dekkai na ROMANCE WAY
でっかいなロマンスウェー
...I'm taking you along for the ride.
kimi wo nosete
君を乗せて
It truly is a romance.
The fact is we're sexy men.
jissai ni ROMANCE
実際にロマンス
jittai ni ROMANCE
実態にロマンス
After I've given you this love
that's meant only for you...
kimi dake ni sasageru ai no sube
君だけに捧げる愛の末
...I'll never leave your side again.
mou hitori ni shinai
もう一人にしない
Our next product is of mixed blood.
He's a college student
and somewhat older...
...but look at his finely textured skin.
His soft chestnut-colored hair.
And the fine features of his face.
It's rare to see this level of quality.
Needless to say, he has never been
taken from behind. Nor frontally.
The lucky winner of the bid should
feel free to examine him personally.
Shall we start at 50 million?
100!
We've just heard 100 million.
Are there any other bids?
Is that the final bid?
It seems so.
Then for 100 million...
120 million!
120 million.
All in cash.
Episode 1
Um... are you all right?
That voice of his...
You seem to be hurt...
That hand of his...
If you'd like, I'll lend you my...
How he rescued me
from the depths of despair...
You're awake now?
W-Where am l?
You okay?
Those bastards... Pumping you
full of those damned drugs...
Should I call a doctor?
I'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
I'll get you something to drink.
Excuse me...
W-What is it?
I-I'm sorry.
I just wanted to thank you...
Thank me?
Um... you saved me, didn't you?
Uh... yes.
I don't know how to thank you...
After you've been so kind to me...
So good to a stranger like me...
Huh?
Hold on... What did he say just now?
Stranger?
Y-You mean you don't remember?
I was shoved into
a car all of a sudden...
And then...
H-Hey, if you move...
I'm sorry...
I'm so dizzy...
L-Like I said, you've still
got drugs in your system!
I remember.
That day, Tetsuo...
my cousin was there too.
They might still be holding
him captive in that restaurant!
That's not it.
You should remember the guy
right in front of you first.
You mean Tetsuo lshii, right?
You know him?
Yeah, very well.
You mean you're a friend of Tetsuo's?
Read this.
Just read it.
I'm a loan shark,
and lshii is one of my clients.
He pinched about
three million and ran off.
Pinched?
He borrowed money.
But...
Debt Report (individual)
From this Axi place too?
He borrowed all these millions?
It appears to be a yakuza-run casino.
As an amateur, he must've gotten
carried away and gotten scammed.
You were auctioned off by Axi
as collateral for lshii's debt.
Then Tetsuo also...
No way! No one in the universe
is eccentric enough to take him...
Well, a guy like that... It's not like
he doesn't have viable body parts.
Liver... kidneys... corneas...
If you sold them piecemeal,
you'd make some money.
I've got to go save him.
What are you talking about? Hey!
Don't you get it? Ishii sold
you off to save his own skin!
He'd never do that... We're cousins...
So what? There are countless
people who'd sell off their relatives!
But...
Stay away from lshii.
You'll just get hurt if you get involved.
I'm telling you this for your own good!
But Tetsuo is my only...
Tetsuo, Tetsuo...
You can deny it, but you can't ignore
the fact lshii doesn't care about you!
No!
Face up to it!
You were used and betrayed!
That it'd be better
for you if that bastard died!
No!
You're wrong!
Ayase...
You...
Shut up! You don't know anything...
It has nothing to do with you...
You're just a stranger...
Nothing to do with me...
Stranger...
You're wrong.
You and I have a stronger bond
than blood between us, don't we?
Ouch!
You still don't get
the position you're in, huh?
I bought you.
Ouch...
Don't you know what
your intended purpose was...
...and who became your owner?
I-intended purpose?
You can't move around much
till the drugs wear off anyway.
You might as well enjoy yourself too.
Let me teach you...
This time around,
so you won't forget...
No...
No!
I know you're a virgin...
...so I'm being gentle, see?
No... No...
I've got to get you conditioned...
If you don't want
to feel any pain, just lie there.
What are you doing?
I can't take any more...
Why?
We're both men...
How can we? It's not right...
Abnormal, you mean?
Who are you to talk?
A man's hand is lifting you
up from behind like this...
Giving you another erection right
away... What does that make you?
I just let you come orally too.
Be honest.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Men doing men... abnormal?
You don't have to tell me. I know that.
Whenever I made love
to you in my mind...
...I thought the same thing
myself over and over.
But none of that really matters.
Abnormal or not...
...I want you!
All of you!
I told you to relax.
What am I doing?
Ayase!
I thought you were
going to cherish him...
So that he'd never get hurt.
I'd protect him myself...
Yet look at what I'm doing...
What did I want...
What did I really want...
Please... I beg of you...
Let me go home...
I've got to go or Tetsuo will... Tetsuo...
I'd be happy to set you free.
On condition that
my money is returned.
The money lshii borrowed
and the money paid for you.
It's 200 million including expenses.
Starting today, I'll let you shoulder it.
But...
Until it's paid in full, you belong to me.
You want to be free, don't you?
What am I saying?
He's forgotten and rejected you,
but you'll still struggle for him?
But 200 million...
Don't worry about it. I'll let you earn it.
Right... If it means I can make
you mine, I'll just bind you to me.
Whether it's by money or whatever...
Starting today, I'll buy that body of
yours for 500,000 yen each time.
He says he'll use
his house as collateral.
The land isn't bad,
but the registry is highly questionable.
It's not worth discussing.
Any other way of collecting?
Yes, there's some real
estate in Kamakura as well.
Damn it... It's left such a bad taste.
But Ayase's to blame too.
Trusting a scumbag like Tetsuo
just because they're cousins.
I take it we should deny him more
funds and try to collect the total soon?
Hi! Miss Kaoruko
has come to pay her debt!
There's nothing besides
the land in Kamakura?
There is, but that's the only thing
we can wring money out of.
The factory...
Hey! Why are you
ignoring me like that?
Is that how you treat childhood
friends? I mean I'm a client!
Creepy transvestites
shouldn't act like clients!
Creepy? If you can't see my beauty,
run to the eye doctor right this second.
You run to a shrink!
Anyway, what are you doing here?
Forgive me. I tried to stop her...
...but Ms. Someya insisted on
meeting with you face to face.
Kuba, no sugar in my coffee, okay?
I'm sorry. I've been ordered not
to serve you anything but salt water.
Hey, come to think of it,
you two are related, right?
Yes. I suppose.
Since we're twins.
Hypothetically, let's say one of you
was actually an evil bastard...
...and was feeding off the other.
I said hypothetically.
The victim hasn't realized he's being
scammed, and out of kindness...
...I expose the evil brother.
So between the scumbag relative
and the well-meaning stranger...
...which would you trust?
Well-meaning? Are you serious?
How can I answer someone who
looks like he just killed 2 or 3 people?
Well, it's true in
this line of business...
...it's not uncommon
to see family quarrels.
Actually, it's often because they're
related that their hatred grows.
But it's human nature...
...to tend to believe in your
relatives even if you're aware of that, right?
Why?
A man who's never
impressed by anything...
A man who has
no compassion for his kin...
A man who's merciless
to traitors, family or not...
It's pointless.
"Human empathy" means nothing to them
I'm done for the day.
Kuba, collect that tranny's
money and get her out of here.
And about that loan... Give it to him.
Are you sure?
But make him bring his daughter
on board as a co-signer.
Since ultimately,
we can make money off women.
His company won't
last another two months.
Cover him and set
him up for the right time...
...and clean him out for all he's got.
If he refuses, tell him
we're collecting in full.
Got that?
Yeah...
Something's not right.
What isn't?
Kanoh's not himself.
It's just women's intuition, but...
I don't see a woman
anywhere in this room.
Because normally, he's more...
He has no vulnerabilities,
and he's hard to approach, right?
That Kanoh...
His work's as flawless as ever.
But he does seem somewhat
distracted in the office...
Also, did you see
that scar by his eye?
That man's like
a walking lethal weapon...
Who in the world did that to him?
Now that you mention it, even
his visualizations were true to form.
Even if you're dumped in
Tokyo Bay, I won't rescue you.
In any case, I've got to create an
environment conducive to calm talks.
Whatever you do,
try not to scare him...
Approach him in a gentle manner...
For some reason, I'm starting
to feel like I'm taming a wild animal...
Like a chipmunk or
a flying squirrel, a small creature.
Are you well enough to be up?
I'm sorry...
Careful! Don't touch it!
Hey, did you cut
yourself somewhere?
You can't even bear to be touched?
U-Um... I'll clean it up right away...
No sense in talking...
If it's come to this, then taking
him by force is the only way...
No good... Then it'll be
the same as last night.
I don't want that again...
It's all right. Let me take a look.
We've got to take care of it.
You...
Touch.
Idiot! You've got a high fever!
What were you walking
around for? Stay in bed!
But the glass...
Shut up!
I'll get something to reduce
that fever. Lie there.
Okay.
Damn it. Where is it?
I know it's somewhere...
I never take medicine myself, so...
U-Um, you don't
have to worry about me.
I'm used to getting fevers like this...
That's even worse!
Queer
I'm busy right now!
When will you ever get that?
Call me like this again and I'll peel
your skin off, you damn queer!
Found it!
W-What's going on?
I-I found it, Ayase...
What am l, an idiot?
I could've saved time by sending out
for medicine instead of looking for it.
One pill per dose.
What the hell's
the matter with me, anyway?
Don't take it yet.
Just do as I say. Hold on a minute.
Eat that.
It says you shouldn't take
this on an empty stomach.
You haven't eaten anything
since yesterday, right?
At least take a bite...
Like he'd eat now.
Well, you don't have to force yourself.
Oh no...
T-Thank you very much.
I've been on my own awhile...
So having someone take care
of me like this when I'm sick...
It's been a long time.
It's the first time
ever for me, you know.
Taking care of someone like this.
Oh, but that stuff is supposed
to be for human consumption.
There's nothing toxic either...
I'll have some.
What's going on?
I thought he was freaked out
and wary, but now all of a sudden...
What a weird kid.
Then again, I guess
I must be pretty weird myself.
Getting nervous that I'm saying the
wrong thing and getting carried away...
I'm going back to the office for now.
Get some rest, all right?
Um...
What?
I'm so sorry.
That scar by your eye. I really...
Yes?
Yes...
What?
What the hell?
Ishii!
Ishii?
Tetsuo! Is that Tetsuo?
Please let me talk to him!
Better not.
He won't give you good news.
Tetsuo?
Y-Yukiya?
Tetsuo... Where are you now?
Help me! They still have me!
They might be planning to kill me!
That's good to hear.
If your life can restore our
stolen money, it's a small price to pay.
Make sure they waste you
in a way that'll be profitable.
Let go...
Before that though, let me talk
to him. He's there, isn't he?
There's no way you
could've found out this number.
Okay, got it.
Don't tell me you still trust that lshii?
Think about it.
If it were you, would you lure
your loved ones back into danger?
The truth is I did think something
was wrong more than once...
Even this time around, I did
suspect that I was being deceived...
But I have no other family
besides the lshii family...
And I couldn't believe Tetsuo would...
I just didn't want to think about it.
Believing in your
relatives is human nature...
No...
Ayase wants to believe in him.
By calling someone his relative...
He's trying to cling to that.
Does it scare you?
Admitting that you're all alone?
If you still want to see lshii...
...I can make it happen.
Really?
Yes.
If I were lshii, I'd never
leave him on his own...
But Ayase needs
someone right now...
...and it isn't me.
Are you ready?
Uh, yes.
Get in.
O-Okay.
The president...
...is getting the door for someone?
Um...
Thank you very much.
Boss, are you really sure about this?
I'm sure that casino's people won't
let him get away unscathed this time...
Probably not.
Let's go.
Then I'll send him to a place where
he has no one to rely on but me.
mado o akehanashitara
窓を開け放したら
When I opened
the window and spoke to you...
...I could see that the wintry
night sky was sparkling.
fuyu no yozora ga kirameite ta
冬の夜空がきらめいてた
Could it be that the emotions
of all the people everywhere...
hitobito no omoi subete ga
人々の思いすべてが
ano hoshi tachi ni natta no ka na
あの星たちになったのかな？
...had turned into those stars?
toki o koeta ano yakusoku o
時を越えたあの約束を
That promise we made so long ago...
ima mou dakishimete iru yo
今もう抱きしめているよ
...is something I still
cling tightly to now.
nemureru yoru wa yume no naka de aa
眠れる夜は 夢の中で ああ
On sleepless nights in my dreams...
Even if a single tear falls...
namida hitotsu koborete mo
涙ひとつこぼれても
wasurenai hohoemi o
忘れない微笑を
...I'll never forget that smile.
itoshii hito yo
愛しい人よ
My beloved,
just keep me warm forever.
永遠に温もりを伝えて
eien ni nukumori o tsutaete
kanashii ame ni utarete mo
悲しい雨に打たれても
Even if I'm caught in a rainfall of grief...
anata no ai ni naritai
...I want to become your love.
あなたの愛になりたい