I started to live alone this spring, and
by now I'm pretty much used to it.
I was a little lonely at first,
but recently I stopped feeling so.
If you ask why...
Hey, good morning, Yuuto.
Morning, Yuuto-kun.
Good morning, Megumi-san and Anna-san.
Yuu-kun, good morning.
Good morning, Mako-san.
Yuu-kun, is it okay we start the your
birthday party this evening?
Yes, thank you.
I didn't expect that you'd even celebrate my birthday.
It's fine. You are helping with our kids, after all.
Yeah, you don't have to be so reserved.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I'll take out everyone's garbage then.
Oh my, then I guess I'll get your help then.
Thanks for doing it all the time.
I'll bring lots of good food tonight.
Have a safe trip!
Yes.
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Madam Was Once a Slut
To Yuuto-kun who has helped so much with our kids,
to Yuuto-kun who would help with the tough
work while our husbands are away,
with thanks and congratulations for your birthday,
Cheers!
I'm happy that they came to celebrate my birthday,
but they're always treating me like
a child, instead of a man, so...
it's a little sad, too.
It's been a while since I've drank,
I think it's getting at me.
Geez, Megumi really can't drink much.
You've always been that way.
It only takes one sip of vodka for Megu-chan to...
Hey! Why do we keep talking about
my embarrassing stories...
Oh by the way... are you sure you don't want to spend
your birthday with your girlfriend or something?
Huh? I, don't have a girlfriend...
Calm down, are you okay, Yuuto-kun?
You look like you’d be popular amongst girls though.
Right? Yuu-kun’s so cute.
Why don't you have a girlfriend?
No, I'm not popular at all...
Besides, girls at the same age just don't attract me...
I think I would want someone older and...
To Yuuto-kun, so this year he will finally get a girlfriend.
Cheers!
Megumi, we'll leave the rest to you.
Goodnight, Yuu-kun!
Megumi-san, let me help.
You're the birthday star today, just sit back and relax.
But, I feel like should be helping...
Geez, you know you can be childish
and self-indulged for today.
Okay...
Geez, Yuuto is such a good child,
I have to give you a reward.
I'll do something for you as your birthday present.
Although you might not want an
unmannerly old wife like me...
You can ask for a massage, or to use my
legs as a pillow, or anything you want
Isn't there something you’d like me to do?
Something... I want you to do...
I want you to...
I would like Megumi-san to help
me graduate from virginity!
Eh?
Don't joke around!
Wait... stop...!
I'm not joking around.
I want to... with Megumi-san...
Are you serious?
I want to have my first sex experience!
The bed... on the bed, okay?
Right, I should shower.
There's nothing on Megumi-san that could be dirty.
You idiot...
We’re just getting started here, you know.
I'm an old lady already, so if you get disappointed
at my body that's too bad.
Megumi-san is still very young!
Hey, it's embarrassing if I'm the only one alone.
Take your clothes off, too.
Huh?... Yes.
You...
I didn't think you'd have such a large
one judging by the cute face of yours.
Is that so?
It Yeah, I'm pretty sure it’s a great one.
Hmm, the smell of a man.
Megumi-san! Please... please teach
me how to get rid of my virginity.
Right, leave it to me.
Well then, come over.
You can touch it, but be gentle.
Woah...being touched by someone...
I haven’t had this sensation... in so long...
There... slowly... there... that's right...
You can try... putting... your finger in...
My pussy... my pussy hole feels good!
Amazing...Megumi-san is sucking onto my finger...
Don't say something... like that!
Yuuto, don’t! Your finger, you don't...
You can take it out now!
This is finally happening. Ready?
Yes...
Since it is your first time, if you
want to do it raw, you can.
Want to do it raw?
Yes. I want to... do it raw...
Thanks for being honest.
Here, this is the hole that will make Yuuto a man.
Come in.
Move your hips...slowly in like that...
Try moving now.
That's right... it's fine if you start slow...
Are you used to it now?
It’s amazing.
I'm... having sex with... Megumi-san...
That's right... we can't go back to being
normal neighbours anymore...
We don't have to go back.
I want you to... look at me as...
a sex partner... from now on...
Then, you have to work harder for it.
C'mon, show me your manliness!
Yes!
Amazing...It's... fitting perfectly... it's stirring inside...!
Megumi-san... I’m going to move more.
If you're that rough... I won't be able to hold back!
Don't...! Too rough... I can't...
Your dick is driving me crazy!
My pussy is being messed up...
Darling, I'm sorry! My pussy feels good!
It hasn't felt so good in so long!
Megumi-san, I'm cumming!
Inside! Inside, I wanted inside!
Drench my pussy with Yuuto's semen!
Cumming!
Me, too! My pussy is cumming, too!
My pussy is cumming! I'm cumming
from being creampied!
Cumming, cumming... my pussy is cumming!
I'm remembering this feeling... of
having my pussy being filled...
You're making me no good as a mom...
You monster...
Making an old lady remember the
pleasures of being a woman...
I'll make you take responsibility.
Coming!
By the way, Yuuto-kun, I wanted to ask something.
Yes? What is it?
Did your first sex feel good?
Wh-what, what, what are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me, we all know already.
Megu-chan was letting crying like an animal.
The soundproof in this apartment is pretty good,
but Megumi's voice last night was just too loud.
I'm sorry...
It's unfair that Megumi gets the cute Yuuto-kun to herself.
That's right.
You gotta share the good food with everyone, right?
I wanted to have you for myself,
but, it can't be helped, so...
Please be... a cock shared between us, Yuuto.
Like this, my hot, hot summer vacation
with three wives began.
I finished cleaning up.
I even asked such a weird request this morning...
Go take a bath.
Okay.
Kouta's asleep, too.
Geez, at least let me wash off my sweat!
The smell of Megumi-san's sweat... is really good...
Stupid, what are you saying...
Yuuto, your tongue is dangerous...
This is bad... this is...
You can't lick that much!
See... you made me squirt...
Hurry and stick... your dick inside me!
It's here! Yuuto's dick!
Megumi-san's insides... are wrapping around me...
Don't you dare cum yet! You have to thrust more!
It feels good! Cock! Cock!
I've been wanting it... since this
morning, I've been wanting this!
Cock! I wanted Yuuto's cock!
No... I... said such embarrassing things...
Forget that...
Megumi-san, me too...
Yuuto...
I has always thinking about doing
it with Megumi-san again!
Stupid! You pervert! If you say that... I'll get turned on!
You wanted my cock too, didn't you, Megumi-san?
You wanted to do it with me, too, right?
I did! My pussy wanted you!
Yuuto! Yuuto!
Are you cumming again? Are you filling
me up with your semen again?
It's happening I'm being filled up!
My insides are getting soaked!
You're filling up my insides again!
Yuuto’s cock... is amazing...
I'll be visiting you today.
Good day to you, Yuuto-kun.
Looks like you know what I came here to do today.
Yuuto-kun's is pretty amazing...
I'm looking forward to it.
I hear that Yuuto-kun’s penis is incredible.
As expected from the young. I'm digging in.
You came lots, it's so nice to be young.
I'm liking Yuuto-kun more and more.
Geez, Yuuto-kun really looks tasty.
Here, I'm eating you.
This is it! Being ravaged by a cock...!
Yuuto-kun, that's a great expression!
Here, it'll going to feel even better.
I haven't had sex in so long, this is great!
Hey, Yuuto-kun!
Geez, Yuuto-kun...
Your dick is reaching so deep!
Anna-san, I'm going to ejaculate!
Then ejaculate! I want it!
My slut pussy is really feeling good!
I'm feeling it from a young man's piston!
My pussy... so full...
I'll make you take lots of responsibility for
waking up my slutty pussy from now on.
Take care!
I'm sorry, Yuu-kun, getting you
to even look after the kids.
It's fine. Your husband is really busy,
and Mako-san has always taken...
Expecting something?
We're finally alone, after all.
I'm also at my limit wanting to do it with Yuu-kun.
Mako-san!
In the change-room, okay?
I got really wet just thinking that I'd
be able to have sex with Yuu-kun.
Amazing, it's such a dirty pussy.
Then please stick Yuu-kun's young
penis into this dirty pussy!
Yes.
This, this is it! Your dick is all the way inside!
Hurry and move!
Then both of us can feel better and better.
Okay.
You're so young, but your technique is great!
Did the others teach you?
Mako-san's insides feel too good!
Yuu-kun's dick is great, too!
I'd give it 100/100!
Yes! Yes!
You're great, Yuu-kun, keep going!
I want Mako-san to feel better!
No, don't! If you try even harder than
this, my hips will give away!
I can't, I can't...!
My body is so hot... it’s hot!
Make me cum, make me cum!
Bring my pussy to ecstasy with Yuu-kun's dick!
My pussy! Fill my pussy with semen!
Mako-san is such a bad wife.
Letting out such lewd voices while
your kids aren't around.
Yuu-kun's a bad boy, too!
You're thrusting me as if trying to get me pregnant!
You've got such a cute face, but you're a beast!
You're an animal...
I'm cumming, I'm really cumming!
I'm gonna cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Cumming, cumming. Cumming!
Me, too. I'm cumming!
I let you make me cum with your creampie...
I came really hard...
Yuu-kun, from now on, please look after
not only theirs but also my pussy...
Hey, good morning, Yuuto.
Morning, Yuuto-kun.
Yuu-kun, good morning.
Good morning!
Huh? That's...!
Yeah, it's the uniform from Slut Academy...
Eh? Megumi, too?
Mako-san, too?!
Geez, don't tease!
Is it really okay to dress like this?
We're wearing this for Yuuto's sake, you know.
That's right. Look.
Yuuto-kun's personal semen hole
Let's all get along well.