www.SubDESU-H.net
Since I started living alone in the spring I've grown quite used to it.
At first, it was a little lonely,
but lately, I've stopped feeling that way.
That's because...
Hey, good morning, Yuuto.
Morning, Yuuto-kun.
Good morning, Megumi-san, Anna-san.
Yuu-kun, morning.
Good morning, Mako-san.
Yuu-kun, is it all right to have your birthday party in the evening?
Yes, thank you very much.
I didn't expect to have my birthday celebrated at all.
Don't worry about it, you've been taking care of our kids, after all.
She's right, there's no need to feel reserved about it.
Thank you very much, really.
I'll take out the garbage for you all.
My, my, I suppose we'll take you up on your offer.
Thanks as always.
We'll have a feast waiting for you tonight.
Have a safe trip.
Okay.
SubDESU-H Presents
Former Sluts Housewives
Now then, to Yuuto who's always looking after our kids for us...
To Yuuto-kun who helps out whenever our husbands
aren't around to do the heavy lifting...
With our feelings of gratitude and in celebration of your birthday...
cheers!
I'm happy they're willing to celebrate my birthday with me,
but getting doted on like this makes me,
feel like they don't see me as a man,
so I can't fully appreciate it.
It's been so long that I'm feeling tipsy already.
Megumi, you're a real lightweight, aren't you?
Same as always, right? Just a sip of a can
of Chu-hi was enough for Megu-chan.
H-Hey... Why are we only talking about
my embarrassing episodes?
That reminds me...
Your birthday's only a once-a-year event, so shouldn't
you be spending it with your girlfriend?
H-Huh? I don't even have a girlfriend.
There, there... Are you okay, Yuuto-kun?
You seem like you'd be popular.
Yeah. Yuu-kun's cute, after all.
I wonder why you don't have a girlfriend.
No, I'm not popular at all.
Besides, girls my age don't really catch my eye.
Personally, an older woman...
In hopes of Yuuto getting a girlfriend now that he's a year older...
Cheers!
Megumi, we'll leave the rest to you.
Yuu-kun, good night.
Megumi-san, I'll help out.
The birthday boy should just relax.
But I'd feel bad otherwise!
Honestly, today's the day for you to be selfish, you know?
Y-Yeah.
Jeez. I suppose I should reward you for being such a good boy.
I'll do something for your as a birthday present.
Y-You may not be satisfied with a tactless mother like me though.
Whether it's a massage or a lap pillow, anything goes.
Isn't there something you want?
Something I want?
Something I want...
I-I...
I want you... to take my virginity.
Huh?
Huh? Are you being serious?
H-Hey... Sto-
I'm not joking.
I... want to...
Really?
I want to have sex for the first time.
O-On the bed...
On the bed, okay?
Th-That's right. We need to take a shower.
There's no bit of you that needs washing.
Idiot...
The main course is coming up.
I'm an old woman now,
so don't blame me if you're disappointed with my figure.
You're still young in my books, Megumi-san.
It's embarrassing if it's just me.
You strip too.
Huh?
O-Oh, okay.
Come on.
Y-You...
Your cute face had me fooled, you know.
R-Really?
Yeah. I think it's amazing.
A man's smell.
M-Megumi-san, p-please teach me how to... lose my virginity.
O-Okay. Leave it to me.
All right, come here.
Feel free to touch, but be gentle.
Oh no, the feeling of getting touched by someone...
It's been so long.
That spot's good. Be gentle.
It's good. Try putting a finger in.
My pussy... My pussy feels so good.
Wow, you're sucking my fingers in.
I don't need to hear that.
Yuuto, time out.
Your finger... That's enough, so pull it out.
It's the moment you've been waiting for.
Are you ready?
Yes.
It's your first time,
so if you want you can do it raw.
Want to do it raw?
Yes. I want to do it raw.
Being honest is good.
Here, this is the spot that'll make you into a man.
Put it in.
Just like that... Push your hips forward slowly.
Okay, now do your best to move.
You can take it slow at first.
Gotten used to it?
This is amazing.
I'm... having sex with you.
You sure are.
We can't go back to being just neighbors anymore.
That's fine with me.
I want you to see me as a sex partner from now on.
You'll have to try harder then.
Come on, show me your manly side.
Okay!
Wow, y-you're...
spreading me out... to fit you.
Me-Megumi-san, I'm gonna take it up a notch.
If you keep going, I won't be able to control myself.
You're being so rough... No, I can't...
Not there!
Your dick is stirring me up inside!
My pussy's going crazy!
Dear, I'm so sorry.
It just feels so good.
It's been so long!
Megumi-san, I can't hold out.
Inside...
Do it inside.
Fill up my pussy with a load of your cum!
I'm coming.
Me too. I'm coming too.
My pussy is cumming too.
I'm almost there. I'm gonna cum from getting cummed into!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! My pussy is cumming!
This feeling of getting my pussy filled up...
It's so nostalgic.
Oh no, I'm going to get pregnant.
You beast.
Making a mother like me remember the joys of being a woman...
Take responsibility for this, okay?
Oh, coming!
Yuuto-kun, there's something I've been wanting to ask.
Y-Yes? What is it?
Did your first time feel good?
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?
Playing dumb won't work.
The beans have already been spilled.
Megu-chan was moaning like she was in heat, after all.
This apartment's properly soundproofed, but
Megumi was being a little too loud last night.
I'm sorry.
It's not fair for Megumi to monopolize Yuuto-kun like that.
That's right.
We should all share our treats, okay?
I wanted to have you to myself, but I guess there's no avoiding it.
Let the three of us share your penis, Yuuto.
And so, my hot, hot summer with three housewives began.
I've finished cleaning up.
Earlier I asked you something weird...
Go and take a bath now.
Okay,
Kouta's already asleep anyway.
Jeez, let me wash away my sweat first will you?
But your sweat smells really nice.
Idiot, what are you saying?
Yu-Yuuto, your tongue feels good...
Oh no, oh no!
Stop licking me down there...
Now I've squirted...
Hurry up and put your dick in already.
It's in, your dick is now inside.
Your insides are wrapping around me.
Don't just cum yet.
You need to rub your dick into me really good first.
It feels good.
Your dick.
Your dick...
I've wanted... I've wanted to have it since this morning.
I wanted to have your dick.
I'm saying these embarrassing things.
Just forget about it.
Me-Megumi-san, me too...
Yuuto...
I've always wanted to do it with you.
I'm always thinking of having sex with you.
I-Idiot.
You pervert.
I'm going to get more sensitive if you say that.
You too, you wanted my dick too, right?
You wanted to do it again too, right?
I wanted to.
My pussy wanted you.
Yuuto.
Yuuto!
Are you about to cum again?
Are you going to fill my insides again?
Filled... It's going to get filled.
My womb is going to get messed up again.
My pussy is getting completely filled.
Your dick... it's amazing.
I'm going to head over to your place today.
Hello Yuuto-kun.
If seems that,
you already have an idea why I came here.
Yuuto-kun, this looks amazing.
I'm looking forward to it.
I heard your dick's amazing.
Just what I'd expect from a young man.
Thanks for the meal.
You came a lot, it's good to be young.
I'm going to play with you lots more.
Jeez, Yuuto-kun, you're practically begging for it.
Here, I'm taking it in again.
This is it.
The sensation of being penetrated by a dick like this.
Yuuto-kun, that's a nice expression.
Here, it's going to feel even better.
It feels good to have sex after a long time.
Hey Yuuto-kun...
Yuuto-kun...
It's driving deep inside me.
Anna-san, I'm going to cum.
Just cum.
I want you to cum!
My slut's pussy is feeling it!
A young man's dick is driving me crazy!
My pussy, is getting filled...
I'm going to hold you completely responsible,
for reawakening my slutty pussy.
Be careful out there.
I'm sorry, Yuu-kun.
And you also had to take care of the kids.
It's okay, your husband seems to be quite busy.
and you're always helping me out-
Are you expecting this?
Now it's just the two of us.
I just can't wait to be done by you.
Mako-san.
We-We'll do it in the dressing room.
I'm already this wet,
from thinking about having sex with you.
Your pussy is amazingly lewd.
Please put your youthful dick inside my horny pussy.
O-Okay.
This... This is it!
It's inserted all the way down there.
Yuu-kun, try moving faster.
We'll both feel better that way.
Got it.
You're still young and you're already this horny.
Did those two teach you a few things?
Your pussy feels really good.
Your dick also feels good.
I give it a 10 out of 10.
Yes... yes!
That's good, that's really good.
I want to,
make you feel even better!
No, oh no...
If you try even harder...
My legs... My legs are going to give out on me.
No, I can't hold myself anymore.
It feels hot, and it feels great!
Let me cum.
Let my pussy taste ecstasy with your dick.
My pussy...
Fill my pussy up with your cum!
Mako-san, you're such a bad mom.
Letting out erotic moans like this while the kids are away.
You're also quite bad yourself.
You're thrusting it in as if you're trying to impregnate me.
You're a wolf in sheep's clothing.
A beast!
I'm going to cum.
I'm really about to cum!
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum too!
Cumming while being cummed in...
This feeling is overwhelming me...
I orgasmed like crazy.
Yuu-kun, from now on,
take care of my pussy, like how you take care of my kids, okay?
Mornin' Yuuto.
Good morning, Yuuto-kun.
Yuu-kun, good morning.
Good morning.
Th-That’s...
Ye-Yep.
This was my uniform when I was still a slutty student.
Oh so you too Megumi?
Even Mako-san as well?
My, oh my!
Everyone, Is It okay to reveal that much?
I wore this because of you, you know.
That's right, look.
Yuuto-kun's personal cum hole
Let's get along well from now on.