Sorry I'm late. Did you wait long?
No, I just got here.
Sorry for making you go
shopping with me in this heat.
Don't sweat it.
I'm pretty happy about it, actually!
I'm glad that we get to go on a date.
Yeah, I guess you could call this a date.
It's been so long since I've gone out with anyone.
It completely slipped my mind.
Being told that this wasn't
meant to be a date stings a little.
Well then, let's get this date started.
I'm going to be wearing this to my daughter's school,
so I want something that doesn't attract attention.
I don't care about the looks I get,
but I don't want the other moms chewing my ear off.
I thought it was strange that you asked me
to help you pick out a plain swimsuit,
but everything makes sense now.
Yep.
I think the fathers will have their eyes glued on you,
regardless of what swimsuit you wear.
Oh, Yuuto-kun.
You've gotten really good at this.
Is this the confidence of a man
who's lost his virginity?
Th-Those aren't empty praises, you know...
Oh, Yuuto-kun.
Yuuto-kun, how about this frilly palais?
This?! I think it exposes too much skin!
It might not be appropriate
for a grade school pool!
You think so?
Then how about this?
A daring, adult bikini.
Y-You definitely can't wear that!
If the children's fathers saw that,
they'll turn into beasts!
You have a point.
Even your eyes, which are normally so cute,
are starting to turn into those of a beast's.
Th-That's not...
Anyway, if you know it's daring,
don't bother considering it!
I guess this will do.
Yeah, that works.
Even so, this might be a bit too much.
Maybe you should wear something over it.
I could try to find a matching parka or something.
But that'd be too hot.
So, listen.
I was thinking of also buying
a swimsuit for private use.
O-Okay.
If you're fine with me,
I'll help you, no matter how long it takes.
I already have my eyes on a swimsuit.
I want you to give me your opinion. Is that fine?
Of course!
Give me a second.
Ta-da!
How do I look?
A-Anna-san!
Hey, Yuuto-kun! Don't shut me out like that!
Hello there.
You're already so hard.
A-Anna-san...
We can't do this here.
Can you really leave with your dick like this?
But people will hear us in a place like this.
So it's fine so long as we don't make any noise?
Hey there!
You're looking very energetic.
Your dick is being very naughty.
Its dirty smell is intoxicating this poor lady here.
Hey, be quiet.
A-Anna-san, I'm gonna cum!
Looks like I'll have to buy this swimsuit.
I-I guess so.
Now I want you to use your dick
and play with my pussy.
What's this?
Looks like you're pretty fond of this swimsuit, too.
Even though I just made you cum...
You've already gotten so hard again.
A-Anna-san? Wait, we can't!
See? We'll be fine. No one will notice.
Fine. If anything happens, it isn't my fault.
I love you Yuuto-kun.
The one you actually love is my cock, isn't it?
N-No, it's not!
I only like this cock because it's yours.
I love you, Yuuto-kun. I really do!
Yuuto-kun!
A-Anna-san, I'm gonna...
Give it to me! I need it!
Let it all out inside of me!
Thanks for carrying the bags too.
Don't worry about it.
You're tired because of me, after all.
You're tired too, aren't you?
You went pretty hard.
Well...
Anyway, you sure bought a lot of stuff.
Yeah. I needed some special underwear too.
For traveling?
It's a secret.
A secret?
I had some vegetables sent to me for free
because they were misshaped. They're really tasty.
Honestly, I wouldn't have any
lunch if it wasn't for you.
Is it really okay for me to eat all of this?
It's fine. I'd never finish all this by myself, anyway.
Thank you very much.
Oh, that's right. I wanted to talk
to you about something, Yuu-kun.
You did?
Yeah. You see,
Anna-chan's, Megu-chan's, and my kids will be
having a sleepover during summer break.
I see.
And you see, during that time,
my husband won't be home because of work.
So we were thinking of having our own little
sleepover and giving you some special service.
Wait, when you went shopping, it was for...
Yep, exactly.
I bought a lot to prepare.
Megu-chan's pretty excited.
Of course, this will only happen if you're okay with it.
O-Of course I am.
Thank goodness!
So, I want to keep you to myself tonight.
M-Mako-san...
You really do have too much energy.
This is what a violent dick like yours gets.
Wow! It's going crazy between my boobs!
Your dick's so cute!
M-Mako-san, you're being too rough!
Your dick's so hot that I just
can't stop my boobs from moving.
Mako-san, I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
Wow, there's so much dripping down my face.
Hey, Yuu-kun, how about you
feed my other mouth too?
Of course. Could you do me a favor then?
You're making me look like
some kind of pervert in this position.
Wow, Mako-san. You're already this wet?
Th-That's not true!
It is. You're like a waterfall down here.
See? You can hear it, can't you?
I don't hear anything!
Y-Yuu-kun, please!
Please let my pussy swallow your cock whole!
Mako-san, what do you say before you eat?
Thanks for the mea...
It tastes so good! You're feeding me your cock!
It's so good!
Your dick is so long, so thick,
and so hard! It's going in so deep!
More! Give me more!
I'm going to cum! Pound me harder!
It's so deep! It's rubbing so deep inside me! It feels so good!
My pussy's changing from the pussy of a wife
and mother to just a regular woman's pussy!
No way! It's hitting it!
It's hitting my soft spot!
Mako-san, you're weak here, right?
Megumi-san and Anna-san have the same weak spot.
Yes! It is! That's my weak spot!
It feels amazing there!
It's so good! This feels so good!
Your dick is really messing up my pussy!
Mako-san, I'm going to cum inside, okay?
Let me have it!
Let my pussy feast on your cum! It wants it!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
There's so much of your hot cum soup inside me.
What do you say after
having a fulfilling meal, Mako-san?
Thank you for your tasty cock.
Yes? Come on in.
Pardon the intrusion.
Welcome.
W-Welco...
Do you like the underwear we chose for you?
Y-Yes! They're really sexy!
Thank you.
We were thinking of giving you
a special service today.
Summer break is coming to an end,
so let's make some memories, 'kay?
R-Right.
Anna-chan, could you taste this for me?
Tastes great.
Could you give me that plate?
Megu-chan, we'll take care of the rest.
Could you take care of Yuu-kun?
What?
Yeah, we can't let him be bored.
W-Wait...
Let's go to my room, okay?
Wow, you're already this hard?
Looking at all of your erotic
underwear really turned me on.
That makes me so happy.
Megumi-san...
Megumi-san! If you suck that hard, I'm gonna...
Please drink every last drop.
Megumi-san!
Thank you for the delicious semen, Yuuto.
Megumi-san, you're really wet.
Take a look. Your delicious dick made me like this.
Megumi-san, it tastes so good.
You idiot.
Yuuto, put it in.
Okay...
Megu-chan, Yuu-kun? Food's ready.
Let's continue this after dinner, okay?
Want some fried eel?
Have some steak and Chinese food too.
Here's some wine.
Yuuto-kun, you can come in now.
Hi, Yuu-kun! I'm Mako.
I'm Megu.
I'm Anna.
Let's have some fun together, all night long.
We're too old to be wearing these clothes.
We don't look weird, do we?
Nope! Not at all!
You look even better than the girls
who are supposed to be wearing them.
We need to show our thanks to you
for always saying such nice things to us.
It feels so good!
Yuu-kun's cock is so hot!
His pre-cum is making my boobs so slippery!
How is it, Yuu-kun?
C-Crap, it feels too good.
We're going to make it feel even better, then.
It's so hot!
Take your pick.
Which pussy do you want to taste?
Megumi-san, your pussy is so slippery and wet!
My pussy feels so good!
Yuu-kun, I can't wait any longer!
No fair! I want his cock too!
Okay!
Me too! Hurry!
Yuuto...
Come on, me too!
W-Wait a second.
No!
It keeps going in and out of me!
Yuu-kun's dick is inside me while being covered
with Anna-chan and Megu-chan's liquids!
It's taking a while, but it's turning me on!
Everyone's pussies are shaped differently. It's amazing!
All three of us are getting fucked!
Make us cum together!
This feels amazing!
Okay, I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Okay, I'm gonna take a picture.
I'm ready whenever.
Our sweet summer break.
Let's take a picture to commemorate it.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: fyurie