The beach!
Beach!
Stop!
Please stretch before going in the water.
The sea is dangerous, after all.
Ah, that's it.
That lifeguard was pretty hot, don't you think?
So you were stretching!
Let Papa help with that.
Hey! Here?! Knock it off!
I guess I'll ask your dad to help me instead.
H-Hey, Airi!
My bikini's gonna come off! Stop!
I'm beat.
Let me put some sunscreen on for you.
Hmph. I don't really want you to, but alright.
If you touch me in weird places, I'll kick your ass.
I won't do that here!
It's cold!
Hey! What the...
What's wrong? You shouldn't be making such weird noises.
You're doing this on purpose! Do it normally!
I am doing it normally, aren't I?
Aren't you the one getting turned on?
At a beach? Now that's just shameful.
Hey, what do you think you're doing? You pervert!
That's not oil, is it? What the hell is that?!
What? Oh, this was lotion?
Oh, no. Looks like Papa made a mistake.
Hey, I told you, not here! Stop it! Sto...
Wha... It's inside. Wait!
You're not really doing it here, are you?
You can see them! You can see my boobs!
Hey, stop moving!
Someone's gonna see us! Stop already!
Over there! That lifeguard...
He can see us from there, right? Stop it!
At this angle, he shouldn't be able to.
The inner tube is blocking his view.
Hey, stop moving! You piece of...
When I move, you get tighter.
Are you doing that just to make me feel better?
In your dreams, idiot! Take it out already.
Stay still, we'll be found out!
You idiot! Just take it out!
It'll be a while before anything comes out.
This is ridiculous, you piece of crap...
I told you, I don't want this!
I'll let you do me when we get home, so stop, please!
You hate this that much?
Guess I have no choice.
Seriously, even here, this piece of crap...
You idiot!
Original Work: Blue Gail
RelenHess Dad
The Cheeky Romance Won't Stop
Oh, it's you, Airi.
What's with him? He's still looking at me.
Hey! What are you doi...
It's inside me again!
It should be fine underwater, right?
No, it's not, you dirt bag!
Hey! Don't play with my boobs.
Someone will see us! Stop!
Nobody's gonna notice.
Yeah, they will.
People are gonna see me naked, you idiot!
If anything, people will see your face in ecstasy.
Screw you!
I don't feel ecstatic at all, idiot.
Getting fucked by your thing is disgusting.
My "thing"? Come on. Say it like you always do.
Idiot! As if I can say it at a place like this, you perv!
You're still worrying about where we are
even though I'm already inside you?
Shut up, idiot!
Just cum and get limp already, you sick fuck!
I can keep on cumming if it's with you, Airi.
Hurry up!
You piece of crap...
There...
No!
It feels good, even though we shouldn't be doing this!
I'll cum inside you.
Damn it!
Squirt out your Papa milk!
Cumming in a place like this?
What a dirty dick!
I'm gonna...
This dirty dick is gonna make me cum!
In a place like this... I'm cumming!
It's coming in!
I'm so jealous of you, Airi.
Sana, you were awake?
Well, you were moaning right next to me...
I couldn't stay asleep even if I wanted to.
What's up with him? He's still looking at me.
Maybe he has the hots for you.
Do you want me to tell him off?
Hold on. It'd be bad if it ends up like last time,
so don't do anything weird, okay?
We really freaked Mom out after all...
I get that she's worried about me,
but asking me to change schools?
I wonder if she's really going to make me transfer.
If that happens, I'll be separated from Sana...
It'd suck if I couldn't meet anyone anymore.
I wonder what'll happen...
H-Hold on. What do you want?
That part's shallow,
but if you go out any further,
it'll get really deep, so be careful.
Sure thing.
Everyone's just trying to have a good time,
so please keep that in mind.
We're at the beach after all.
Okay.
Anything deemed inappropriate
is forbidden. This is a beach after all.
G-Got it.
I know it's tempting with your boyfriend around...
H-He's not my boyfriend.
I'll be careful! I got it!
She really isn't my girlfriend.
Oh, that so?
But I saw you having sex just a moment ago.
Oh, no way... We weren't doing anything like that.
Oh. I guess I was just seeing things...
This is a beach, after all.
What was up with him? Such a creep.
It must be hard being a lifeguard.
He said that we should be careful while having sex.
So he could see us then!
I convinced him otherwise though.
Jeez, stop talking crap. It's your fault.
He's looking at us again.
Nothing we can do about it, it's his job.
What the hell? You're siding with him?!
So you're not on my side?
I am on your side!
Are you supporting him 'cause you're both dirt bags?
You make me sick. I'm gonna buy something to drink.
Bring me some orange juice, please.
You're not gonna come with me?
I'm tired, so good luck.
Well, I guess I can get it
without you coming along.
Oh, grab me a coffee!
Wait a minute, young lady!
You're no fun.
It's dangerous to be walking around here
with a cute lace like that.
Please stop it.
Stop what? You're cute.
Come on, just give me a little bit of your time.
No. Why should Airi do that?
So your name's Airi?
C'mon! It'll be fine.
Sir, this kind of behavior will not be tolerated,
so I kindly ask you to leave her alone.
Ow. I get it, okay?
See you around, Airi!
Thank you very much.
Don't mention it. It's my job.
Your boyfriend must be worried too.
He's not my boyfriend!
Are you sure?
It looked like you two were having sex.
We did no such thing!
Aren't your eyes just bad?
For sure, okay?
Got it.
See ya!
Yeah.
Here's your coffee.
What's wrong, Airi? You look pretty mad.
The lifeguard thought that
this trash here is my boyfriend.
Meanwhile, other women are flirting with him.
Men really are pigs!
Must be hard being you.
Are you jealous? Don't worry.
You're the only one I've got eyes on.
Ah, what about me?
Left out again...
I'll be there tomorrow, Dad.
Airi, wanna go to the limestone cave?
I'll go grab my stuff, so you go on ahead.
The one we heard rumors about? Okay!
What's this about a limestone cave?
It's supposed to be a power spot.
But you can stay here to guard our stuff.
Damn it. I told you to stay there
and guard our stuff, you piece of crap.
I thought you might feel lonely.
What's that supposed to mean?
Who said I'd be lonely and when?
You really are an idiot.
Vacations with no limits are fun, aren't they?
You should also free your body and mind.
Shut up, you raging sexual maniac!
Idiot!
Wh-What the? Cut it out!
Hey! Stop... doing...
No! Hey!
You got wet so fast.
You really do love your Papa, don't you?
Yeah, keep dreaming!
Not in a million years!
Excuse me! This place is off-limits!
You again?
Airi, was it?
Can you please leave now?
I'm sorry. I was just... Uh...
Tell him you're doing your business.
I'm just doing my business. I'll leave soon!
What the hell am I saying?
Stop that, you scumbag!
We can't have you doing that here.
We have actual toilets set up.
You couldn't hold it in?
I'm sorry!
I'll be done real quick.
I'll wait here, so please hurry up.
What?
This'll... uh... take some more time.
Wait, are you going for number 2?
I-It's not like that!
What's with this shameful situation?
You're gonna make me look like a sicko.
Aren't you one, though?
Shut up, moron!
Still not done yet?
Um... uh... please wait a little bit more.
Are you constipated or something?
I already told you, no!
But you're taking so long.
You're supposed to ask and then leave.
This guy is weird.
What should I do?
I got it. Gimme a minute.
No way! It's in! His dirty dick is in!
You idiot. Stop moving.
What the hell are you thinking when that guy's around?
So you are constipated, huh?
Please set some sand aside when you're done.
I'll clean it up for you.
Like I said, I-It's not...
If I deny it now...
Got it!
So, um...
Someone's calling me. Please hurry up.
You disgusting old man...
Hey!
What the heck? Why're you turning me into a pervert?
Scumbag!
You can't just do whatever you want
to me with your disgusting dick.
You animal! Stupid sex maniac!
How can you put me in this kind of
embarrassing position when someone's around?
You're cute no matter how you look.
Shut up! You piss me off!
I'm not going to let your disgusting dick inside me again!
You idiot!
Idiot, idiot, idiot!
Scum! You came inside me!
You low-life, perverted, dirt bag!
All that stuff with Mom isn't even settled
and yet, we're here on vacation.
And I've been turned into some kind
of exhibitionist freak show.
I'm so sick of it.
I'm on vacation, but I can't even relax.
What's up with that?
Damn it.
That scared me!
My boat...
Damn...
My legs are cramping up.
No way! This can't be happening! Papa!
No...
Help me! Someone... Please... Someone!
No! Papa, Sana, Sis...
Who is that?
translator: jimaku-danshaku
translator check: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: punk4real
quality control: fyurie