Papa...
Your dick is amazing,
it's really rubbing me hard.
Having me is already enough, right?
Please just love me, okay?
Jeez, just be honest with yourself already.
I'm the one who makes her suffer like this.
Airi, just stop.
Stop and think for a moment.
What is this?
I can't pull it out.
Hey, don't pull it out!
I want it to be inside of me.
Papa, this is amazing.
You're doing me here to show everyone
that I'm the only one for you.
My hips won't stop... why?
Yes, please keep it inserted in me forever.
Please take care of no one else but me.
Then, you'll divorce Mom, and stay with me.
You're going to live your entire life for me!
I really can't pull out.
Mama, I'm sorry.
Papa is already mine.
I love you, but you're just second to Papa.
Oh, is that so?
Then I need to get out now.
Well then.
Are we done introducing our relationship to Mom?
Next up is Onee-chan.
Kayoko? Hey!
Airi come back to your senses!
No, Dad, don't...
Don't tease me like that.
Mom, my pussy is overflowing.
And it's craving for Dad's dick.
Onee-chan, I'm sorry.
But Papa is now mine.
I can let your play with his dick, though.
Is that so? I see he's only yours now.
But, share him with me from time to time, okay?
Marina, stop Airi!
Kayoko, Sara, Yuka!
Anybody!
Now we're done telling Onee-chan about our relationship.
She now knows your dick is mine.
The only one left now is Yuka-senpai.
Airi, I beg of you, stop this already!
Are you about to cum?
Then pour it all in my womb.
You're going to make me pregnant.
Alright make sure to fill me up.
Release all of your Papa milk inside me,
and we'll live happily with our child.
Love only me...
Is he okay?
It's a different kind of drug.
Not the type that would harm your Dad.
You might be going wild inside his mind already.
That perverted research, huh?
The drug might be reacting to male
hormones to induce hallucinations?
It takes some time before it goes into full effect, though.
This is punishment for leaving me behind.
I heard from him that it was suddenly prohibited
while being tested on Yuka-senpai.
I really don't understand at all why
Yuka goes to such great lengths.
Haven't you heard, Airi?
What?
So you're even more jealous toward him than your mother.
Th-That's not it!
What are you talking about, Sana?
Stop laughing like that!
Ow!
Hey, you're really getting more violent these days.
You always get serious whenever it's about your Papa.
Sana!
I thought he never told you about Yuka-senpai.
Wh-What about it?
Going crazy with that cheeky moe face
Jeez, what an idiot.
Though, I may be the idiot here.
Betraying Mom like this, and getting all irritated without reason.
I really am a brat.
I wonder what I could've done without you.
My precious practice time has all been wasted by this jerk.
I never thought that you'd actually get worried about it like that.
How are you going to take responsibility for this?!
Papa-san, were you surprised?
You're in the real world now.
H-Huh? Airi? Huh?
Using that drug again,
we observed that the drug induces hallucinations
when used on males.
It has that kind of effect?
Wait, that goes for me too?
Yuka-senpai also asked me to tell you
that it also has a hypnotic effect.
I already explained all about Senpai to Airi.
That's no good.
You shouldn't worry Airi too much.
Well then, laters.
Jeez, she's really not serious about this.
S-Sorry.
I've heard everything about Mikami-senpai.
I see.
I'll try to explain everything later.
Okay.
B-Bye.
Umm...
I-I'm sorry!
I was a bad girl.
I just ran my mouth off without knowing anything.
No, that goes for me as well.
I just didn't want you bad-mouthing other people.
I got too agitated about it...
Doing something that hurt you, that hurt my daughter...
I'm a failure as a father.
No...
Does Mikami-senpai...
I'm sorry about Yuka,
but ever since I met you, I...
Stop. I know it already.
This is embarrassing...
It's gotten big ever since you started fondling it.
My body's now grown used to you.
Your dick is getting bigger,
and it's rubbing my ass.
Your dick is filling up my pussy as
it did when you took my virginity.
It's giving its love to me.
I'm sorry, I thought you already left me.
I just didn't want you to worry.
I was sad that you got angry with me,
but I was an idiot, and I'm really sorry
for saying those outrageous things.
I was an idiot too, so I'm sorry as well.
Sana told me everything, so I finally
understood those things about you.
That's why I'll forgive you.
I'm sorry for lashing out at you, I'm sorry for being such a brat.
I finally realized it after you scolded me.
Thank you, Papa.
I love you, Papa.
Oh no, that kiss with you was actually for real.
What should I do?
Your dick is amazing, it's very intense.
Airi, I'm going to impregnate you this time.
Papa, you still have Mama, so we can't just do that.
We're not allowed to do that.
I told you, I'm going to protect you.
Papa, I'm happy.
I'm really happy.
Just give me all of your Papa milk.
I'm going to cum, Papa.
Give it all to me.
It's going to fill me up.
Your Papa milk is pumping inside me.
I'm going to cum too!
I'm very happy with your Papa milk.
I love you, Papa...
Are you going?
I'm sorry.
Do you love me?
Yeah.
Are you going to hold me dear?
Are you going to do anything I ask?
Yeah.
Huh? Airi?
Man, that was tiring.
22 minutes was just too long.
Lovey Dovey time is over!
Hey, Airi, you switched too fast!
I really wanted to record more of your lovey dovey self.
Hmph, you never told me anything even though
you're supposed to be my best friend.
We're done already.
But I did tell you.
Wait, you told her more than just about Yuka?
She's my best friend after all.
I didn't want her to get all worried about that stuff.
I did feel sorry about bad-mouthing her.
I even apologized, right?
But I still can't forgive how horribly you treated me.
Telling me that I'm some brat or something.
Hey, Airi, you...!
Jeez, you're treating me like some kind of fool.
Airi!
Hmph, next time you do something
like this I really won't forgive you.
I'm saying that you should trust me more, okay, idiot?
The next time I'll do that again will be in about 80 years.
What?!
I still can't go to school...
I already finished the costume so try it on.
I think I've done a really good job with this.
Really? Okay then.
Hey, have you seen Airi?
Huh? She was here a moment ago.
Did she go to the bathroom?
I can't find her anywhere.
What should I do?
I never thought that this would happen, Senpai.
Try finding her there.
I'm also going to find her but I'll still
have to prepare things over there.
Okay, I understand.
Oh crap, oh crap.
Prev Next 1
Gorgeous Model Student
Actually a Slut
291: Nameless-kun
We shall do it today.
The target girl didn't go to scholl today,
so we'll just attack the cheeky one
instead
She shall be stained with
a mark that she'll never forget
292: Nameless-kun
girl's changing room
So this is it.
She did quite a good job here.
Let's get changed already.
The last one was soiled by someone's dirty milk.
Stop with that.
Oh yeah, I think she went to check out her costume.
You!
Idiot, you just suddenly...
What are you doing here?
So this is your costume this time.
It looks good.
The last one was soiled by you, anyway.
This new one looks great, right?
I think it'll feel even better if we have sex while you're wearing this.
Jeez, I'm telling you not to soil it with your dirty milk.
Good grief.
Just help yourself with this.
It's already this big...
This dick really is a worthless piece of trash.
Letting me do this in a place where anyone
can come in at any time... idiot.
You're the one who started it.
I just wanted a hug, you know.
Okay, so we can stop this now, huh.
Papa's dick is quite honest.
Well have to explain to them once we're found out, and yet...
I told you before,
I don't care even if I'm caught.
I don't care if I'm caught with you.
I'm not the least bit happy with that, idiot.
It's twitching hard.
How unsightly.
This is stupid.
Sucking Papa's dick right here,
I'm such a slut.
Just who is it that made me like this?
Take responsibility for turning me into a slut.
You're my wife.
Cum already.
Cum, cum!
Hey!
You came too much.
My costume will get soiled if it drips.
Jeez, try to control yourself a bit, will you?
Hey!
Idiot I said it's going to get dirty!
I'm exclusively yours, right? Then it's okay.
Jeez, then you'll have to completely satisfy me.
Amazing.
His dick feels even better than before.
Don't be too rough, the costume will get dirty!
His dick is pushing really deep inside me.
Airi, please, be safe.
Please...
Airi!
Hey, it's going to leave a mark!
I can't believe that I'm actually putting up with this trashy dick.
Your stamina's clearly decreased ever since your surgery.
It was a success, though.
So what? You're trying to act too cool by
meddling with my personal history.
Your trashy dick just feels too great.
Can't be helped then, I'll just let you pour your milk into me.
You just wanted some, right?
That's not true.
It's going deep again.
I'm really a pervert to be doing something like this here.
My body wants to be soiled with your dick.
I'm peeing.
It's actually leaking out.
Why don't you bring Onee-chan's classmate next time?
I-I want to at least give her a proper greeting that way.
Thank you.
I think Yuka will also be happy too.
Hmph, now I'm pissed.
Huh? I'm still...!
What should we do?
This is bad!
Airi, hey Airi!
Eh? Sana?
Aw man...
Airi...
Airi!
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Sana? Hey, what's wrong?
Hey, Sana!
Airi?
What happened?
No way, it went that far?
I started panicking when I lost sight of you.
But, Mr. Papa here should have told me!
Sorry, but I was actually hogging... I mean holding her in here.
I don't want to hear your wisecracks.
Wait, I'll just contact Yuka-senpai.
That was close.
I was about to sleep all day.
Oh no, I slept after playing with myself.
Oh, so it's here.
We haven't properly broken up.
Wait, does Masato know about my relationship with father?
Prev Next
Gorgeous Model Student
Actually a Slut
1: Nameless-kun
let's talk about it
that's just farfetched—
Wait, Masato's hobby is... photography...
Could he be the one?
It's okay, her injuries aren't severe.
So that's what happened.
Mama looked quite well, though.
The drug was already administered,
but he suddenly acted violently.
It's good that he's finally worn out.
Maybe she thought Mama was Onee-chan.
He just took too much.
You should have detained him in a proper facility!
Jeez.
Are you alright, Marina?
Huh? Me? I'm okay.
I wasn't really there.
I wouldn't know until I saw the scene for myself.
No, I mean, about him...
Oh, you mean what I thought about the scum that injured Mama?
Figures.
I know this muse be a bad time,
and I really like you Sana,
but I'm...
It's okay, Airi.
It's just for a short while.
I want you to leave it to me.
We're best friends, right?
So we need to help each other.
That's true, but...
Even before you...
That was then, this is now.
But...!
You said this was an apology for making me really worried.
Jeez, just this once, okay...
Now we're talking!
Sucking this trashy dick with Sana like this is just...
It's been a while since I got a taste of his dick.
It's because you won't let me.
Hmph, I've been helping you a lot before, so just...
It's at moments like these that you really become selfish.
I found out lots of new things about you since he came.
Jeez, just shut up.
Airi...!
Sana...!
Airi, I think I'm really getting horny.
Sana, I'm...
Me too, this is...
What should I do with this trashy dick?
Airi, don't forget me.
Just a bit more before the record is complete.
Oh no, Sana, his tongue is rubbing me.
This is... Sana!
Airi, your Dad's dick is amazing.
It's rubbing hard inside me.
It's really amazing!
Sana... me too, I want his dick too.
No, you can't, it's mine right now.
It's filling me inside right now.
I think I've experienced something similar before.
Please, release all of your cum milk inside me.
Mister, just do it.
Sana, no fair.
I'm next!
Oh yes...
Mlik...
Airi, that felt great.
Papa, your dick...
It's all the way inside your pussy.
It's completely filled.
I want you to still cum lots even after Sana did it.
I'll stir it more inside my pussy.
Your expression is so slutty.
You're the school's idol, but right now
I'm looking at this expression.
Show me more, Airi.
Sana, you pulled that out again.
Now I really can't show that to anyone.
It's totally recording the part where my
pussy is being fucked by Papa's dick.
No, Sana, don't record it.
My slutty self is being recorded.
Stop, I'm not a slut, Sana.
I'm not lewd.
That's cute, Airi.
Please show me more of your cute self.
I'm about to cum, Sana.
I'm about to sloppily cum in front of you.
I'm right in front of her, and yet I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Your pussy is now filled with Papa's milk.
Sana, I told you not to.
Stalking, assault, rape.
I think it's okay now.
I was worried when I tried to consult Kayoko about it, but...
All's well that ends well.
And the expressions the two gave when
I told them about Yuka coming here.
I'm really aroused now.
The copy's about to be done.
I'll go take a leak.
Stop that already.
I can't believe you're using that here.
Kouzo-san.
This girl...
Looks just like Airi!
Oh, they said it looks like her so I...
That was close.
I thought she'd already gone to sleep after getting drunk.
Maybe it's edited, and people might think that it's really her.
It's quite likely.
I see, if there's something like this...
The case was already solved for Marina,
but now we have Airi.
I-I think it's going to be okay.
Marina, Airi, I've decided.
This is something that I must do to protect you two.
Change schools.
I've already finished the preparations.
Huh?
Heh?
Eh?
Eh?!