Previously on Oni Chichi Refresh.
We're here!
Beach!
If you touch me anywhere inappropriate, I'll kick your ass.
I won't do that here!
That's col...
Oops. Looks like Papa made a mistake.
Shh, people are going to notice!
You idiot! Take it out!
It'll be a while before anything comes out.
Nobody will notice if we do it underwater.
Hey!
Don't take my boobs out!
People are going to see me naked, stupid!
It feels good, even though we shouldn't be doing this!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm at the beach and I'm cumming!
What's with that guy? He's still staring at me.
Maybe he has the hots for you.
Should I tell him to back off?
Yeah, I know!
I know it's tempting with your boyfriend around...
H-He's not my boyfriend!
I'll be careful! I understand!
He's still staring?
What? You're not taking my side on this?
Feeling a bit of camaraderie for your fellow dirt bag?
Not too friendly, huh?
Your cute face is going to waste.
P-Please leave me alone.
You're so cute.
I hate guys so much.
U-Um, s-sorry! I just...
I'll leave right after I've finished my business...
What the heck am I saying?!
He's inside me!
What if some other guy sees me like this
when we're doing it in the open?
Stupid! Idiot! Dummy!
Wai... This can't be... Papa...
No...
Help me...
Please, somebody!
The small, cheeky perverted frieng's beach bitch.
Did he save me?
Is Airi okay?
She was pulled out of the water
right away, so she should be.
She just needs some rest.
We're having barbecue tonight,
so I'm sure she'll feel better after resting
and getting something inside her.
I can't believe you made that kind of joke after
what just happened to her, oji-sama.
I'm worrying about her in my own way.
Being depressed won't make anything better.
You're not wrong, but I think I know Airi better than you.
That aside, aren't you a bit more curvaceous than usual?
Huh?
What are you saying? That's not true at all.
I haven't gotten fat!
That's not what I meant.
I meant that you've become rather womanly.
Oji-sama...
You have a plump, juicy, sexy body.
Oji-sama... will you play with me too?
How have you been doing, Mr. Dick?
Do you remember who I am?
You've been playing with Marina and Airi
for so long, you might not remember me.
I really wish you would play with me more often.
Don't you get enough of this from the professor?
I always have room for your dick.
A lot of room.
Give me your milk, the milk that's
even thicker than oyaji-san's.
I want you to put it in me,
but I want to drink your milk too.
Cum! Shoot that milk inside my mouth!
Oji-sama's milk!
Your milk's amazing! It's so thick.
Wai... Sana...
Will you play with me a little more now that I've done this?
This position...
You're such a pervert, oji-sama!
You're not really one to talk after you learned
all these ways to jack guys off.
No, don't be so mean.
I learned all that stuff to make you happy.
Don't worry. I'm overjoyed.
Oji-sama, your dick is so hard!
We shouldn't be having sex here,
but I'm so turned on!
I feel bad for Airi, but right now, this dick is all mine!
I've been a burden to you, haven't I?
I'll make sure that I satisfy you.
My pussy is throbbing like crazy!
Oji-sama, your dick feels so good!
My pussy is stuffed with that cock!
I don't want to make Airi mad,
so I'll just make do with your dick for now.
I might want to take all of your milk though.
Sorry, that's for Airi only.
Oh, Marina too.
You say that, but your dick is just
shoving itself in and out of me.
I'm cool with doing it with you,
but Airi might get lonely.
You can be my slave.
I'll make sure you get equally as much loving.
That's what the drug was for, right?
Thanks to that, I can enjoy this, too!
Oji-sama, your milk!
Right now, this belongs to me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It just keeps coming out!
It's swirling around inside me.
There's so much of your milk. It's spilling out!
What a waste!
It feels like your milk is going to flow out of me.
So good! What is this?! It's so good!
Sana, your food's not going anywhere. Eat slowly!
This meat's delicious. This beer's delicious!
Airi's also delicious!
Onee-chan's coming tomorrow,
so I think we'll have a lot more fun then.
Geez, oji-sama...
Wow, are all these people couples?
Wait, are they doing it?
Hey, now. You shouldn't point at people, Airi.
How come you wanted to come on a walk with me, alone?
Are you finally being honest with yourself?
I wonder if we look like a couple when
we're walking side by side like this.
Hm, I wonder.
Our ages are clearly different,
so maybe we look like father and daughter.
Then, what if I did this?
Oh, I get it.
Right now, you're being the nice Airi.
Is that a problem?
You like me this way too, don't you?
Do you want to do what everyone else is doing?
This might be the first time we've kissed like this.
P-Probably... Wait, did Sana tell you?
Do you want to do it?
My boobs feel so good.
It's turning me on!
I like the warmth from your hands,
but this is embarrassing.
So good! Your tongue is making me so hot!
You've gotten pretty big.
I'll make you feel good too.
Isn't the sky beautiful?
I'm being so daring out here!
Your dick is so big and stiff!
Even though I know I'm doing lewd
things out here, I can't stop!
You're going to cum, aren't you?
It's okay, cum!
Wow, there's so much!
You came a lot, didn't you?
Look, I'm so wet.
Your finger's in my pussy!
Wow, it's already this big again!
Put it inside me.
It feels good when you rub it against me!
You're being so rough.
It feels so good!
You're rubbing it deep inside me.
My pussy loves it!
You keep hitting all of my weak spots!
That's because I know everything about you, Airi.
You mean it? I'm so happy!
She could be acting, but damn, this feels good!
We're kissing so much.
You're gonna make me go crazy the way you're
rubbing my boobs and fucking me.
At this rate, I'm gonna...
Oh my god, this feels amazing!
I'm gonna cum if we keep doing it like this!
No! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Your thing is pumping lots of hot cum into my pussy!
I can't believe I was daring enough to have sex out here.
Doesn't look like anyone cares.
Everyone's doing it with the person they love, right?
Oh God, look at all that cum spilling out.
So, I guess since I'm a kid and all, I don't really understand,
but... liking someone is nice, isn't it?
What?
You see, I'm planning on putting an end to this.
By "this", you mean...
Wait... Airi?
I might have liked you too, Kozou-san,
but I think we should stop doing this.
Wait, Airi. I don't get what you're saying.
You're doing great Airi.
You're doing all this cute stuff without
a care in the world. I can't stop filming!
I'm gonna cum just by looking at your face!
You want me to do it again?!
Last time, you didn't even see it through
to the end. Be sure to make up for it.
Sheesh. I can't do it out here!
I already thought of that. Apparently, all these couples
are doing it out in the open come night time.
Are you serious?
No way. I can't do that!
You're doing this for me.
I saved you, didn't I?
Ugh, fine! But after this, I'm never doing it again, okay?
Yeah, of course.
I'm happy as long as I can record your cute side.
Airi was really into it.
But what was she saying at the end?
She even called Kozou-san by his first name.
Wait, what's going on! No, stop!
What the hell are you doing! Stop!
This one's fine, right?
Yeah, she's fine.
Both of them are cute anyway.
She'll be perfect. We'll have some fun.
Hell yeah! We re going to have a lot of fun.
If we use this chick to call Airi, she'll come running.
I can't wait.
From here on out, let's go back to normal.
Let's stop doing these things.
Okay, dad?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent