Is Airi okay?
She was pulled out of the water
immediately, so she should be.
She just needs some rest.
So how've you been doing Mr. Dick?
Do you remember who I am?
You've been playing with Marina and Airi so
much that I'm basically just a side dish now.
Your dick is so hard!
We shouldn't be having sex here, but I can't help myself!
I feel bad for Airi, but right now, this dick is all mine!
Doing it like this is fine with me, but it might make
Airi upset. That's what the drug was for, right?
Thanks to that, I can enjoy this too!
Then what if I did this?
My boobs feel so good! I'm getting so turned on!
Even though I know I'm doing something
really lewd out here, I can't stop!
You're going to cum, aren't you? It's okay, cum!
You're rubbing my boobs and pussy
so much! I'm going to lose my mind!
I'm going to...
What is this? It's so good!
I'm going to stop this.
Wait, Airi, I don't understand what you're saying.
Yeah, that girl's fine. Both of them were cute anyway.
From now on, we should go back to normal,
so let's stop doing these things...
Okay, Dad?
Cheeky Attitude
Wait, Airi.
What was all that about?
Hm?
It was exactly what it sounded like.
What? Are you going to make me
horny with the drug again?
Are you going to abuse me?
Just kidding. I understand it's all really
sudden, so I'll lend you just my body.
Oh, so it was all just a joke? Don't scare me like that.
Then how about a quickie?
Sheesh. Fine, come over here then.
H-Hey...
Sorry, I'm texting Sana.
This is weird. We were going to meet up.
Airi, you're really looking at your phone right now?
Huh? It doesn't feel good?
You're already about to cum, aren't you?
Let's hurry and look for Sana.
Shit. So this is what she meant by lending me her body?
Just watch!
You can do the rest yourself.
Come on, let's go.
Are you kidding me? My plan is ruined!
Welcome home dear!
Do you want dinner?
Or maybe a bath?
Or maybe me?
You're rubbing my boobs so roughly!
You're playing with them like clay!
No, he's going to find out that I've been waiting for this!
It's not what you think!
I swear I wasn't using an eggplant to hold me over.
Your dick shot straight inside me!
Your dick is pounding against me! My pussy's so happy!
You're going to spray erotic dressing
on top of the food at this rate!
No!
It feels even more amazing than usual!
I can't anymore!
Cum inside me! Make me pregnant!
Mess me up!
This is weird.
We were supposed to meet up around here.
Hey, are you listening?
Huh, yeah.
Sana?
Where are you?
Master, your dick... It's so full of energy
first thing in the morning.
Have you awoken, Master?
How is my service?
Master's raw morning milk is pouring out!
Well then, breakfast is read...
Master, no! We can't!
Master's dick is filling up my pussy!
We shouldn't be doing this!
This isn't something that can be forgiven.
But my body is rejoicing!
From now on, I'll be your dick's slave, Master.
Please take good care of me, Master!
Geez, knock it off already, will you?
Are you even listening to me?
Why do you keep spacing out?
O-Oh, sorry.
She's not here.
This can't be happening!
She was just bagged and then thrown
into a van out of the blue.
I couldn't process it at all, so I still haven't called the police.
What should we do? I can't believe
that she might've been kidnapped!
I can't even reach her cell.
It's from Sana!
We're having a party, Airi-chan
This guy's from the afternoon!
Come the hell on!
Going alone is exactly what he wants!
Then what am I supposed to do?
Let go of me!
Sorry to ask you to do something weird like this.
I'm part of a vigilante group anyway. Also,
this area's pretty hard to navigate.
It's hard to walk this path if you're
not used to it, so be careful.
Welcome, Airi-chan.
Hey...
Where's Sana?!
I'll tell you after we have some fun.
You're scum!
You're really a piece of shit for doing this!
You've got quite the spunk. Can't wait to
break you down into a moaning mess.
Don't disappoint me.
It'd be a problem if people saw my face
when it goes up on the internet.
Screw that, you scum bag!
It's just a protective measure.
If you're a good girl, I'll make sure
this never reaches the internet.
You're sexy. It's really easy to see like this.
You scared?
I'll be sure to drown you in pleasure.
You really think I'd submit that easily?
Being touched by scum like you is just gross.
My boobs... What's going on? His hands are like a girl's.
You scum! Loser!
I'm having my boobs rubbed by a guy like him!
Your boobs sure are big.
Feel good?
It actually feels disgusting, scum bag.
What's with this guy? His technique is...
Hurry up and end it already!
Yeah, act tough while you still can.
Die, you piece of shit! Pervert! Scum!
Next is down here.
If you're not more obedient, you won't see Sana-chan.
He's playing with it! He's playing with my special place!
Trash! Scum! You piece of...
No, this movement... What's going on?!
Looks like your body's feeling good.
Stop it!
His finger's going inside... No! No!!
Stop this already! It doesn't even feel good!
You piece of trash!
Your strong front will soon melt away.
No!
What? Why does he know?!
No! This is too much!
Why does he know my body so well?
It's time for the main attraction.
Wait, no! Not that!
Stop! Please! Anything but that!
Want to trade places with Sana-chan?
What am I hoping for? Of course nothing's going
to happen. This isn't a dream, this is reality.
Just put it in already then!
Hurry up and end this already!
That's good resolve.
What is this?
Is this really a dick?!
Why's it moving like that?! What's going on?!
What's going on? It's spinning around
inside me! It feels weird!
No! No! This is so nasty! So disgusting! No!
Feels good, doesn't it?
It's disgusting! Just finish already you piece of trash! Scum!
It's coming really deep inside me!
If this... If this keeps up, I'll... No!
How long can you hold on for?
It's just rampaging around as it likes inside me!
She's mine...
What's with that sloppy face? Is his better than mine?
You're such a pervert, Airi!
Screw you! You idiot!
You're right! It feels so much better than yours!
Hurry up and end already!
You're just a brain dead idiot who only
knows how to put his dick inside.
So can you endure this too?
What's going on?!
It's happening again! It's squirming around inside me!
What kind of dick is this?!
No! No! I don't want this, but my body's...
No! I don't like this!
You about ready to cum?
Does it feel good?
No, I can't do anything about this anymore!
You're mine!
I won't forgive you if you cum without my permission!
You perverted daughter!
Are you an idiot? Who's yours? You scum.
Knock it off already.
You really think this is enough
to break me? You scum! Idiot!
But you look like you're about to cum.
I'm not gonna cum from something like this!
Cum all you want. Flaccid dick! Trash dick! Pervert!
Don't get the wrong idea, you idiot!
I'm going to make you cum!
Huh? What are you saying?
I told you I'm not going to cum... Hey!
This is the end!
What's the end? Are you listening?!
You piece of trash! You...
Hey, stop trying to make my Airi fall for you!
You're not gonna get away with this! You...
You scum! I'm not anybody's thing! You idiot!
I definitely won't forgive you!
I'm going to make you pay for what you did to me!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч