It's so cold!
Don't come close to me, trash.
We'll be warmer if we're closer together.
I don't want scum like you touching me.
Who's fault is it that we're in this situation, anyway?
It's your fault, isn't it?
It's cold! Do something!
Geez, you're so useless, In a situation like this,
you should start a fire, or call for help.
We could just wait for the blizzard to die down and go back.
You're making such a big deal out of this.
– Idiot! What are you doing? I told you, I'm cold!
– Yep, I'm an idiot.
Hey, what are you doing when it's this cold?!
It'll be fine as long as we hold each other.
No, stop! Not in this cold weather, you idiot!
Yes, resist some more.
Your ski wear is pretty good.
Stop! Don't strip me! I'll catch a cold! I'll die!
I'll warm you up.
Don't rub them! Not here!
Looks like it feels good.
It doesn't! Stop touching me there!
Stop pinching it!
You really think I'm going to suck this?
Stop moving your tongue like that!
Your gloves feel good.
No! Don't move! Stop, you idiot!
It'd be bad if I got anything on your clothes, so suck it.
I told you, I don't want to!
You're not allowed to cum! Trash!
Your clothes are rented,
do you really want to return them smelling weird?
You're the worst. I don't even want
to do this... You better be thankful!
Yeah, I'm really thankful.
Sorry, you're just so full of it
that I accidentally bit down.
Nobody will take care of your dick, other than me.
No! I can't keep sucking it like this!
Hurry up and cum!
What? Why isn't it getting smaller?
Geez, you're such a pervert.
It won't get smaller until I put it in you.
Hey, seriously, stop it already!
Was this your plan from the start?!
You're the one who fell in the first place.
What? That's because you weren't
helping me keep balance!
It's your fault, because you weren't helping at al...
We seriously can't be doing this he...
Your trashy dick is playing with my pussy!
No, your trashy dick isn't allowed to use my pussy!
Your face is saying otherwise, though.
It's not because your dick feels good!
You're just wasting your time if you move like that.
Why? Why does it feel even better than usual?
You're fucking me while holding me up!
Your dick is going so deep, it's dangerous!
Don't put me in this position, you idiot!
Oh god, this position feels so good!
Feels good, doesn't it?
Screw you! You're always putting your
filthy dick inside me whenever you want!
Oh no, I think I'm gonna cum!
No, are you stupid?
You're going to cum inside me?!
No! You can't! You're not allowed to cum!
No! Don't!
It's coming out... so much of your milk is coming out, Papa!
No! I'm peeing! No!
Why? Why did it feel so good?
Oh, a raccoon.
Onichichi Transforming Vacation
Fun with Small Cheeky Raccoon
The snow is so white.
The snowy countryside scenery is nice, isn't it?
It was worth dragging you out here.
Too bad Marina couldn't come.
You're horrible, Dad. I hate you.
Buddhist
memorial
service
Test
How is this any different from how you
usually screw me with your shitty dick?
This is so nostalgic.
Back in the day, there was a girl
in the neighborhood who I looked up to.
She was a student here.
Did she have a nice ass or something?
Don't be silly. She was nice.
She was very mature. She was my first love.
First love? You mean your first crime, don't you?
I didn't do anything to her!
More like, she never let me do anything.
She even promised me that we could...
Maybe she figured out what you're
really like and decided to run.
Huh? Kou-chan?
Mari-neechan?
Mari-chan?
Ah, it's already that time of year, huh?
When you come back here.
You've really grown.
Back then, you only came up to around my butt.
Hey, don't say it like that.
Your cute lover over there needs to know everything.
H-Hey, we're not lovers!
H-Huh? You're not?
Huh? Wait, does that mean you two are... Fuck buddi...
No! I'm his daughter! His step-daughter.
Oh, is that right? Well you are at that age, Kou-chan.
Hey, Mari-oneechan, you're older...
Hey, that's rude.
You still have no delicacy at all, huh?
Are you free tomorrow?
I'll take you someplace nice.
A place that'll get him really embarrassed.
You were really made a fool of, weren't you?
It's not like there was anything I could do.
I'm looking forward to seeing her
embarrass you tomorrow.
Bathroom...
This is kinda embarrassing.
Mari-san definitely doesn't
seem older than that scumbag.
I guess they were friends from back then?
Hey, what do you think you're doing here?
We can't do anything, okay?
I know I'm cute and all,
but we can't do it right here.
Yeah, you're cute. You done with the bathroom?
Dad's gonna use it next.
Hmph. Whatever, being touched by him
only makes me pissed, anyway.
We're going to our relatives house,
so you need to hold back a little, okay?
You think I need to hold back? That's funny.
I wasn't expecting him to do anything...
I just want to do this...
It's not because of him that
my body is acting this way.
Papa...
I knew this would be the place.
This really takes me back.
To your peeping, raping, and exhibitionism days?
Hey, that's rude... wait,
what do you mean by exhibitionism?
Well, Mari-nee and I used this room
to kill a lot of time in the past.
Your true intentions were probably
written all over your face, though.
He was always asking to touch my boobs
or kiss me. It was tough being his tutor.
Seriously? That's gross.
That was just because I was young and stupid.
Though, she never let me do anything,
even when I got good grades.
Really? I don't even remember.
Let's put that aside for now, though.
Airi-chan, come over here.
Huh? What? Where are we going?
So this is what this school's uniform is like.
Your uniform is so cute!
That's the uniform I wore
when I was enrolled here.
I think you can tell, but back then I was kinda...
I doubt he cared.
Yeah, but that was kind of vexing in its own way.
Well, you're good to go.
Hey, wait! You're wearing Mari-neechan's uniform?
She let me try it on.
You don't have a better reaction than that?
Your daughter just changed, you know?
Or maybe you're remembering me from back then?
Oh, yeah. It looks good on you.
Well, Airi looks good no matter what she wears.
Wow, since when did you learn those lines?
Well, I guess I'm up next.
Mari-san...
Hey, what are you doing? Mari-san is here!
She always takes her time changing.
Just until she comes back, okay?
Screw you! Stop messing around, trash! Scumbag!
Shut up! If I said we're gonna do it, we're gonna do it!
Seriously, this is bad! This is going too far! Stop!
I said stop, didn't I?!
Stop, you animal, trash, pervert!
Yeah, I'm an animal. I'm trash!
If it means I can do it with you, I'll be anything!
If she sees us, we'll be in trouble.
Why'd you put it in me, you dirtbag?!
You're seriously complaining?
I'm serious! Stop!
You horny animal! Pervert! Scum!
Wait, seriously? What's gotten into you?
You're acting weird.
Are you trying to get me to stop? I'm not gonna.
You're nothing but a perverted old pedophile
who gets aroused from his daughter.
Cut it out! Wake up!
No, stop! I'll be seen! I don't like this!
You get excited by the idea of that, don't you!
Shut up, I don't! Your always do
things that I hate! You're the worst!
You love verbally abusing me when
you feel good, don't you? How cheeky.
Take it out! Scum! I'm not feeling good from this,
I definitely won't cum! Stupid!
You're being so rough!
Are you seriously going to cum in me?
No, you're being so rough!
Stop! Don't! Don't! Don't!
It's shooting inside me! I told you not to!
That was great. It felt good, right?
I told you, it didn't feel good at all!
This should just about do it.
They'll be so surprised.
Sorry to keep you waiting...
What are they even doing?
Mari-san, listen to this...
Wha... Airi?!
Huh? But you're right here... What?
M-Mari-neechan?
How's my Airi-chan cosplay?
Cosplay? You look just like me!
Wow, you can't tell the difference at all.
It's like looking into a mirror.
Mari-san, you're amazing.
Can you teach me how to do that?
Kou-chan? Wait, no... Dad?
Airi called me Dad!
Thought as much.
Kou-chan, you said that she was your daughter,
but she's actually your girlfriend, isn't she?
No, she really is my daughter.
Yeah, I really...
Well, It's not that important.
Oh, it's not?
It's now or never, for me.
I wouldn't ever have the courage
to do it unless it was like this.
This has always been on my mind, so... You know?
Mari-neechan...
Just call me Mari, Kou-chan.
Wow, it gets like this?
It feels good if I do it like this, right?
It's sour.
It's so hard, yet also soft... It's so strange.
Hey, Airi-chan, why don't you join me?
Huh? Um...
A double-Airi blowjob? Awesome!
It feels so weird licking his dick along with
someone that has the same face as me.
I'm happy that I got to do this with you, Airi-chan.
You already licked it enough.
Why don't you try somewhere else?
Huh? I guess I'll lick his balls then.
You feel like you're going to cum
now that we're both sucking your dick?
You can cum all you want.
Just let me drink your cum, Kou-chan.
Cum!
Wow!
It's so bitter!
Wow, you drink it so easily.
That's because, um...
Was that your first time?
O-Of course it was!
I knew what to do,
but I never put it into practice!
That's such a waste, you're so cute.
Geez, you really don't know how to be subtle, do you?
I'm gonna suck the rest of your cum out of you.
Kou-chan, this is so embarrassing.
Seeing Airi all bashful like this is so refreshing...
You're rubbing my boobs!
You're going to change their shape!
Kou-chan, take my first time!
You're wet.
No, don't say that to me! It's so embarrassing.
It's going in! Kou-chan's dick is going inside me!
Kou-chan, go all the way inside me.
Hurry! I want us to be connected, now!
You're all the way in!
My stomach is completely filled up with you!
I'm so happy that you're my first!
Your dick is going so deep into me, my pussy is going crazy!
Ah! Thrust your dick even deeper inside me!
Airi-chan is attacking Kou-chan, too!
You were so rough when you were taking my first time...
You completely ignored me.
I'm starting to get really wet.
Airi-chan, you're so bold.
It's because that's what this guy likes.
Really? You're such a pervert, Kou-chan.
Hey, that's not true. What are you saying, Airi...
If you have time to talk, then make me feel good!
I know what I need to do.
I'll make you feel good too!
You're sucking on my pussy!
This is how you do the cowgirl, right?
I only know about it, but I've never done it before.
Seeing myself move my hips
like that makes me feel so weird!
What's this? My stomach feels so good!
Mari-san, that means you're going to cum.
It's your first time, but you're going
to cum from that trashy dick.
It feels so good that I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum just like this!
No, what is this?
I...
It's shooting out into me!
I can feel it flowing inside me.
You and that crappy dick came at the same time!
I guess I don't have a choice,
so I'll let you put it inside me, too.
You're hard again already? Your dick is so energetic.
I'm such a nice girl,
helping this worthless dick feel good.
I'm even nice enough to do it for you.
Your dick is so happy.
It's bulging inside of me!
No! Using this trashy dick like this is weird!
If this keeps up, I'll cum!
Don't be so rough!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
You're letting out so much cum inside me again!
Airi-chan, you're so dirty.
I'm not dirty at all!
I don't feel anything from this.
I'm not happy because his crappy dick milk came out!
Thank you, Airi-chan.
I got the courage because you guys
called out to me that time.
I pulled a little prank on him back then.
It traumatized him, and he became kind of warped.
I was worried about him,
but it seems like I didn't have to worry at all.
Huh? What do you mean?
Mari-san? What are you saying?
Hey...
They're calling for me. I gotta go now.
Kou-chan is a pervert,
but take good care of him, okay?
Airi! Airi! Airi!
Onee-chan...
What am I doing here?
Airi? You know who I am?
Airi, are you okay?!
We passed out? We did?
I don't remember anything.
I don't even remember collapsing.
That was dangerous! They only found you
because a raccoon was making a lot of noise.
Even the locals don't know that area well.
It's a miracle you two were found.
You said the blizzard would pass quickly.
You just say whatever you want, don't you?
Mari-neechan taught me that,
back when I was little.
Who's this Mari-neechan?
You're such a pervert, Dad. Lowlife.
Even Marina is starting to badmouth me!
It wasn't like that. I didn't do anything perverted at all.
You only asked if you could fondle
her boobs or kiss her, right?
Airi? Wait, so that really wasn't a dream...
You really are perverted.
You're a perverted idiot, Dad.
I didn't say that. Airi, about that...
Mari-san will just keep worrying about you, at this rate.
So? Just who is this Mari-san?!
Tell me, too!
Come on, you gotta tell her.
Come on! You're the guy who got possessed, traumatized,
and then became the biggest pervert, Kou-chan!
translation: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч