www.SubDESU-H.net
It's just natural, huh?
Kouzo-san, it'll be ready in a minute, okay?
Marina, Airi, food's ready!
Okay.
I'm really relieved that you're with us Dad.
I'd just finished my work,
so it was really great timing.
And here I thought I'd finally be able to walk home with just Onee-chan.
Why didn't you just go away as soon as you got your stuff?
Besides, all that lewd "research" you've been doing,
is that what you call your work?
Pervert.
Hey, that research is important to me.
It's true that testing it on Airi may not have been wholly right,
but even so—
Huh?
Why?
The door is unlocked.
Did you forget to lock it?
No, I couldn't have.
I definitely would not have forgotten.
I really did lock it.
I-Is it okay?
What if it's a burglar?
Oh, Kouzo-san, welcome home.
Were you with our daughters?
Oh, so you're back already Kayoko.
Welcome home, Mom.
Welcome home.
SubDESU-H
Vol. 1 Cheeky Jealousy Rondo
Original Animation
Oni
Chichi
There's been a few sudden changes, you see.
So I had to come back without even contacting you all first.
You have been kind of busy lately Mom,
and you don't often get the chance to rest.
Please take care of yourself.
Thank you, Marina.
It's also good that Airi seems to be getting along well with Daddy.
Yep, she is.
What? I'm not on good terms with him!
Hmph, what's with you?
Jeez, Airi, you're such a kid.
Sorry about that Kouzo-san.
I'm not a kid!
Hmph, I wonder what Mom ever saw in you.
She's just getting tricked by you.
Kouzo-san is a sincere and kind person.
Oh? Sincere, eh?
Sorry if I'm cheeky.
Sorry if I'm selfish.
Please, let me go already.
Kind...
No, stop, Dad!
Don't, please!
Besides, he treats me very preciously.
I hope you two will be able to find someone like Daddy.
Oh yes, tomorrow you have your swimming lessons right?
Don't forget your swimwear okay?
Swimming? Swimwear?
Papa, your dick feels good.
It's stirring up my insides.
Your tongue is teasing me Dad.
My pussy is getting all sloppy.
Kouzo-san, huh?
It's a bit...
Hey, what are you doing?
Mama's here you know!
She's going to the convenience store.
Jeez, stop fooling around!
Are you stupid? You scum!
What were you doing by the mirror?
Touching your breasts like that.
Oh, did you gain weight?
You!
Is that something that you should say to a girl?
Insensitive! Trash! Pervert!
Jeez, it's nothing like that.
They just, kind of... got a bit bigger...
I said stop fooling around!
Besides, who made them this big anyway?
My perverted father of course, who kept fondling and playing with them.
Is that so?
So your breasts got bigger because of me?
Hey, if someone finds us here...!
Stop it already!
What are you thinking you idiot?!
Don't shout too much, or Kayoko will find us.
Then just stop!
Jeez.
Here, I'm going to make them bigger for you.
Jeez, stop messing around already stupid!
Airi, is something wrong?
I heard you scream earlier.
I-I-It's nothing.
I was just surprised by a large cockroach.
That's not good, are you alright?
Should I bring some repellent?
Well, I think I need some,
but it's gone already, so it's okay.
I see, be careful there okay?
Jeez, he's just a beast that wants to keep on doing it.
What are you saying after startling me like that?
Shut up.
I've done nothing like that.
Stop saying things on your own, you piece of trash!
You want it inside right?
You're really not honest with yourself.
This piece of trash's dick is rubbing inside my pussy.
Stop, we're at home...
You're already this wet.
So you were waiting for me to do it.
You...!
Stop making up your own perverted delusions!
Stop fooling around!
I wasn't waiting for this!
Why is my body always like this...
This is...
This just can't feel good...
Jeez, stop inserting it inside me already.
Your words and expression don't match Airi.
Shut up.
Your trashy dick feels gross.
I want your rotten dick just for myself,
I don't want you to do it with Mama.
I'm not going to be aroused by anyone but you.
Hmph, liar.
Jeez, your dick is just way beyond help.
Impudent words.
Here, I'm going to cum inside.
Stupid, you can't cum inside!
I'm totally not safe today!
I said you can't, hey!
Stupid!
Stop moving your trashy dick already!
It can't be helped.
Jeez, there's lots of it.
Jeez, stop making me your toilet.
Yeah.
Is that so? Thank you.
I understand, Sana-chan.
You're still awake?
I wanted to be beside you.
I'd be really into her if her body was still the way it was before.
Sorry for always leaving the kids to you.
If only I had more time.
It's okay.
You're at a crucial moment,
so you need to concentrate.
Thank you, Kouzo-san.
It's the best experience to be able to see Airi-sama in her swimwear!
What are you saying Sana?
Cut it out already.
Now, now, everyone's gone already.
So let's get on with it.
I'm so excited I already wore mine though.
Huh? That's strange.
I'm sure I put it in here.
No way, why?
What's wrong?
My swimsuit is gone.
What?!
But you're supposed to be in your swimwear now!
Oh, Mister!
What?
I have no business with you.
Besides, we're about to go to class.
You're looking for this right?
Hey, why are you holding that?
Jeez, I was looking for that—
Hey, wait!
Did you look through my things again?
You pervert!
Thief!
Trash!
Oh, oh, your vigor has returned!
What's the problem with that?
You and your Dad were getting along well.
Ah, Kayoko got back home yesterday.
My oh my, are you feeling jealous because of your Mom?
Hey Sana, what are you talking about?
Stop joking around!
Of course I'm not!
Sana, tell them that it's her period today so she can't swim.
Okay, Mister!
Just give me the pictures of her in her swimwear, okay?
Hey, why are you deciding that?
You too, Sana...!
Okay, Airi.
Why don't we go to our swimming class?
And why would I wear this for you?
Stop being so cocky, you pervert!
I see.
I really wanted you to wear that,
but okay, I'll just ask Marina.
Hmph, Onee-chan's preparing for the exams.
She doesn't have time for you,
so that's too bad.
Then, I'll just ask Sana.
She'd probably be more than happy to show me hers.
Hey, you're fooling around too much!
Do you plan on raping everyone I know, you brute?
I-It won't be rape, you know?
Idiot, that is  rape!
Rape!
It will be a crime, stupid!
When the cops do arrive,
they'll easily catch you,
and it will be decades worth of life behind bars.
Your mouth is really impudent as usual.
If it's come to this, then my new drug will...
If someone like you remains unbound by the authorities,
everyone I know will just be violated by you.
Which is why I'm going to specially allow you to see me in my swimwear.
What? Why here?
No will come here at this time.
Only I can see you in your swimwear.
You're just saying what you want to say, idiot.
This is your exclusive opportunity, so be grateful.
Hey, you're getting too excited from this.
Stupid, stop fooling around...
You...
Jeez, I'm completely disappointed in you.
You're getting too aroused, you idiot.
We can't do this you know?
You're also going along with it.
Don't try to fool me.
I'm not getting aroused at all you piece of trash.
Doing it while wearing this...
It's just for this one time!
This, trashy dick...
There, keep it up Airi.
I'm the one servicing you here,
so you need to really thank me for this.
Getting totally stiff in this pathetic position,
you're just a piece of trash getting violated by your cute daughter.
It looks really absurd.
It feels good, but I feel a bit upset.
How unsightly.
Totally exposed while your dick's being played with like this.
Hey, I'm the one trying to play with you here!
Papa's dick is entering me!
You're already this wet.
Idiot, that's...
My pussy's being rubbed hard.
Hey, don't just fondle my breasts like that.
That lewd expression.
It'd be bad if someone sees that from below.
Shut up.
I don't look lewd!
Just shut up and make me feel it inside!
No, stop!
This is...
Even if you say it with that expression.
Your dick is going deep inside me again.
You piece of trash.
Drilling it inside like this...
Jeez, this rotten dick just thrusts inside my pussy however it wants to.
I'm going to continue until I cum inside.
Give me your milk, Papa!
My insides are getting filled with your cum!
You've just made a mess of me.
You really are such a moron.
Scum.
Jeez, violating me as such a place...
You really are a piece of trash, stupid.
And you're at it again as soon as we finish.
Good grief, you're impertinence is really—
Hey, someone's up here!
What are we going to do?
Wait.
Classes are still going on.
I'm still a teacher here anyway.
I'll give whoever it is a warning.
Oh, that's right.
Kouzo-san?
No way, Mama?
Yuka, I told you not to do that here at school, right?
It's not Mama?
I'm sorry, Akitsuki-sensei.
I was so happy, I just...
Classes are still going on, right?
You told me that you’d study hard, right?
I've been found out.
But, you also weren't around.
So I...
I'm about to go back now.
So, hurry and go.
Okay.
What was that?
Well, she's just some student I know.
She's from the same class as Marina.
This is the first time I've heard about this,
and I'm not asking about that!
Anyway, put your uniform on already.
The next class is about to begin,
okay?
What did you come here for?
I'm about to study you know?
Before that, I wanted to explain what happened earlier this afternoon.
What? I don't want to hear your excuses.
Did she say something to you?
No, she didn't,
she's someone I met at the school lab...
And went on to become acquaintances from there.
The fact that you were able to hide that is quite commendable.
That's not what I'm saying!
She's one of the subjects that helps me obtain samples for my research.
Research, huh?
Samples for your perverted research?
What are you even doing there, you rotten father of mine?
I don't care what you say about me.
But Yuka is simply one of my research subjects,
and nothing else!
Yuka, eh?
And she's a test subject you say?
She called you Kouzo-san, you know?
You probably made her take your drug,
then had her suck your dick and have sex with you, didn't you?
No, she's not...
Anyway, I'm curious about this girl.
Getting involved with someone who violated me and made me a slave to his dick.
Stop it already, Airi.
Stop saying such things about her!
Did you see her face?
She made such a slovenly face,
not even knowing that she's being tricked.
She probably trusts you a lot.
And for a piece of trash like you to even be trusted,
isn't she a bit delusional?
Stop badmouthing Yuka.
Jeez, your cheekiness really never changes.
That hurt.
You just hit a girl after she laid things down straight to you.
You really are the worst.
Trash!
Scum!
You're coming way too close even for a perverted father!
Know your place!
I've been violated by you so many times that I—
It's okay if I'm the only who tries to reach for you, right?
But aren't you also getting too close to me?
Hey, I said it hurts!
I thought for a moment that you'd gotten a bit more honest,
but that's the usual you I guess.
Seems you need a little punishment.
Something befitting for a damned school girl brat!
Hey, cut it out you piece of trash, this is—
Go tell Kayoko if you want to.
Oh, should I call her and let her watch this instead?
What's with him?
Is he serious?
Is she really that important to him?
This cheeky girl needs a mouthful of my dick!
Cut this out already!
What is he thinking?
Making me do this...
Then I'll do as you suggested.
I can't breathe.
It's even deep in my throat.
It hurts.
You brute, mongrel, moron!
Stop fooling around already!
So you can still speak that way eh?
My punishment doesn't seem to be enough.
Stupid... hey...!
No way.
He's really doing it to me.
Are you wet?
Then you're the pervert, getting all wet like this after giving me a blowjob.
Shut up.
I'm not wet.
Don't misunderstand, you idiot!
Stop saying stupid and idiot already.
Your slutty body has just taken my rotten dick in.
Look who's the idiot now?
Don't come near me.
It feels gross to be touched by some pervert like you.
Gross?
Don't you mean "good"?
No, stop this already, hey!
Stupid!
This is...!
No way, just a wait a sec!
I don't want this.
I said this is your punishment.
No, no way.
Inside my butt?
No, hey, that's the wrong hole!
It won't be punishment if I put it inside your wet pussy.
Though, I think it still feels the same in here.
You brutal scum!
It's not the same at all!
I'm not getting aroused from this!
This is just... I don't want this.
Don't try acting innocent when you have that sloppy expression.
You're a real deal pervert you know?
What? You're making a fool of me by calling me a pervert now?
I'm not going to let some idiot treat me as a pervert!
You still don't understand?
This is terrible.
You piece of trash, what are you doing now?
You, what's with this?
Hey, it hurts.
Papa, I'm sorry.
Stop this already.
I'm not going to stop with that insincere apology!
Besides, you're getting wetter here as I slap you, my perverted daughter.
Pervert! Brute! Scum!
Stop this already!
What do you think of me?
A pervert like you, deserves some real anal punishment like this!
Pervert!
Shut up you pervert!
I'm not the pervert here!
This guy, he just came lots inside me...
That scum dick just soiled me.
You still don't understand my perverted daughter?
Can't you see yourself as the one who's perverted?
What was that?
Are you talking about me?
As long as you don't listen to Papa,
your punishment will continue, Airi.
Airi, what’s wrong?
You were just screaming.
Are you with Daddy?
Hey!
Is this true?
She is excellent academically, and a hard working student.
I wanted her to be so...
Anyway, can we confirm what has actually happened?
That's right.
We haven't seen Akitsuki-sensei since earlier,
but if he comes, we'll question him immediately.
www.SubDESU-H.net