I guess that's how it's supposed to be...
Kouzou-san, it'll be ready right away.
Marina! Airi! It's dinner time!
Coming!
It helps a lot to happen to meet up with Dad on the way home!
I just happened to have finished work, such a nice timing.
Geez, just when I thought I could go home with Onee-chan.
Why don't you just take the bags and hurry ahead already?
And besides, why do you even call
that fishy research of yours "work"?
You pervert.
Hey, it's an important research, you know.
Well, it might not have been the
best to test it on you girls but...
H-Huh?
Why isn't the door locked?
Did you forget to lock it, Onee-chan?
No, I don't think so.
I don't forget about these things, ever.
I definitely locked it.
Is it okay? Maybe there's a thief?
Kouzou-san, welcome back!
Oh, the daughters are together with you?
Ah, you're back, Kayoko.
Welcome back, Mom!
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Demonic Father
Cheeky Rondo of Jealousy
The plans where changed due to some sudden events,
and I ended up coming back without
time to contact you guys...
Well you have been very busy lately.
Yo haven't had any breaks or anything, either.
Please take care of your body.
Thank you, Marina.
It's great that Airi is getting along with Dad now.
I know, right?
What's with that? We're not getting along at all!
Who do you think you are!? Some guy like you...
Geez, Airi, don't be such a child...
Sorry about it, Kouzou-san.
I'm not a child!
Geez, what do you even see in him, Mom?
You're just being fooled by him!
You know, Kouzou-san is very earnest, and kind...
I see... earnest, huh...
I'm sorry for being cheeky! I’m sorry for being stubborn!
Please, forgive me!
Kind...
No, stop it! Dad, you can't!
I beg you...
In addition, he treasures Mom very much!
You girls should look for someone like Dad!
Oh by the way, don't your swimming classes start tomorrow?
Be sure not to forget your swimsuits.
Swimming! Swimsuits!
Papa's dick feels so good!
I'm soaked all the way inside!
Dad's tongue feels so good inside!
What's with this... why is my pussy so lewd?
Kouzou-san, huh...
A little bit...
Huh? What are you doing!?
Mom is here, you know!?
I asked Kayoko to go to the convenience store.
Geez, don't mess around! Are you stupid, you lowlife!?
What were you doing in front of the mirror,
pressing your boobs like that?
Did you gain weight?
How dare you!? That's not something you say to a girl!
You insensitive! Lowlife! Pervert!
Geez, it's not like that!
It was just... my boobs grew a bit so...
I'm telling you not to mess around!
Whose fault is it that they're growing in the first place?
Humpf.
You perverted old man who touches and rubs
them whenever and wherever you want.
I see, so Airi's boobs are larger thanks to Papa.
Hey! You know if we're found you... Geez, stop!
Really, what are you thinking you idiot...
Don’t struggle so violently, Kayoko will find out.
Then just stop already!
Here, I'll make them even larger.
Geez, learn some restraint you idiot!
Am? I heard you shout, is something wrong?
It's, it's nothing!
There was a large cockroach so I was a bit surprised...
Oh dear. Are you okay? Should I bring the insecticide?
Well, although I'll need it,
I can't find the cockroach anymore,
so I'll be okay...
I see. Please be careful!
Geez, you sick, touch-all-you-want pervert!
What are you saying while you are asking for it?
Shut up! That's not true! Stop saying whatever
you want, you piece of trash!
You want me to put it in, right?
You're never very honest, you know.
The lowlife's dick is... pushing its way inside...
Stop... you... not here...
You so drenched... you were waiting for Papa, weren't you?
You... Quit the perverted fantasies!
Don't joke around!
Like I'd be waiting for a disgusting penis like yours!
Geez, why is Airi's body always, always so...
There's no way... something like this could...
Geez... don't go putting your Papa-dick-inside!
Your words and your expressions don't match, Airi.
Shut up! Your trashy dick is just disgusting!
Only love Airi with this rotten dick... not Mom...
I only get excited from Airi, you know.
Stop lying! Geez, you have such a helpless Papa-dick.
A very stubborn mouth you have.
Here, I'll creampie you.
Hey, idiot! Not inside... today's a bad day!
Hey, you can't! Idiot! Stop your trashy dick!
Guess that can't be helped.
Geez, so much...
Geez, show some restraint...
Oh, I see, thank you. I get it, Sana-chan.
You are still awake?
I'll just lie beside you, okay?
She would be seriously my type before
her body had become like this...
Sorry for leaving my daughters all to you.
If only I could make more time...
It's fine.
It's an important time for you, so
you should focus on your work.
Thank you, Kouzou-san.
To think that I'd be able to see Airi-sama's
in a swimsuit... this is the best!
What are you talking about, Sana?
Quit it already.
C'mon, everyone’s gone already!
Hurry and do it already!
I've been really looking forward to it.
Huh? That's strange, I remember putting it in here...
No way, why?
I don't have my swimsuit!
Eh!? But I was looking forward to Airi-sama's swimsuit!
Oh, it's uncle-sama!
Geez, why are you here? Not like
you have anything important.
I mean, I am about to go to class.
Oh, this right?
Hey! Why do you have it!?
Geez, I was looking for it...
So, what!?
You were flipping through my bag again!?
You pervert! Thief! Garbage!
Oh? Airi has returned to what she was like before.
What happened? You've been getting
along with uncle recently.
Yeah, it's because Kayoko came back yesterday.
Oh my, so Airi-sama is jealous of Mom?
What are you saying, Sana?
Stop joking around, there's no way it's like that!
Sana, please tell the class that Airi will be
missing swimming because of her period.
Yes, Uncle-sama!
I'll leave Airi's swimsuit shots to you!
Hey, stop saying whatever you want like that!
C'mon Sana, say something already!
Well then, Airi. Let's pretend this is a swimming class.
Who'd wear it for you, you idiot!
Don't get too full of yourself, pervert!
I see... I thought I'd get Airi to wear it...
Guess that can't be helped... Maybe I'll ask Marina.
Onee-chan is taking exams and won't have
the time for that. Too bad for you.
Then, I'll ask Sana.
It seems like she'll be happy to show me.
You're really messing around too much!
Are you planning to violate every single
girl around Airi, you monster!?
It's not like I'm violating...
Are you stupid? You're violating them!
It's rape! It's a crime, you idiot!
If I send you to the police now, you'll be caught right away,
and it'll be decades in jail for you...
Hmph, impudent talk as always.
If this goes on I'll just have to use the magic drug...
If a criminal like you is let loose,
all the girls around me will get violated...
So, I'll let you see me in a swimsuit this time.
Huh? Why out here?
No one will come here during this time.
I'm the only one who can see Airi in her swimsuit!
Say what you want, you idiot!
It's a special service, so thank me!
Hey, you're getting too excited!
Idiot! Stop it already... you...
Geez.
You're getting too excited from me, you idiot!
Geez, you can't do this... you lowlife...
Airi's getting excited too, aren't you?
Stop joking around!
I'm not excited, you trash!
Not... while looking like this...
Doing these things... while dressed like this...
This is special service, okay?
You... trashy dick...
Just like that, Airi.
Geez, Airi is serving you,
so be more grateful!
You're just a miserable lowlife who gets hard helplessly
and has to attack your own daughter!
Shame on you.
It feels really good, but it's also pissing me off...
You poor thing! Your dick and how I'm
squeezing it is completely exposed!
Geez, what are you getting so serious about?
The papa-dick is coming inside Airi!
Getting so wet like this...
Idiot! Not that...
Not while you're rubbing inside my pussy!
Hey! Don't do whatever you want with my boobs like that!
It’d be bad if someone saw that
slutty face of yours from below.
Shut up! I'm not slutty!
Let's see you trying to make me feel it more!
No! Don't!
Not this...
It's not convincing when you say it with a face like that...
The papa-dick is coming even deeper inside!
You garbage! Geez, so much... inside...
This rotten dick is thrusting inside Airi's pussy!
I'm letting it out inside you like this!
Give lots of... papa-milk to... Airi's pussy!
Papa-milk is flowing inside Airi!
Getting it so dirty... geez, you're such an idiot... you lowlife...
Geez, raping Airi in a place like this...
You're the worst of the worst, you idiot!
Back to the insults right away? Geez, when will you get-
I thought you said no one would come? What do we do?
Wait, it's still class time.
l am a teacher after all. I'll send them back.
Oh, right.
Kouzou-san!
No way, Mom?
Yuka! Didn't I tell you not to do it at school?
It's not Mom?
I'm sorry, Professor Akitsuki.
I was so happy I couldn't help it...
It's still class time,
you promised to study hard, right?
Oh, you found out.
But, Professor Akitsuki wasn't there so I...
I'll be back right away, so please go back.
Yes!
What's with that!?
No, she's just a student I know and
she's in the same class as Marina!
I haven't even heard of her, and I
haven't heard you say anything!
For now just get dressed properly.
The next class is starting soon.
Huh, so what are you here for?
I'm about to start studying, you know.
Uh, before that I thought I'd explain about earlier today.
Huh? What?
Excused are just annoying, you know.
Did she say something to you?
That's not it, um, you see, she works
at my laboratory and, um...
Oh I see, getting along very well in the labs, huh?
Well it's great to know you can do
what you want in hidden places!
That's not it!
She's providing samples needed for the
research! She’s a volunteer subject!
Oh, you research. The samples for your pervert research!?
What are you doing, you shitty old man!
Never mind me,
but Yuka is just a subject for the experiment! Nothing more!
Yuka, huh? Just a subject, huh?
She calls you Kouzou-san, huh?
You’re drugging that girt and making her blow
you and doing her as you want, right!?
No with her... that's...
I mean, that poor girl! She's being turned into a slave
of a lowlife like you that even attacked Airi!
Stop it, Airi!
Don't talk about her anymore!
Did you even see her face?
Such a naive face, not even knowing she's being fooled.
She must trust you, huh?
Trusting a lowlife like you... she must be living in fantasy!
Stop saying bad things about Yuka!
Geez, imprudent as always.
Ouch... Geez, hitting a woman when you lost
the argument, you're really the worst!
Lowlife! Piece of shit!
I’m saying she should know her limits and
not stick onto a pervert old man like that!
She must be going crazy because you did her so many-
You can just blame me then.
Because you're sticking onto me just as she is.
Hey it hurts!
Just when I thought you got a little honest,
it turns out the you're still the same!
Looks like you need punishment, you cheeky high school kid!
Hey! Don't mess around, you trash! Not when, Mom...
Hmph, if you want to tell Kayoko then do what
you want. Shall I call her over and show her?
What's with him, is he serious?
What? Is that girl that important...
Such an imprudent mouth should be shut with a dick!
I'm telling to quit already!
What's with this, doing this to me?
I'll give you what you want!
It's painful... all the way down my throat...
It's painful...
You... monster! Pervert! Idiot! Stop messing around!
So you’re still talking back?
I guess you need more punishment.
Idiot! Hey!
No way, he’s doing this to me? This guy...
Huh, you're wet?
You're the real pervert for getting
wet sucking on a trashy dick!
Shut up! I'm not wet!
Don't get it wrong, you idiot!
Stop saying "idiot".
Airi is the idiot for having a body
that gets wet from a rotten dick.
Don't come here! It's disgusting to be touched by a pervert!
Disgusting? You mean wonderful, right?
No! Hey stop already, idiot! Not here!
No way! Wait, time out! No, stop it already!
I'm telling you it’s a punishment!
No, no way... my butt??
No! Not there, that's the wrong place!
It won't be a punishment if it's with
your drenched pussy, right?
Well I guess this side is just the same.
You sick monster! What do you mean,
the same!? Airi isn't feeling it at all!
I don't want... something like this!
Don't struggle with a face saying you feel good.
Airi is a true, genuine pervert!
What are you saying! Calling me a pervert like that, you...
Airi-sama isn't someone who a pervert can make fun of!
Why can't you understand?
Ouch! What are you doing, you garbage!
You... what's with you!?
Hey, it hurts! Papa, I'm sorry, hey, stop this already!
Like I'd stop with such a lame apology!
Besides, aren't you getting wetting
as I spank you, you perverted girl!
You pervert! You douchebag! Lowlife! Stop it already!
Who do you think I am!?
Pounding in the asshole is just right for a pervert like you!
Pervert! Shut up you pervert! I'm not a pervert!
This guy... spraying this much on me...
How dare you dirty Airi with your rotten dick...
Look at yourself; don't you think you're a pervert?
What's with that!? Why are you treating me like this?
It'll be continuous punishment until
you listen to what Papa says, Airi.
Airi? You were shouting, what's wrong?
Is Dad there, too? Hey!
Teachers' Office
Is it true? Her grades are high and she's a
very good student with a serious attitude.
We hope it is. Anyways, can we get you to confirm the truth?
Okay. Well, Professor Akitsuki isn't here today
yet, but when he is, we'll ask him right away.