Previously on Oni Chichi Refresh
It was exactly what it sounded like.
What? Are you going to make
me horny with that drug again?
Are you going to abuse me?
Just kidding. I know this is all really
sudden, so I'll lend you my body.
H-Hey...
Sorry, I'm just texting Sana.
This is weird. We were going to meet up.
Airi, you're really looking at your phone right now?
Huh? Doesn't it feel good?
You're about to cum though, aren't you?
Let's hurry and look for Sana.
This is bad, he's going to find out
that I've been waiting for this!
It's not what you think!
I swear I wasn't using an eggplant to
hold me over until you came home.
Your dick shot straight inside me!
You're going to spray erotic dressing
on top of the food at this rate!
From now on, I'll be your dick's slave, Master.
So please take good care of me, Master!
Welcome, Airi-chan.
Hey...
Where's Sana?!
I'll tell you after we have some fun.
You're sexy. It's plain as day.
Are you scared?
I'll be sure to drown you in pleasure.
This movement... What's going on?!
Looks like your body's feeling good.
What is this?
Is this really a dick?!
Why's it moving like that?! What's going on?!
The Small Cheeky Romantic Won't Get Hooked
You're disgusting, you pig!
I don't belong to anyone!
You're not getting away with this!
I'm gonna make you regret doing this to me!
Ah, geez. Why are things turning out this way?
The entire plan is falling apart.
Huh?
Huh?! Sana?!
Sana!
Aw man.
What's wrong, Sana-chan?
What're you doing oji-sama. Stick to
what we practiced! The camera's rolling!
But wait, huh? Sana, you're inside me... How...
I was so close too.
Test Ballsy Courage Great Success!
What the heck is that?
Sana, you're so mean. How could you do this to me? Geez.
A-Airi, I'm sorry. Don't cry.
Did I overdo it? I'm so sorry.
What's up with this whole test of
courage thing? What did you do to me?
Oji-sama didn't tell you?
Test of courage?
We were doing a guerrilla promotional shoot for a product.
Oji-sama, some others, and myself got together to plan it.
This is oji-sama's prototype product.
It's much quieter and feels more realistic
than what's out in the market right now.
Drugs come out of it too.
Drugs?
So that's why my body started feeling weird.
Exactly. It was because of the aphrodisiac.
It comes out of the tip.
Seriously? What's up with that?
I hate you Sana!
And then there's you...
We need to punish him for forgetting to tell you about this.
Well now that that's settled, Airi...
Hey... Sana, that tickles.
Your body can't wait any longer, can it?
I want to fuck you so hard right now.
Hey Sana, what do you think you're doing?
No, stop. Don't rape me, Sana.
Stop!
Not cumming feels bad and isn't good for the body, so...
I'm gonna break down that strong willed attitude
of yours and make one of my dreams come true.
Huh? One of your dreams?
Sana, let's try making a different
dream come true, huh? Yeah?
I've always wanted to get raped, but raping
someone else has been one of my dreams too.
It's coming again! That thing is coming again!
No, if that comes in me...
I don't want anyone else to have your pussy!
It's in! The weird thing is inside me!
It's messing up my insides so badly!
It feels good because of the drug, doesn't it?
Feels better than his, doesn't it?
Doesn't it, Airi?
This feels too good!
It's wriggling inside me and going
so deep... I've never felt this before!
I'm gonna cum from being inside you, Airi!
No, don't! I'm gonna cum so hard! I can feel it!
Sana, I'm gonna...
That's fine. I'll cum with you, Airi.
Sana, no... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!!
What was that? Sana, you're too good.
I'm losing my mind.
Airi, it was amazing for me too.
I've never felt this good before.
Oji-sama, did you get all that?
Did you get Airi's cuteness on camera?
We're done, onii-chan.
H-Huh?! Onii-chan?!
Yep, he's my older cousin.
My friend Shuu-san and the old
guy from back home is here too.
This is a lot bigger than I thought.
But Shuu-san won't leave the beach...
Oh, what's this? Airi, do you have a cru...
He said it was love at first sight.
With that guy.
Huh? What'd you say right now?
Huh, oh yeah, Shuuichi likes guys.
– Huh?
So he swings that way?
I never knew either.
This makes sense!
Well we'll have to help him release those feelings!
Okay then, Shuuichi-san, have fun!
We left him tied up, so just do what you want with him.
Huh?!
W-W-Wait!
What the hell?!
I'm so tired right now.
I'm not a fan of how that whole thing was set up.
I thought we'd finally be able to get a full
version of our love making, but I guess not.
It's hard to get you motivated.
Yeah, but after I found out it was
you, maybe I was a little more willing.
Really? So it felt good when I did it?
Who knows?
Sana, you...
When I was doing you, I was so turned on. Hey, Airi...
Can we do it again?
It's because of the drug. That's why my body's so hot!
You're still really sensitive, right?
Sana, that's the thing from before...
Wow it's this elaborate?
Hey, Airi, I can put it in, right?
You know, when I saw this, I...
Airi! I want to do it!
No, stop!
Airi, that feels too good!
Sana, you're so cute.
I'm starting to feel weird.
What should I do? This development makes
me so happy, I don't know what to do!
It's pretty easy to use.
Oh no, I grew a dick.
And now I'm gonna put it inside you.
I'm being raped by Airi!
No, this is so amazing!
It's going crazy inside me!
I'm pounding you with my dick. I'm raping you!
Your dick is exploding inside me, Airi.
It's rubbing inside me all over, I feel like I'm gonna melt!
This is so good.
I'm starting to feel good from raping you.
I think I could get addicted to your dick!
I've never felt anything this amazing!
Sana, I feel the same. I think I could get hooked on this.
This just feels too good!
Oh god, so good, you're being so rough!
It feels good being pounded by you.
I think I can kind of understand why his dick feels so good.
Oh no, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from being raped by you!
I'm cumming too!
Your dick made me cum.
This is just too much.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna get addicted to this.
I just want to screw your brains out.
Huh? Home already?
You should've spent more time with your boyfriend.
Maybe you swing that way now?
I like sticking it to others rather than being stuck in to!
No, wait! Not right now!
What is this? Your dick is so good!
Yeah, it feels good, doesn't it?
No! It doesn't feel good at all!
It feels gross!
It doesn't feel good one bit!
Don't put that gross thing inside me!
You dirty piece of trash!
Stop already!
I don't want this!
It feels gross!
You keep yelling at me but you're moving on your own.
You're such a cheeky kid.
Hey, Sana... wait, where do you
think you're touching?! Wait!
No! That's... Not my butt! Definitely not my butt! No!
I'm gonna put mine inside you too.
Wait, Sana! No! That's not happening.
There's no way, that's going in!
You're going to rip my asshole!
It's coming inside me! Don't put it in my butt!
You can't!
No! It's in my butt too!
Your hole is quivering, Airi.
It's so cute!
My butt and my pussy are being
pounded so hard by these dicks!
It's going crazy inside me! I'm gonna lose my mind!
This trash dick and Sana's dick are going so hard inside me!
Stop it already!
Sana... I...
Airi, you're so cute.
You're getting even cuter with my dick.
You just came earlier, right, Airi?
Next time you cum, let's cum together, okay?
So deep... It's going all the way to my womb!
It's pushing so hard!
Both my butt and my pussy are...
No... Not there!
It feels so good!
No, I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!!
Airi!
Papa's milk is dribbling out inside me.
So good! I've never felt this good before!
This feels too good!
I told you we should stop having
sex, didn't I? I can't believe you.
Our vacation's over, but I feel so refreshed.
Yeah, seriously.
And also, you know, I'm really happy
that I got to have sex with you, Sana.
Airi, you're finally accepting my feelings, huh?
You're my waifu Airi!
Yep, so that's why I'm gonna return the favor.
Just like what you did to me, I'm gonna...
What are you planning to do, Airi?
I wonder if this can cure constipation.
Airi, you're gonna make my butt go crazy!
This is your punishment for scaring me.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч