Papa...
Your dick is amazing..
Papa-dick is rubbing inside my pussy!
Just Airi's pussy is enough, right?
C'mon, Papa...
Love only Airi!
Geez, you have to be honest.
Was I causing her pain?
So she...
Airi, stop.
C'mon, calm down...
What is this? It won't pull out!
Geez, you can't pull it out!
I want you to me always be inside me!
Papa, amazing!
You're going to announce to everyone
that Airi's your one and only like this!
My hips won't stop. Why?
Yes!
Keep Papa's dick always inside Airi!
Always love only Airi!
You're going to break up with Mama and be with Airi...
You'll give your entire life to Airi...
I really can't pull out...
Mama... I'm sorry,
but Papa belongs to Airi!
I love Mama... but only next to Papa!
Oh, I see...
Then Mama has to leave, right?
Well then.
We've introduced ourselves to Mama...
Is it Onee-chan next, Papa?
Kayoko... Hey!
Airi! Get back to your senses!
You can't... Dad, this is...
Don't be mean to Marina...
Dad... Marina' s pussy is dripping...
It's drooling from wanting Dad's penis!
Onee-chan, I'm sorry...
I made Papa only for Airi!
I'll allow you to look at Papa's dick but not anything more!
I see... so it's just for Airi now...
But do let me share once in a while...
Marina, please stop Airi!
Kayoko, Sana, Yuka!
Anyone!
We've introduced to Onee-chan...
Now Papa's dick belongs to Airi... right?
Now, I only need to get rid of Yuka senpai, right?
Airi, please! Please stop!
Papa's dick is about to cum...
You're going to ejaculate in Airi's
womb, and make me pregnant!
Okay, cum lots!
Let out lots of Papa's milk in my pussy,
and you'll live happily with me and the baby!
Love only Airi!
Is he really alright?
It's a drug, after all.
He said that it has no effect on the body,
but inside Papa-san's mind, Airi might be going crazy!
That perverted research of his...
He mentioned that if it reacts with androgens...
it become hallucinating and stuff...
Although it takes time to have effect.
Hmph, it's the punishment for treating Airi like an outcast.
He was also talking about how Yuka senpai
discovered it during the experiments.
That Mikami... I can't understand why she's such a try hard!
Huh? Did you hear, Airi?
What?
Looks like Airi was jealous here even more than of Mama!
That's not it! What are you talking about, Sana!?
Stop making bad jokes already!
Ouch!
Geez, you've been way too violent recently!
You really get unreasonable when it comes to Papa-san.
Sana!
On the other hand, to think he didn't
even tell you about Yuka-senpai...
What?
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Demonic father
~Falling for the Cheeky Cute Face~
Geez, he's such an idiot...
Well, I guess the real idiot is me...
I betrayed Mama... and I'm getting
angry over pointless things...
Airi is really a child...
If Sana wasn't here for me... I wouldn't know what to do...
Even all my important practice went
to waste because of this bastard...
Well it was also unexpected that you'd be so worried.
How are you going to take responsibility!?
Papa-san, were you surprised?
Welcome back to reality!
Huh, Airi? Huh?
It's the side effect of that drug.
When you use it on males, they will hallucinate and...
There's such an effect!?
You mean, I also?
It's also hypnotic, so Yuka senpai said to use this one.
I explained what's going on about senpai to Airi.
You shouldn't let Airi worry like that.
Well then, later.
Geez, you've really gone too far.
I... my bad.
I heard... about Mikami-senpai...
I see...
I was going to explain later...
Then...
Um...
I'm sorry!
I was a bad kid...
I spoke irresponsibly without knowing anything.
No, me too...
I just didn't want to hear Airi talk
bad about others... you know...
I was being unreasonable and...
I was leaving Airi, my daughter in pain...
I've failed as a father.
Mikami-senpai... is she...
I feel bad for Yuka...
But the moment I met Airi, I...
It's fine. I know.
It's embarrassing...
My boobs... got bigger after Papa started rubbing them...
Airi's body... is changing to match Papa's preferences...
Papa's dick is getting larger...
It's rubbing against Airis butt...
Papa's dick is filling Airi up just like the first time...
Papa's dick is loving Airi...
Sorry, I misunderstood...
I thought you were treating me like an outcast...
I didn't want Airi to be worried.
I was sad that Papa got angry at me...
But I was being stupid... I'm sorry I talked bad about senpai!
I was wrong, too. I'm sorry.
I heard from Sana and understood
the situation... so I'll forgive you!
I'm sorry for drugging Papa! I'm sorry I'm a bad child!
I realized after you scolded me, so thank you, papa!
I love you, Papa!
No... Airi... spilled the beans about how I feel...
What do I do?
Papa's dick is amazing!
Be rough!
Airi, I'm really going to make you pregnant.
Papa! But there's Mama...
You can't do that...
Something like that won't be forgiven...
I'm telling you I'm going to protect you, Airi!
Papa... I'm so happy...
Airi is so happy...
Please give me your Papa milk like this!
Papa... I'm going to cum...
I... I want you!
So much milk is coming!
Papa's milk is shooting into Airi's body!
Airi is cumming, too!
Airi is so happy from Papa's milk!
I love you, Papa...
Are you going?
I'm sorry.
Do you love Airi?
Yeah.
Will you treat Airi preciously?
Will you listen to any orders Airi gives?
Yeah.
Huh, Airi?
Ah, that was tiring!
Geez, 22 minutes was longer than I thought.
Ok, end of show time!
Geez, Airi that was too fast!
I wanted to film more of the cute Airi!
Hmph, you kept quiet even though you were my close friend.
That's all you get.
Geez, but I told you...
Did you tell her about other things as well?
Airi is my best friend after all.
I wasn't going to make her worry to the point she falls ill.
I'm sorry that I said bad things about
someone else, and I did apologize.
However. I will never forgive you for hitting
me and saying horrible things yourself.
Calling me a second-hand item or a
stupid kid... saying all you want!
Hey, Airi, you...
Geez, you're really looking down on me too much!
Airi!?
Hmph, there's no way I'm forgiving you
next time something like this happens.
You have to trust me more, you stupid.
The next film time will be a hundred years later.
I'm still on break...
Airi, the clothing are done, so you should go try them on!
They seem pretty well done!
Really? Alright!
Hey, have you seen Airi?
Huh? She was here a moment ago,
did she go to the washroom?
I can't find Airi anywhere!
What do I do!? I didn't think I'd lose her... senpai!
Go look over there, Sana.
I'll look for her, too, but we'll keep things going as planned.
Ok, I get it.
This is bad, this is bad!
The beautiful honor student
might be a slut?
291: Nameless-kun
I'm going today.
The targeted girl is absent from school,
so I'll go after her cheeky sister instead.
I'll hurt her so hard she never forgets about it for the rest of her life.
Girls' Changing Room
So this is it!
True that it turned out pretty well.
I've got to try it on.
The previous one got stained by that lowlife's milk...
Don't joke around, geez.
Now that you mention it, she went to try on the outfit.
You...
Stupid, what are you doing... all of a sudden!
So this is the outfit this time... it looks nice on you.
Hmph, the previous one got dirty because of you.
The new one looks great, doesn't it?
It looks like it'll feel even better if we have sex in this.
Geez, don't ruin it with your lowlife milk so fast.
You'll have to bear with just this.
Getting so hard... what a helplessly lowlife dick...
You're making me do something like this in a
place where anyone can come in... stupid.
But Airi's the one who started it.
I just wanted to hug you.
I see... so I can stop right now, can't I?
Papa's dick is sure honest.
Even though we'd have no excuse if someone found out...
Geez...
I've said this before, but I don't care about being found out.
As long as I'm with Airi.
That doesn't make me happy, stupid.
It's twitching so hard... how filthy...
Such an idiot...
Sucking on Papa's dick in a place like this...
Airi's being way too slutty...
Who made Airi like this, huh?
You made Airi a slutty girl... take responsibility!
Airi will me my wife!
Just cum already!
Cum, cum!
Hey...
You came too much!
If it spills, you'll stain the outfit.
Geez, have some limit!
Hey! Stupid, you'll stain the clothing!
It's just for Airi, right? Then it'll be fine.
Geez... then you'd better satisfy Airi lots!
Wow... Papa's dick...
It's even better than usual!
Don't be so rough!
The outfit will be ruined!
Papa's dick... is coming to deep inside today, too!
Airi, please!
Please be alright!
Something like this... Airi!
Geez! I'm telling you it'll get wrinkled!
This stupid dick... is taking care of senpai's life?
Who'd believe that?
The operation took away more energy than expected...
The moment it succeeded...
Even so, you're adopting her... Stop acting cool!
Geez... you lowlife dick... feels too good!
I guess it can't be helped... so I’
let you let out your Papa milk...
Airi just wants it, don't you?
That's not true...
It's deep... inside again...
Somewhere like this... Airi is too perverted!
I dirtied the clothes... wanting Papa's milk!
Pee is coming out!
Airi is peeing her pants!
Bring her home next time...
She's a classmate with Onee-chan, too...
And Airi can at least say hi...
Thank you.
I'm sure Yuka will be happy, too.
Somehow that pisses me off. Hmph!
Wait, like this... what do I do?
This is bad!
Airi, Airi!
Huh, Sana?
Geez, and I thought...
Airi...
Airi... Airi!
I'm sorry... I...
No, no!
Sana? What, what happened?!
Hey, Sana, wait!
Airi...
What happened?
No way... just because of that?
I lost Airi, and I panicked...
But, Papa-san should have told me at least!
Sorry, I was going to stop Airi in her tracks...
I mean, in her pussy.
Stop it with you lame dad jokes.
Wait, I have to contact Yuka-senpai...
That was close, I almost overslept.
No way, I just fell asleep after doing it myself...
Oh, so it was there...
I didn't say goodbye properly, did I...
Wait... Masato knew about me and Dad!?
No way... Masato's hobby... was photography?
Could it be... that he...
Don't worry. It's wasn't a very deep cut.
That's what happened...
Mama looked alright, but...
We did drug him... and before I noticed, he went crazy...
It was a good thing he was worn out...
Did he see Mom as Onee-chan?
He went too crazy, geez.
No!
He should be sent to some kind of juvenile facility, geez!
Are you alright, Marina?
Huh, me? I'm fine...
I was at home after all.
Well it would be different if I was there...
No, about... him... you know.
Oh, what I think about the lowlife that hurt mom?
I suppose...
It's a time like this... and I like Sana, but... I...
It's fine, Airi.
It's a one-time thing, right?
Just leave it to Sana.
We're best friends, right?
We have to help each other.
That's true, but...
But before, Sana had...
That's that and this is this, right?
Eh!?
But...
You made me worry so much; you said you'd apologize, right?
Geez, just once.
Alright!
Taking the lowlife dick... with Sana...
I haven't had Oji-san's dick in so long...
Airi would never let me!
Well, Sana has helped me lots... so once in a while...
I didn't that Airi had such monopolistic desire...
I've discovered so much ever since Oji-san came!
Geez, be quiet!
C’mon, Airi!
Geez, Sana...
Airi, Sana is close... what about you?
Sana... Airi is close, too..
Airi... only Sana... something like this...
What should I do... such a lowlife dick...
Airi, don't forget about Sana...
Almost there until a fivesome...
No, Sana... it s rubbing my pussy...
This... Sana!
Airi! Amazing!
Oji-sama’s dick... it s thrusting so hard!
Airi... Oji-sama’s dick is amazing...
Sana... Airi wants... Papa's dick, too!
You can't! It's Sana's dick today...
Sana's pussy is so full!
This... this happened before didn't it!?
It's coming! Let out lots of milk inside Sana!
Oji-sama, go ahead!
Sana... that’ not fair!
It's Airi's turn next!
Yes! Milk!
Airi... it feels good...
Papa's dick! It's so...
Ah... Oji-sama's dick is inside Airi's pussy...
It's filling it up...
Even if it's after Sana, let out lots inside Airi's pussy!
Stir and mess up Airi's pussy!
Airi has such a lewd face... even
though she's an idol at school...
But she's showing this face to Sana...
Show me more, Airi!
Sana! Delete that right away!
There's no way I could show anyone!
I'm being filmed while having Papa's dick thrust inside me!
No... Sana's filming...
No... Sana's going to film all of Airi's lewd side!
No... Sana... Airi's not perverted! I'm not slutty!
Airi's so cute...
Show more... show me more of Airi's cute side!
Sana... Airi's cumming soon...
I'm going to cum... in front of Sana!
Even though Sana's here... Airi is cumming!
Cumming...
I'm cumming!
Airi’s pussy... it's so full with Papa-milk.
Sana... I said you can't... geez...
Stalking, assault and rape...
Looks like it'll be fine for a while.
I was really worried when Kayoko came to me,
but it all turned out well.
Their faces when I told then we'd adopt Yuka...
Priceless.
I'm almost there with the fivesome.
Let's go to the washroom.
Geez, stop it already.
Don't film something like this...
Are you listening?
Kouzou-san...
This child...
Looks so similar to Airi!
Yeah... someone told me they looked alike...
That was close! I thought she was drunk and asleep...
So they mistook this for Airi and
wrote those things about her...
The possibility of that is very high.
That's right... if this exists...
We resolved it for Marina, but soon Airi will...
It-it'll be okay.
Marina. Airi.
Mom has decided.
This is to protect the two of you. It can't be helped.
The two of you are transferring.
I've finished all the procedures needed.