Even though I told you not to go for the others...
You keep ignoring me.
Haruka is sure stubborn,
with all that jealousy.
I'm not jealous...
I'm just enduring it, hoping that you'll go back to before.
But aren't you overflowing?
You say all that, but in reality you just want cock.
Dad!
Geez, why did it become like this? This is just weird...
I haven't change, don't worry.
Just hurry and try and do what I tell you.
Don't try to fool me and get away with it.
You have to do this.
I, I get it already. Geez...
Onee-chan? Hurry and come out!
W-wait...
What? Do you have constipation or something!?
Geez, that Natsume...
Well, it's not my fetish, but...
Try pooing as well while you're at it.
Eh!?
No! I'm not going to do that!
I really don't want anything of this!
That's great, now c'mon!
Don't joke with me.
I'd rather kill Dad right now than be
forced to do something like that...
I just joking, I won't make you do it.
More importantly...
No, Dad, not so sudden!
Hey, wait...
Natsume's waiting!
That's right, we've got to be fast.
No! Not early in the morning...
Dad...
No, no, you say that, but your hips are moving.
That's not... true!
I just want Dad... to go back to normal!
I'm enduring... all of this!
I get it. I'll be satisfied with just Haruka!
Dad!
Please go back to normal... and live just like before...
That's an impossible order.
Dad... that's too... too rough!
No...
Dad's is... inside!
Haruka looks the most similar...
I'm going to spill it!
I... I couldn't hold it...
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net |#erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Demonic Father
~Day for doing the Busty Airhead~
Onee-chan?
What's wrong?
Are you okay, Onee-chan?
Do you want me to talk, too?
Onee-chan will go and convince him.
I won't let him do anything more to you guys.
Do you have to go that far?
This can't go on! It's abnormal!
You'll really get pregnant.
Oh. True...
Anyways, I will be his partner from now on.
We'll being Dad back to normal.
Don't worry, I'm your big sister.
I'll do my best to bring him back.
I actually think it's fine just like this...
No! You can't, you can't!
This isn't normal! Between father and daughter...
That's true, but...
But I like Dad...
Wait, Akira, what are you talking about!?
Besides, Natsume and Fuyu both also
enjoy it despite their complaints...
Wait, what, have you been doing it with dad that much?
Eh? Um...
Could it that even during the camp...
Uhh, that's...
Oh my gosh! Before I knew...
This is bad, this is bad!
Everyone is being brainwashed by Dad!
I have to bring you back to normal!
Listen, you can't do it with Dad anymore!
No way, okay?
'Kay...
Not just me, but everyone is...
This can't goon...
Dad's overwhelming sexual urges taking over the others...
I like Dad... and I don't want to have sex with him...
I have to endure, or even Akira and the others will go crazy...
Oh, Natsume, come with me on an errand.
I'll go, where are we going?
Natsume has homework to do, right?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, Akira, for dinner...
What? Should I cook dinner?
I guess I can't... Akira, I'll be waiting for dinner, too!
Is Fuyu in her room on her phone again!?
I've got to go warn her.
Oh, I've already talked to her. She's studying now.
Well then I'll go check...
Oh, I'll go check later.
What are you trying to do!?
Eh? What is it?
Don't ‘What is it’ me. What's going on?
Talk to Dad about it.
It's Dad' s fault. You know it's wrong, don't you!?
Having sex with your daughters...
Besides, I told you not to go after the others right!?
But you said you'd do it instead, didn't you? And you haven't.
Is it my fault now!? What is that!?
See?
I'm always hard, but Haruka would
never do it, so it can't be helped.
How does it end up like this?
I don't want you to become an adult who's
irresponsible about her words.
C’mon, will you do it?
Dad will have a bad time if it's always erect like this.
Geez, I get it... wait a moment...
From now on... if I ever see this, I'll do it...
This?
Um... penis... your erect penis...
Haruka is worrying too much.
Wait...
You see, Dad has a very strong sexual urge.
I have to be having sex all the time.
So when my well grown daughters are around,
it's not my fault that I go after them.
Wait, are you serious? Don't you get it's abnormal!?
Half of you guys came from Dad's sperm,
in other words, you're like a part of me.
Using that to ejaculate... that is the ultimate masturbation.
Dad... I have no idea what you're talking about!
Natsume and the others actually want it, don't they?
You're the only one that thinks like that!
Natsume and the others are also enduring
it and holding back for you!
That's not...
That is true! So please stop already!
Please go back to the Dad I love!
And before that I'll work hard to...
I see...
Okay, Haruka.
I understand, I was wrong before.
From now, I'll do only Haruka.
Huh?
I was thinking of treating all of you equally, but...
Oh, use your boobs next.
I don't mean that when I say I'll do it for you!
I don't want it!
This can't happen! A daughter should
not be doing it for her Dad!
Besides, something like using my boobs...
Bear it with just this!
It was like this since the beginning, but,
you're just saying pretty things and
indulging in your self-sacrifice.
That's not true!
I really want... so save Dad...
If you won't do it for me, I'll find someone
else for the ultimate masturbation.
I get it... um... wait a moment... geez...
Dad's is too big...
It's because it's Haruka.
Even amongst the sisters, you feel the best.
Even if you say that...
You aren't happy? But Dad is praising you.
Praising... on something like this...
It's very important.
Even Mom... at first she was bad...
But she worked so hard... with her small mouth for me...
Wait, I don't want to hear something like that.
Sheesh.
How selfish... does that mean you want only
yourself to be the center of attention?
C'mon, just a bit more.
I can't cum with just that.
I get it...
This is enough, right?
There's no way that's enough.
After your mouth, it's your pussy's turn.
Dad!
Hey, wait!
Hmm? You're soaked.
Did you get wet from sucking my dick? You pervert.
That's not true!
No... what is this...
My Dad's penis is...
This... stop!
My body... why?
Your penis is amazing!
I'm feeling it from Dad being inside!
I... this...
Dad... thrust more!
Drive Akira's pussy crazy!
So Akira does it like that...
This is...
No way, this is strange!
After Dad did it, it's really...
I can't, no, no! My fingers won't stop!
This is the first time I...
I can't hold back like this!
Why... is it like this...
Dad, I'm telling you you can't...
This dick... you...
Oh, uhh...
What happened? She's suddenly got a preaching attitude...
You're a perverted Papa! How embarrassing at your age!
Geez!
Hey, Haruka, that's too much to say!
Shut up!
How can you say that when your pathetic cock is so hard!?
You perverted old man!
A pervert like you should just be like
a pervert and let out all your semen!
Even though it's wrong...
An incest dick is so amazing... it s so much
better than doing it on my own...
Something like an eggplant just can't create this sensation!
An eggplant!? Haruka!?
I can't hold back!
Even though you thrust so much it's not enough!
Let it out! Let out lots!
Cover every nook and crannies of my body with your semen!
Yes!
Dad's cock is so deep inside!
Semen... so much...
Dad's... is coming inside...
Hey, Haruka. Hey...
To think she fainted from the orgasm...
Looks like she is the one most similar to her mother.
Huh, where's Haruka?
She's at her part time.
They wanted more help all of a sudden.
I see, oh dear...
By the way, where is she working?
Geez, have you forgotten?
It's the family restaurant on the corner near the station.
Really? I can't seem to recall...
I think I'll go check.
Oh, buy some milk when you come back.
Even if you drink milk, you won't grow anymore.
Especially your boobs.
Shut up! Hmph!
Welcome!
Is this everything you've ordered?
Okay!
Haruka-chan, over here, too!
Coming!
Haruka-chan, here, here!
Thank you for waiting!
Onee-chan is really popular.
True...
But then, Akira you didn't have to come...
I wanted to have a walk with Dad.
You can't go for Akira and the others, okay?
You did it with Onee-chan, huh?
But you wouldn't do it with me.
Onee-chan!
No way, what's up?
We wanted to see how you are at work?
Huh? What's with that?
So embarrassing...
Oh, is the usual okay, Akira?
Yup.
Do you come here often?
Yeah, the sweets are pretty popular.
Besides, Onee-chan is here, so I can get treats sometimes.
Oh, that's the manager.
He's really handsome, so some people come here to see him.
But I think he might be after Onee-chan.
He's always talking with her.
But then, Onee-chan is...
Dad?
I need to use the washroom.
O-Okay.
Huh, where's Dad?
The washroom, he said.
Oh, I see...
But it'll melt if you don't eat it quickly.
I'll go tell him.
Dad?
What happened? Water's all over the place.
I have to clean this.
I brought the sweets, so go eat them.
There also a treat from me.
Cleaning in Process | Caution: Slippery Floor
Huh? But I told you that you could go back...
If you don't hurry, the Ice-cream will melt.
Hey, Dad!
I'm at work!
No way! You can't! No here...
I got in the mood...
Only with you, right?
If you won't do it, I'll go for Akira.
Dad...
Geez...
You can get a part-time somewhere else, can't you?
This place is popular...
And they give me many hours...
Plus, I want to work at a place I like...
You like being with that manager?
What's with that?
You want to suck his dick?
Dad won't forgive that!
What are you talking about!?
There's no way there's something like that!
Don't have those weird fantasies!
That guy was staring at your boobs!
His eyes said that he wanted to violate and impregnate you.
That's you, Dad!
There's no way that's true! The manager is a good person!
You never know what he's plotting behind you.
I already tell he's got a crazy sex drive like me.
That's...
Maybe it's because of your uniform, I'm fast today.
You don't want to stain your uniform right?
Be sure to swallow it all.
No way, like this...
No!
No way! Stop already!
I have to get back to work!
Dad! Hey!
Makino-san?
Manager!?
Are you alright? Should I help you with cleaning?
I'm... okay...
I'll be done... soon...
You're cleaning with the door closed...
It's the men's room... so I thought it might be hard
for the customers to come in if I'm here...
So I closed the door.
That's thoughtful. As expected of you.
Thank you...
Stop Dad! He'll find out!
I really love those things about Makino-san...
How dare he use this as an excuse
to say something like that...
There are few people who are thoughtful
like Makino-san that come here to work.
And also, you're really cute...
Makino-san, did you say something?
No... it's just a little embarrassing when you say it like that.
Sorry, what am I saying...
But I just... wanted Makino-san to know about my feeling...
Woah, is he going to confess at a place like this?
What should I say...
I can't help but take notice of Makino-san all the time.
Even before, the others got mad at me,
and said “you treat Makino-san
batter than others!" and stuff...
Even though I didn't mean to, but I ended
up leaving that impression...
I know this isn't fair to Makino-san, either...
Not fair to Haruka? Is he acting as if she's already his!?
Did you have sex with this guy?
No I haven't! What are you talking about!
Even my first time was with Dad...
I've only done it with Dad...
It's embarrassing, but...
You are happy with me, too, right?
This is...
I don't know!
So he's having fantasies...
No way, but, the manager's a nice person...
But he's saying so many odd things.
So, before Makino-san says anything...
That's, true but...
I thought I'd say it... you know...
But, I don't know the manager that well..
From now... with me... um...
Besides, he's not my type...
If it's what you want,
I see... looks like it's hard for this guys, too.
don't hold back. You can be beside me.
It's about time I'm tired of hiding.
Geez, stop already! I like my part-time!
But then, when someone like that's around...
He treats my nicely, so I thought he was a good person...
So only to you, huh?
But, isn't this actually bad?
I just have to act like nothing happened!
Even if you say that...
Umm, there's panic over there?
Oh, I'm so sorry, I'll be there right away.
Then, I'll talk to you later, Haruka-chan.
Dad is here too, right?
Huh? Akira?
Hmm, I don't know... He might be?
Well, I'll go home first. Dad.
Geez, Dad, Akira knows!
Hey, wait Dad!
Don't you understand the situation!?
Stop!
If someone comes in, they'll hear!
Haruka's the one who's so turned on!
As expected, you're a slut.
That's not true!
Having it inside at my work place...
Such a large dick being so rough, I...
It's Dad unprincipled dick that's wrong!
You can't stand not being inside my pussy!
Geez, you perverted dick!
Haruka, your voice is too loud, someone will find out!
Dad was the one who said he didn't care if anyone found out!
Making me like this...
What are you saying after all that!?
A pervert who thrusts his dick inside
his daughter trying to preach now!?
How bad of a failure are you!?
Hey, your personality changes too?
You're really like your mom.
It's because you put your dick in, I'm going crazy!
You know I have to go back to work with
a dripping pussy filled with semen!
Even though I can't... no! No!
A load of pervert milk is going to be inside me!
You're going to ejaculate!
What do I do... my body...
Is going to be... like the sweets...
Filled with thick milk!
Cum! Cum!
What do I do...
Dad's not changing at all...
He's still coming after my body nonstop...
If this goes on, he'll soon get bored of me, and
again he'll go for Natsume and the others...
I can't! No way, no way!
I have to stop Dad in his tracks!
Dad... what's wrong?
Ah, um, you know.
Dad? Could it be he finally realized?
He's here to apologize for the wrong things he's done?
If that's the case...
You know they say after your hunger is
satisfied your sexual hunger comes.
I'm pretty sure no one says that...
Haruka wants her dessert milk, too, right?
I don't want...
But, if I don't do it, Natsume and the others will...
You're anticipating it, aren't you?
As expected of my daughter.
Haruka is the most like Mom.
What's with that?
Mom was also like that, yearning for
it while saying ‘no’ all the time.
Haruka is the same.
Your body can't bear it.
That's not true! I'm enduring this to stop Dad!
Enduring, huh? You're enduring from admitting your lewdness.
What are you saying!? No, that's not true...
No... that's not...
Holding back is not good for your body.
Amazing! Even though this is wrong,
Dad's dick is so energetic!
Even though I'm saying no, it s coming deep inside!
Incest dick is being so rough!
You're thrusting so much!
Even though I'm your daughter this feels so good!
Looks like Haruka's body might be
the most compatible to mine.
Geez, Dad!
You say the same things to Natsume
and the others don't you!?
You thrusted in so many times...
Even my womb gets filled with semen, I'm going crazy!
You've let out so much even the
baby will be drowned in semen!
Even though it's your daughter's womb,
you're letting out so much!
This incest dick...
Is going to get me pregnant with a baby!
So much is coming!
Dad's dick... you pervert!!
Haruka's also a pervert.
I became a pervert, too!
Having sex with Dad... being creampied...
This... feels too good!
I'll get Dad's child...
I'll... become Dad's bride...
Let out your semen... creampie me more...
Give me a baby!
It's really... going to come!
Semen... into my womb...
Semen!
So much! It's flowing in!
Dad's dick is still so large!
There's still lots and lots to go!
No way!
My womb is going to be incest creampied again!
Dad's dick... I have to tame it... but...
It's teaching weird things to my body...
Dad's milk from just now... is spilling out...
It's such a waste!
You're thrusting... so much...
Dad... let it out!
Before the stuff from before spills out, let it out!
Let out lots into my womb!
I'll be sure to let out lots and knock you up.
Dad's milk... again...
Come! Milk!
Come!
Semen is coming inside...
So much inside my womb!
Even though I'm your daughter... I
definitely got pregnant from this!
She definitely likes him, right?
Yeah, I think so.
She says it's for us, but she's actually enjoying it!
What should we do?
Even though she complains all the time, she won't let go.
Yeah.
Even I haven't had it that deep inside.
No way, me?
That's... but...
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Um... Onee-chan... what should I say...
Ah, screw it. It's about you keeping
the lowlife dick all to yourself.
Keeping it to myself? I'm doing it for everyone...
Don't lie! that's just your excuse!
You just want to make it your own!
Onee-chan is the most perverted of us, after all.
Even just now, you had such an expression...
Natsume!
Huh? W-What?
W-What's that?
You were peeking? No way!
But, Onee-chan's voice was so loud...
If you come so deep inside...
Dad's milk is going to pour so deep inside,
I'll get pregnant!
Um, that's, um...
And your voice is also pretty loud when you're doing it alone.
Eh?
Wait, um...
You were doing it so rough with Mom's favourite toy.
Even though it was too big for me...
Onee-chan, you're too much of a pervert.
Natsume... I... umm...
Geez, just admit it already!
We want to have sex with Dad, too.
Eh?
But something like that... you can't!
No, no!
Geez, stop it. I'm doing it with Dad.
Me, too.
No way... I can't let them go down that path.
I have to do something!
Dad's is so amazing!
This is bad!
Dad's penis... I can't leave it alone...
I have to keep it inside me!
I wonder what is this?
I'll squeeze it until you can't do it with anyone else!
I have to tame Dad's dick!
I have to keep it inside my pussy!
It's coming!
Dad's dick is so full deep inside!
It's thrusting so much!
Can we also have a share?
After Onee-chan has squeezed him... just a little...
Eh!? That's not fair, Onee-chan!
Come, Dad!
Creampie inside Haruka's pussy again!
Give me the root to a baby!
Fill me up! Come with lots... of Dad's semen!
Come!
I love Dad's dick!