Because I love you, Dad...
So let's do this together... okay?
Geez...
It's all your fault, you know.
Onee-chan is really scary when you make her angry.
I didn't want to say this since we're here, but...
Airi!
Try to be more modest!
It's-um...
Yes, that's it! Th-That's because he's a pervert.
Besides, I didn't know anything.
Hey, that's not how it was.
"I love you Papa.
Just keep it in me"
What in the world are you saying?!
Stop messing around!
Dad!
Even if Airi said that,
you're still a father.
Please do not forget that.
Oh, now I understand...
Marina, you're jealous, aren't you?
Eh? What do you mean?
Don't say such weird things...
I see. I see.
I'm sorry, Marina.
Wait, Dad, don't...
Hey, Airi, help me out here!
Hey!
Hmph, already getting in the mood for it again?
Idiot!
Airi...
No...
No, Dad.
I said stop.
Dad, don't!
I'll take good care of you, Marina.
Let me go.
Dad!
This is great...
Wow...
Dad's cock...
It's inside me!
No...
Dad's cock is too intense...
Dad, you're already...
How do you compare mine with his?
Mine is better, right?
Dad..
What are you talking about?
Taking my first time away from me...
Well, your virginity's one thing.
My first kiss
was taken by you, Dad.
Even your first kiss was his?
Huh?
It wasn't that jumbled up.
At that time, we were only supposed to study...
He was a bit flustered,
but I didn't have the guts to do that.
I was also able to move the topic aside.
Anyways, I can't fully remember everything.
Do you understand?
This is considered a crime.
It's forced, so it's considered rape.
Despite that, you're enjoying it.
That's-Well...
Airi didn't mind it, either.
I thought I was the only one who thought differently.
Besides, you've also been doing different things to Airi.
You're a real jerk, Dad
And that jerk's cock feels great, right?
This doesn't feel good at all.
I hate you, Dad.
I no longer want you.
You say that,
yet you're still holding my hand.
Geez, I don't want this anymore.
Why is this pervert guy...
You've been ignoring me these past few days.
No...
Dad, your cock is twitching inside me.
It's getting poured on strongly.
Geez...
You're really bothersome, Dad.
At any given time or day, you become perverted.
Airi...
It's just a cold.
She'll be me.
She already had her injections.
I hope she gets well soon.
Okay.
Why don't I insert a suppository to make her feel better?
I'm just kidding.
Are you getting jealous?
Isn't that obvious?
What were you thinking?
Geez, you must choose a proper place.
No...
I don't want this.
Hey,
what are you doing?
Don't...
Inserting it so suddenly...
Dad,
please do it normally
Yeah, I'll pour it in normally.
Mama?
What? Already?
Impudent Secret Hot Spring Encounter
Please give me candy, Mama.
Here you go.
It seems to be a minor case of memory defect.
She'll be fine.
She'll be back to normal in a few days.
Are you sure?
Could it be that simple?
What a weird doctor...
Airi, will you play with Papa?
Papa?
Airi finally said "papa"!
Marina, she said "Papa"!
Papa!
Hasn't she always said "Papa"?
No, she usually says "cock" along with "Papa."
As in, "Papa's cock."
Airi's quite honest now.
She'll listen to anything that Papa says.
Yeah.
Good girl.
Let me give you candy as a treat.
Okay?
Here, Airi you like this right?
Mama...
No violence allowed...
Oh, so Marina's the mother?
Guess a young wife's useful at times...
Dad,
this is too sudden...
Airi's currently...
It's okay. Just stay here...
No way. This isn't okay...
Airi will...
No...
Don't fondle my breasts.
My nipples are getting pinched.
No, Dad...
Airi is...
Don't look, okay?
Close your eyes, and be a good girl.
It's going deep inside me.
My pussy is being penetrated by Dad's cock.
No, Dad.
Airi's watching...
She won't remember this...
Oh, what's this?
Are you getting more wet than usual?
Dad's cock is grinding me...
Are you getting aroused in front of Airi?
You're such a pervert.
That's not true!
I'm not a...
Your cock's making me
making me shake like this...
This is terrible.
I see. I see.
So you've become quite the fine daughter...
Airi, you can also...
Airi...
Mama's great...
Mama...
Airi, what are you doing?
What in the world are you doing?
Wait....
No way, Dad.
What does this mean, Dad?
It's getting bigger?
It's bigger than earlier...
Dad!
This is-
It's already in me...
It's terrible. It got bigger when you saw Airi...
It's this big? Why?
No...
This is-
Why am I feeling this?
And I don't even want to...
It's rubbing in me hard...
Mama...
Oh no..
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming...
Mama...
It's milk..
What is it, Airi?
So you're interested in this, are you?
Do you want to lick
That was terrible.
You've made a fool out of me, Dad.
Geez, I'm going to take a bath.
Airi, let's go.
Mama...
Dad.
We're going to take a bath.
Yeah, you did...
The family bath is open right now.
Family bath?
Look,
there seems to be no one using it.
We can rent it out.
No, I said I want it to be just Airi and I...
Mama...
Airi, you can come here too.
No, I hate Dad.
You bullied Mama.
I didn't bully her.
Mama said she wanted it, so I did.
Hey, Dad...
Don't say such weird things...
Don't...
Dad...
Airi, hey.
Wait...
Boobies!
Oh, so Marina is the type of pervert
that gets aroused when kids suck her breasts?
What are you saying?
Hey, don't...
Even you are...
No, don't...
Don't do it in this kind of place...
Someone will see us...
No! Dad's cock is rubbing against me...
Dad?
No.
Kids aren't supposed to go that far...
Your cock's amazing.
Mama...
Dad,
you're also doing Airi.
You set up this whole thing...
Yep, that's the body of a healthy adult.
This is so good...
Getting my pussy rubbed by Dad's cock...
Mama...
Dad's cock is too much...
It feels great...
It's even better than usual...
My pussy will break...
No.
If you keep thrusting in like that...
No...
I'll cum in this place.
I'm cumming!
You have absolutely no control, Dad.
Even when Airi's in this state.
Geez...
What will you do if she never regains her memories?
Don't say such scary things!
But we don't know for sure.
There is no proof that she'll be back to normal.
Mama, I want to take a walk.
Okay.
Let's take a walk.
We are preparing your meal.
We'll return by dinner time.
It's a great place, isn't it?
I wish we could stay here...
I want to pee.
My, my, that's not good.
Here, Airi...
Do it here.
I'll be waiting at the other side.
is Airi peeing turning you on?
What's wrong, Marina?
You're always the one who makes the move.
It's only natural for me to do it once in a while.
It's getting bigger.
It seems you want it now.
A-Airi's back.
I want this cock a little longer.
Hey, Marina...
Just wait there, Airi.
I'm making Dad feel good right now.
Here, Dad,
you can cum here.
Release it.
That's a lot.
So you still have a lot built up inside?
You have to release more of it.
Dad, give it to me.
Your cock...
Your cock is entering my wet pussy...
Wow...
The cock is stirring me up.
My pussy can't get enough of it.
What's wrong with you, Marina?
Taking the offensive like this.
This is just mine...
This belongs to my pussy.
Yeah, it's yours.
Dad's cock and "milk"
are mine.
This great feeling...
All of these are mine!
Just continue and pour your milk in my pussy.
Yes.
This is great!
My pussy feels good, Dad.
Yeah...
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
Will she get better if she sleeps today?
Wouldn't she?
But wouldn't it be better if she stayed that way?
It's possible for us to escape and go somewhere far away, right?
Marina, what are you...
Because, this isn't something normal!
Doing something unacceptable like this...
Even before, I've always tried to hide it...
The words that I said were terrible, weren't they?
That's why this is the only...
Marina...
Wait!
Calm down!
Can you answer one question for me?
0-O-okay.
Between me,
this girl
and that person,
who do you love most?
Eh? Um-that's...
I love both Airi and Marina!
I also love Kayoko!
Now, I understand.
Oh you...
Too bad...
Onee-chan!
So can you explain why you did it?
Because you seemed happy at the time...
I thought I should keep it a secret for a while.
What? How in the world?
Airi's memory returned quickly.
When?
I kind of got confused, or something...
I don't understand it myself.
When I got into the bath, I got my memories back.
Geez, you could have told us sooner.
Hey, Onee-chan didn't even notice it had come back.
I only noticed when we went out for a walk.
It's because you wore your shoes perfectly fine, without any problems.
That's when I noticed.
Is that the reason you made your move?
Were you surprised?
I've always been selfish
and spoiled...
I was trying to hog things.
What would happen if you didn't come back?
You're my cute little sister, you know.
Onee-chan...
What a relief.
I was surprised back there.
I've been watching drama lately.
I just wanted to act like the heroine of
"Loyal Wife: The Hot Spring of Shame and Rape." Something like that...
I see.
That was a bit too weird, though.
I really thought you were planning to...
What was that, Dad?
Nothing.
But, Dad, you also need to consider your daughter's feelings more.
This feels good.
It's thick.
Onee-chan, were you actually angry?
What are you saying?
That's not true.
It's rubbing in me.
Then I want some of Papa's cock too!
My pussy feels empty.
I'm going to let you have it next time.
Not today.
Geez...
So you really are angry, Onee-chan?
Dad's cock is firmly...
Yes.
And so the enjoyable hot spring trip has ended.
Dad bought Airi and I presents as an apology.
Well, it couldn't be helped, so I just accepted-them.
Don't think you'll be forgiven because of this, okay?
I want to go on another trip
Well, I suppose I could look forward to that.
Let's look forward to it, okay?
I-I'm looking forward to it.
Onee-chan, you're scary... geez.