Marina... Marina!
Yes?
It's running.
S-Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Huh, where's Airi?
She went out ahead.
Oh, no! It's this late already?!
Sorry, Dad. I'm going too.
How boring, what was that about?
While Airi's going down on you...
So you plan to put this into Onee-chan's pussy?
Although I don't think Onee-chan's a virgin any more.
"That person" probably got to her.
That person?
A-Airi...
The guy in her class...
He gets good grades, he works out...
Everyone in the academy says they make the best couple.
Although I don't know how far they've gone...
Marina is...
Airi...
Geez, don't think you're everything.
How dare you think about another woman while Airi-sama goes down on you.
Now then...
Papa, your perverted dick is getting all perky around Airi's feet.
What would happen if I stepped on these balls?
Airi won't forgive you if you're thinking about Onee-chan in front of me.
You're about to cum, aren't you.
While Airi steps on you, I'll make your perverted dick shoot out that smelly semen.
Look, you can cum.
Come on, cum from Airi's foot!
Whoa, amazing...
Airi's foot is all wet.
Papa, your semen's spilling out.
I'll get more tight on Papa's dick.
Oni
Chichi
Part 2
Subbed by YarashiiSubs
Translation - jhkplaya888, kingkouta
TLC - zhurai
Editor - enfiend
Timer - Fuko Ibuki
Encoder - WolfReborn
Second Volume "Vulgar Tidy Leggings"
Sorry about earlier.
I hadn't considered your feelings...
That's not it.
Even I...
She's actually...
But I just wasn't mentally prepared...
I think the pace we're going at is okay.
Thanks.
I can't think about anyone else when it comes to it, Masato.
Th-Then, is tonight okay?
Okay...
Marina...
I'm glad to hear that, Marina.
Akitsuki-sensei.
Da...
Hey, you can call me Dad.
And?
I'm Ono Masato.
I'm in Marina-san's class.
Ono-kun, eh?
Break time's almost over.
You should go back to class soon.
You're right!
Ono-kun, we better hurry.
I'll be studying with a friend tonight.
She asked me if I could stay over for the night...
I see. The last time was a sleepover too...
Yeah... They figured it'd be more effective if everyone just stayed.
E-Everyone there?
Amazing!
More! Pour it all into Marina!
See you...
Marina...
Since when could you lie so easily?
Is it his fault? He changed Marina from being honest...
Received Mail
Ono Masato
In the park
Re: About earlier
Ono Masato
In the park
Tonight at 10,
I'll be waiting in the park.
You could let your guard down
once in a while.
Masato
I'm washing myself more carefully than usual.
I wonder if he's expecting it?
Will he accept me?
Are we going too fast?
But everyone else is experienced at this age...
Me too...
Hmph, let your guard down?
It's more like you're trying to bring it down.
I won't let your nasty dick touch my Marina!
What's this smell?
I didn't leave anything weird out, did I?
Dad, then I'll be going.
Airi's out on a sleepover too.
Maybe you should reschedule the study day...
But, that's...
I've already promised.
Well, you can tell them something came up, right?
But today...
Sorry for having to leave you alone.
I see.
So you want that guy's dick that much?
Um...
Marina, tonight...
S-Senpai!
Thank goodness.
Hey, please. My friend's in trouble over there!
W-Who are you?
Senpai, please help!
Um, I...
Please, I can only count on you, Senpai.
Only you!
Just for a moment then...
All right!
This way!
Senpai, in here, hurry!
Hey!
W-Who is it?
It doesn't matter who...
Give me... your dick...
It's really effective.
I jacked it from papa's pocket.
Well, it should be good medicine for them.
Airi's not going to hand over Papa's dick.
How can you say that about him, Dad?
I hate people like that!
I see.
So you want his dick inside you that badly?
Or are you already sex slaves to each other?
Sex slaves?! What do you mean?
Masato and I are still...
Still, eh?
As expected of an honor student, Marina.
I love you for that, Marina.
What is this?
Why are you pulling pranks on me all of a sudden?
Are you done yet?
I'll be late for my friends.
Huh?
Ow!
Sorry, I...
Dad, you're acting weird.
You're not how you usually are.
I...
I hate you, Dad!
Hate?
Marina hates me?
Marina, how could you...
No, let go!
You're not my dad!
My real papa wouldn't...
I see.
Marina, you didn't think of me as a real father, did you.
That's not it! I'm sorry.
Well, that's okay.
A father wouldn't want to do this to his daughter, after all.
No way!
His lips... Dad!
What is this?
N-No!
I thought you'd be easier than Airi, but...
Easier than Airi?
Dad?
You'll still call me Dad?
Go ahead and do that, Marina.
Please, stop...
Dad, please...
No!
Dad... Stop!
Please stop!
What cute breasts.
Your nipples are getting stiff.
Does it feel good?
Dad is sucking my nipples!
No, my breasts... why is Dad licking them?
No, please stop! Dad...
Airi resisted more.
Marina, are you turned on already?
I knew you were an honor student, but you excel in being perverted too, I see.
Dad, no...
No, don't, Dad!
Please stop!
This is weird!
This is... this is... no!
Marina, you're dripping perverted juices.
No! I can't keep up!
No, no!
Dad, please!
Even though you say that, what's this?
No way, why?
My body wants to say no, but it's like that...
No matter what you do, you can't hide being wet.
No, Dad!
You can't do this!
Please, stop! Dad!
Do I have to hit you again?
You're so pretty, Marina.
What a good voice. Let me hear more.
No!
Dad's licking me so much.
It's so embarrassing and wet...
I don't want it, yet...
Masato, I'm sorry!
Dad, please! Dad...
Dad, stop, please...
I don't want this! Stop!
No, Father, stop!
Good girl.
You've gotta resist like that.
No, no!
Please...
Anything but that... No...
No, no!
Da...
No way...
It's just the tip.
It starts from here.
No, this is...
You're a total pervert!
No! No!
To think I could hear that from your mouth, Marina...
No, no, no, no!
No, stop!
Any more and I'd break your virginity, after all.
Keep resisting!
It hurts, it hurts!
No!
If you push in more, I'll... I'll...
It's your first time!
Dad's dick is this big...
It hurts!
Why am I doing this?
No way, no way! This is so cruel!
It's going in deeper...
This is so cruel!
I trusted you... why?
Marina, it's your fault.
You and Airi are just so cute.
That's...
Mom was too...
I'll tell her that I fell for Marina instead.
Fell for me... Why?
Why am I...
This won't... be forgiven...
I'll tell the police...
If you do, you'll be okay, but Airi and Kayoko will suffer.
It'll be your selfish fault, Marina.
Selfish, that's not...
Society is a cruel thing.
Marina, you don't know about it.
That's why you went with a guy like that.
Masato is a nice man!
He's not like you at all...
He's so much better. He thinks for my well being!
That's what you might think now.
But after what happens inside you soon...
Inside?
No way... No...
This isn't a good day for it!
Going to throw away your virginity on a day like that, that's your fault!
Then I'll substitute...
No! Stop!
No, stop!
No!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Masato, I'm so sorry.
Dad came inside me...
This is so cruel.
Dad, I hate you...
Masato...
Your boyfriend is probably doing another girl right now.
Here.
You...!
This is...
I didn't think you could do anything without that.
But I guess even Onee-chan was taken by this dirty dick...
It's already cummed this much...
Airi...
That wasn't a dream...
But Airi doesn't think anything of that?
No, Dad!
Airi!
I'm only letting you borrow it, okay?
This dick is Airi's, got it?
It's... thrusting in so hard again...
No!
Hurry and cum.
Airi's next...
No!
Airi, your tongue's hitting it...!
No, Dad's getting so big again...
It's coming inside again...
No!
Good!
Papa, you're amazing! It's so big!
More, give me more!
Your semen... give me lots!
Shoot it into Airi!
It's coming... Airi's coming!
I'm going to come from Papa's dick while Onee-chan's nearby!
Papa cummed so much again...
Akitsuki-sensei's calling for you.
Student Council Room
Um, I heard you had business...
It seems I've been hated.
Even though I helped you out.
What are you talking about?
Because of you, I...
Don't come closer!
If you want to talk, you can do it there!
P-Please stop this.
Don't do more mean things to me.
It's all right.
I won't do mean things to you, Marina.
Come on, come here.
What are you doing?
I thought I'd show you something interesting.
Wha-
Don't show me this... Stop!
If you do this...
Please, come on!
This is...
This girl is Airi's...
It's okay, no one's here.
You wanted this too, right?
You get it, Marina?
Men are simple beings.
Even if you trust them.
This is...
Why?
Why is this happening to me, Masato?
Hey, can we do it?
I can't hold back any longer.
Can we?
But, in a place like this...
Besides, you're so fast, Senpai.
I'll be better this time.
It was so sudden earlier, after all...
Besides, don't you have a girlfriend?
Although you didn't seem so interested in her.
That's not true!
If you could be quiet about that...
Even if I did stay quiet, it's not like it was much.
Well, I guess I will.
Thank you!
Senpai, you're clinging too much!
You're excited, aren't you?
Why is this happening?
I don't want to do this, yet...
Masato's doing someone else, yet...
Dad's making me suck his dick...
My body's saying it feels good!
I shouldn't be doing this, yet...
It's so big!
It's hitting me!
Huh? Is someone here...
So deep, no!
Masato! No!
Don't look!
I look terrible...
Hey, Senpai, hurry!
Make my pussy feel good!
Um...
Marina, that's...
Masato, don't look!
Dad's dick is doing something dirty!
I...
Masato's watching me doing something so dirty, but it feels good...
I'm coming!
Masato's watching me, Dad's dick is thrusting into me...
Amazing, Masato...
What's with that?
After forgetting to meet up with me, now you're trying to show me a sex act?
Weren't you enjoying it too?
And you even pressured her.
That's because these guys all...!
You're a pretty low person.
Parents having sex with their children are even more low!
Pervert.
Hey sir, do me next, okay?
He's so half-assed.
I can't hold back. Okay?
Sana...
Crap!
It's delicious...
Doing something like this right in the morning...
Dad, I'll make you feel good.
Ah, I'm late!
Onee-chan, how unfair!
Airi, you should wake up earlier.
I'm sleepy.
I was up late last night.
That's because Dad cummed so much in your pussy last night, isn't it?
Yeah, but I want more.
No, Dad's morning semen is mine.
Right, Dad?
I'll lick it up lots so that it stays healthy for the rest of the day.
Then I'll do it too!
No!
Airi, you got plenty yesterday.
But, hey.
Papa feels better inside Airi's pussy more.
Right?
Geez, Airi.
He's mine today.
Put lots inside Marina's vagina.
Okay, Dad?