Hey Dad, are you okay?
Dad, are you listening? Dad!
Oh, sorry.
You haven't fully recovered yet, so you should take it easy.
I guess you're right.
Ah, you sure are starting to look like your mother, Akira.
W-Wha... Oh come on...
Jeez Dad, what are you saying?
I-I'm gonna take a bath before I go to bed.
Okay. It's only been a week since that accident, so take care, okay?
R-Right...
Have I... become sexually attracted to my daughters?
Shit! Since that accident, I can't stop myself...
Ahh! Pervert! Noo-!
W-Wait! You're the one that came in!
Die you fat turtle! What sort of situation is this?!
You pedophile! How are you even my father?!
O-Okay, I'll get out right away!
Dad, wha-!?
You scum! You beast with a menopausal disorder!
Jeez, why was he in there?
I bet he wanted to see his daughter naked. He's the worst!
Natsume, you have to make sure before you walk in.
But I was in a hurry!
Hmph! It's his fault! This pisses me off...
Oh, that Natsume...
Damn that stupid daughter of mine, she is so defenseless!
She can't complain if she's sexually assaulted.
Even though she has a petite body, she is grown in the right places...
I guess I'll have something to drink and go to sleep...
No, I ended up seeing Dad's cock...
It was so big, I haven't seen anything like it!
Is that hard cock of his going to enter me?
No, D-Dad... Dad!
Dad-!!
Oh no, what am I doing?
presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Original Video Animation
~Volume 1~
A Foolish Hakama-clad Daughter's Repentance
Oni Chichi
What's with Habekura tripping so obviously?
Because of that I'm called... Because of that I was laughed at...
See you then, Makino!
Make sure you lock the place before you leave, oh, and don't be so down.
Heh?!
Whoa, scary!
I'm going to leave you to it.
Why am I not as strong?
Dammit! Making me do what they want...
Natsume-kun has, um... caused further problems...
Yes...
Her bad attitude from yesterday and today...
Who did she get it from?
She's the only one...
Even on school grounds, I'm-!
What? What do you want?
R-Right, I heard from the teachers that you caused another incident.
Not really.
Not really?! I heard that you physically assaulted a teacher!
That's totally exaggerated!
I just kicked a desk over and he tripped on his own!
Besides, why does this concern you?
I'm your parent! Of course it concerns me!
Your persistence is starting to annoy me...
Parent?
What parent will try and peep on their naked daughter?
When I think about you seeing me with that dirty look,
it's disgusting.
Dirty? Disgusting?
Why do I have to put up with my daughter saying this to me?!
Lately, even if I lightly graze her, she yells "assault!" or "molestation!"
If it could be dealt with by discipline from her parents...
Discipline, huh?
Was my discipline too light?
Is that why she's grown up so rebellious...
What are you doing?!
It was my fault, wasn't it...
Because of me, you became like you are now...
What are you muttering about?
Give me back my fencing stick!
Huh? Oh sure.
W-What is this?!
Y-You, t-that is, w-wha? Why?
Looks like you're the only one here.
I guess it'll be safe even if you scream.
P-Pervert! What are you doing...?
Letting it out like that in front of your daughter...
You-
I told you to quit it!
A father shouldn't be doing this!
Something like...
Wait! Cut out the joke! Stop it really!
A joke?
Don't be stupid, this is something called discipline, which a father gives his daughter!
No! Stop it! Pervert! Opportunist! Doing such things to your daughter!
You're really stupid, aren't you?
Repeating the same words like that.
No! Stop it, it's wrong!
Idiot! D-Don't grab me!
Fixing your stupidity is a parent's job.
You're breasts sure are small, Natsume!
Cut it out! Where do you think you're touching?!
Don't touch me with those dirty hands, scum!
Dammit, isn't anyone here?! Hey! Anyone!
Hey-!
You, you bully!
Oh, did that hurt?
Well, this is part of the discipline so bear with it.
No... No, No!
No...
No!
It's disgusting, dirty! Stop it!
Sheesh! All you've been saying dirty and disgusting!
This is the real essence of the training.
And, I'm about to put this essence inside you.
No! Stop it! Cut it out-!
I guess your stupidity can't be cured unless I put this in, will it Natsume?
You're not wet, but oh well.
Stop it, please! Wait-!
It's tight!
Who would have thought I'd be entering a pussy which was created by me.
It hurts!
This should make you reflect on your behavior!
It hurts...
You bastard...! You really put it into your daughter...!
You sure are tight down here...
Cut it out! Pull it out already!
Haven't you had enough by putting it in?
Oh sure, I'll take it out in a moment.
Don't think you can get away with this!
I'm definitely going to-!
It hurts!
It's coming inside!
Hmm, yeah.
I'll take it out inside you.
You bastard-! I'm going to tell Onee-chan, and the police, and-!
Oh really?
I guess my discipline is still not enough.
What are the police going to do?
T-They're going to take you away, pervert!
Looks like the blood is making a good lubricant, but we've got a bit to go...
Is this because you're the reject of our family?
What? Who's the reject?
If you tell the police, you'll find out anyway, so I'll tell you.
You're adopted.
What? That's the first time I've heard-
Because this is the first time I've told you.
I didn't beforehand because I thought you'd be a loner.
Lies! I'm twins with Akira...
Twins aren't born that easily.
You just looked like each other, that's all.
That's... That's not true!
Besides, Haruka is going to get a job, right?
It's hard even with just Akira and Fuyu...
Do you think that Haruka will support someone like you, who isn't even part of the family?
Lies...! I'm...
Don't worry.
If you do as Dad says, everything will be the same. Okay?
I... No way...
If you understand, then make sure you accept this!
No... Don't... Don't!
Discipline sure is hard work, especially with misbehaving foster children the likes of you!
This... is...
This is a secret between us, right?
We don't want you to be a loner...
Dad's going to go home first,
so make sure you finish up here, okay?
From today on, Onee-chan won't be having dinner at home, so it's only the three of us.
Oh? Where's Fuyu?
Fuyu seems to have caught a cold,
and she's sleeping at the moment.
I think I'll see how she's doing later.
Do Akira and I... Look alike?
Huh? What do you mean? Is that a quiz question?
No! It's nothing...
What's his problem? Jeez...
I'm adopted?
I don't get it...
It still feels like he's stuck inside me.
Disgusting...
How should I get back at him?
Jeez, you're still thinking about such things...
What are you doing barging into my room like this?
I'm just renting this room to my adopted daughter.
Shouldn't I be able to come here when I want?
That's not-!
Your good intentions only appear on the surface, huh?
I think I'll have to discipline you again so you'll understand.
That's a good girl, maybe if you sit still like that, something good will happen.
What the hell are you talking about?
You've already done what's possibly the worst thing I've ever experienced!
I'm doing this because you're too cute to go to waste!
C'mon, do your studies properly!
Don't be silly...how... can... I... do... such a thing?
You're flooding down here like last time,
you must be a pervert as well as an idiotic daughter!
Saying such things as 'pervert' or 'idiot' to your daughter,
what kind of father are you?
I think I've changed from that accident... Well, that, and your-
What? You're the one who... It wasn't my fault!
H-Hey! Say something!
Hey!
Natsume, you can have your bath first.
Oh, O-Okay-!
Also, do you know where Dad is?
I haven't seen him around.
H-How should I know!
Why would I know where that freak is?
Jeez Natsume...
Okay, then.
While you were shouting, you sure tightened around me.
Do you get excited when you complain?
Excited? Why would I get excited?
Oh really? Try saying "Dad you jerk!" out loud.
Be serious!
Why would I say such thing?
You... jerk!
Look you're saying it anyway.
You're starting to tighten down there, Natsume!
What are you saying?
You pervert! Idiot of a father!
A father doing such things as putting his cock inside his daughter and making them complain...
It's wrong! You insolent sadist!
Whoa! You're tightening! You're tightening around me Natsume!
Incest freak! Rape-man!
There is seriously something wrong with you getting excited like this!
Not so hard, you're... actually getting excited from me calling you names?!
From... Such a... Pervert's cock...
From such a pervert's cock,
I'm going to have semen... poured inside me!
No-!
I'm going to get fertilized by my father's dirty cock!
His hard dick is going to let it out inside my-
It's coming out...
-Ouch!
How can you kiss me with such a pleased look?
You perverted father!
Someone will see us!
Stop it already!
This place isn't used often, is it?
No one will notice that you're missing.
Even so, I haven't called absent...
You idiot!
Oh? Makino isn't here?
No, she hasn't come today.
Really? No wonder it's so quiet!
Agreed.
She's quite cute if she's quiet, you know...
P-President! Don't tell me that...
I-It's not like that!
Well, I agree nevertheless.
Don't you think?
If only she was more timid...
I'd rather be bossed around.
You tightened when they said you were cute.
That's not true...
Hey! You're overflowing...
Dammit! You don't get this wet when I praise you!
I-It's just your imagination! Pervert!
Anyway, someone who's doing this shouldn't get jealous.
You... Jerk...
Wha? No wait! Don't hold me there!
If you do that-!
What is this?!
D-Don't touch there!
No way... Hey!
I'm going to leak... Hey! I'm gonna leak!
I said that I'm gonna leak!
Really... I can't-!
No way! No! Don't!
I'm-I'm gonna leak!
N-No... No! No!
I'm wetting myself... No!
Oh, oh. What an embarrassing daughter, wetting yourself in such a place.
You-!
Jeez! Give me a break! You clean this up, okay?! Hmph!
I don't get this.
Family relation information?
Where does it say whether I'm a daughter?
Sheesh! I can't ask Onee-chan or Akira...
Jeez, I guess I'll have to ask my stupid father, dammit.
Huh? He's not here.
Is he in the toilet?
Gosh, he's never here when you need him.
Akira's voice...
N-No way!
She's so loud!
I-Idiot!
There-! Dad!
No, it's deep! Your cock is penetrating me so deep!
Dad's cock's mixing my insides up!
It feels so good!
Akira! Dad feels good too!
It's because it's your cock, Dad!
Release lots... Lots... Lots!
Please release it inside! Dad, I want you to release lots inside me!
More!
Deeper!
Cum... cum deep inside me, okay?
I want you to fill me up, Dad!
Dad... Your stuff is filling me up.
...Didn't you say that it was a secret between us?