But I wanna go with you, Onee-chan!
How can you say that?
Two girls going alone is too dangerous.
Hot springs, eh?
Sounds nice.
I have a little vacation coming up after all.
Shut up, don’t talk, you vile weed!
If we go, I’m not sharing a room with this worm.
PROMISE me that I won't.
Airi, stop being so rude…
Promise me, or I won’t go.
Thanks for breakfast.
I thought we’d finally patched things up… but she’s acting weird again.
Dad, you know why, don’t you?
Airi won’t talk about it, though.
Y-Yeah…
I hope things get patched up soon.
I want to get married with a clear conscience.
Sorry about that.
You sure are cute, Marina.
And pretty. And nice.
You’ve got it all.
Oh, no, don’t embarrass me, Dad.
We're only going this far for now.
I’m looking forward to the trip.
Looking forward?
Dad… you’re the best!
Marina’s pussy needs to be full!
No!
Airi’s pussy wants your cock, too!
Airi can’t hold back!
Hmph. What a disgusting face.
Gross.
Airi!
I’m bored.
Onee-chan couldn’t come all of a sudden.
Why does a pretty girl like me have to be alone with a gross old man like you?
Marina couldn’t help it.
And she said she’d come later.
And I have to be alone with a worm like you in the meantime?
That makes me wanna vomit.
Wh-why, you…
Looking for this?
You never learn. Try being sorry for once.
The insides are all clean.
SubDESU-
H
Oni Chichi
~Hot Springs With the Rude Little Bitch~
On vacation
Wh-what’s going on?
I feel hot.
Airi. Is something wrong?
No…
Stay away!
Your panties are all wet – what are you trying to hide?
No way. What’s this? What’s going on?
No…
Eew, he’s touching my pussy.
Stop it.
Hey… stop it!
Oh no.
My body is turned on!
Hey! You put drugs… in that last candy…
Did you notice?
It’s in its final research phases.
And only yesterday it was finally approved.
N-not again… you’ll use Airi… for your own…
Just like before.
I couldn’t turn down an offer.
But I still don’t know the full effects of the drug.
The… effects?
For men, it has great rejuvenation powers.
There’s sexual juices in the sweat that comes out.
These excite a potential partner just by the touch.
Wh… then… back then was because of the drugs…
Don’t fuck with me, you ass…
Do you have any idea how much I… you…
Well, my worth in the company has risen because of this drug.
And I owe it all to you, Airi.
You retard!
Pervert!
My worth in society is lowering while yours is rising!
You stink…
Hey…
No… don’t…
No… oh no. I’m too turned on.
You just aren’t honest, Airi.
You’re almost there, aren’t you?
Shut up, retard!
I’m not… huh?
No. Oh no.
Shit.
I don’t want this worm to make me cum… But I can’t hold back!
A-Airi?
What is it?
Did the effects not kick in?
Oh no… I’m gonna wet myself…
I want to go to the bathroom…
W-Wait, Airi, the bathroom…
I-It’s that way.
Okay.
R-Retard, you stay in the seat.
Don’t say that.
Come on, go.
N-Not like this.
You’re this wet. You can’t hold back, can you?
No… I don’t want to go now.
No… don't…
No… Eeew…
Eeew, so much is coming out!
I can’t stop it!
You worm!
How dare you do this.
You’ll pay for it.
Not in a place like this.
No… don’t put it in.
You filthy worm.
You’re overflowing with juice, you hypocrite.
It’s your fault… you… stop it…
No… no…
Wait… don’t…
Not… no… shit… you retard.
Who would willingly… with you…
Eew, I said no!
I don’t want a worm… to make me cum again…
You’re a good girl.
I’ll make you feel good.
I don’t… feel good…
So… no…
You worm!
Scum! Pervert!
Why, you… not inside…
Airi, stay there for a while so people won’t notice.
Manji Hot Springs
Hot spring eggs!
The insides are all goopy.
That’s right.
They’re all goopy just like your insides.
Jeez. You have no sense of culture, pervert.
Not yet?
How much longer?
I think she’s probably here. Marina’s email said…
Maybe that’s the place?
Welcome.
There should be a reservation under Kitsuki.
So pleased to have you here.
Come, come. This way.
Oh, one room?
That’s what was ordered…
Yes.
Momiji
No way!
Stupid Onee-chan!
I told her to get us separate rooms!
Hot springs!
There’s one in our room!
Awesome!
Maybe I’ll get in right away.
Really? Then maybe I should get in with you.
Retard. Who’d want to bathe with you? Go in there by yourself.
I’m going for a walk.
BY MYSELF.
You’re not coming along.
This feels great!
I think it’s important to relax in a place like this every once in a while.
Oopsie.
Wow, so big!
What a nice shrine.
Guess I’ll go worship for a bit.
Hey, babe, you alone?
Wh… what’s going on?
No way. Not again!
I’m really knowledgeable about this place.
I’ll give you some allowance.
Really? Then give me the tour too. I’m joining.
Airi!
Those types are everywhere.
Are you okay, Airi?
Yeah.
Wow, that scared me.
Jeez, what was his problem?
Walking alone is dangerous.
You could be attacked at any time.
Shut up!
Even when I’m with you, I’m attacked!
Retard.
You’re just so…
Hey, where’re you looking?
Don’t fuck with me!
No matter where we are or what time it is, you’re always..
You were hiding more of that?
Airi, we’ll be discovered.
I need to silence that loud mouth of yours.
You… worm…
It’s so hard…
Airi, this feels great.
It doesn’t… you stupid…
You came too much.
Hey, no, not standing up… hey!
You… I don’t wanna… I said no!
You’re pushing your hips into me, Airi.
What’re you saying?
That’s because of the drugs.
Using your own daughter in your experiments… you worm!
Well, the experiments are over.
Now you just need to relax and be a good girl.
No… I can’t…
Your… penis… is hot…
You’re getting bigger… what a gross dad.
You’re rude as always.
Jeez. I need to pacify you with the drugs.
You… you’re such a retard.
No matter how much you do this… it won’t make me feel good.
Awesome!
So you enjoy this?
No! Not there. I don’t feel anything!
Not from me, of course.
But from me as a professor?
Why you… you really are… you really are… a pervert…
I don’t want to be turned on from this.
Just surrender to being turned on.
Holding back is bad for your health.
No. I don’t want this.
No!
You can’t hold back, can you.
Come on, I’m gonna cum in your soon.
No.
I don’t… don’t cum… in me…
No!
Why you… fucking worm…
Eew. Why is my body so happy about this?
You fucking worm. Retarded dick!
I’m all wet from cum and sweat.
I feel gross!
Jeez!
I’m gonna take a bath.
I need to rinse your stench off of me.
Just take your time, Airi.
Everything is going according to plan.
This feels great!
And at this time, no one else is out here.
It’s like my private bath.
I’ve always wanted to do this.
I’m in heaven!
Though it’s partly his fault, it feels good.
Damn it, I didn’t want to remember.
What?
How dare you snap my daughter!
You fucking asshole!
Hey, wait… no Daddy?
Airi’s beauty belongs only to me!
Hand over the camera!
I won’t let you have Airi!
You worm!
Get out!
Jeez, what a fucking moron.
That was close.
He was taking pictures of Airi.
Jeez, she’s my daughter.
I ate up too much time.
I don’t suppose Airi knows.
Hot!
Jeez. You really are a retard.
I’m so full!
And now I’ve gotten a bit hot.
This place sure is great.
I wish Onee-chan would get here soon.
Nope, you can’t have it. It’s mine – I bought it.
I'm not giving you any.
You can have this one.
You get to share a drink-kiss with Airi, what a lucky man you are.
Come on, Airi, this one is colder.
Well? Want some?
Nope. Stay away, pervert.
Leave it there for me.
F-Fine, fine. It’s on the table. See?
Oh well. You look good in anything, Airi.
Even a plain robe like that looks elegant on you.
What’re you saying?
Hearing it from you doesn’t make me happy.
Yep. You’re my sweet daughter.
Of course I feel that way.
But I’m happy I’m raising you to be such a slut.
I’m not happy, retard.
Even you, Airi, you love your Dad, don’t you?
Are you shy to admit it?
That’s bullshit. Just a touch from you makes me wanna puke.
Or maybe what you really want is this…?
Why do you always go there, retard?
And why is it hard again…?
We shouldn’t hold back, Airi.
Just admit you want…
Hmph! That’s how you revive yourself so quickly.
It's the drugs.
Are you retarded?
You really are a retard!
You’re the worst!
A worm among worms!
I mean, it would never melt in a cold drink anyway.
And you call yourself a scientist?
In that case…
Airi?
Jeez. You really suck. You’re a worm. You…
Why do you… make me…
How do you feel about me?
Using drugs all the time!
Doing weird things to me.
Is it that you can only touch me if I’m out of my mind?
You’ll only have sex with me if I’m acting weird?
No…
You’re lying! Lying lying lying!
But I’m not lying.
Then… then why won’t you tell me nice things?
You’re always telling Onee-chan that she’s sweet and pretty.
But you never told me those things!
I’m sweet, aren’t I? I’m pretty, right?
Or am I only pretty to you if you’re drugged up?
Am I only a sex toy to you?
That’s not true, Airi!
I’m a girl! I want the one I love to tell me he loves me!
Airi. I’m sorry.
You’re my beloved daughter.
My favorite girl in the whole world that I love.
Really? Do you really love me?
You think I’m sweet?
Yes, I love you.
You’re the sweetest of all.
I was wrong.
Daddy!
Daddy, your dick… it’s gotten so big.
Daddy, your mouth is twiddling my pussy…
Daddy, you’re so…
Daddy!
Touch me more…
I can’t… hold back
Daddy, you’re fucking me!
Daddy… do you love me? Will you swear to love me forever?
I’ll swear it. I swear to love you forever, Airi.
Really? You won’t ever let me go?
Yes. I will never let you go, Airi.
Daddy… not so sudden… I’m embarrassed.
This is so dirty…
Airi, you’re sweet and pretty all the time.
Daddy… I’m so happy…
Daddy’s all the way inside.
Swirling around inside me.
Airi’s pussy… belongs only to you, Daddy.
Yes. I’m all you have.
I love you, Daddy!
More… fill me more!
All the way deep inside… fill me up!
My pussy is squeezing…
From your thrusting cock.
You’re making me feel so good… yes…
Daddy, I want to see your face.
Embrace me.
Daddy, am I turning you on?
Are you gonna cum?
Daddy.
It’s okay.
Cum inside me lots.
Make me pregnant.
Daddy, I love you.
I love you, Daddy.
No…
N-no…
Daddy’s dick… is squirting inside… so much is flowing…
Daddy, I’m full of you.
Daddy…
Good mor-ninnng.
Looks like they made up.
Wh-wha…
In this position… sleeping… how lewd!
I wonder if that feels good.
Eew, how could I!
Come on, Airi!
Airi!
Onee-chan’s voice…
Airi, you!
Wake up!
My head hurts…
And my butt…
Wh-wha…
What’s this??
Owww.
My head hurts.
It’s pounding.
Airi, you drank alcohol.
I only had juice.
What’re you saying, this has alcohol.
You’re so weak just the smell of liquor gets you drunk, but you drank something this strong.
You have a hangover.
Really? Alcohol? That can’t be.
I mean, last night, I… owwww
I don’t remember anything.
You drank so much you lost your memory?
Yeah. I wonder why?
Trying to remember things makes me feel embarrassed.
Airi, good morning.
You look pretty this morning.
I love you.
Stop saying weird things first thing in the morning.
You fucking retard!
Goodness, Dad!
Oh, Marina?
I will have you explain exactly what happened last night.