Do... do I really have to do this?
It’d be bad if someone found out. It can’t be helped.
We were fine last night,
but since this morning it’s been...
I get it.
You're looking too much, Dad!
It's embarrassing, so look away.
I can’t!
From what they say in the texts, they’re
probably watching from somewhere.
We have to do what they say.
Fine...
Just a little more...
No...
So much is coming out...
Dad, this is enough, right? You don’t
have to stare so intensely, right?
Yes, I have to. It’s to show them.
But by the way, that’s quite a lot.
Dad! Just being watched is embarrassing enough.
This is the worst!
I'm just worried about Akira.
It’d be bad if it were cystitis or something.
Let me have a look.
Hey, wait!
Dad, don’t! It’s dirty! C'mon...
They asked for more.
We have to have sex!
No way. That’s...
How far are these demands going to go?
Dad...
All we can do is pray.
I don’t think it’ll escalate anymore, so please endure it.
I'm here with you, too.
Dad...
I get it...
Dad, wait!
Not so sudden in this kind of position!
You say so, but Dad’s hand was soaked with naughty juices.
Dad's dick is inside!
Dad’s dick is stirring inside me!
Even though it's a time like this... Dad!
I'm sorry, Akira. We don’t have very far to go.
Please bear with me.
Dad... I want to bear it...
But if you thrust that much... I won’t be able to take it!
Patience, dear. Patience.
You can’t knock so deep inside!
If Dad is that rough, I won t be able to stop!
I wonder if Akira would be an exhibitionist.
No... even though I’m being watched...
by someone I don't even know...
I can't, but my pussy is going crazy from Dad’s dick!
Come Dad! You can’t... but you can!
It’s coming...
Dad’s milk is filling my pussy!
Why... am I so aroused...
I...
Presented by Erobeat |http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Demonic Father
~Revenge of the Bob Haired Girl and the Girl in a Hakama~
Hey, this is enough, right?
Hey, are you listening?
Geez, why are you still peeing yourself at your age?
You're dumb plus you're sloppy!
It’s not every time!
Last time it was your fault, and this time it was him...
I'm not sloppy!
How long do I have to clean up after you?
Geez, quite treating your daughters as idiots...
I'm sorry! Did my daughter do something?
Oh, you're her father?
You see, a lot of molesters roam around here.
I just wanted to warn her.
Oh my, thank you.
We were just playing hide and seek here.
At this time of the day?
We were going to head to the convenience store ahead.
Well I’m sure it’ll be fine if you are with here,
but please still be careful.
Oh, so it was you, Natsume.
You surprised me.
Akira was shocked from being seen, too.
Hey, Natsume?
What’s wrong?
I lost my strength...
Wait, you...
Don’t joke around!
Not at a place like this! Stop!
Do you have diabetes or something?
This taste of your pee...
Besides, some other fluids are overflowing, too.
You... What’s with you?
How much do you have to make fun of
your daughter before you’re done?
Someone's... it's coming...
Huh? Someone’s using it?
Let's come back later then.
But...
Did she just say someone’s is coming? What?
Not so sudden...
You have to say “someone's inside" at times like this!
You’re such a dumb girl.
Geez, don’t thrust like a pig while
calling your daughter stupid...
You...
I said stop already!
What are you thinking!? Doing it at a place like this...
You might not need it with your size,
but you should still put on a bra.
Shut up!
I wasn't planning to come here,
and I said stop!
It’s Natsume’s pussy that won’t let go, but...
I guess it can't be helped.
Hey! Don’t cum at a place like this!
Wait! Hey! If it spills...
Hey!
It won’t as long as you hold it.
It’s Daddy’s seed, you've got to treasure it.
No way... you’re joking, right?
You...
Letting out so much... at a place like this...
Geez...
Geez! How am supposed to go out now?
What if the girls earlier are waiting outside?
Natsume you can cling tight onto me.
If we leave fast, it'll be fine.
Geez, that sure sounds reliable.
Huh? A man?
Just now it was...
I'm sorry about the wait.
Ouch...
Geez, cut it out already!
I already took a shower, and you make me sweat again!
It’s your own fault.
Running out, and peeing yourself.
You’re such a dumb daughter, geez!
Oh, a text from Akira.
It was because you left the house.
Beside, if someone appears like that
in the dark, anyone would be scared!
Akira would laugh at you for that.
From: Akira
Sub: Are you okay?
How did it go? Are you all right? Let me know.
Even if she doesn't,
A young girl like you...
Shut up!
Besides, there’s no way I'd let you tell anyone...
I didn't know you had a sense of shame.
Oh, I know...
You understand!
If you do that, I won't tell Akira and the
others about what happened tonight.
Before that, what’s with a father
blackmailing his own daughter...
Huh?
No, it's nothing.
What’s wrong, Onee-chan?
Hey you, have you done it with that guy?
I got him to do it on the beach at noon yesterday.
I couldn't tell it was him at first because of the wind...
So I was scared and I peed myself...
Did Onee-chan get him to do it as well?
We have done it!
Geez, getting that dirty old man to do it with you, you...
I'm sorry...
Don’t apologize so easily!
It's not like it's your fault!
Then, good night.
Geez, why do I have to do this...
Oh, I made a mistake and sent it to Fuyu instead.
I'll tell her tomorrow.
What do I do?
Doing it with Dad and being watched yesterday...
And having things turning out like this...
Dad, at this time?
It came again.
I've been negotiating with them,
but they just tell me to obey unless I want them to expose us.
No way... did they even take pictures?
Everyone is going to know what I did with Dad...
Don’t worry about that,
but we have to endure it for the time we are here.
When that’s done, they'll leave us alone.
But you can never know!
They could be lying for all we know!
These kinds of things just keep escalating...
Then what are we supposed to do!?
You don’t mind being exposed!?
It’s not just Akira being affected.
Are you fine with all of your sisters being
looked at weirdly by everyone?
I don't! I don’t, but...
They just demand us to do perverted things, right? I don't ...
If you endure, all of you sisters will be saved.
Isn't saying no to that, being selfish!?
Selfish? That's just not...
You want to sacrifice everyone just to save yourself?
That’s not it! I don’t want that!
I don't want to be saved like that...
I’ll be sure to make them stop.
So just bear with me, okay?
Okay...
But, what will they make us do?
The orders come through text messages,
and we have to follows those.
It’ll probably be like masturbating or having sex.
That’s...
In this position again?
"Have sex with your daughter in the bath
and face the window”, they said,
"I want to see her boobs swing", too.
They want to watch your aroused face,
so you have to face outside.
Why do I... have to do such things...
You have to endure.
This is the last day of all of this.
If we endure this, we can go back to just like before.
What’s wrong, Akira?
Could it be that you are getting excited?
Even though you're being watched?
What about it?
What are you saying, Dad!?
Don't ask if I'm getting excited or something,
just don't! There’s no way!
You sure?
But isn't your voice getting shaky?
Besides, dirty juices over here, too...
That... that’s not it!
I guess you’re right.
Getting excited from being watched makes you a pervert!
There’s no way Akira is like that, right?
Then, I’m putting it in now.
I'll cum soon, so just endure for a bit more.
Dad, wasn't it just going to be rubbing my boobs?
What’s wrong? It went in really smoothly!
Are you actually excited?
That’s not it! There’s no such thing!
It was just smooth from the water!
Dad... cum quickly, right?
I get it. I'll cum right away, so endure.
What's wrong? Can you not help moan?
Are you getting aroused from being watched?
Are you a pervert?
That’s not it! It isn't!
This... I just really need to cough! I’m not getting excited!
That’s right, there’s no way that Akira, no
way that my daughter could be a pervert!
No... no, I have to bear it!
Just a little more. Endure, be patient.
No... I think I'm going to cum...
But I have to endure,., this...
Akira, just a bit more...
Hurry, Dad!
That was close... I...
Huh? Dad?
Hmm, that’s strange. I thought I'd cum,
but I guess the timing was bad.
Sorry, Akira, just a bit more.
No way, Dad, don’t!
No... if he moves now, I...
Don’t! Dad, you can’t!
What’s wrong, Akira? Are you excited?
Even though you're being watched?
Are you a pervert after all?
Don’t, Dad! That’s not it! I’m not...
What are you not? You’re letting out
such voices; you re a pervert, Akira!
To think my daughter is an exhibitionist...
Exhibitionist? What are you talking about?
That’s... I’m not!
Getting aroused from being watched
makes you an exhibitionist!
Akira is a perverted exhibitionist woman!
Mo! I'm not an exhibitionist!
I’m not getting excited!
Akira is a pervert! You’re dirty!
You’re going to cum while being watched, aren't you?
No, that’s not true! It's just Dad being mean...
You grew to be such a pervert!
Even though I believed that you were different!
I’m not a pervert!
Why does Dad have to say that? I...
No! Dad is... I...
I...
So much is flowing in...
Flowing into my pussy...
I’m not a pervert, but... Dad...
Are you alright?
Dad is surprised, too.
That Akira is... you know.
That’s not it!
It's because it’s Dad’s dick...
I'm not getting excited from being watched!
You don't have to look or excuses. Akira
got excited from being watched.
Why!? I’m telling you that’s not it! Why?
As long as you endure through tomorrow,
we ll be able to forget all of this.
You just have to bear.
Geez... I'm telling it's not it... why...
My cold was horrible when I just came,
but I did gain a lot otherwise.
Getting to see the different faces of Fuyu and Akira is great.
Natsume is stupid like usual, but
next time I'll do her at school...
Well then, gotta give the stupid girl the next instructions.
I'm... A pervert...
Getting excited even I was being watched...
Even Dad said so...
From Natsume?
Huh... Aki...
Dad...
Hey, Dad...
Is it really here and now?
That’s right.
If anything, this should be the last demand from them.
See?
Is this really the last? There won’t be anymore?
Will we really be safe?
That's right. Let's really end it.
Really for real?
I don't think I’ll be able to bear anymore.
Alright, I know. So here,
Titty fuck me.
I get it. Well here I go then.
But, Dad...
What is it?
Why are you so hard even though your daughter
is being forced to do things she hates?
Even before I squeeze you with my
boobs, you were hard already!
Ah, because the text came... I was preparing for it.
I see... You’re really prepared.
Is it the next demand?
Yeah, that might be it!
What’s with you Natsume? You’re too fast!
From: Natsume
sub:Blackmail phrase
Pour enough semen deep into her throat to choke her
Hey, whoa! What is this girl thinking!?
What are the orders?
Uh no! It just says “hurry and cum and make her drink it”.
I see... then you have to hurry and cum, right?
Akira... no more will come out.
What? Again?
What is she trying to make us do? Stupid girl!
What's the demand this time?
From: Natsume
sub:You shitty old man
Roll up in a blanket and expose yourself.
That idiot! What is she thinking?
Didn't I give her instructions? Geez!
Hey, what’s the demand?
Uh, it's just saying to have more sex with you.
Let have sex.
Really? It was like that?
Yeah, of course.
I'm sure this is the last.
Then let me have a look, too!
Uh, wait, I'll show you right away, wait!
Roll up and show everyone...
It's completely different,
from having sex...
No. that’s...
There’s no way I could do that to you!
Not to my dear daughter...
Daughter? That's strange.
They didn't write who you have to do it to.
I’m sure doing it to Dad would work, too.
Huh? That’s...
What is this!?
...Akira? Huh...
Huh?
Akira, what is this?
I spent so much time explaining, but
you still didn't understand... Dad...
What, what is it Akira?
What’s wrong?
It’s, it’s dangerous, something like that!
You’re still trying to fool me?
Right, Natsume?
Na-...tsume?
I got a text from Natsume yesterday.
Though I couldn't really understand it.
Stuff like, "embarrass Akira".
I got her to talk quite a bit,
because I believed that Dad wouldn't
do something so horrible.
But...
I've said it before, right?
If that happens again, there no more.
Right?
Hey, hey wait, wait Akira!
I’m sure we can talk through this!
Heyy! Hey Natsume! You were part of it, too! Hey!
Trying to blame your daughter for what
you've done? What a horrible Dad.
The dick of that kind of Dad...
It's soft now...
Since you teased and bullied me around,
this time it's my turn.
It’s your fault that I was almost killed by Akira!
Na-Natsume...
Let's get that mouth that’s always calling
me an idiot, to clean this up.
It reeks! You've got athlete's foot?
You shitty old man!
I'm shutting that mouth of yours!
You’re getting hard.
Did you get hard from Natsume stuffing
her foot in your mouth?
You’re such a pervert!
For such a perverted dick, we've got to punish it!
Ow, that hurt!
Wait, Akira!
I’ll make you feel good lots and lots today, Dad.
Dad’s dick... it’s inside!
Woah, that was bad...
You stupid daughter! You trying to kill me!?
Geez, calling me stupid again!
Then I'll stuff you not with my foot, but a place you like.
Look at you!
You’ll always complaining and never loving me like the others,
try serving me once with that dirty mouth of yours!
Dad’s dick is twitching!
Wow... his tongue... could be good...
Dad's dick is making my pussy naughty!
This shitty old man's mouth is licking me pussy...
It's good!
Akira... it hurts...
Take off... the rubber...
I'm telling you it’s a punishment!
That’s staying on... until the very end!
You’re not getting untied until both of us are satisfied!
My pussy is going to cum from Dad's mouth!
No... Akira got the dick, but...
This side is... good too!!
Dad's dick...
It s going to... it’s gonna stay in my pussy!
It's Dad's fault, okay?
So please, untie me!
Really?
You say so, but it feels like you’d do it again.
Huh? Is everyone coming?
This is bad! I told them the wrong time!
You stupid girl!
It'd be bad if someone saw this!
C'mon, hurry and untie me!
You’re calling me stupid again!
You shitty old man...
But what do we do... we have to hurry...
Oh, if we roll him over then you can’t see...
Hey hurry, c’mon!
I see. This is perfect for hitting the Shinai, too.
That's true, It serves Dad right.
Hey, hey!
Akira, Natsume, Fuyu, let me go!
It’s my bad, alright?
Like this, right?