Come on, hurry a bit!
Getting on me early in the morning... You perv.
What were you thinking, coming at me when I wasn't even awake?
Airi, it's morning.
Airi!
Hey, wai-
Just...
It's... It's...
Seriously... Don't get so full of yourself.
Papa's milk, fresh in the morning.
It's thick, isn't it?
Keeping all the fun for yourself...
It's not over yet, is it?
Sticking it it like that when i'm still half asleep...
I...
What? Are you pushing off the responsibility to the cute girl?
How much lower can you get?
Well, dad is always like that.
We don't have time, so hurry!
Sana is waiting for us!
Sana! Sorry for making you wait!
Airi, good morning!
I'm so sleepy... This came out of the blue.
Ah, Mister! Good morning!
It's been a while since we last met.
Hey, Sana, who are you greeting?
This is mine!
And mine alone!
So boring... and here I had high hopes for it.
This is not about the complicated love life of father and daughter,
just a plain perverted movie!
It's boring, right?
Hey, wha-
If you're loud, they'll see your cute little tits.
What... What's going on here?
Just what... why?
They're not hard at all... so plump.
Stop... Don't touch me...
This is sick... So sick!
Such a lecherous body. It feels good.
Hey... Wake up...!
Don't... Don't... That's...
You're wet.
I don't want it...
I don't want a finger in my pussy...
Why...? I don't get it... I...
Even if you shut your legs, your insides are opening up.
Leave me alone!
What is he saying? I wouldn't...
Does it feel good?
Don't... Don't even hope! I wouldn't feel anything from this!
So brave... Or you just don't like it if it's not that guy beside you?
If it's not Papa?
What? He knows about me?
Stop...
This... I can't... If he keeps this up... Papa...
See you later, Airi.
Huh? I fell asleep?
Airi?
Come.
Ai... ri?
Oh damn, I fell asleep.
The movie's over already.
Huh? Airi? Mister?
I guess him and Airi couldn't bear it...
You shouldn't be so loud here!
This... Don't...
You've loosened up so nicely.
Stop it! It's disgusting!
Airi... Why... That guy...
FAKKU! Presents
Oni Chichi Re-birth
Saucy little hiphole
Airi, wake up! You'll be late!
Don't you have something to say?
Well, just... How should I say this...
Did you feel it?
What are you thinking? Are you stupid?
Your cute little daughter was raped by another man!
You're a good for nothing Pervert! You premature ejaculating bastard!
What does that mean? Another man? Father!
I'm so angry!
Doesn't he care about me at all?
Hey, it went all limp...
What's this? Why?
He's using my mouth as he pleases...
This feels terrible...
Compared to Father...
He's wants me to use my breasts?
How long until he comes?
This can't be... How can he hold back this much?
What? This is way too much...
But his cock is still hard...
Why?
I don't want to! Stop!
You won't get away with this!
What do you think you're doing?
His tongue... Is amazing... This...
Stop... That's... Don't...
What are you thinking?!
Stop! Stop, please! Stop!
That's... Stop... Don't...
Seriously...
Stop! Don't do that! I don't want it! Please stop!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
How...? He made me come...
No way...
Stop, please wait!
He's all in the way inside my pussy!
And that's not all of it! There's more...
Don't... There... Please... Don't...
All the way in...
My body is feeling so strange!
Please, stop already, please!
I don't want this!
I don't want to make you feel bad.
I just want to show you a new world.
Don't resist.
Shut up... I don't want your new world.
I didn't ask for this! I don't want this!
You won't get away with this!
That resistance you show is cute.
Don't... This...
What? If you're done, get out of me already!
This is disgusting!
An immature body like yours can still improve.
You want me to do it again, right?
Shut up! Get out of me already!
You...
You don't have to try to resist so much.
What are you doing?
This pose... What?
That's... There... Stop... Don't.
What? This can't be!
He's in my butt! This can't be! That's...
Pull it out!
This is strange! Stop!
Is this your first time?
But don't worry. You'll feel it soon.
I shouldn't worry you say?!
This is disgusting! Pull it o-
Oh, it went deeper.
What?
Stop! Pull it out!
It's nice and tight.
This doesn't feel good at all!
Please stop it!
This body is different.
Wait... No...
You're enjoying it by now.
Shut up! I'm not holding back!
Hey, what...? Stop!
What's going on? I don't get it!
This way i'll...
Don't... Stop... Why?
This pig... I won't come... from this!
You won't get away with this!
Don't... Stop... Not anymore...
The fun starts now.
Don't... Don't...
That can't be... His cock is still hard.
That can't be!
Why are they all using me like that?
He...
You're pathetic.
I get mad just from remembering it!
It's because he passed out there! That idiot!
Huh? Why?
I wasn't holding back!
It's no use complaining to him...
I haven't forgiven you, you know.
Doing that to Airi...
Airi can't get it out of her mind.
What if she comes while we're at it?
It's... so much bigger... than Mister's...
It's amazing... all the way in...
My pussy's turning inside out...
Your cock... is filling me...
Feels like my pussy's going crazy...
I'm...
Amazing... Really...
Amazing...
More!
I told you it feels so good!
You dummy.
What do you think?
Am I cute?
Then see you later!
Even Sana...?
You even got your hands on Sana?!
Why are you here at all?
Didn't you hear?
What? Perverted teachers should leave the school!
Really?
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Huh? What do you mean?
I understand your anger.
I won't touch you anymore, so don't worry.
So, is that all?
You know I'm quite busy with my work.
Wait a second!
After doing that to me,
How could I believe in you?
How could I trust you?
Proof! Give me some proof!
Proof?
With this?
You're such a pervert! How is that a proof?
I have no other proof,
than making you feel good with this.
What are you pressing against me?
Stop it already! Disgusting!
Then run away.
I'm telling you to stop.
What's wrong? Are you tempted by it?
What are you thinking?
I would never...
No one will hear.
Shut up! Pervert!
How do you know that...?
Then do you want me to plug my ear?
Or is making you feel good a good enough proof?
That... doesn't make me feel good at all...
If you're that persistent, I'm fine with it.
So suddenly...
Amazing!
I'm happy you're satisfied.
I wouldn't be satisfied with this!
This much is nothing! Are you stupid?
You play on people's nerves, don't you.
I know another pig like you...
Pervert... Thinks of nothing else...
Did you get angry from what I said?
Getting all sullen...
Getting told by such a cute little girl...
Does it annoy you?
Then why don't you try and satisfy me?
You won't be so cheeky for much longer.
My butt... so suddenly...
Amazing! I never felt this before...
Why does my butt feel so...
My butthole is opening... It's opening...
This way...
So wild...
It's coming... A lot of sperm is coming in...
Don't! Don't! I'm feeling strange!
Excuse me.
Professor Kuranaka, actually...
Professor... Kuranaka?
That's... Kuranaka?!
So that professor gave you the medicine...
So you agreed to exchange girls?
You filthy Dad...
And you were tricking me...
Coming with me...
Then getting turned on by watching another guy doing me...
Then you knew that the other guy will
put a cock much bigger than yours
into me... right in front of your eyes, right?