www.SubDESU-H.net
Marina.
Marina?
Yes?
It's overflowing.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I spaced out.
Huh, where's Airi?
She has already left it seems.
Oh no, it's already time.
Sorry Dad, I'm going off now too.
That was just lame.
Here I am sucking your thing.
So you do plan on getting inside her with this.
I don't think she's a virgin anymore though.
Maybe that guy already did it to her.
That guy?
A-Airi...
Some guy from her class.
He's got good grades.
Great at sports.
They're often looked upon as the school's best couple.
Really, I don't know how far they've already gone.
Marina, huh?
Airi...?
Jeez, don't get too cocky.
How dare you think of other girls while I'm here sucking your dick.
Papa, your perverted cock is getting all twitchy under my feet.
I wonder what will happen if I step on these balls?
Even if it is Onee-chan, I'm not going to forgive you,
if you dare think of any other woman in front of me.
You're about to cum, right?
I'm going to squeeze those perverted juices with my foot.
Here, just cum if you want to.
Hey, cum with my foot already!
Oh, that's amazing.
It's going wild under my foot!
Papa, your cum is overflowing.
I'm going to squeeze more of your cum okay, Papa?
Sub
DESU
H
Sub
DESU
H
Oni
Chichi
Original Animation Video
gg
in
Part
Sorry for what happened the other day.
I didn't even think about your feelings.
That's not true.
Even I, if it's possible I'd like to be your...
But I'm still not mentally prepared for this.
I think it's okay to take our time.
Thank you.
Me too, if it's you Masato...
Then there's nobody else for me.
T-Then, are you free tonight?
Huh? Well, yeah.
Marina.
I'm happy, Marina.
Akitsuki-sensei.
Da... Akitsuki-sensei.
It's okay to call me "Dad".
Dad?
I'm Ohno Masato.
A classmate of hers.
Ohno-kun, eh?
Lunchbreak's about to end soon.
You should get back to your classrooms as soon as possible.
Oh, it really is time already.
Ohno-kun, we need to hurry back.
I'm going to a friend's house tonight to study.
I think I'm going to stay the night there.
Is that so?
Is it the same friend as before?
Yes.
It's a lot easier to do it as a group.
D-Do it as a group?
Oh wow.
More, more!
Fill my insides!
See you later.
Marina, since when have you been able to lie so easily like that.
It's that guy's fault.
He's the one that changed my honest Marina.
Ohno Masato
by the park
I'm going to wait by the park
at 10pm tonight.
Are you okay if we let loose
for this? Just once.
Masato
I'm cleaning myself more carefully than normal.
Am I looking forward to this?
Will he really accept me completely?
Is it too soon?
But everyone says they've already done it.
Even I...
Let loose?
You're getting the wrong idea here kid.
Message Deleted
My Marina...
I won't let your filthy dick cum on her!
What is this smell?
I didn't put anything weird in here, did I?
Dad, I'll be going now.
Airi seems to have stayed over at a friends house as well.
I think you might have to put off that study session for now.
Eh? But, well...
I already promised.
Just call them and say there was an emergency or something, okay?
But tonight I...
I'm sorry for leaving you here alone.
I see.
So you really want his dick that bad.
Umm, well...
Huh?
Marina, tonight we'll...
Senpai, thank goodness!
Can I ask for a favor?
Something terrible is happening to my friend over there!
Who are you?
Please senpai, help me!
Me?
Please, there's no one around whom I can count on.
No one but you.
If it doesn't take too much time...
Okay!
It's this way.
Here.
Hurry senpai, over here!
Hey, wait!
W-Who's there?
I don't care who it is,
just give me your dick.
This seems to be really effective.
Though I just grabbed it from Papa's pocket.
This is perfect for Sana I guess.
I'm not going to give Papa's dick to anyone else.
Even if you're my Dad, it's still terrible for you to shame him like that.
I hate people who say those things.
Is that so?
You really want him to drill his dick into you that bad?
Or maybe you're already his sex slave?
Sex slave? What are you saying?
Masato and I are still...
Oh, not yet eh?
That's Marina, the school's top student for you.
I love you that way Marina.
What is this?
Why are you doing this?
You're done already, right?
I'm already late for my appointment.
Huh?
Ouch!
I'm really sorry, I...
Dad, you're acting weird.
You're not your usual self.
I...
I hate you Dad.
You... hate me?
Of all people, I don't want you to hate me.
No, let me go!
You're not my Dad!
If you're really my Dad then...
I see, you don't think of me as your Dad either.
That's not what I meant!
I'm sorry, I...
Well, that's fine for me though.
Dads don't really do these sort of things, do they?
What? No way.
My lips... Dad...?
What is this?
No!
I thought you'd be easier than Airi, but...
Easier than Airi, you say?
Dad?
Are you still going to call me Dad?
Yes, just keep calling me that.
Stop, please.
Dad, I beg of you...
No, Dad...
Stop.
Stop please.
What cute breasts we have here.
Your nipples are even getting hard.
So you're getting aroused.
My Dad's sucking my...!
No, why is Dad sucking my breasts?
Stop, please stop already.
Dad, wait...
Airi put up a better fight than this.
Does it feel good for you already, Marina?
I knew that you were a top student,
but it seems you're also good at being horny.
Dad, don't...
No, you can't do that.
Stop!
This is weird!
You can't just... You can’t just do this!
Marina, your horny juices are overflowing.
No, stop, it's touching my...
No, don't!
Please, I beg you!
You say that, but what is this?
No way.
Why?
I don't want this and yet,
my body became like that.
Even if you do that...
You can’t really hide the overflowing juices.
Stop, Dad, you really mustn't do this!
Please!
Dad!
I think we need to expose it a bit more.
It looks beautiful, Marina.
Nice moan you have there.
Just keep letting it out.
Oh no, Dad's licking me down there,
and these embarrassing juices continue to drip out.
I don't want this...
I'm sorry, Masato.
Dad, please...
Dad...
Dad, please no...
I beg of you.
I really don't want this!
No!
No, stop!
Dad, you mustn't!
Good girl, now that's how you should resist.
No, please no.
I beg of you!
Anything but that.
Don't.
Stop, no!
Da...
No way.
I'm just at the tip, you know.
It's still a long way down.
No, this just can't be...
You beast!
Pervert!
No, no!
Marina, I can't believe that I'd really hear those words from that cute mouth of yours.
No, no, no, no!
No, stop!
I'm about to take away your virginity.
But you can resist all you want.
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't, stop!
If you go deeper than that,
I, I...
You're going to fully experience it.
Dad's dick went all the way in.
Ouch...
It hurts.
Why this?
Why did this have to happen?
This can't be.
No way.
This is terrible.
It's going even deeper.
This is terrible!
I believed in you.
Why?
It's your own fault of course.
You and Airi are just so cute.
That's...
But you have Mom...
I'll just tell Kayoko that you stole me from her.
Stole you from her?
What are you saying?
Why would I be the one who...
I won't forgive you for this.
I'm going to turn you into the police.
That might be good for you,
but Airi and Kayoko would take the brunt of the public humiliation.
All because of your selfish decision.
Me, being selfish?
That can't be...
Society is a terrible monster,
and you don't know anything about it.
This ignorance is the very reason why you'd even want that guy.
Masato is a good person.
Unlike you, he's someone who truly, truly thinks of my feelings.
But your relationship with him ends here.
It's about to pour inside you soon.
Inside me...?
No way, no...
You can't do that.
It's not safe for me today.
And you were planning on fucking that guy today?
Bad girl.
Then just take my seed instead.
No!
Don't!
You mustn't!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
No!!
Masato, I'm sorry.
My insides are filled with Dad's cum.
This is terrible.
Dad, you're such a...
Masato...
Your boyfriend is hooking up with someone else at the moment.
Here.
This is... Did you...?
You're the one who is constantly using that to do things.
So you did it to Onee-chan after all.
This crazy dick should be...
It already came a lot.
Airi...
It wasn't a dream was it?
Airi wasn't even bothered by the situation.
That was just...
No, Dad...
This is...
Airi.
I'm just lending him to you for now, okay?
This dick is all mine.
It's going to pour inside me again.
Please no!
Just cum already.
It's my turn next.
No, Airi, your tongue is touching my butt.
Dad, it's getting big again.
You can't cum inside me again!
Yes!
Papa, you’re great!
It's filling my insides.
Give me more please.
I want more of your cum.
I want that stinky stuff inside my pussy!
It's coming
I'm about to cum.
Onee-chan is watching me cum while Papa drills it inside me!
Papa, your seed is filling me again.
Akitsuki-sensei is calling for you.
Student Counseling Room
Umm, I heard you wanted something from me?
So you hate me now, huh?
You know, I tried to save you.
What are you saying?
It's all your fault that I...
Don’t come closer!
If you want to say something just say it already.
Stop it already!
Please don’t do those terrible things to me again!
It’s okay.
I'm not going to do anything bad to you.
Here, come this way.
What are you going to do?
I thought I'd show you something that might interest you.
You’re showing me... this?
Please stop!
Even if you show me this...
Please...
That's Airi's....
It's fine, there's nobody around.
You also wanted this, right?
Do you understand now, Marina?
Men are very simple.
Even if you believe in them.
This is...
Why am I reacting like this to his...
Masato...
Hey, it's okay right?
I can't hold myself anymore.
Hey, hey.
Eh? But we can't do it here.
Besides, you came really fast.
It'd be okay this time, I swear!
It was all just so sudden before.
Also, you have a girlfriend right?
You never once showed interest in me before.
That's not true!
See? If you just keep this our secret...
Secret? It's not like I'm doing anything in particular.
Well, I guess it can’t be helped.
Thanks!
Senpai, you’re too rough.
You're getting horny now, right?
Why does it have to be like this?
I don't want to do this...
Masato is doing it with another girl and yet...
Dad is making me suck his dick,
and my body is reacting pleasurably to it.
I mustn't do this.
This is unfair.
No, don’t go too deep inside.
Huh? Is someone...
Masato, no!
Please don't look!
I'm not really...!
Hey, senpai hurry.
Make my pussy feel good already.
Umm, I'm...
Marina...
Masato, don't look.
My Dad's dick is starting to make me horny.
He's looking at me, and yet I'm feeling good inside.
No, I'm going to cum while Masato watches me get fucked by my Dad.
I'm cumming!
That was great, Masato.
What the hell was that?
First, you didn't show up last night,
and now you're showing yourself having sex with someone?
You also had a good time, didn't you?
And you even did it forcibly.
That's because she just...!
What a wreck of a human you are.
A father having sex with his daughter is even crazier!
Hmph, pervert.
Mister, do it to me next, okay?
He's simply half-assed.
I can’t hold it in anymore, so please?
Sana.
Oh crap!
Delicious.
It's already like this early in the morning.
Oh, Dad.
I'm going to make you feel good, okay?
I'm going to be late!
Onee-chan, that's unfair!
Airi, I already reminded you to wake up early.
I'm sleepy. I stayed up late last night.
Dad came lots inside you last night, right?
Well, that's true, but I still wanted more.
You can't.
Dad's morning cum is mine, okay?
Right, Dad?
I'm going to continue sucking it so it stays lively.
Then I'm going to do it as well!
Nope.
You already did it a lot yesterday.
But...
Papa thinks my pussy feels better, right?
Jeez, Airi, but it’s my turn today.
Please cum inside me until I get pregnant.
Please Dad?
www.SubDESU-H.net