No...
My pussy is all wet.
Soon your big dick will take my virginity.
Your dick is filling up my entire pussy!
It feels so good, I can't take it.
It's my first time... Yet, it feels amazing.
Don't!
Even though it's my first time, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum, I'm going to cum!
Well, I'm counting on you.
Yes, Uncle.
Airi, are you coming?
Ah, I'm so late!
Really, you should try and be on time.
I was up late, so I didn't sleep too well.
Daddy, Good Morning.
Good morning, in a hurry?
Yeah, Airi is running late.
Hey perv.
Airi!
Come on, sis, we'll be late!
Airi, I know you're in a hurry, but...
you should greet him properly in the morning.
Yo, I'm leavin'.
Airi, I can't believe...
I'm sorry, Dad.
It's okay, don't worry...
Well then, I'm off!
Oni
Chichi
Part 1
Subbed by YarashiiSubs
Translation - jhkplaya888, kingkouta
TLC - zhurai
Editor - kaizoku, BlazerSoul
Timer - BlazerSoul
Encoder - WolfReborn
Oh man, why do we have to live with him!
He's always smelling them.
Airi, don't speak so badly of daddy like that.
You know that's not the case.
He's not our real dad, he's only our dad because he married mom.
Don't say that!
My dad, is my only dad.
That guy is not my dad!
Yes, but even so...
He treats us like we're dogs.
Like dogs?
He is always giving both of us dirty looks.
What are you trying to imply Airi?
The last time we changed into our uniforms...
And he's always watching.
Take a guess at what!
Quit talking nonsense, and be serious...
He also hides our panties from the dirty laundry and what do you think he does?
If that were the case, you'd be embarrassed wouldn't you?
If he doesn't then there is no reason to be shy.
Really you say such stupid things sometimes.
I'm not a kid anymore!
Oh look it's our academies princess.
Sana, what are you doing here?
It's ok, it's ok, what a cute face.
Yes! Come and have a look!
You just became an honor student on this campus, about to go to the school festival, Airi-tan!
Well, that's why, please don't take weird videos of me.
Because if that's the case...
Uh, Sana, Don't! STOP!
Ooh, Airi what do we have here!
Good, just like that, just like that.
Lier, S-Sana, just a second, not in this outfit.
It's okay, it's ok, don't worry.
Anyway, let's start by taking your bra off.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING SANA!
Stop it, Uncle may walk in...
You're so cute and stylish.
And you have a sexy body.
Airi that girl, acting all shy and getting me all turned on.
So cute.
Geez, that's enough.
No, you never know when a story might pop up.
Really? If anyone else saw this I'll die.
What are you talking about... You're really cute...
I'll delete the file and even destroy the CD.
It doesn't matter!
You shouldn't even be doing this...
I don't want anyone seeing it...
Atsuki-sensei, don't forget to look over the report.
I got it, I'm looking at it right now.
Thanks again, Hikuzuki.
No problem!
Trail drug research, huh?
All the results are the same as before.
A sexual side effect...
But were the samples, enough?
It doesn't matter, I'll get more soon!
Nambu-kun, I have some terrible back pain.
Ah, Airi...
Sicko!
I told him not to talk to me at school.
I don't want to be seen with him.
He's really the worst.
Good thing I don't have to see him often.
Well, Airi could it be that you...
Don't worry so much.
I don't really know what kind of person he is.
But I bet he is way better then my dad.
That's what I would like to say, cause.
He is always busy with research, so yeah...
Then I'll bring you home to meet him.
Huh, can I really meet him?
Airi.
I'm home!
Sis, are you here?
Huh, you?
Welcome home.
Hello, Uncle.
Are you Kuranaka-san?
She wanted to come over today.
It seems like your mom won't be home tonight...
Really? I knew she's wasn't going to come home.
What about sis?
Well, I guess it's just us today.
Then let's go to dinner, the 3 of us...
Shut up you dirty perv.
Sana, let's go shower and then order takeout.
Uh. Airi.
I guess I might as well listen to music.
Airi will be taking a shower for a while.
What are you doing? S-Sana...
Stop it, this is embarrassing.
These videos are private so let's make it sexy.
Wait! What's going on!
What an arrogant tone, that bitch... huh?
Sana and me are here so get out.
This is my room.
What are you doing in here you sicko!
I find it strange...
Entering my room like your own.
I bet you took something! You thief! Give it back!
You're not my Dad so don't act like it!
You are with my mom!
You always come around calling me perv.
For once, would you call me Dad?
Airi, I never realized how beautiful you are.
Shut up! Stop talking...
I really can't stand people like you!
It's not only you, look at this girl.
S-Sana! What the... Wait a sec...
Airi.
S-Sana what are you doing...?
Don't be mistaken, this isn't Uncle's doing...
I asked him if he'd please let me do this.
S-Sana... No way...
You trashy Loli-con!
Sana, hurry up and get out of here you perv!
It's time for you to shut up!
That's...
What's going on... What's with my body ?
No...
The new drug must be working...
No, this heat, it feels so good!
I can't stop it, is there no way to end this!
Can you move?
I guess I should check to see...
Try not to move to much Airi.
Even if you cry and call me Dad.
I hate you, you pervert!
A woman shouldn't say stuff like that, that's not good Airi.
Noooo!
Stop that!
I'm tired of fooling around.
No, please.... Stop!
No, stop looking at me with those perverted eyes.
That's mean.
But I'm gonna love this, Airi.
No, don't do this, I will definitely make you pay.
I don't think you get it yet.
Stop fooling around.
Sana, please help me!
I'm sorry.
I asked uncle if I could video tape your first time.
Airi, it only hurts at first.
So look this way and let me see that cute expression on your face.
S-Sana, stop!
I know I was wrong, and I apologize, I'm sorry!
I apologized so let me go.
It's okay Airi.
Uncle's dick is big and will feel good.
No, this is not something that a Dad would do!
You may be saying no, but your pussy is wet like it's saying yes.
How cute.
Airi's virginity is about to be taken.
And here it goes.
No, no, NOO!
Owww!
Stop it!
Airi, you're just like me. I had sex with uncle too.
It hurts, so much!
I beg you stop this!
No, it hurts, owww, so much!
It hurts, it huuuuuuuuuuurts!
I'm sorry please forgive me Daddy!
How dare you call me daddy now you arrogant little bitch!
You animal, pull that disgusting thing out!
Yeah, yeah, you like this?
You want to have my baby, Airi?
No, I won't! You can't...
Stop... wait!
Airi, this will be your first internal cumshot.
Your pussy will soon be full with cum.
No, stop, I don't like this at all!
I'm really sorry!
I'm sorry I was so bad!
Like I said, I'm sorry!
I beg you, I apologized!
How can I forgive you so easily...
I hate that, stop already, please...
I beg you stop now!
You... Came inside...
I feel it, your cum inside me.
And she was out like a light!
Airi, are you okay, did you sleep at all?
You were playing with him this morning!
It's so good!
Use more tongue Airi...
Even though I hate this I can't stop.
Stop!
No, for some reason I feel warm inside.
Stop, I don't like it, Daddy, stop...
You know your dad can't stop, Airi...
Shut up! I don't want to hear that from you.
I .. can't ... even ... speak... it feels so good.
Please, stop!!
Feels so good, I can't stop.
Stop!
Don't cum inside of me... Nooo!
I hate this, but for some reason it feels so good...
How can I feel so good even though it's him...
I can't go on!
It's horrible.
I'm not mom!
Airi, you are like your sister, so cute.
What did you say? You and sis have done this too?
Not yet... Unfortunately.
Only you so far Airi...
Oh sis...
Stop it!
Airi...
Hmph, you traitor.
But... I wanted to see Airi's cute face.
What are you talking about? I hate you Sana.
Wait, why did you bring me here!
Class is starting you know!
I want to see your cute face just like yesterday.
Don't joke, what if someone sees us?
So what if they do. I'm a just a teacher right?
I can always find another place to work.
You can cry all you want, because I like that lustful look it gives you.
Stop it, right now!
Soon, you will feel good.
Again...
It seems the drug is getting more effective.
Not there!
No, don't do it, NOO!
You say that now but you know you want it.
No, stop, I'm not that sensitive...
Take your dick out...
Stop you pervert. My pussy...
Doesn't feel good at all!
This is so unlike me.
I not supposed to like what he is doing...
Right now I'm scared...
Hold on tight or you'll fall
Damn, you're so tight.
Stop!
I'm so scare, but for some reason I want him to come in me.
I'm disgusted with what he's doing.
But I'm soaking wet, it feels good.
That's enough I'm begging you, please stop already...
I hate it, the pain is too much.
I hate that you're inside of me.
Nooooo!
No, stop it!
No, don't look at it!
Stop, please!
This is the only way to discipline a bad girl.
I don't even know what I did wrong.
Why are you punishing me?
I don't want my sis to see me here.
She is studying now... So serious...
Sis said that she had a boyfriend and that was that.
We only hear from her once in a while.
What? Are you serious?
She said she was going to move in with her boyfriend before she left.
What's wrong?
Don't you have sex with her!!
I am here to take her place, you should be happy. So I am enough, ok!
I can feel it all the way inside.
Well truly...
You're the worst, just keep going, stick it in me further...
I'm not Sis.
I can feel his perverted dick in me.
Stop, I don't want you to cum in me.
If you do all your sticky cum will be all up in me.
Cum in me, ok?
I want you to cum in me and fill me up!
Hurry up, I'm ready!
I want your big load, cum in me...
CUM IN MEEEEEEEE!
I'm perfect and I will use your cum to have lots of kids.
Tell me the truth Marina, do you have a boyfriend?
Why not introduce me to him.
Dad, why do you ask so suddenly?
I'm not with anyone...
Oh, this time already... Gotta go.
This is so hard, I bet my mom never did this much did she?
I just want to comfort you. No matter what it takes.
Please. Hurry up and cum Dad.
The Academy Festival is drawing near.
They said a band is supposed to be there.
Isn't little Airi in it?
You have to take me to see that!
You serious?
You don't think she'll expose herself, do you?
Really, I hope she does.
You like me right, You like me right now?
What ever you do is fine with me.
Sure you say that now, but you feel good, right?
So, simple...
I'll finish this.
Does that feel good?
I will always do my best to take care of you.
You can't help it, right? If your dick ever gets hard you can use my pussy at any time.
That is all I want to do.
It went in!
Your perverted dick went inside me!
I want to mother your children!
It feels so good! Ahhh!
Let me be your comfort, stick your dick in more!
It feels really really good.
My pussy is so wet and your dick feels so good.
Your dick will be mine and mine only. You can use me as you like.
Mom and Sis are missing out...
Cum in me.
I want you to cum in me and fill me up again,
Give it all to me, I want it. I WANT IT!