www.SubDESU-H.net
Is it something that you can't talk about?
N-No, it's just that I'm really...
I'm really...
This isn't real, right?
This is my father and I.
Mom hasn't noticed though, and...
Dad, stop this already.
I still haven't forgiven you.
Doing your daughter like that...
You even did the same thing to Airi and Sana...
No Dad, I beg of you.
Please stop this!
Why is this happening?
Dad!
No!
I-I'll have you arrested!
I'll also tell Mom,
the kind of man that you are.
That'd be troubling.
Because you're now my sex slave, you know?
So you have to be more obedient.
S-Sex slave?!
Please stop fooling around.
You think I'm kidding?
Okay, let's go in here.
Open 24 hours
All rooms are equipped with
sauna
karaoke
Video
Microwave
Black Light
N-No, I don't want to be here!
What? You want to do it outside?
You sure are bold, Marina.
N-No...!
P-Please, stop this...
Are you sure you want to be that loud?
Other students are walking by.
Everyone will find out if you keep that up.
In my case, I don't really care if that happens.
But if Kayoko hears about this, she'll probably get depressed.
If she found out that you stole me from her,
what would she think?
N-No one will believe that I'm the one who seduced you.
Just keep still,
and you won't get hurt.
Your boyfriend seems to have lost his affection for you.
So from now on I'm going to use you as I please.
No...
That's good.
You also feel quite fulfilled with this, right?
It feels great, so you just have to enjoy it.
Please finish quickly.
I can't be exposed like this for much longer.
Okay, then give me a tit fuck.
I... I can't do that, I can't use my boobs to...
So you know what a tit fuck is.
It's still early for Airi to know that stuff though.
You sure are a pervert, Marina.
Umm...
Did you just hear or read about it somewhere?
T-That's, with my friends I...
H-Hey, Mari...!
I-I'm sorry.
Do it gently.
I'll use those boobs to pleasure my dick then.
The real thing starts now.
His dick is between my boobs.
You put adequate pressure in between, and then rub it up and down.
L-Like this?
That's good, do it faster.
I'm doing this kind of thing here...
I-Is this enough?
Far from it.
Let's see, why don't you drip some of your saliva to lubricate it?
I'm doing something embarrassing.
Why do I have to do something like this?
Just a little more, just a little faster.
Marina, just keep at it and take it all on your face.
Lots of Dad's cum is on my face.
It felt good, Marina.
Wa... No wait Dad, doing it here is just...
Doing it here is just...
It hurts.
Oh no, we're doing it at the park.
He made me do a tit fuck, and now we're having sex here.
He's making me do all of these lewd things.
Does it still hurt?
It will get better soon.
This won't get any better!
Please don't say things like that!
You say that, but your body is feeling pleasure.
Oh no...
It's the same for Airi,
but it looks like our bodies are compatible with each other.
W-What are you saying?
I guess it's all thanks to your real Dad.
He's French, right?
Is our compatibility affected by the fact that you are of half foreign descent?
No, please stop talking about Papa!
I really would have wanted to be called Papa...
That's...
Dad, you're....
You're not going to call me Papa?
But I just can't...
Oh well then,
it seems that doing it the gentle way is a bit difficult.
In this position, any peeper is in for a treat.
No, that can't be...
I don’t want to do it here!
We'll be seen!
Please stop this already.
I can't stop now.
Because I'm about to pour my...
I mean Papa's existence inside you.
No!
We're going to be seen.
I'm going to lose it if we're exposed here.
How about I impregnate you,
and make all three of you my family.
No way, no way.
You can't do that!
I want to give you pleasure at all times, as my sex slave.
Why?
Sex slave...?
Lots of Dad's cum is pouring inside me.
Oni Chichi
~Purity Riding Cosplay NEET~
Original Work Blue Gale
Original Animation Video
Oni
Chichi
I think there has been some sort of mistake.
I didn't go to this place.
Is that so?
If you insist that you did not, then I understand.
I'll talk with Dad, and...
Mom, don't you believe me?
Bringing this up with Dad will just be too embarrassing.
This isn't the time to be concerned about that.
Besides, we have to plan something for this as early as possible.
A plan?
Listen. This picture was sent directly to the principal.
Someone wants to frame you for this.
Also,
maybe it's better for you not to know this, but...
T-This is...
Suspicions that a pretty
top student is a whore
Nameless-kun
Talk about it
Aban Aban
Sannoue
For real? Those sisters sure
were good though.
So it's the same for the golden haired younger sister?
34: 0nititi: 09/16  00:49
Putting on that pure
face, and yet already
doing it, I feel
like doing her now
35:Masa:09/16  01:05
I wonder how much
she would ask?
36:Nameless-kun:09/16  01:23
But she's probably
"filled" already
37:NASA:09/16  01:36
No way, and here I was
idolizing her as the school's
songstress
38:Nameless-san:09/16
I can't believe this,
she acts so nice during
class, this is just the worst
39:Nameless-kun:09/16  05:49
They're probably referring to you two.
I was also called back because of this incident.
We don't know if the situation will change,
but at the very least, I want you to stay at home in the meantime.
No way...
No. It's dangerous out there nowadays.
I want Airi to do the same, but we need to secure you first.
Even sending an edited photo like this...
There's also an upcoming emergency faculty meeting,
so I'll probably come home a bit late than usual.
Okay.
I'm overjoyed to see you wearing bloomers,
but you've been acting strangely since your Mom came back.
You don't seem to be your usual self during practice, either.
Do you really want to be with him that badly?
What? What are you saying?
Of course not!
I said I was going to give that beast to you, right?
W-When did you ever say that?
Airi, is something wrong?
Hmph, I don't know anything.
Huh, I can't see anything...
What is this?
Airi, Dad?
Sorry, Mom.
Are you okay?
Huh, Marina?
What's the meaning of this?
What about Airi and Dad?
I heard a loud voice earlier, but...
Huh, Dad? He's not here.
Also, the voice you heard was probably me practicing my piece.
Listen...
It's my voice, right?
Huh? But Dad and Airi were on the bed just earlier, right?
What? That was Airi and I.
Oh, with that outfit?
Yep, we're doing a café.
I was practicing my piece for the greetings.
Welcome home, Master.
Please take care, Master.
You see.
But that's weird.
I think I really saw Dad, though.
Jeez, Mom you're showing your age already.
Oh my, Marina. Mom is still very young, you know.
You can't compete with your daughter with that, though.
But you just...
Just who was that, Mikami?
And how was she able to sing that well?
Airi?
Hey! Airi...?
Airi, oh no!
Don't worry, she's fine.
I was able to catch her in time.
It seems that she's just sleep deprived.
She's just sleeping soundly right now.
Jeez, she looks so innocent when she's sleeping.
Maybe I should imprint my smell on her.
Is that what's called sleep learning?
Hey, Airi.
This part's turned back to its normal state.
It's the best.
This one's good,
but I guess the ones that are just worn and undressed are better.
Huh? Was I asleep?
What happened to me?
Hey, wait... What are you...?
Stop fucking around, you trash!
What are you thinking?
Hey!
So you're finally awake.
I heard you weren't sleeping well, what were you doing last night then?
Were you masturbating?
Don't worry, Papa will loosen you up with a little sex.
Stop fooling around!
I'm not going to let you arouse me, you idiot!
Hmph, how cheeky of you.
Wait, what's that smell?
Oh, vaginal discharge.
So you're having your period.
You insensitive pervert!
Idiot! Stop that already, you...!
This beast...
I'm not going to let myself be aroused!
Are you going to resist?
Then I'll just use you as my sex slave.
You're treating me like an idiot again.
Are you crying?
Only little girls are forgiven for that.
It won't do any good for someone as developed as you.
Shut up. Are you talking about me?
I'm going to continue punishing you until you agree with me.
This guy... This...
Hey, why are you soiling my clothes?
Stupid!
Oh, it’s all dirty now.
Okay, wear this then.
It seems there's an upcoming school festival.
I took a lot of things that could be used for cosplay.
I love this.
It's no use trying to resist, right?
Your perverted body is already beyond twisted.
Just do whatever you want.
It'd just feel gross whenever you do it, you trash.
Stop fooling around!
This guy...
Then what is that girl for?
You're quite wet already.
So your perverted pussy is already craving for my dick.
Shut up!
That trash of a dick isn't...
You idiot!
Seems that your body is the only thing that matured after all.
The inside is still a total brat, jeez.
If you really want it, then I'm going to pour lots.
Hey...!
Who's the brat? Is he talking about me?
Just cum already, you scum!
I'm going to fully enjoy this first.
I'm just a brat, huh?
Then I won't let myself be aroused by something like this.
Just pull out that shitty dick of yours already.
It doesn't feel good at all.
You trash!
Hmph, what an annoying brat.
He came lots on me and even made me drink some.
He should really quit fooling around already.
That felt good, Airi.
We're going to continue this at home.
Mister, you two aren't being completely honest.
Oh, Sana.
You really do act like you're the one being troubled.
Sana, how's progress over there?
Currently at work.
Though, it's Yuka-senpai herself that is hard at work.
I really don't have anything against her, anyway.
Oh, where's Marina-san?
Seems she's suspended and is staying home,
at the insistence of Kayoko.
Maybe that's for the best.
Even if she was here, it'd probably be too difficult for her.
I-I don't think so.
Marina is mine, anyway.
Mister, I've already said this to Airi,
but you have to express yourself better.
Can't I get some assurance about it?
Well, as for Yuka-senpai...
Oh, she said something about borrowing some medicine.
What did you say?
Damn!
She needs to be taught a lesson.
Well then!
Kouzou-san.
Sorry for the wait.
I'm sorry for asking you to do so much.
No, it was a pleasure doing those things for you.
Let's get started then.
Okay.
This is the worst!
I can't understand him one bit.
What was that all about?
How many drops?
Two drops.
How long?
15 minutes.
It's gotten quite moist.
My vagina also feels hotter than before.
It feels like my insides are... trembling.
Are you aroused right now?
You can't do that. Otherwise, we won't be able to determine the medicine's actual effects.
Y-Yes, I understand that.
But, I feel embarrassed being exposed like this in front of you.
I'm sorry.
Hold on for a bit.
It seems that it's starting to take effect faster than before.
Looks like we've refined it.
There was one time that it was used so much that a female subject went crazy.
So we need to proceed with its development very carefully.
Oh, I heard from Sana about the medicine.
Looks like you need to be taught a lesson.
I-I'm sorry.
Please, punish me.
Do you feel any physiological changes?
W-Well, I want you inside me already.
Oh yeah, I've been spending too much time with those two lately.
After we finish the examination, okay?
Thank you very much.
That doesn't mean I'm going to cry myself to sleep because of this.
I'm definitely going to...
Kouzou-san, please proceed.
I'm happy.
Your dick is...
Did you want it that badly?
It's wonderful,
your dick is wonderful.
I felt really lonely when you were with Marina and Airi.
Your thing is filling me up inside.
I thought she was Marina's friend, is she timid at school?
Please, fill my pussy more.
I want your...
Oh yes, your dick is going in and out.
My pussy feels great.
Kouzou-san, I can see it, please do it to me more.
My pussy is very wet, it's starting to feel very good.
I'm very happy to have you inside me.
Please do it to me more.
If it's for you I...
Oh no, I'm about to...
I want you to... cum inside me.
I'm going to try it using the medicine next time.
I'm happy that you're concerned about me, Kouzou-san.
I love you.
Kouzou-san, oh no...
I'm cumming...!
I'm cumming!
Looks like Yuka is now easily aroused.
That's all my doing, though.
Oh yeah,
maybe I should let her become friends with those two.
Maybe we could do a foursome!
Wait, with Sana that's going to be a fivesome!
D-Dad, are we really going do this?
You were inviting me before with that outfit, right?
That's why.
I-Inviting? What are you saying?
Making Airi cry like that,
and almost getting caught by Mom!
Besides, I'm already...
This is my safety plan.
It's the same as home study.
Besides, we can have sex at any time this way.
Dad! Jeez...
M-Marina, so now you're acting cheeky, too?
I already said that we were going to do a Tsundere Maid Café.
O-Oh, I see...
So it's just fine with you?
I just have to imitate Airi, though.
So it's very easy.
Well, you're right.
It's going to take way  less effort.
Hope you enjoy your school festival.
Yes.
Though, you have to make me happy first.
Dad!
Your dick...!
Why?
Something's different with him today.
Marina, drink it all.
Dad!
I can't breathe... Da...
So you're going to service boys in this outfit, huh?
The way you say it makes it seem like it's erotic.
It's just a café!
Boys would probably masturbate at the sight of this.
P-Please don't say something like that.
Masturbating is just...
You saw the messages, right?
All of them are seeing you that way.
That's not... true.
I'm not... somebody else's porn material...!
Your thing is going deep inside!
I want to violate you this way.
I want to drill into your perverted pussy as it invites me in.
That's not true.
I don't want to be violated...
Everyone wants to squirt it all into you, the so-called top class student bitch.
I'm not a bitch...
I'm the one being fucked here.
You're the one making me crazy.
Other than lewd, what else do you call a skirt that exposes your panties when you bend over?
I'll be careful about that from now on.
You say that, but won't you be the one showing it off to them?
I won't!
I won't do anything that weird!
Everyone's going to stare at me weirdly!
They're going to peek at your panties, take pictures of you,
and masturbate after that.
No, I don't want that!
Please don't say those terrible things.
Though, at that time you would probably already be pregnant.
Dad, release it. Dad, I know this should be Mom's,
but I want your dick milk too.
Dad, please.
Give me your milk!
It's pouring inside.
It's going deep inside.
Your cum milk is going into my womb.
I've decided to take some days off as a teacher,
for the duration of your suspension.
Okay, thanks Dad.
Jeez, it's Airi's turn, Papa.
A-Airi? What are you...?
I just want your naughty dick.
You left me and went to do it with Onee-chan.
I'm getting lonely already, you know.
Oh, is this another act?
After the brat, you're going to try and be the dependent one, eh?
I-I'm not going to be fooled.
What are you saying, Papa?
I just want you to notice me, too.
If I cling onto that, you'll probably just call me an idiot or stupid again.
What is this? What's happening?
Your dick is really big.
You just came inside Onee-chan, and yet...
You're about to do naughty things to me.
Airi! If this is an act then cut it out already!
Stop fooling around!
Ai—
That's...
Has she gone out of control because of that ?
Stir me up with your naughty dick,
and fill my naughty pussy with it.
But, the one that Airi had was...
Your naughty dick is amazing!
It's penetrating me completely.
Papa, it feels too good.
But this condition is...
Oh, she said something about borrowing some medicine.
I'm sorry.
Yuka did?
That can’t be...
Your dick feels good.
My wet and naughty pussy is getting completely fucked by it.
I love this!
I'm really happy with your dick, Papa!
www.SubDESU-H.net