I'm home, Dad!
Oh, welcome home, Haruka.
W-Welcome back.
Natsume, were you being scolded by Dad again? It looks like it.
N-No, it's not that-!
I-It's nothing.
Onee-chan, welcome back!
I'm home!
Geez, I sure am hungry!
Yeah, I just started making something. It shouldn't take long.
Okay!
Then I'm going to get changed-
Huh? Where's Fuyu?
She's caught a cold and is resting at the moment.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll see how she's doing before I change.
SubDESU-
H
Oni Chichi
Fuyu?
Huh? Oh, Onee-chan, welcome home...
How you feeling?
I'll come back later, okay?
Sure..
Natsume sure hasn't changed, she still dislikes Dad.
I-I'm sorry!
T-That was surprising, since he was naked!
He was so big down there,
does that mean that he had an erection?
It also looked as if it was wet.
T-That was scary!
Geez, y-you could have at least locked the door!
That was scary!
I don't mind if they found out, though.
Don't be ridiculous!
If they were to find out, you'd be the one in trouble!
I won't let you touch the others.
Hm? Are you commanding me?
You think you're allowed to say that to me?
I-I'm sorry!
Oh! See, you can be an obedient girl!
W-Wait I'm-!
For you to release this much inside your daughters mouth...
This penis is...
T-This is dangerous!
You're in the Kendo Club, right?
This is just training.
Are you stupid?
This isn't-!
You pervert!
Assaulting your daughter like this with that face...
What kind of monster are you?
You're this wet, so you're a pervert as well!
It's so deep! No! It's coming right inside me!
Your penis is rubbing against me!
My pussy, it's being rubbed by Dad!
Why is my body so hot when I hate this penis?
Y-You jerk, what's the hold up? Let it out!
Onee-chan is waiting!
Here...
If I do this, you can't hold back, can you?
You can thrust harder, so hurry up and cum!
W-Wait, w-why did you stop?
Hey, aren't you nearly there? I said we need to hurry!
Yes but finishing like this is a bit...
N-No! W-What are you doing?
Don't you remember me holding you like then when you were younger?
Now you swallow my dick like this.
You sure have grown up.
What are you talking about?
You took my virginity and fuck me whenever you want.
What kind of father holds their daughter like this? Don't be stupid!
C-C'mon, let it out already! Otherwise onee-chan will-!
You just want it, don't you? Geez.
It's poking me deeply again!
No, I'll cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming~!!
Natsume, that hurts. Natsume?
N-No! T-This isn't happening!
Geez, you mustn't wet yourself at your age!
I-It's your fault, you-!
U-Um, Dad...
I'm sorry about before.
It was so sudden, and...
I don't mind, since you're my daughter.
Or do you want to see it again?
W-What are you saying?!
Oh, I'm sorry. My hand slipped.
Um, Dad? I can do it on my own...
So, um, you don't need to help...
Okay? You're tired, right?
We're family, there's no need to be embarrassed.
C'mon, show me your back.
O-Okay...
Hurry and get better Fuyu.
Okay, now lift your arm.
Looks like you've been sweating.
Good, you've grown up very nicely.
H-Huh? N-No...
What? Why Dad?
Hey, please stop, please stop...
No, you can't...
This is just discipline, you can't just leave your cellphone around!
Anyone could have seen it, but you're lucky it was me.
Y-You saw, Dad?
That's horrible.
Even if it is Dad, it's still mean.
Who's the horrible one?
You've been talking behind your sister's back.
I didn't know you thought such a thing behind that smile.
Gosh, I feel betrayed.
Eh? I thought I locked it, no way...
I wonder what everyone would think were they to see your true self.
No, you're wrong, you're wrong!
I like my sisters.
I...
If you want things to stay the same between you lot,
it all depends on your attitude now.
You're a good girl, Fuyu.
No, please don't, Dad!
You're not wet, but bear with me, okay?
It hurts! Dad, it hurts a lot!
Please wait, I beg of you!
You'll feel better soon!
No...
It hurts, it hurts...
I'm sorry, Dad, I'm sorry!
Dad...
No please, no more, Dad...
No, Dad! I said I'm sorry!
No! Not there, it hurts dad, not there! That's my ass!
Dad... Please...
This is discipline, bear with it.
No, no more...
It's coming in, Dad's penis is coming into my pussy...
Why? I'm your daughter...
Why is Dad's penis- No!
Dad, you're being rough...
No Dad, no!
No Dad, not inside, please!
No, Dad's stuff is inside me...
Why, Dad?
Because I have to discipline you for-
You idiot! I told you not to touch the others, you bastard!
You too! Why did you let him do such thing?!
Geez! You're always-!
Goddamn it! You hit me as hard as you could!
Hmph!
Maybe the pain will wake you up!
O-Onee-chan, I'm sorry... It's my fault...um...
Stop with that self-blaming attitude!
Try to change it a bit, will you?!
Hmph!
W-What's this? What's going on?!
You've got to be kidding, right?
Dad and Fuyu were... and Natsume, why was she so...
Does that mean Fuyu was having sex with Dad?
Then Natsume got angry and...
Oh, it's you Haruka, I was wondering who it was.
Where have you been?
Hm? I just came to have a drink.
You're lying! Dad, what were you doing in Fuyu's room?!
We're family!
What are you thinking?!
That was...
discipline.
W-What are you talking about?
Discipline?
Is raping your daughter discipline?
Dad! You've gone crazy! What happened to you?
Oh I get it, you also want my discipline!
Then just say so.
W-W-W-What's this?!
Dad, W-Why... Why are you taking that out?! Hey!
Why? You know why.
Please stop it, Dad.
What's happened to you? Seriously!
I know that you may feel lonely since Mom died,
but doing it with your daughter is-!
Oh really?
Then I guess I'll have to settle with doing Fuyu while imagining your mother.
Wha-! Dad! I told you to stop it!
It can't be helped since you, the oldest daughter, doesn't want it, right?
No way-!
Fine then, I get it, I get it! Just don't touch Fuyu or the others again!
I'll take their place!
Only if you satisfy me.
I-Is this alright?
Whoa, it's so hard-!
I didn't know penises got this hot...
Haruka, can you lick it now?
Huh? S-Sure.
No, something is coming out... What is this? It's sour...
Put it in your mouth.
No, this shape, this is perverted!
I wonder if Dad is about to cum...
Dad, are you going to cum?
I can't breathe-
What's this? I didn't know semen was this yucky and sticky...
Haruka, clean me up.
Dad? Why? You're getting large again.
It's because you feel good, as expected from the oldest daughter.
I can't be pleased when you praise me for something like that!
Oh really?
It makes Dad happy when you please me by doing such things.
What are you saying? Quit it...
You're getting embarrassed?
You secretly wanted this, didn't you Haruka?
Dad!
Dad, are we really going to do this?
You want me, don't you Haruka?
Of course I don't! Doing such immoral things...
Well, if you don't want it, then I'll-
Fine! I get it! I get it, okay?
Oh! So you want me?
Yes, I want you Dad.
However, this is my first time, so please don't make it too painful.
I know darling, it will only hurt for a moment.
So, show me yourself.
This is embarrassing, dad!
Looks like you're quite wet!
Did sucking me off arouse you?
That's, that's not true! No way...
You're dripping fluid. See? This is going to enter you.
It's coming in! Dad's penis is coming into my pussy!
It's tight...
No! It's coming right in!
N-Noo! It hurts! It hurts, Dad! It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts a lot!
No Dad, take it out! Please, Dad, take it out!
Sure, I'll take it out soon.
It hurts, no, it hurts! I can't bear something like this!
No! Pull it out! Pull it out!
If you don't relax yourself, you won't feel good!
It hurts! Dad, it really hurts! Please stop it!
If you can't bear it, maybe I'll have to get Natsume too.
You can't do that either!
If you say I can't do this, then I can't do that.
I won't be able to hold back.
Seems like the pain is fading, isn't this great?
Now you can feel good.
Something like that....
Oh no! My body is getting hot...
Do you wanna see our child? Huh?
N-No! No, you can't Dad!
What are you thinking?! We can't do that!
We just can't!
No! Dad please, really, you can't!
You can put your penis inside me, but you can't do that-!
Dad! Dad you're not listening!
Don't! No!
Dad, you can't! Please don't Dad! Dad!
No, no! This can't be happening...
Your sperm is coming out inside of me...
No... So much, no way...
I'll get pregnant... with Dad's baby...
A-A-Akira? Umm... This isn't-
Do you want some apple? You must be tired...
Y-Yeah...
Tsk! She got ahead.
Jeez, Dad sure is taking ages reading the newspaper in the toilet!
I might wet myself!
Oh? Come to think of it Natsume also went to the toilet.
Eh?
You jerk, you ended up doing all of them.
You pervert, scum!
H-Hey, Natsume!
If you keep going like this, they'll...
It's in-!
I won't let you touch the others!
Amazing-!
If I do this, then you won't be as horny, so-!
What are you say-
Shut it old man, just keep moving your hips.
Natsume! You're in there, right?
What are you doing so early in the morning?
Dad! You're inside there, aren't you?
If you keep doing such things, I don't know what will happen!
Huh? Dad, didn't you say you wouldn't touch the others?
I don't really mind, but...
Dad...
Hey Natsume! You should hear yourself moan!
Natsume! What has happened to you?
H-H-Hey Akira! Don't do that!
No! Lemme go! I can't just let them-!
Your penis is rubbing against my insides!
It's good, it feels so good!
Hey! C'mon, release it!
Give me your semen!
As well as everyone else's share!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!