Hey Makino!
Hurry up already!
I'll let Natsume go right away, so please leave first.
I get it! Thanks, Sensei.
C’mon Natsume, hurry up and cum, or you'll be late.
Geez you sick pervert! Even though I've
got a cold you’re doing this to me!
Hurry up and end it already!
Putting it in at somewhere like this...
This man... fucking his daughter’s pussy all he wants...
Geez, if you want it that much then I guess it can't be helped.
Stop joking around... there's no way I want
it! Just hurry up and get it over with!
Why is my pussy...
Your pussy is squeezing as you speak.
It’s obvious you’re want more.
Who do you think... make me like this?... You Idiot!
Idiot? How dare you say "idiot" to your father!?
What's with this guy... geez...
Do you need more training, Natsume?
I... I’m sorry...
At least you apologize more properly now. Here’s your reward.
Hey, wait... too rough!
Hey!
No... not there...
Letting out so much semen again... this shit of a father!
Geez... I'm about to run after this,
it’s gonna spill out! Pervert...
Onee-chan... Are you okay?
Geez....
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: romeyo007 | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Demon Father
~REVENGE~
Yeah, a training camp.
You want me to go along?
You’re not at your best condition right now, and the advisor's
sick at the moment, so we don’t have anyone suitable.
Was this your idea?
That’s right.
So, It's fine, right?
I guess. I'm on vacation anyways, so
I guess everyone can go together.
I have training camp, too. It's at a different place, too...
Who is it? Please stop this already.
Please!
They’re huge boobs aren't they? Way too slutty.
That’s not true! Please let go of me before
saying something like that...
Huh? She doesn't realize it’s me? Or
is she going for that kind of play?
Well then...
They’re getting hard!
Is your pussy soaked as well?
Stop!
No! Stop it!
You...
No... no way... is that a penis?
No way... No, no!
His finger is inside... No way... something like this...
I could use that to... fight off this guy...
It’s no use! I'm gonna put it in your right here right now!
No, please stop, I beg you! No! I have a person I like...
No, please, don't put it in! Don't
put something like that inside!
No! It’s coming in... It's coming inside... No way...
If you don’t want worse things to
happen to you, then stay put.
No!!
No way! No way, no way!
Why? Why?
A penis is inside me... No!
Heh, a stranger’s dick is inside, and
yet your pussy is soaked! Pervert.
No, stop... You’re the pervert! Let me go already!
Why... my body is...
No! Why are you doing such things...
Help me, Dad!
I’ll plant my seed inside you like this!
No... Stop... Please spare me from at least that!
Why? If he cums like this... I’ll bear
a child of someone I don’t know...
No!!
No way...
It’s coming inside... sperm is flowing inside!
No way... why did this happen... why me...
Huh? She did realize...
Um, Akira! Akira! It’s Dad! Getup!
Dad!?
If you ever do this again... it'll be one.
I think no one will come this way.
What, is Fuyu blogging on her own again?
Akira didn't know it was me... it was quite exciting...
I guess that s a place where no one comes around.
No one’s around, right?
I have to write today’s update!
Eh? What’s this!? Is this a..
Painful... who is it?
Why... is he sticking his penis between my boobs?
No... No more!
You want to pee?
Want to try peeing while sucking on a dick?
No way... did he find out?
Who is this person? Why is he doing this?
No...
It's going down my throat...
No!
No! No!!
No please! You can’t do this!
Help me, Dad!
Struggling wont' help you.
Asking help from me? Such a cute daughter of you.
No way... it’s in... a penis is inside!
No... Stop already... Why are you doing this to me... No!
Dad?
Oh, so you found out. Sorry for scaring you, Fuyu.
So it’s Dad...
No way... Dad is doing this to me? Why...
Fuyu is just so cute, I couldn't help
but force it on you. My bad.
Dad... Dad!... Dad...
It’s Dad’s penis... I’m being... by Dad... Dad! Penis...
Oh? She started to feel it after knowing it's me.
Amazing! Dad’s penis is amazing!
So this is Dad's penis...
Amazing...
I’m pissing while having Dad pour sperm inside of me...
Fuyu's reaction was quite refreshing...
Natsume's inside right now... Don’t peek, Dad.
Just hold back for now.
If you wait ‘till we go back, then... um, everyone would be...
I'm fine.
Are you going somewhere?
I thought I'd get some evening air.
Just going for a walk.
You’re so cute.
Akira, so you were here.
Oh Dad. it’s a wild cat, the real I stick
to people, and they’re really cute...
Dad...
Hey, wait!
Dad wants to be pet by Akira, too.
Dad... not out here... no way!
I see. Then where would it be okay?
I said earlier that when we head back...
Even if you say that... I can't hold back for that long.
If Akira won't do it then I’ll go for Natsume or...
Dad, I said you can’t! Um, hold back already! I'll...
Dad... Um, only with my hands and mouth, okay?
Geez... doing it some place like this...
it’s your fault if someone sees us!
you're this... hard... Geez, Dad...
Sorry about that. Akira's so cute I could help it.
Geez, let it out already.
Oh I know, if you use your boobs it’ll end faster.
Out here? You’re kidding, right?
Well, then I guess it can't be helped if it takes longer.
Geez, I get it already.
Even though it’s embarrassing... out here...
Hurry up and cum already!
It’s getting larger...
Are you about to cum, Dad?
Let it out... on my boobs!
So much is coming out...
So much of Dad's milk...
Amazing... I drank so much of Dad's...
Hey, Dad! Why are you hard again?
I said no! Dad... what are you trying
to do somewhere like this!?
It can't be help right? Akira is just too cute.
It’ll end with this, so, okay?
Just hold back! If someone finds us
we won't even have an excuse...
and I wouldn't be able to feel good!
Feel good, huh? Even if you're this wet?
No! Stop it Dad! I said stop it! Geez... this
isn't a joke! Dad, stop messing around!
You say that and yet your pussy is this wet!
You were such an honest girl before... are
you going through the rebellious phase?
No! I just don’t want to do it somewhere like this! Hey!
Dad, please!
Saying please won’t help you. A girl in he?
rebellious phase needs strict discipline!
Hey Dad... um, it’s not that I don’t want
to do it... but... not out here...
No! It hurt... Dad! What are you doing?
It s discipline. Although I thought that Akira
wouldn't need it, unlike Natsume.
What’s that? Dad’s the one with problems! Even though
I’m saying I don’t want to do it out here...
No!
I want to do it here. And yet my daughter is being
so selfish. She needs discipline, right?
Stop it already, come on, Dad!
No.
Not my butt... it’s strange! It feels fuzzy!
Stop...
No... No!
While I give you discipline I’ll train this part of you as well.
No... don’t tease there... it’s too embarrassing! No!
There’s nothing to be embarrassed about, since
all of Akira came out from this part of Dad!
No! Geez stop already! I’m embarrassed! Come on...
No way, Dad, what’s with that? You can't
Put it in there! It won't fit! Come on!
No, no please! I’m sorry! Dad!
This is discipline. It's love from Dad!
No... It’s going in... It’s going inside! My butt... Dad! No!!
It feels sick! My butt is getting hot!
You can feel good from this side
as well. Your mom loved it, too.
No way... I don’t want to hear stuff like that...
You're so self-indulgent, Akira, just bear it.
It’s inside...
It's inside... a penis is in my butt!
It’s fine, it’ll feel good right away.
No... this is so weird... No!!
I said no! This isn't right!
No, penis...
Are you feeling good already? As expected
from someone who’s like Mother.
That s not it! What are you saying!? It
doesn't feel good... it’s just weird!
It doesn't feel good!
You're this wet, there’s no way you’re not feeling it, right?
No... why are you hitting me!?
Discipline is becoming a reward, isn't it, Akira?
That's not true! This isn't it... I don’t like Dad’s penis!
You’re feeling good even though I’m this rough,
Akira's the sluttiest amongst you sisters!
No... That’s not true! I’m not slutty!
I’m not!
There’s no way... that’s true! Something
like this... doesn't feel good!
No... what’s this... amazing!
Why... what's this... so deep!
Even though I don’t want to... I'm
going crazy... from my butt!
No... no!
No... Dad! What’s... this?
You’re about to cum, huh?
No way... I’m cumming... from by butt?
I’m cumming? No way, no way! No!
It's going in... inside my butt... milk is going in!
I'm cummmg... from my butt!
What’s wrong, Akira? Are you unsatisfied?
Even though I said no, Dad's so forceful...
somewhere like this... Geez...
It can’t be helped, right? I want to
do it with Akira. I can’t hold back.
Geez... Dad...
Geez! What is that old man doing!?
What do you mean "do it with your butt"! Pervert!
Let’s just keep on walking.
Shoot!
No way, Dad! Someone saw us, they
saw us, right!? What do we do!?
Just go back to the camp, Akira.
That was close! I hope they didn't see it was me.
Wait, I guess it's actually fine even if they do...
Everyone knows anyways...
Geez, I guess I'll talk to Akira about it when I get back.