Is it something you can't explain?
No, it's not! This is really, I... this...
No way, this... me and Dad isn't it?
Although Mom hasn't noticed yet...
Besides...
Dad. Please stop it already.
I haven't forgiven you yet!
How can you attack your daughter...
You did the same things to Airi, too.
And even Sana-chan!
No!
Dad! Please!
You can’t! Please stop!
Why are you doing this?
Dad!
No!
I'll tell the police!
And mom will also...
To think that'd you'd do something like this...
That would be troubling.
From now on you’re my sex slave,
so you should be more obedient.
S-Sex!?
Please don’t joke like that!
Do you think I'm joking?
C’mon, let's go in here.
No! Not somewhere like this!
Oh, so you prefer being outside?
Marina is sure bold.
No!
Please stop.
You sure you want to be so loud?
Students come here, too, don’t they?
Other people will find out.
I wouldn't care if they did,
but if Kayoko knew she'd be so sad.
Or if Airi finds out that you've stolen me from here...
I wonder what shell think.
That I am seducing you or stole you?
No one is going to think that way!
Just keep it down.
Then I won't do anything bad.
I’m sure he's given up by now.
From now on I'll train you to my liking.
No...
Marina doesn't hate this, don't you?
It’s something pleasurable, so you should enjoy it.
Just hurry and finish, please.
I don't want to be here like this for long...
I see. Then let’s use Marina's boobs to squeeze it.
I can't do something like that!
Not something like using my boobs...
Oh so you know about a titty fuck!
Airi didn't have that kind of knowledge.
Marina’s quite the pervert.
Um...
I guess he just taught you the knowledge about this stuff.
That’s not...
It was just with my friends... I...
Wait, Mari...
I'm sorry...
You've got to be gentle.
Let's use your boobs to treat this pain.
The real thing starts now.
A penis is coming between my boobs...
Squeeze your boobs so it doesn't fall
out while moving up and down.
Like... like this?
Just like that, but faster.
At some place like this, I...
Is this enough?
Of course not.
Well, it could be better if you use
your saliva to make it slippery.
I’m doing embarrassing things...
Why am I going so far?
Just it bit more. Faster.
Marina, keep that position and take it with your face.
There’s so much of... Dad’s stuff... on my face...
It felt great, Marina.
Hey, Dad, wait!
Not here...
It hurts...
No, we're doing it at the park!
He made me give him a titty fuck and
now we're going all the way...
I’m doing so many perverted things...
Does it still hurt?
It’ll get better eventually.
Something like this... won’t get better!
Please don’t say something so selfish!
Although you say that, your body seems quite happy.
No...
Airi was like this, too.
But it seems like our bodies are quite compatible.
What are you saying!?
I guess I've got to thank Marina's dad.
He was French, right?
This compatibility could be from the foreign blood.
No, stop! Don’t talk about Papa like that...
I wish you would call me “Papa", too.
That’s...
Dad is... just Dad...
You won’t call me Papa?
That's because... well...
I guess that can’t be helped.
I was trying to be gentle, but I guess it's too hard.
This position could make us good prey for people peeping.
No! Don’t do... something like this..!
No! I don't want this!
We’ll be seen! Stop!
There’s no way I could stop.
I’m going to make sure you feel me,
the presence of your Daddy!
Deep...no! Too deep!
I’ll be seen..
I'm being exposed in embarrassing
positions... I'll... go crazy!
Why don’t I get you pregnant here...
And make you and Kayoko a belly
blobbing mother and daughter?
No way, no way...
That's... You really can't do that!
I want you to be my sex slave,
and pleasure me when I want.
Why!?
Something like... a sex slave...
So much is flowing inside...
Dad’s is... inside...
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Demonic father
~Cosplaying NEET in Cowgirl Position~
This is... some kind of misunderstanding.
I haven’t been to such places.
I see. If you say so...
I get it. I'll talk with Dad and...
Mom, you won't believe what I’m saying?
Even telling Dad... it’s embarrassing.
It's not a situation where you can say that.
Besides, we've got to think of some
kind of plan ahead of time.
Plan? For what?
Geez...
Listen. This was purposely sent to Kyoutou-sensei.
It’s obviously targeted at you.
Also...
Although it was better that you didn't know this, but...
Th-this...
The beautiful honor student
might be a slut?
Anon-kun
Talk.
Really? I like the blond younger sister.
The blond sister, too?
Looking innocent while doing what you do, huh?
Let me have a go, too!
I wonder for how much?
But doesn't it sound ridiculous?
Now way! I always looked up to her as
the diva of the school!
Ubelievable! Shis plays good-kid in class, too
That's the worst.
It's probably about you guys.
I was even called back for this.
We don't know what it’s going to end up like,
so for a while I want you to stay at home.
Huh? But...
No buts. It’s been dangerous outside recently.
I want Airi to take a break, too,
but let’s start with you.
To think they'd even send a fake picture...
There’s going to me an emergency staff meeting soon,
so Mom is going to get home late today.
I’m glad that I get to see Airi-tan in her bloomers,
but since your mother’s back you been strange, Airi.
You’re not concentrated during practice, either...
Do you want Oji-sama to yourself that bad?
What!? What does that mean?
There’s no way that’s true,
And I've already said that I'll give that devil to Sana! Hmph!
When did that happen?
Really, Airi. Did something happen?
No idea!
Huh? What?
I can't see anything...
Huh? What is this?
Airi? Dad?
I’m sorry, Mom.
Are you alright?
Why? Wait, get me...
Oh Marina?
What happened?
Where are Airi and Dad?
I heard loud voices...
Huh? Dad? He’s not home.
Also, the loud voices might have been me practicing.
See?
Wasn't it my voice?
Huh? But just now, I saw Dad and Airi on the bed...
Huh? It was me and Airi.
Oh? Dress like that?
Yeah, because we're preparing a café, right?
We need to greet the customers, so I was practicing my voice.
Welcome back, Master.
Have a safe trip, Darling.
Stuff like that.
I see...
That’s strange, I thought it was Dad...
Geez Mom, could you be getting old?
Don’t be mean, Marina!
Mom is still young!
Don’t be so stubborn around your daughter!
Geez, well...
What was that?
What's with Mikami?
Why is she standing like that over there?
Hey, Airi!
Oh, Airi, hey!
She’s fine.
I managed to catch her.
But, it seems like she sleeped deprived.
She’s sound asleep now.
Geez, cocky as she is she’s quite adorable while asleep.
Let's give her some of my smell.
Sleep-learning, they call it.
There, Airi...
It's back to this shape down here.
This is the best.
This is good, too,
But it’s definitely best while she's wearing it.
Huh? I fell asleep?
What happened to Airi...
Wait, hey! You...
Don’t joke with me you lowlife! Demon!
What are you thinking!?
Hey!
You’re finally noticing.
They say you’re sleep deprived.
What were you doing at night?
Masturbating?
Papa will help relieve your body with sex.
I'm telling you to stop joking!
Like I'd get turned on by you, stupid!
Hmph, how cocky.
Hmm? The smell...
Oh, it’s the discharge. You got your period, Airi.
You careless bastard! Pervert! Stupid!
Hurry and stop it, you...
This bastard... like I'd feel it from him!
Are you planning to hold back?
Then I’ll use you the way I want like a sex slave.
You’re treating me as a fool again...
Are you crying?
Only virgins are forgiven when the cry.
Second-hand products like you won’t do.
Shut up! Why are you doing this to me...
Hmph. I’m punishing you until you’re in shape.
This bastard... this...
Hey, why did you get them dirty! Stupid!
Oh, they're dirty now.
Then you should put this on.
Seems like there’ll be a school festival soon.
A lot of cosplay costumes were around.
Hmm, irresistible.
It's useless to play stubborn for any longer.
Airi's perverted body just can’t be helped.
Just say what you want!
It’s just gross to be touched by you! Lowlife!
Don't fool around with me!
This bastard...
Geez, then what was with that woman! Geez!
You’re soaking wet.
So Airi's perverted pussy is yearning for Papa's dick.
Shut up! A stinky dick like that...
Stupid!
Although you've got the adult complaints, cockiness and body,
you’re just a brat on the inside.
Geez.
If you want it that much, I’ll give you plenty.
Hey, wait...
What does he mean, brat?
Airi is...
Hurry and... cum, you stupid!
I've got to enjoy myself first.
Airi is just a kid!
Something like this... dammit, I don’t feel it!
Take out your shitty dick already!
It doesn't feel good, you lowlife!
Geez, what an irritating brat.
Again, he sprayed so much on Airi
and make me drink... stop it already!
That felt great, Airi.
Next time I'll love you at home.
Geez, Oji-sama needs to be honest!
Oh, it's Sana.
You really look like you need help with this.
Sana, how are things going over there?
As planned.
But though I say that, it's Yuka-senpai working hard.
Well, it's not like I don’t hold any grudges at all.
Oh, how is Marina-san?
Seems like she'll be staying at home for a while.
Kayoko told me.
I think that's best.
Being here could start to be hard for her.
How's that going to happen?
Marina belongs to me.
Geez, Oji-sama.
Same for Airi, too. You have to say it out clearly!
Right now we need something definite and conclusive.
About that, it's also Yuka-senpai...
Oh, she also mentioned that she borrowed
some drugs from Oji-sama.
What!?
Geez. I’ll be going back now. I've got to punish her.
Well see you later...
Kouzou-san.
Thanks for the wait.
And sorry for making you do so much for me.
No, I’m glad to work for Kouzou-san.
Then let’s begin.
Yes..
Geez, this is the worst!
That bastard... this is so messed up!
What is this!? This...
How many did you take?
Two.
Time passed?
Fifteen minutes.
Hmm, it's getting a little moist.
Compared to the beginning...
The vagina is gaining heat...
It also feels like... the lips... are quivering...
Are you getting excited?
You can't. We won’t be able to tell the effect of the drug.
Y-Yes, I understand.
But, it's in front of Kouzou-san, so it's embarrassing...
I'm sorry...
Please endure for a while.
The effect appears to take place faster than before.
You might be close to the outbreak.
Once there was a young teacher who went crazy
after being too close to some students.
You've got to be careful.
Oh, and I heard from Sana about the drugs.
It's time for punishment.
I’m sorry.
Please... punish me...
Do you feel anything different?
Yes... I want Kouzou-san’s... really badly...
Come to think of it, I've been with Airi
and the others all the time recently.
After the inspection, okay?
Thank you very much.
Hmph, like I’d cry myself to sleep because of that!
I’m definitely going to...
Kouzou-san, please...
I'm so happy. Kouzou-san’s penis...
Did you want it that much?
It’s wonderful. Kouzou-san's dear penis... it’s great!
You've been with just Marina-san and Airi-san...
I was so lonely...
I’m so full with Kouzou-san’s dick!
I thought she was friends with Marina...
Maybe they don’t show it at school?
My pussy... please give me lots more...
Kouzou-san’s...
Yes... your penis is going in and out...
My pussy... amazing...
I can see... Kouzou-san...
You’re doing... so much for me...
My pussy is so wet, I'm going crazy!
I’m so happy... to have been saved... by Kouzou-san!
I want Kouzou-san to do lots to me!
I’d do anything... for Kouzou-san...
No, Kouzou-san, I... I’m going to...
Even though I want your penis to cum, too...
I'll do it again anytime you want.
I so happy,.. you have me in your eyes, too...
Kouzou-san, I love you, I love you!
No, Kouzou-san... I’m cumming...
I'm cumming!
Yuka has gotten sensitive, too.
Though it’s all thanks to me.
Oh I know!
If she becomes friends with Marina,
counting Airi we can have a foursome!
With Sana it'll be a fivesome!
Dad... are we really doing this?
You were seducing me in those clothes before, so, you know.
I was not seducing you! What are you saying?
You made Airi cry, and you almost let Mom find out!
Besides, I’m already...
It’s just a safely procedure.
It’s like you're schooling yourself at home.
Besides, we can have sex any time we want now.
Dad!
Geez...
Marina? Are you taking that cocky personality, too?
Apparently it’s a Tsudere Maid Café. Our class.
Oh, I see...
Will you do alright with that?
All I need it to imitate Airi. It’s easy.
True...
Don't overwork yourself about it...
and enjoy the school festival.
Yes.
But before that it's my turn to enjoy.
Dad!
You penis... wait...
Deep inside...
What happened? Dad is different from the usual.
Marina, drink it all like this.
Dad!
It's painful... Dad...
So you’ll be serving those boys in this uniform...
Don’t say it like that... it's perverted!
It’s just a café!
Hmph, but the men will be tapping all they have to this.
Don't say something like that...
I'm not...
You read the posts, didn't you?
That’s how you’re being looked at right now.
That’s not true! I...
I’m not... anyone’s...
Dad’s is coming deep inside!
They want to violate you like this!
They want to thrust into you as you
seduce with in that sexy uniform!
That's not true!
The only person who’d do that... is Dad!
Everyone's thinking of spraying the perverted Marina
who's pretending to be a good honor student!
Don't say... that’s not true!
I'm having sex with Dad!
I'm just going crazy from Dad's dick!
You’re wearing a uniform that shows your
underwear as soon as you squat down.
What is that but perverted?
I’ll be careful about... those kinds of things!
You say that, but in fact you plan to show them huh?
I won’t!
I won't do... embarrassing things...
Everyone will look at me strangely!
Everyone will peek at your panties and
take photos to use as fap material!
No!
Don’t say... mean things!
But, by then you might be big-bellied though.
Dad, let it out!
Dad's milk... belongs to Mom, but...
I want it, too!
Dad! Give it to me!
Give milk to Marina!
It’s coming! Dad's milk is deep inside Marina!
So much baby-making juice is coming from Dad's penis!
While Marina's self-studying at home,
I've decided to take a break from my job as a teacher.
Thank you, Dad.
Geez, it’s Airi's turn now, right, Papa?
Airi, what are you...
I want Papa's mean dick!
How could you leave Airi to be with Onee-chan!
Geez, I was so lonely...
Oh, acting again?
So it's the spoiled child this time?
I, I won't be fooled.
What are you saying, Airi?
I just want Papa to love me.
Hmph, you’re planning to call me stupid
after getting on, aren't you?
What is this? What’s happening?
You dick is sure big!
Even though you just came in Onee-chan,
You're going to tease Airi again!
Airi, hey!
If you're acting then stop!
Know you limits, Ai...!
That’s...
Could it be... the outbreak!? Airi!?
Stir up Airi with your dick!
Fill up Airi's perverted pussy!
No, but, the one that Airi had was...
You mean dick is amazing!
Airi's pussy is going crazy!
Papa, it feels too good!
But this situation...
Yuka-senpai said that she borrowed some drugs from you.
I’m sorry.
Yuka had!? No way...
Papa’s dick... feels so good...
It fits perfectly inside Airi's soaked, perverted pussy!
This... I love this...!
Airi is so happy from Papa's dick!