No! I want to be with you, Marina!
What are you saying...
It would be dangerous as well, just two girls alone...
Ah, hot springs, so nice...
We have more days off because of the holidays,
and Kayoko's busy with her study group.
Shut up, didn't ask you, pig!
But then I don't want to be in the same room with this trash!
No way, no way!
Oh come on, Airi...
I won't go otherwise.
Thanks for the meal.
Just when I thought you two were getting along well, now it's weird again.
Dad, you know the reason, right?
Airi won't tell me...
Yeah...
Then make up with her.
Let's all enjoy the trip.
Sorry.
You're so cute, Marina.
You're beautiful and so good-natured.
And you react so nicely.
Don't say such embarrassing things, Dad...
Just this much for now.
I'm looking forward to the trip!
Looking forward...
Dad, you're wonderful!
My pussy's stuffed with you!
I want your cock in my pussy too!
I can't hold back anymore!
Such a perverted face. You're creepy.
Airi!
I'm bored! In the last minute Marina said she couldn't come...
Why does a beautiful girl like me have to go with an old freak like you?
Marina didn't have a choice. And she said she'd join us later.
And I have to endure you until then. I feel like throwing up.
You little...
This?
You never learn. Reflect on your actions.
I washed it clean for you.
Onichichi Re-born: Travellers' Emotions
Saucy little trip to the hot springs
What's this? It feels so hot inside...
Airi, is something wrong?
Don't come here!
Says the girl whose panties are already dripping.
No way, what's this?! Why?!
No...
No... he's touching my pussy... This is...
Stop it!
Damn, my body's enjoying it!
You... that candy earlier... had something in it?
You just realized? It's now hip among researchers.
And it's really so effective.
You're screwing with me again...
You know, I couldn't resist such a request...
But I know the side effects now.
Side effects?
The guys' version is really powerful, it can cure all impotency,
but the agent is present in the sweat,
so it turns on those who come in contact with it.
So that was because the medicine?
Don't screw with me, you pig!
How dare you do this to me?
My rating got even better because of that.
It's thanks to you.
Disgusting! You freak!
My rating's as low as can be! You dog!
Hey!
Sto-
Don't...
I'm enjoying it too much!
You're not honest, Airi. You're about to cum, aren't you?
Shut up, idiot! There's no way...
No...
Damn, he'll make me cum!
I can't take it!
Airi?
What? Is this a side effect?
I'll wet myself... I must go to the toilet... I may not make it...
Wait, Airi... The toilet is...
That way!
Okay!
Stupid! You don't have to...
What are you saying? Just let it go!
This is so embarrassing!
You're so wet, I bet you can't hold back anymore...
It's nothing to do...
No, don't!
Don't! It... it won't stop...
You trash! I'll remember this for you!
Don't just put it in here! Don't put it in!
I don't want you in me!
You turned me on, so shut it.
It's your fault, you freak!
Hey, stop it!
Stop... I feel like I'm gonna throw up... Stop...
I told you to pull out...
I don't want it!
You'll make me cum again, trash...
Just enjoy my boy's service.
I said I don't...
I don't want...
You trash...
Trash! Prevert!
You...
Why in me...
Airi, wait a little before following me.
Look! Eggs boiled in the hot springs!
Their insides are juicy white!
Yeah, just like my cock!
You seriously don't know when to stop?
You freak!
We're still not there? Just how far is it?
We should be there, according to Marina's directions...
Wait, that's it!
Welcome!
I'm Akitsuki, we have a reservation...
Welcome, and thanks for your visit!
Please do come in!
Exchange contacts? Okay.
Let's see, the address...
Maple
Damn Marina! I asked her not to put me in one room with you!
Ah, a hot bath!
We have one in the room! Great!
I'll take a bath right away!
Then let's go together!
As if I would, stupid!
Go alone!
I'm going for a walk. Don't follow me!
I'm going alone.
This is so beautiful! It feels so nice to relax at a place like this every now and then!
So big! It's a matchmaker god's!
I should say a prayer...
You're alone, girlie?
What's this? No way, this again?!
I know these parts quite well. And I do babysitting.
Really? Then you should guide us together. Together!
Come, Airi!
There are men like that everywhere.
Are you all right, Airi?
Yeah... I was so surprised!
What the hell's wrong with these people?
It's dangerous to walk alone.
You can never know when will someone assault you.
Shut up! You assaulted me as well! Stupid!
It's because you're so lame!
W-What are you looking at?!
Don't screw with me!
You're always thinking about only that!
You had something hidden again...
Airi, he'll find us...
If we don't stuff your loud little mouth.
You trash!
You're so stiff!
Airi, it feels great!
Shut up, you freak!
Your honey's out!
Hey, we're outside!
Stupid! I don't want to do it with you!
You say that, but you move your hips.
As if I would! It's just because your drug!
You use a cute girl for your experiments, you freak!
Well, the experiment's already done,
so now just be a nice cute girl for me.
My insides are on fire...
You're getting bigger in me, you creepy old man!
You're as foul-mouthed as ever.
I'll have to fix that with some drugs.
You're... No matter...
How much you do it... It won't feel good...
Don't!
You enjoy this too, don't you?
No! I can't even feel it!
So you say to me.
But the professor?
You're really so lame!
I don't even want to enjoy this!
If you can, just enjoy it honestly.
Holding back is bad for your body.
I don't want this!
Don't...
You can't hold back anymore.
Watch, I'll cum in you right away!
Don't... Don't cum inside me!
Please don't!
You trash!
Why is my body so happy about it?
You freak! Stupid pig!
I'm all sweaty! It's disgusting!
Jeez...
I must take a bath and get rid of your stink.
Wash yourself carefully, Airi.
And don't forget your used underwear.
This feels so good!
And there's no one here at this time.
It's as if the whole place's mine!
I wanted to try this for so long!
I feel so relaxed...
Though it could be twice this good if it wasn't for him...
I don't even want to remember.
Huh? What?
Don't even think about my girl!
Drop dead you filthy freak!
Wait, what? What's going on?
Airi's cuteness is mine only!
Get lost, dammit! I won't let you have Airi!
You trash! Get lost!
He's so stupid...
That was close... I can't let anyone have Airi.
Damn, I lost so much time.
Is Airi out already?
Ouch, hot!
You're so stupid.
I'm so full!
I feel so warm and relaxed!
This place is really nice!
I hope Marina will come soon too.
Don't even think about it.
I bought it, it's mine!
You can't have any!
Here, that's yours.
Be happy you can have an indirect kiss from me.
Here, Airi, this one's cooler!
How about it?
Don't want it. Don't come here, freak.
Just put it down there.
Okay, okay. I'll leave it here on the table then.
Darn, you look gorgeous whatever you wear.
A plain bathrobe looks like royal wear on you.
What are you saying?
Hearing it from you won't make me any happier.
And you're my cute little girl.
Your dad's really happy that you grew up so lewd.
I'm not so happy about it.
You love me too, don't you?
You're embarrassed to say?
You're stupid! Just touching you is disgusting!
Or you want him instead?
How did you conclude that, stupid?
But you're hard again.
Don't hold back, Airi. You know you...
You're so confident because of that, aren't you?
Drugs again? Are you really this stupid?
Idiot! Lowest of the low! Worst of trash!
It wouldn't dissolve so quickly! And you call yourself a scientist?
Then I must...
Airi?
Really? You pig! Trash!
Why would you...
What do you think of me? Why do you always use drugs?
Why do you make me lose myself?
You can't touch me if I'm not drugged?
You don't want to hold me if I'm not out of my mind?
That's not-
Liar! You lie!
I'm serious...
Then why can't you say it?
You only call Marina cute and beautiful...
You never said such stuff to me!
I'm cute too! And beautiful, right?
Or I'm not cute without drugs?
Am I just a test subject for you?
That's not it, Airi!
I'm a girl you know!
I want the guy I like to call me cute!
Airi... I'm sorry...
You're my precious girl.
The girl I love the most in this world.
Really? You love me? I'm cute?
Yeah. I love you. You're the cutest.
It was all my fault.
Papa...
Papa, your cock got so big!
And you're teasing my pussy with your mouth!
Your cock is...
Papa... Take me...
Please...
It feels so good in me...
You'll always love me quietly, right?
No, I'll keep saying it aloud!
Really? You won't let me go?
Not ever, Airi!
I feel so embarrassed suddenly!
I'm not cute now...
You're always cute, Airi!
Papa, I'm so happy...
I can feel you deep in me...
You're turning me inside out!
My pussy's yours!
You're mine, Airi!
I love you! I want to be full with you!
Fill me all the way in!
My pussy's on fire!
I'm stuffed with your cock...
You're making me feel so good!
I want to see your face! Hold me!
Your cock feels so good! I feel I'm cumming soon!
Papa... it's okay, fill me!
Mess me up!
Papa, I love you! I love you, Papa!
Your cock is filling me with juice...
I'm full of you... Papa...
Good morning!
Looks like you made up after all!
How can they sleep like that?!
It's so shameful!
Does it feel good?
How can I say that!
Come on, Airi! Airi?
I'm hearing Marina's voice...
Come on, wake up, Airi!
My head kinda hurts... And my hip's cold...
What's this?
It hurts! My head hurts! It's like someone's hitting it!
Airi, you drank booze?
I only had juice!
What are you saying? This is a cocktail!
You get drunk just from smelling booze, and you drank so much...
I bet you're hungover!
Booze? But I... Ouch!
I can't remember anything!
You got so drunk you blacked out?
It feels so embarrassing when I try to remember...
Ah, good morning!
Airi, you're cute as ever! I love you.
Don't say weird stuff from morning, stupid!
Come on, Dad!
Eh? Marina?
Explain what exactly transpired here yesterday!