I'm home, Dad!
Oh, welcome home Haruka.
W-Welcome back.
Natsume, were you being scolded by Dad again? Putting on such face...
N-No, it's not that-!
I-It's nothing.
Onee-chan, welcome back!
I'm home!
Jeez, I sure am hungry!
Yeah, I'll make something now. It shouldn't take long.
Okay!
Then I'm going to get changed.
Hey, where's Fuyu?
She's caught a cold and is resting at the moment.
Oh, I see.
Then I'll see how she's doing before I change.
presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
Original Video Animation
~Volume 2~
The Big Breasted, The Natural Airhead, The Vulgar and The Jealous
Oni Chichi
Fuyu?
Huh? Oh, Onee-chan, welcome home...
How are you feeling?
I'll come back later, okay?
Sure...
Natsume sure hasn't changed, she still dislikes Dad.
I-I'm sorry!
T-That was surprising, since he was naked!
And he was so big down there...
does that mean that he had an erection?
It also looked as if it was wet.
T-That was scary!
Jeez, y-you could have at least locked the door!
That was scary!
I don't mind if they found out, though.
Don't be ridiculous!
If they were to find out, you'd be the one in trouble!
I won't let you touch the others.
Hm? Are you commanding me?
You think you're allowed to say that to me?
I-I'm sorry!
Oh! See, you can be an obedient girl! Strict discipline is important!
W-Wait I'm-!
For you to release this much inside your daughters mouth...
This cock is...
T-This is dangerous!
You're in the Kendo Club, right?
This is just training.
Are you stupid?
This isn't-!
You pervert!
Assaulting your daughter with a face like that...
What kind of monster are you?
You're this wet, so you're a pervert as well!
It's so deep-! No! Don't thrust it in so deep!
Your cock is rubbing against me!
My pussy, it's being rubbed by Dad!
Why is my body so hot when I hate this?
Y-You jerk, what's the hold up? Let it out!
Onee-chan is waiting!
Here...
If I do this, you can't hold back, can you?
You can thrust harder, so hurry up and cum!
W-Wait, w-why did you stop?
Hey, aren't you nearly there? I said we need to hurry!
Yes, but finishing like this is a bit...
No-! W-What are you doing?
Don't you remember me holding you like this when you were younger?
And now you swallow Dad's cock like this.
You sure have grown.
What are you talking about?
You took my virginity and do me whenever you want.
What kind of father has sex with his daughter like this? Don't be stupid!
Let it out already! Otherwise, Onee-chan will...!
You just want it, don't you? Jeez.
It's poking me so deep again!
No-!
No, I'll cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Na-Natsume, that hurts. Natsume?
N-No! T-This isn't happening!
Jeez, you mustn't wet yourself at your age!
I-It's your fault, you-!
U-Um, Dad...
I'm sorry about before.
It was so sudden, and...
I don't mind, since you're my daughter.
Or do you want to see it again?
W-What are you saying?
Oh, I-I'm sorry. My hand slipped.
Um, Dad? I can do it on my own...
So, um, you don't need to help...
Okay? You're tired too, right?
We're family, there's no need to be embarrassed.
C'mon, show me your back.
Okay...
Hurry and get well Fuyu.
Okay, now lift your arm.
Looks like you've been sweating.
Good, you've grown up very nicely.
H-Huh? N-No...
What? Why Dad?
Hey, please stop, please stop...
No, you can't...
This is just discipline, you can't just leave your cellphone around!
Anyone could have seen it, but you're lucky it was Dad.
Y-You saw, Dad?
That's horrible.
Even if it's Dad, it's still mean.
Who's the horrible one?
You've been talking behind your sister's back.
I didn't know you thought such things behind that smile.
Gosh, Dad feels betrayed.
Eh? I thought I put a lock on, no way...
I wonder what everyone would think were they to see your true colors.
No, you're wrong, you're wrong!
I like my sisters.
I...
If you want things to stay the same between you lot,
it all depends on your attitude now.
You're a good girl, Fuyu.
No, please don't, Dad!
You're not wet, but bear with me, okay?
It hurts! Dad, it hurts a lot!
Please wait, I beg of you!
You'll feel better soon!
It hurts, it hurts...
I'm sorry, Dad, I'm sorry!
Dad...
No please, no more, Dad...
No, Dad! I said I'm sorry!
No! Not there, it hurts dad, not there! That's my butt!
Dad... Please...
This is discipline, bear with it.
No, no more...
It's going in, Dad's cock is going into my pussy...
Why? I-I'm your daughter...
Why is Dad's penis- No!
Dad, you're being too rough...
No Dad, no!
No Dad, not inside, please!
No, Dad's stuff is filling Fuyu up...
Why, Dad?
Because I have to discipline you for-
You've got to be kidding! I told you not to touch the others, you bastard!
You too! Why did you let him do such thing?!
Geez! You're always-!
You...! You hit me as hard as you could!
Hmph!
Maybe the pain will wake you up!
O-Onee-chan, I'm sorry... It's my fault... um...
Enough with that abject attitude!
Try to change it a bit, will you?!
Hmph!
W-What's this? What's going on?!
You've got to be kidding, right?
Dad and Fuyu were... and Natsume, why was she so...
Does that mean Fuyu was having sex with Dad?
Then Natsume got angry and...
Oh, it's you Haruka, I was wondering who it was.
Where have you been?
Hm? I just came to have a drink.
You're lying! Dad, what were you doing in Fuyu's room?!
W-We're family!
What are you thinking?!
That was...
discipline.
W-What are you talking about?
Discipline?
Is raping your daughter discipline?
Dad! You've gone crazy! What happened to you?
Oh I get it, you also want my discipline!
Then just say so.
W-W-What's this?!
Dad, W-Why... Why are you taking that out?! Hey!
Why? You know why.
Please stop it, Dad.
What's happened to you? Seriously!
I know that you may feel lonely since Mom died,
but doing it with your daughter is-!
Oh really?
Then I guess I'll have to settle with doing Fuyu while imagining your mother.
Wha-! Dad! I told you to stop it!
It can't be helped since you, the oldest daughter, doesn't want it, right?
No way-!
Fine then, I get it, I get it! Just don't touch Fuyu or the others again!
I'll take their place!
Only if you satisfy me.
I-Is this alright?
Whoa, it's so hard-!
I didn't know that cocks got this hot...
Haruka, can you lick it now?
Huh? S-Sure.
No, something is coming out... What is this? It's bitter...
Put it in your mouth.
No, this shape, this is perverted!
I wonder if Dad is about to cum...?
Dad, are you going to cum?
I can't breathe-!
What's this? I didn't know semen was this yucky and sticky...
Haruka, clean me up.
Dad? Why? You're getting large again.
It's because it feels good, as expected from the eldest daughter.
I can't be pleased when you praise me for something like that!
Oh really?
It makes Dad happy when you please me by doing such things.
What are you saying? Quit it...
You're getting embarrassed?
You secretly wanted this, didn't you Haruka?
Dad!
Dad, are we really going to do this?
You want Dad's cock, don't you Haruka?
Of course I don't! Doing such immoral things...
Well, if you don't want it, then I'll-
Fine! I get it! I get it, okay?
Oh! So you want it?
Yes, I want your cock, Dad.
However, this is my first time, so please don't make it too painful.
I know darling, it will only hurt for a moment.
So, show me yourself.
This is embarrassing, Dad!
Looks like you're quite wet!
Did sucking me off arouse you?
That's, that's not true! No way...
You're dripping fluid. See? This is going to enter you.
It's coming in! Dad's cock is entering my pussy!
It's tight...
No! It's coming right in!
N-No! It hurts! It hurts, Dad! It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts so much!
No Dad, take it out! Please, Dad, take it out!
Sure, I'll take it out soon.
It hurts, no, it hurts! I can't bear something like this!
No! Pull it out! Pull it out!
If you don't relax yourself, you won't feel good!
It hurts! Dad, it really hurts! Please stop it!
If you can't bear it, maybe I'll have to get Natsume too.
You can't do that either!
If you say I can't do this, then I can't do that.
Then Dad won't be able to hold back.
Seems like the pain is fading, isn't this great?
Now you can feel good.
Something like that....
No... My body is getting hot...
Do you wanna see our child? Huh?
N-No! No, you can't Dad!
What are you thinking?! We can't do that!
We just can't! No-!
No! Dad please, really, you can't!
You can put your cock inside me, but you can't do that-!
Dad! Dad you're not listening!
Don't! No-!
Dad, you can't! Please don't Dad! Dad!
No, no! No way...
Your semen is coming out inside of me...
No... So much, no way...
I'll get pregnant... with Dad's baby...
A-Akira? Umm... This isn't-
Do you want some apple? You must be tired...
Y-Yeah...
Tsk! She got ahead.
Jeez, I bet that Dad's reading the newspaper in the toilet!
I might wet myself!
Oh? Come to think of it, Natsume also went to the toilet.
Eh?
You jerk, you ended up doing all of them.
You pervert, scum!
H-Hey, Natsume!
Hmph! If you keep going like this, they'll...
It's in-!
I won't let you touch the others!
Amazing-!
If I do this, then you won't be as horny, so-!
What are you say-
Shut it old man, just keep moving your hips.
Natsume! You're in there, aren't you?
What are you doing so early in the morning?
Dad! You're inside there, aren't you?
Hey! If you keep doing such things, I don't know what will happen!
Huh? Dad, didn't you say you wouldn't touch the others?
I don't really mind...
Dad...
Hey Natsume! You should hear yourself moan-!
Natsume! What will happen to you?
H-Hey Akira! Don't do that!
No! Lemme go! I'm gonna...!
Dad's cock is rubbing against my insides!
It's good, it feels so good!
Hey! C'mon, let it out!
Give me your semen!
As well as everyone else's share!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!