www.SubDESU-H.net
No...
My pussy feels funny...
My virgin pussy's about to be penetrated...
I can tightly feel your dick all the way inside.
Whenever you drill it in like that my insides twitch.
It's my first time... Yet, it feels good.
Oh no.
Even though it's my first time, I am going to cum!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Now, I leave it up to you.
Okay, mister.
Airi, are you still not done yet?
I'm going to be late!
Silly Airi.
I already told you to hurry up.
But I'm sleepy.
I stayed up late last night.
Oh, Dad.
Good morning.
Good morning, you two are early.
Yes, Airi has morning practice.
You reek of sweat!
Airi!
Onee-chan, we'll be late.
Airi, I understand you're in a rush,
but you need to greet Dad properly.
See ya 'round, I'm going.
Airi's such a...
I'm sorry Dad.
Well, just be careful okay?
Sub
DESU
H
Sub
DESU
H
Oni
Chichi
I'm also going then.
Part
Aw jeez, that's just irritating.
Why was he even there?
I just want him to disappear.
He just stinks.
Airi, don't say things like that about Dad.
It's been almost a year already.
He's not our real Dad,
he's just someone that Mom married.
That's exactly why you should...
There's only one Papa for me!
And he's not the one!
Even so, you really have to...
No, I won't ever treat that dog like our father.
Dog you say?
Besides, I'm sure he's sexually interested in us.
That scum.
What are you saying, Airi?
You know, when I bought a new set of clothes,
he just ogled me.
Staring all the time around my waist.
You're just saying what you want to think.
It's all just in your head, you know.
Even you Onee-chan,
you also constantly hide your used clothes and underwear from him.
Of course I do.
Because well...it's embarrassing for them to be seen.
Embarrassing because he's not  our father, right?
Jeez, now you're quibbling.
I'm not.
Oh, it's the arrival of our schools princess.
Sana, you're recording even here?
That's great.
Okay, show me more of that bored face of yours!
It's a film in the making, so this is important!
Something that we can show at the school festival, our Airi-tan!
Jeez, I already told you to stop with these weird recording sessions.
Like that other time.
Sana, don't!
Stop!
Okay, Airi-tan is getting even closer.
Good, just keep that pose.
Stop it Sana, I'm only wearing...
It's okay, it's okay, don't worry.
How about we start by taking your bra off first?
What are you doing Sana?
Stop that, you're acting like an old pervert!
Airi, you look cute.
Your body is also gorgeous.
We need to properly show you off as the voluptuous girl.
What is she squealing for?
She just acts like a cheeky little brat.
But damn, she's really cute.
Hey, stop that already.
It's okay.
You never know when a big scoop with show up.
I think I would really die if someone saw this.
What are you saying?
I've been recording these to capture how cute you are.
All the data get deleted,
and you just keep on confiscating the discs.
Of course I would.
I can't just leave them lying around.
They're definitely not for show.
Akitsuki-sensei, I've finished filing the report.
Okay, I understand.
I'll look into it.
Just continue as always.
Got it.
Research for new medicine, huh?
Quite different from what I did last time.
Though this one is a potent sleeping drug.
There aren't many sample tests for it however.
Oh well, the number is just about to get higher anyway.
Nambu-kun, something came up so I'll be taking off early.
H-Hello Airi.
Creep.
Jeez, I already told him not to talk to me here.
I don't care about his position here as a lecturer.
This is the worst.
He's a stinky nuisance and a creep!
Like he hasn't even used a deodorant his entire life.
Oh yeah, so he's your stepfather...
What, he seems fine.
And here I thought he's some terribly guy.
He seems to be a lot better than my old man.
I mean, even though this might not mean much,
I think his status as a researcher makes him strangely attractive.
Then you can have him.
Take him home with you.
Really, can I?
Airi...
I'm home!
Onee-chan, you know I...
Oh, it's you.
Welcome home.
Hello mister.
You're, Kuronaka-san.
Sana will be staying here tonight.
Marina and your mom are both going to be out tonight.
Really? I knew mom would be out, but...
Onee-chan too?
Then I guess it's just us tonight.
Why don't the three of us go out for dinner?
Shut up, don't talk!
You stink.
Sana, let's take a shower then get something to eat.
Airi!
Though...
I can't really stop collecting these "materials".
Can't get into the bathroom while she's in there anyway.
Hey, that's..!
S-Sana, stop that, it's embarrassing!
These are private videos,
so it wouldn't hurt to make them sexy, right?
Hey, what in the world is this?
Jeez, speaking like that with her rude mouth.
Wait, huh?
I finished quickly because Sana is here.
This is my room!
What are you taking those out for?
Pervert!
I already thought something weird was going on,
but here you are in my room.
You thief!
Give them back!
I see.
This is not something a father would do!
I'm going to tell mom about this!
You're always calling me a dog or something else.
Treating me like a father only when it's convenient for you, huh.
Airi, so you can act cute like this.
Shut up, just stop it!
I don't want it to be seen by the likes of you!
Besides, it’s not yours, right?
It's hers.
Wha... S-Sana?
Why?
Wait a minute...
Airi.
S-Sana, what are you doing?
This is not what you think.
It's not his fault.
I asked him to let me do this.
Sana, no way...
You scum!
Pedophile!
Let Sana go right now you trash!
You're being really noisy.
That's...
What?
What's happening?
My body just...
No...
So it seems to have different effects on everyone.
Oh no.
My body feels hot.
It feels all tingly down there.
I can't stop it.
What's happening to my body?
No...!
So you're still able to move.
I think I may have to re-evaluate its potency.
Stop forcing yourself, Airi.
I'm going to make it all easy for you.
As your father.
Damn.
Don't come near, you pervert!
Good girls shouldn't swear like that, Airi.
No!
No, stop!
You make fun of me all the time.
No, stop this!
No, don't show me that dirty thing!
That's terrible of you.
You know, I'm about to take real good care of you.
I don't want that!
I definitely don’t!
You still don't understand the position you're in?
Stop messing around!
Sana, save me.
I'm sorry.
I asked mister if I could record your first time.
Airi, it only hurts at first.
So please show me that cute face of yours.
S-Sana!
Stop, please.
I just need to apologize, right?
I'm sorry, it was my fault.
I'm apologizing already so please let me go!
Airi, it's okay.
His dick is huge, so it'll feel good.
No, this is not something a father would do!
You say that, but your pussy is already dripping wet.
How cute!
Airi, your virginity is about to be taken!
His dick is entering you now.
No, no, stop!
It hurts.
Stop!
Airi, you've become a woman with his cock.
You're the same as me now.
It hurts, it hurts!
Stop moving!
Please.
It hurts, it hurts!
It's being opened wide.
No, this hurts...
Pull it out.
Please, forgive me already.
Please, Dad!
I'm sorry!
Now you call me Dad?
You cheeky little brat!
You're a beast!
Pull this gross thing out!
That's right, just keep that vigor up,
and give birth to my child, Airi.
No way, I don't want that!
Are you serious?!
Don't!
Wait!
Oh, Airi, it's your first time and you get to be cummed inside.
Your womb is going to be filled soon.
No!
You can't!
You definitely can't!
Hey!
I've already apologized!
Sorry for being naughty!
Sorry for being a brat!
Please, hey...
I said I'm sorry.
You know I can't just forgive you that easily.
No, no, no!
No, I really don't want this.
So please, stop already!
My insides are...
being filled with cum. Lots of it is coming out.
Guess she's gone already, huh.
Airi, what's wrong?
No sleep last night?
He just kept going until morning.
Like this...?
Be gentler with it, Airi.
This stinky thing.
He's making me suck it...
Stop...
Oh no, I don't want this and yet,
my body is getting aroused.
I don't want this anymore.
Dad, please stop.
You said you weren't going to call me Dad, right?
Shut up.
You're just a....!
Oh no, if you keep hitting deep inside like that again I'll...
My womb will get filled again!
No, stop this!
It feels tight.
It won't fit inside anymore.
I don't want this.
No, you can’t cum inside me.
Oh no...
Why is my body feeling pleasure from this?
Why is my body feeling excited from being done like this?
I can't take this anymore.
I'm about to...
Why are you...
You have my Mom already.
It's you and Marina's fault.
Both of you are so cute.
What’s that?
You did it with Onee-chan too?
Not yet, I'm afraid.
But it's up to you Airi.
No way...
Onee-chan mustn't...
Stop!
Airi.
Hmph, you traitor.
B-But I really wanted to see your cute face.
What are you saying? Jeez.
I hate you now.
Hmph.
Jeez.
Hey, why did you bring me here?
Classes are going to start soon!
I wanted you to show me your cute face like yesterday.
Stop joking around!
If someone finds us here...
Is something wrong with that?
I'm just an instructor here.
I can always find a new job.
Or maybe you want to scream and let everyone see just how perverted you really are?
Stop, we can’t do this!
I'll make you feel good soon.
This thing again...
It looks like the effect seems to get stronger the more I use it.
No, that's...
Stop, we can’t do this here!
Did you already come?
You're feeling really aroused, aren't you?
No way! I'd never get aroused with you!
Your dick just can't make me...
This pervert's dick,
it's making my pussy feel good.
This isn't me.
I can't let this guy's dick arouse me.
Hey, this spot is scary.
You'll fall if you don't hold on tight.
There, you're squeezing me better now.
No...
I'm scared, and yet whenever he drives in deep...
My pussy just...
Oh no...
I'm getting really wet as he penetrates me.
You've had enough already.
Hey, please...
Stop it...
No, it's getting intense.
I'm going to fall.
Hey!
You're going to cum inside me again?
No!
No, don't...!
No, don’t look...
Stop.
I have to punish you whenever you mess up.
Please forget that already.
Just get on with my punishment.
If Onee-chan ever saw us like this...
She's probably studying right now.
She's a hard-working girl.
Onee-chan told me that she's started dating someone recently.
Maybe she's on the phone with him right now.
What, is that true?
Like the other night.
She was invited by her boyfriend to spend the night.
What's with that?
You can't lay your hands on Onee-chan, you know?
This stinky dick,
should only be satisfied by my pussy.
I just wouldn't be able to feel as good if you didn't.
Marina...
Your dick is inside me at the moment.
Not in Onee-chan's.
This perverted dick is actually making me horny.
Oh no, he's about to cum.
He's about to pour his stinky and sticky cum inside me.
You want to cum already, right?
You want to release the cum that is stored up in your stiff dick, right?
Hurry, let it out.
Fill me with that stinky cum of yours.
Cum inside me!
My womb is getting filled with your seed.
Marina, I heard you got a boyfriend.
Why don't you introduce him to me sometime.
D-Dad, why are you suddenly asking?
I really don't have...
Oh, it's time already.
I'll be going!
If you can get it this big,
why don't you just do it with Mom?
If she knew that I was licking your stinky dick...
You're about to cum, right?
The school's festival is just around the corner!
Speaking of which, I heard that band's going to do a live concert.
Oh, Airi-chan!
I definitely want to see that!
Kuronaka showed us their uniform.
That was great.
For real?
Its exposure level is over the top!
Really?
Now I'm really looking forward to it.
See? I'm pretty popular, right?
Yeah, and as I think about them I...
You're making me do this and you're still feeling jealous?
Guys are so simple.
And when I do this...
Feeling good?
Want to insert it into my slutty pussy now?
You can't resist it anymore, right?
Hey, do you want me to comfort this dick?
It's in!
Your perverted dick is hitting my womb!
Give me more than what you would give Mom!
It feels a lot better inside me!
Yeah.
I want you to be the only one that makes me feel good.
Make me horny forever and ever!
Your dick is completely filling me inside.
I want this dick to be specially fit for me!
It'd be a waste on Onee-chan and Mom!
Here.
Want to cum inside?
You want to fill me with your sticky cum, right?
Give me all of it.
Give it to no one but me!
www.SubDESU-H.net