There's that one...
Hey!
You over there!
Me?
De-Demon Lord?!
What are you doing here...?
That's not even important!
Starting now... you're going to give me your cum!
Hm? Wh-what did you just...?
Li-like I said, you can use my body however you like,
so give me your cum!
What...!
Why is the Demon King... doing something like this for me...
Sh-shut up!
Just hurry up and give me your cum already!
I-if you squeeze me that tightly...!
Yo-your dick is hitting the best spot inside me...
It's fucking my pussy so hard...
So good...
So good... it feels so good...!
Your di-dick is so amazing...
You bastard...
Do you think that something like this will make me...
Make me...
It's squeezing me...
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Cu-cumming... I'm going to cum!
Go deeper... deeper...
Cumming, cumming...!
Your tongue makes me feel like I'm going to melt.
Hold on now, are you sure you're okay with this?
There's a reason why I want your cum.
I hope for your co-operation.
Can't get enough of this!
Come on now, suck harder!
His dick is pulsing, and getting hotter.
How filthy.
I can't believe that such a hot maid is begging for my cum.
That's right, this is all for the sake of cum.
I can't let the Demon Lord do something
so embarrassing by herself.
Not bad.
Come on now, take all of it in.
There you go, that's the way.
It's painful...
But it feels good...
My pussy is already so wet...
Very nice...
This guy... just hurry up and cum already!
Give my body the cum... the cum it wants...
Th-that's nice...
U-um... how does it feel?
Do my tits feel good?
Yeah, they're the bomb.
Who would have thought that a hero
would be begging for my cum.
Th-this is...
There's a reason why I'm doing this...
I-I just need someone's cum...
That's what you're saying, but the truth is you're feeling it, right?
Your nipples look like they're going to burst.
Do-don't say that...
Th-this wasn't what was supposed to happen...
I...
If you grope me that tightly, I...
Nice, very nice...!
No...!
I-I can feel it...!
So roughly...
Nice, very nice...
I'll squirt my cum all over these filthy tits of yours.
Thank you so much...
C-cum...! Shoot loads of your cum for me!
Lots of it!
You're going to cum with me!
G-got it...
I will, I will, I'm going to cum!
Cu-cu-cumming, cumming...!
I can't anymore...
I'm going to cum...!
Just a bit more...
And like this, we continue to gather cum together,
but we have a reason as to why we're doing this.
We've been surrounded.
You're right.
God damn.
Are we gonna do this?
Of course.
Eat lightning!
Take this!
That took some time.
I did it!
But, if we were able to use our full power, there's no way
we would have struggled with monsters of this class.
You're right, if only someone didn't mess up trying out
some new magic, causing our power to get sealed...
So-sorry...
It's all my fault...
Even then, how dumb is it that we have to
get cum in order to get back our powers...
B-but, I've come to like begging for cum lately...
Are you retarded?
Demon Lord!
Wh-what do we do!?
We're surrounded.
Freaking annoying little...
Wh-what...
Our magic was used up from the last battle...
Wh-what...!
Which means...
St-stop, no...!
D-damn you, that spot...
Don't touch it you freaking...
It hurts...
This is bad, stop...!
Wa-wait, you freaking tentacle...
That spot is...
S-stop...
God damn it, stop already...
De-Demon Lord...
I-I'm so sorry...
Even with me by your side...
Something like this happened...
Don't do it so strongly, st-stop it...
No...!
De-Demon Lord...
It's no use... I don't have any strength to even resist...
A-at this rate...
I-I'll break if this many tentacles rape me...
Don't be so rough...
N-no...
St-stop it...!
I can't believe I'm getting turned on by this...
N-no, don't touch that spot...
You're kidding!
Don't tease that spot!
You can't!
It's going inside...
My asshole and pussy are both getting stirred!
No...
You freaking lowly tentacles, how dare you...
This is... don't get carried away!
Something like this won't make me...
There's no way this would make me feel good...
St-stop it...!
It's going in and out of my pussy and asshole...
St-stop already...!
If this keeps going, I...
No...!
A-amazing...!
It's cumming! It's cumming inside me!
I-I'm at my limit...
These tentacles, these cocks are going
to pump cum into my pussy and ass...!
W-we got fucked...
I-I'm so sorry...
B-but at least we got more sperm again...
Damn you! Just watch!
I definitely won't lose next time!
This freaking curse, I'll break it once and for all!
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч