Honjou Rumiko, an English professor teaching at
the nearby first-class university, Seiei University,
was molested on the train
on her way to work one day.
She desperately tries to resist,
but guys calling themselves member
of the Yuuzaki Group showed up,
and she becomes their play thing.
She is forced to take whatever they do to her.
They take her to their place and rape her,
in addition to taking pictures of her.
Blackmailed with the threat
of spreading those pictures,
Rumiko even broke up with her fiance.
But that was simply the start of her tragedy.
Her days filled with nothing but despair, things
only get worse when they involve her workplace...
Onna Kyoushi Nijuusan-sai
This really does feel like a dream though.
Who would have thought that Prof.
Honjou would be giving me a blowjob.
I would fantasize about this whenever
I was fucking other woman.
Isn't she just as I said, Tsunekawa?
Yeah... I'm sorry I doubted you.
Come on now, do a better job sucking his dick.
Be honored that he offered
so much for your body.
What?! I-I can't... You didn't tell me...
Huh?! What did you say?
I-I can't do it...
You fucking...
Stop fucking around.
What do you think we
trained you for all this time?!
There there now, Ken.
You can't scare her like that.
Tsk.
Then you have to say this to him.
I can't...
Come on, say it already.
Thank you so much for buying my body...
Squirt your milk...
all over my tits...
Very well...
Then I'll give you plenty of my stuff.
Her tits are so soft that they might even melt.
Now this is something...
I might burst already...
Thank you so much...
Alright then Tsune, next up is doing it on the bed.
Oh, I suppose you're right.
Um...
Is Prof. Honjou
still not coming yet?
How strange...
She said that she would be waiting here.
What a nice body this bitch has...
That's right!
Eh...
I'll give you a lesson before Prof. Honjou comes.
Th-that's... I'll pass...
What's your cup size?
I can't tell you something like that...
Here's some advice. If you're going to act
you have to abandon all sense of shame.
That's where your acting fell short before.
No...
Look, you're so tight from being
nervous and are trying to run away.
That's your downfall.
What... Are you saying it's
part of your lesson then?
Yes.
For example, you're running away
in this scene where two lovers are going to fuck.
It tickles...
That's no good.
You have to convince yourself
you like the other person.
Alright now, put your arms behind your back.
Okay...
She's completely fooled right now.
Yo-you can't...
It's just to create the atmosphere...
Um, what was your name again?
E-Eri... Kazato Eri...
This feeling again...
Th-that's enough...
You're just no good...
I-I... Please...
Please stop it...!
No...!
No...
Stop it please...
Who in their right mind would stop
when such a nice body is
right in front of their eyes...
What a happy life you must live if
you still don't realize what this is.
Wh-what does that mean...
I'm not a director or anything.
I'm Rumiko's fuck buddy.
Oh, here she's called Prof. Honjou I guess.
Now then...
preparations are over.
The door is locked, so all that's left is...
What, you don't have to be that scared.
I'm just going to teach you what it
means to be happy to be a woman.
Your body is betraying you
even with you trying to hold it back, Missy.
N-no...
N-no... I don't want it and yet...
I don't want it...
Here... take a look.
This is all from your pussy.
Look how sticky it is.
N-no... this...
Why is my body...
No...! Anything but that!
Looks like someone's pretty wet.
It might hurt a bit,
but it'll feel good soon enough.
There's no where for you to run.
No...
Professor...
Almost there...
Are you ready, Missy?
Alright, open up to page 48 of the textbook...
Ishikawa.
Okay.
Heather Whitestone was elected
to be the first deaf Miss America,
at the 68th Miss America Beauty Contest.
She's 21 year old student from Dothan, Alabama.
She lost her hearing at the age of 1 year and a half
after suffering a bad ear infection.
Now, she can only hear in her left ear.
She...
Will you actually tell me where Eri is?
It took a lot of time and
money to find that girl, so...
What do you want from me...
Professor, this right here
is a high-end product made in Germany.
Putting it on that spot makes
it overflow with juices.
N-no...!
Y-you can't...!
Oh, are you starting to feel it already?
But it must be lonely with just that.
This right here can be operated remotely...
...State University.
She uses a hearing aid and knows sign language.
Although she is hearing impaired,
She has...
It's inside me...
Whitestone needed 6 years of
speech training to learn how to say her last name.
Professor?
Where do I have to read up to?
I'm already at page 51...
Then next up is Aoki...
Okay.
Whitestone needed 6 years of speech training to...
I feel like I'm going to go crazy...
Something like that is inside
me while I'm teaching...
I-if only I could get it out...
N-no...!
This is going to make me cum...
Pl-please...
Don't do this to me...
My pussy is going crazy...!
Looks like the drug was too effective.
You're sweating so much.
We should wipe it off quickly.
Th-that's... I'll do it by myself.
Are you really going to do it by yourself?
Tsu-Tsunekawa...
Pl-please wipe my body for me...
It's so hot...
Please...
Then would you stick your ass out for me?
Yes...
This is no good.
You're sweating even in a spot like this.
Tsu-Tsunekawa...
Wh-what do I have to do now?
You're asking me what, Professor...?
Put it...
in already...!
Don't tease me.
I see.
Do you want my dick that much?
I do... I want it...
Please...
So good...
It's so good...!
I see...
Is it that good for you...
In that case...
N-no...
I'm cumming...!
How was it?
It felt good, right?
Here.
That's where that girl is right now.
I see... so she's not here anymore...
Yeah.
She stopped coming about a
week ago, and called in to quit.
That's all.
Okay...
I can't believe I want a man this bad...
Moreover...
I feel empty on days when nothing happens...
Finding Eri's whereabouts is just an excuse.
I've fallen as far as I can...
Yoiichi...
Ru-Rumi...
What happened?! You're all...
Leave me alone!
Go away...
I can't believe your the mistress of the Yakuza...
Of course you would be this pretty all of a sudden,
when you're taking in all
that dick every single day.
No! That's not it!
Listen to what I have to say!
Heh... Shut the fuck up!
I broke up with you like you wished.
You should be satisfied now.
I wasn't able to return home after
what happened with Yoiichi.
I am nothing but a shame to my strict parents.
I have no where to go anymore...
Besides there...
Professor, Professor... come join us.
This bitch right has an amazing pussy on her.
I'll give your asshole some love.
I should be at the bottom of the pit of despair.
And yet I feel a sense of happiness.
Those two will sell for really high.
We'll just leave them like that for today.
Eri...
I'm sorry...
At the very least, I'll be with you along the way.
Professor...
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Fogil
softsub: торрент иваниваныч