Professor Hayama, are you leaving already?
I'm not used to this kind of setting, so...
That's too bad. I wanted to talk to you more.
I mean, I wanted to talk to you about the student education policy.
There are a lot of students playing hooky these days, so...
I'm going to go now. I'll see you Monday.
I wonder if it's true that she doesn't like men?
HOT FOR TEACHER
Episode 1
What's happening? I didn't drink that much, but...
Is something wrong, Professor Hayama?
Vice Principal...
You should rest somewhere.
No... I'm going home. I'm fine.
What are you doing?
It's mouth to mouth.
And I'm giving you a heart massage.
I'm fine. Please get off of me.
What are you talking about? You shouldn't push yourself.
Plus you're dripping wet, and your nipples are hard.
Stop it. Please...
I can't do that. You're drenched in sweat.
Let me take your temperature.
No!
I'll call for help if you don't stop!
You've got it all wrong. I was taking care of you because you're so drunk.
Well, I must admit I went a bit far, but...
I'm not drunk! I didn't drink at all.
Have one before you leave...
Did you drug me?
Oh come on, you don't have any proof.
How do you plan to make up for this?
Of course, you're leaving the academy, right?
Now, now. There's no need to get so upset.
Can't you leave it as something that happened in a drunken stupor?
If you want, I'll more than make it up to you.
Do you honestly think you can talk your way out of this?
You don't deserve to be a teacher!
I'll apologize, but are you gonna insist on making a big deal out of it?
It's your own fault!
If you're not going to quit, I'll take this up with the Board of Education!
Are you sure you want to do that?
I'm very well connected to the Board of Education in this prefecture.
Then I'll tell the police!
I guess the drug didn't work so well.
I have to do something fast.
I won't forgive him. I won't...
W... what are you doing!?
We're engaged. Don't you think it's about time we...
You promised you'd wait until we were married.
Stop being so uptight. You're not a virgin, for God's sake!
I didn't think you were like that, Matsunaga!
It's over. I'm breaking off the engagement. Please leave!
What are you doing?
I've never been slapped, not even by my mother.
Stop... Please!
I hate men...
What's wrong, Katsutoshi?
Keiko ran away from home... she's at my house.
Keiko... Miss Fujimura, from second year?
I told her she can't stay with me because I live alone, and that wouldn't look good.
But she won't listen to me.
I thought maybe if you talked to her, she'd listen...
I'm glad you told me. Hold on.
Come to think of it, you two are a strange pair.
"A pair", as in the best student and the worst student?
I didn't mean it like that... but you two are a cute couple...
We're childhood friends.
He's Gondo. He hasn't been to class, but he's a third year, too.
W... wait, where are we? This isn't your house.
Get out.
What's going on?
I said get out!
Katsutoshi!
I would listen to what he says...
Huh?
Do you think you can get away with this?
I like professors with attitudes...
What are you doing?
I should have gone to class, since I had a professor with such a hot body!
Stop it!
You say that, but you're feeling it. Let me see...
Stop.
Hey, you're completely wet.
Help me... Katsutoshi.
Gondo... This isn't what you said. You said you were going to scare her.
Shut up! Keep taping!
But...
What, can't you hear me? I told you to keep taping!
I won't let you get away with this! How dare you do this to your teacher!
You're only students!
What a loud professor. I'm gonna have to shut you up.
You feel so good, Professor. Your lips feel so great!
Come on, you need to make more dirty noises.
I can't hold it anymore!
Hey, you're hogging all the fun.
I can't help it.
How am I supposed to hold myself back when she's got such a sexy body?
I know how you feel! I can't wait myself. My cock is so hard.
Don't worry. I saved her pussy for you, Vice Principal.
You should be ashamed of yourself, Vice Principal!
Professor Hayama... you won't be talking like that for long.
Well? Are you feeling it?
I'm going to break!
Wanna feel good?
I don't know. I feel like I'm going to go crazy.
You want to feel it more, right?
You want it, right?
Y... yes...
Then move that ass against my cock.
What a view, Professor Hayama...
I can't watch anymore.
You don't hate men. You're just a slut! Say it!
No!
Say you're a slut!
I... I'm a whore.
You're our sex slave, starting today! Swear on it!
I'm your sex slave...
No... I'm going to cum!
All right... I'm going to cum inside you.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
Did you take the video? It's our precious blackmail video.
I guess we'll get to fully enjoy her this weekend.
Katsu, I called you all last weekend. Where were you?
Katsu.
Good morning.
Good girl, she's not wearing any underwear like I told her to.
I can't teach like this...
Don't take it out, and don't you run.
It'll fall out if I relax my muscles, but if I squeeze too hard I'll feel it...
Professor, is something wrong?
N... no...
You don't look so well.
Thank you. I'm fine. Does anyone have any questions?
I do!
Gondo.
You're not wearing a bra today, right? Are you wearing any underwear?
What? Of course I am.
Are you sure? Then show us.
I can't do that!
I don't believe you. You look excited. You've got perky nipples.
If you're going to interrupt class, then leave!
Since when are you allowed to talk to me like that?
Well? How does the double vibrator feel?
That's not fair. It's in my pussy and my rear...
Professor. I can't read the beginning of page five. How do you pronounce this?
That's...
You don't know?
How are... you...
Fine... Thank you...
How ah... you...
I'm going to pee...
Max level.
What's going on?
Professor Hayama, please come to the Vice Principal's office.
Professor Hayama...
Please, not at school...
What are you saying? You peed in the classroom. You need to be punished.
If you keep doing that, I'll pee again...
Hold it. Hold it.
I can't!
I wonder what she's doing? She's been in there for a while.
Katsu?
This time the Vice Principal is hogging her.
I haven't cum yet. She came on her own. What a slut.
Let's do it again.
No, why don't we let him do it this time.
Huh? It's fine. I'm...
You say that, but you're hard. You're a virgin, right?
Keiko Fujimura always turns you down.
Come on Professor Hayama, make Katsutoshi feel good.
She's a fuck-loving slut now.
Thanks to our good instruction.
I can't wait anymore.
Then I'll fuck her in this hole.
It hurts!
You idiot! Don't let go!
Her ass is so tight, it's great.
What a great view. The three of us are connected.
Well, how is it?
I'm going to cum.
We're all together.
All right! Let's go, Professor Hayama!
I'm going to cum!
For the next week...
...Yumi became their sex toy at school, and in the basement of the factory...
...but I couldn't do anything about it.
Because they knew my secret...
I came to make you dinner.
Your father and mother have been gone for a while. Have they contacted you?
Don't you think Professor Hayama has been acting strange lately?
You know something, don't you?
Is it Gondo? You need to stop hanging out with him.
Shut up!
I knew it! What happened? Tell me.
Go home. You're annoying.
I'm not leaving until you tell me.
Are you that worried about her?
I look up to her.
I want to become a wonderful and passionate teacher like her.
I'll tell you...
Really?
If you let me fuck you.
See... You don't mean it when you say you want to help her.
That's not true!
Then do it to help Professor Hayama.
No!
Come to think of it... That was my first kiss.
Keiko...
You promise you'll tell me?
You're going to tell me, right?
Y... yeah...
Are you sure?
Don't make it hurt, okay?
Hurry... Please...
What's wrong?
I... What am I supposed to do?