I was so happy to finally be a teacher.
Silence, fool!
Thirty seconds or not, tardy is tardy!
My name is Morinaga Ayako.
But that place...
Not like that!
Sencei, I'm gonna...
Not yet.
What should I do?
I can't use being raped as an excuse
to skip work the next day.
If I don't go back to the prep school tomorrow,
will that be the end of my teaching career?
I know!
Let's go to school together every day.
That's right!
He promised me.
He promised we'd ride together every day.
And I'm a teacher.
I can't let something like this get me down.
Female Teacher
– Body Lecture –
Part 2
Good morning.
Sensei... sure is pretty today.
And she smells great, as usual.
Is something wrong?
N-No, it's nothing.
Oh.
Oh dear, why is he getting
hard at a time like this?
Every girl that walks past them is
judged purely on her sexual merit.
They even bring dirty magazines to school.
I wonder if Nitoh-kun is the same way.
Oh, that's right.
Sensei, I have something to ask you.
What?
About English, there's
something I still don't get.
I wonder if he also wants to
do something like before.
Like that..
Sensei?
Sensei, are you listening?
Yes, I'm listening.
So what part don't you understand?
I just told you that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, Nitoh-kun.
Yes?
It's a little awkward in the train,
so I'll teach you later.
That okay with you?
Yes, I don't mind.
I want to know more about him.
Sensei?
Um...
I've got it.
We have tomorrow off.
Why not come over to my place?
To your house?
Lecture Hall
Okay.
Misaki-chan, you've sure got a nice body.
Throwing it away? That's cold.
Don't you like that thing, Misaki-chani?
Boys!
What do you think you're doing,
bringing these things into the classroom!
They're just presents.
Nevertheless, don’t do it again!
I'm not sure about that.
Sayama-kun!
I'll obey if you go down on me. Right here.
What are you suggesting?
If you do it, I'll promise not to
disturb your lecture again.
Or would you prefer it the way
we did it last night instead?
I'd like that.
You really fucked her?
Guess so.
For real?
The boys treat her like that
because she's so naive.
She really pisses me off.
That boy in the train with her this
morning is a student here, huh.
English Department Lounge
Running out on a lecture?
What were you thinking?
But...
No excuse is good enough.
You're a teacher.
If a teacher doesn't teach,
then what does she do?
...to me.
You have no right to say
that sort of thing to me!
Talking back to me like that.
So not only are you
abandoning your students,
you also want to rebel against me?
When you did that...
You were having sex with one of the students.
You have no right to tell people
how to be a good teacher!
It seems like you misunderstand.
Having sex with a student is wrong?
Why?
That is also a part of our job.
"Devote your life to teaching, body and soul."
That isn't just an expression.
The kind of teachers I seek are the
ones who can teach students
with their bodies as well as their minds.
I've produced excellent
results by that method.
To someone like you, however, with no
experience and nothing to show for it,
perhaps my methods don’t apply.
Nitoh-kun.
Over here.
Ninagawa-san?
Wh-What?
Hold on, Ninagawa-san.
Stop it, please!
Wh-What are you gonna do?
Exhilarating, isn't it?
Let's have some fun.
Infirmary | Ebina Yukie
Good point.
But I think Morinaga-sensei
also has a good point.
No way!
How can that be a good way to teach?
Well, different teachers have
different methods.
I think you should go home for the day.
I'll take you home.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Do you masturbate every day?
You smell.
You get hard even at a time like this?
Have you no shame?
But, you know, I love this sort of thing.
Feels good, doesn't it?
But I won't let you cum so easily.
You wanna cum so bad?
Not yet.
It's time for me to feel good next.
Well? A girl is masturbating in front of you.
You wanna see, right?
Too bad.
Listen to the sounds instead.
Well? You can tell I’m wet, right?
Seems it's about time now.
Did you know?
The longer you hold out,
the better it feels when you cum.
I'll take care of everything for you.
So just sit back and relax.
Here we go.
Well? How does your first time feel?
He may not be enjoying it now...
But after this, I'll show him paradise.
And then he'll be my slave.
I'll make him forget all about that old bitch.
I hope you have a big cry,
Misaki-sensei.
This book...
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Nitoh-kun!
Move it.
Ninagawa-san, what are you doing?
Aw, busted.
I was only trying to show him a good time.
Are you okay, Nitoh-kun?
"Come to my house on Sunday," my ass.
Stop pretending you're in high school!
How... How did you know that?
I told you, didn't I?
Women like you piss me off.
But I'm okay now.
You guys can go be high schoolers
and cry in the bathroom together.
I have no interest in you anymore.
Just make sure to let him finish, okay?
I wonder if he'll show up after
what happened yesterday?
Coming!
Hi, good afternoon.
Hello. Come in!
My mom and dad are both
on vacation right now,
so you don't have to be so nervous.
That means we're alone?
I guess it does.
This conjunction means that something
does something to something, right?
That's what the textbook says,
but it can also mean "because."
Oh, really?
If you look it up in a dictionary,
you'll see it for yourself.
Nitoh-kun?
Y-Yes?
Wihat are you thinking about?
Um, nothing.
Should we take a little break?
Hey, Nitoh-kun, I checked over your grades,
and you'll need to work a little harder.
Yeah.
I promise you'll pass next year.
The only subject I can help
teach you is English,
but promise me you'll study
all the other subjects.
I will.
There's more if you want it.
Oh, thank you.
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
It was my fault.
It'll stain!
Sensei...
Hold still.
Nitoh-kun, you’re hard.
I mean, we're in your room.
And besides, that top...
You got this way because of me?
No need to be ashamed.
You're a boy.
It's only natural.
Sensei, what are you...
I don't mind.
Leave it to me.
Don't be ashamed.
But...
I know you went through
something horrible yesterday,
but I'm sure sex is
supposed to feel wonderful.
I know how he feels.
If my first time had been under different
circumstances, it would've felt great.
You too, Sensei.
You're so pretty.
Don't stare too long.
But...
Don't.
I'm going to cum.
I'll lick it clean.
This time, I want to take care of your body.
This is embarrassing.
It's not fair for me to feel all the pleasure.
Okay.
Sensei!
No!
Sensei. Sensei!
That hurts.
Sensei!
Sensei...
Nitoh-kun, that hurts.
I'm sorry.
I'm just too excited.
That's okay.
It's your first time. You should feel nervous.
I know. Let's make you less nervous.
There. Now you can lick it.
Yes.
Don't bite.
Be more gentle.
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
Sensei, where next?
Next is...
right here, Nitoh-kun.
That's right!
This is a woman's special place.
This is...
And this is the clitoris.
Sensei, I can't...
You want to go further, right?
Yes.
Touch it.
It's wet.
That means I'm ready.
Then...
I'm coming in.
Go slowly.
I'm moving.
That's fine!
Nitoh-kun, I'm almost there.
I can't hold back much longer!
Me either.
So let's cum together, inside of me!
How was it?
It felt wonderful.
It was wonderful for me too.
So this is what sex is supposed to be.
Hey, Sensei, I want to learn more from you.
So...
Oh well, you're so silly, Nitoh-kun.
One more time.
I'll give you a private lesson
next weekend as well.
In exchange, be sure to study your other
subjects during the rest of the week.
I will.
In this year's final exams,
Nitoh Takaya scored at the top
of his class in all subjects.
In particular,
his English scores were excellent.
He sure worked hard.
No, you were the one who worked hard.
Nagasawa-sensei,
what is our job as female teachers?
Teaching lessons, of course.
But even male teachers can do that.
A boy's first sexual experience...
plays a huge role in his emotional
and intellectual development.
It marks the point at which he is
transformed from a boy to a man.
Depending on what kind of experience it is,
the boy's future relationships
and grades will be different.
That is why being a boy's first sexual
partner is both an honor and a challenge.
If we don't take care of this, then who will?
I've been using sex to help guide
the boys in the right direction.
That is the sort of female
teacher I strive to be.
It's obvious to me what your
relationship with Nitoh Takaya is.
You have steered him in the right direction.
Take pride in yourself.
You will steer the boys of this prep
school in the right direction.
Misaki-chan.
What are you doing in this deserted place?
Sayama-kun...
Hey, Sayama-kun?
Wow!
You're amazing, Misaki-chan!
Don't touch it.
Why not?
If you put your hands down
here, I'm stopping.
Hey, don't talk to me like that.
But if you hold out nicely for me,
I'll give you even more pleasure.
I'm gonna cum.
You don't need to hold back anymore.
If you keep licking me like
that, I'll get hard again.
I'll pleasure you this time.
That's all for today.
Wh-What the hell?
I can't stop now!
Are you sure?
Didn't it feel good?
Much better than in the abandoned room?
Well, yeah.
If you want more, then do as I say.
If you score higher than
80% on the next quiz,
l-will-con-tin-ue.
Misaki-chan, what did you...
So things did turn out the way
Morinaga-sensei said.
And here I was all ready to comfort
her when she got upset again.
Oh, well.
Guess I'll grab a student.
Morinaga-sensei, I'll give it a try.
I will steer the students in the right direction.
What are you thinking about?
I'll continue giving you private lessons,
regardless of your test scores.
So don't worry.
Translation:
Voldemort
Snake
Edit:
Collectr
Timing:
v1touch
Typeset & Encode:
ShocWave
Quality Check:
Morpheus_Stiltzkin
Presented by:
Erobeat
http://www.erobeat.net
#erobeat @ irc.rizon.net