Again... It's not by accident.
You have beautiful hair.
Your ass is nice too, its perfect.
Please stop it.
What are you talking about Miss?
Stop feigning ignorance, you've
been molesting me.
Don't misconstrue everything,
even if I didn't want to touch
you when the train shifts.
I end up touching you anyways.
Its not my fault.
In any case, you're going to come
with me at the next train station.
What is it? Is it groping?
It's groping.
You guys sure are noisy.
I can't even read a magazine
(with all this noise).
Hey Kenji, what's wrong?
This woman is accusing
me of groping, brother.
What?
Lady, since you are accusing my younger brother
of groping, you have clear evidence right?
But, he really touched my body.
Where did he touch you and what
did he do exactly? Tell us clearly.
It's fine now (I no longer
accuse him).
It's not fine.
Let's make it clear. Lift up your
skirt and show us proof lady.
I'll check to see if your privates
were touched.
What are you doing?
What? We're looking for proof.
Brother, how is it?
There's nothing going on here.
It was a false accusation after all. Lady,
how are you going to apologize for this?
Everyone is tired from working
seriously everyday.
In a train when they are
almost able to relax
you make a fuss about groping, about being
touched, this leads to becoming even more tired.
You're causing an inconvenience
for the other customers, you!
No one is going to help you.
You're the one to blame for this.
No... please stop this.
What are you talking about?
You called my cute little
brother a groper?
You need to pay for
this of course.
No way.
– You have great tits.
– No.
These are your panties?
They sure are soft.
Too much covering is one thing,
this fluffy lace is nice.
Please stop it!
Nice smell, you're turning me on.
Please forgive me.
What's this? You sure
are dripping...
You're feeling it because
of my tit massage,
I'm good at massaging tits.
No, no.
What do you mean "No"?
An ass like this, those huge tits.
No matter how you look at it you
were the one tricking us into this.
There are types like this.
Please, please stop.
There's no need to be modest, we're
not finished with the lesson yet.
I'll get off at the next train station,
please forgive me. I won't tell anyone.
Did you say something, lady?
What should we do brother?
Let's have her play a little more, I just
started sticking my fingers in her pussy.
You're unfair brother, well then.
I'll have to stick it into her asshole.
No, I can't, please don't do that.
Such a pleasant opportunity and
you're saying "No, no" getting all wet.
Really.
She's soaked.
Stop it please.
Please someone, please.
Do you feel that good?
She might get hooked on this.
Real groping is like this!
Remember it well.
With this you'll never
talk big again.
Having fingers in your ass shouldn't
be easy on you, come on.
You sure like to attack assholes.
You sure are tight. Your pussy
is of the highest quality.
Please someone help me.
Female Teacher 23
years old (Part 1)
Have you come to, lady.
Please let me go home.
Stop joking.
The real stuff starts now now.
I'll cry for help.
Lady, we're a part of the Ryuzaki-gumi
(Yakuza/gang). You know what that means right.
This man is Mr. Kuroshima, in line with
that, he's famous as a roughneck.
Staying quiet is for
your own good.
Rumiko Honjo, 23 years old.
She's a teacher for Seigakuen
it seems.
What are you teaching there?
Answer me!
I teach English.
You call that thing "fuck" right?
At least I know that much.
Hey teacher.
Let me kiss you!
No never.
Open your mouth
properly, or else.
You sure are showing
off. Well then, I'll...
You're using expensive
perfume aren't you.
Were you going to go on a date?
Anyhow, these tits are amazing.
What are you eating all the time?
Educationally this isn't good.
There are guys you
teach aren't there?
They must struggle every night.
They wouldn't be able to
keep their minds off you.
This pink is pretty.
You're a waste being a teacher, you're
tight where you're supposed to be tight.
Are you doing some kind
of sports, Ms. Rumiko?
Is it swimming?
But THESE get in the
way don't they.
If it's Sumo, these are
Yokozuna level.
We don't mind you peaking
but drive carefully.
Yes, sir.
This is a sight to die for.
A picture first brother?
A picture in this embarrassing position?
Let's fuck her first, I can't hold it back
anymore. We let the lady show us her tools.
No!!!
These lips are beautiful.
You don't have to be afraid.
My brother is a technician.
Your clitoris is small and cute.
Mr. Ryoichi, I'm sorry.
Take it easy, we won't
fuck you just yet.
We'll let you suck us after
we've gotten you all wet.
This is no good.
Kenji, don't just stand there.
Sorry brother.
Please stop it. Please.
Hey, hey.
Teacher, you worry us by making
that type of face already.
We just started.
Your tits sure are sticking up. My
fingers will have holes in them.
They look lonely down there
they're convulsing.
Is this your first time with
something as big as this?
Does this hurt teacher?
No, it won't fit!
What's wrong? Do you
want it inside?
What is this, its hot and numbing.
It's about time for me to go
inside. Only half has gone in...
No, please make it short.
It went all the way in.
No, no.
Brother, let me have
some fun too.
You idiot, her mouth
is open isn't it?
Oh yeah, it is isn't
it, alright. Suck it!
It's not like you don't
know how right?
Use your tongue properly, no teeth.
Amazing, I feel dizzy.
This is horrible, but I can't think of anything.
I don't want to think of anything.
Have you both come?
Well then its my turn to squirt
and join you.
Brother, she's ready.
Is that right? I'm coming.
Wake up.
Open your eyes properly.
No.
Please stop. Please I beg you.
Please don't take pictures.
We have your address.
If you don't do as we say these photos will be
dispersed to your acquaintances, do as your told.
Rumi.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with you today?
It seems like your thinking of something
all this time. Is something bothering you?
No, not at all. I was just thinking.
Is it something you can't even
tell me, your boyfriend.
No, it's really nothing.
You're beautiful.
You're perfect.
It's as if you've been reborn.
Ryoichi...
please forgive me. The girl you once
knew... Rumiko is now gone...
What? Why?
I'm sorry, please break up
without saying anything.
Please.
What happened Rumi?
I'm no longer worthy
to go out with you.
No, I'll never leave you.
I'm sorry, farewell.
Farewell, Ryoichi.
I'll never give you up.
I'll never give up.
With this kind of timing the
lighting won't be in time.
Should we go over
this part again.
But we need to check
the pronunciation.
Yes, it would be bad to have
Romeo and Juliet sound strange.
It's no use. What can I do?
They're polluting me both
in mind and spirit.
You have to keep
it nice and clean.
Here you go.
You're going to put in more?
It looks like its saying
its not enough.
Don't break her.
Well then.
Even if I look like this
I like to stay clean.
I had to separate from
my boyfriend Ryoichi.
I was unworthy to
go out with him.
Teacher, its a guest.
Yes, who is it?
Eri is getting him.
Oh.
Something is still wrong.
One more time?
One more time!
Teacher?
This is the guest.
I had a hard time finding you.
A girl that age sure is
fine, nice and lively.
Please go. This is an important
practice for the English club.
I see. There are some nice girls.
There aren't many days left until we do this.
Don't say that.
It's a tragedy, a tragedy.
Translation: hanime.tv
Timing: hanime.tv
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч