My name is Nagasawa Misaki.
I graduated from university this spring,
and from today I'll be an English teacher
at the Toukoku Preparatory School.
Toukoku Preparatory School is the
largest preparatory school in Japan.
It has a huge campus in the suburbs of Tokyo,
and is famous for having even better
equipment that some universities.
To become a teacher there,
you have to go through many
difficult and competitive tests.
Despite the difficulties, I managed to pass.
Well, from today I’m a teacher!
Female Teacher
– Body Lecture –
Part 1
Oh, dear.
I had no idea the train was
so crowded at this time.
What?
Could this be...
a train molester?
Why you!
That hurt, man!
I'm sorry.
Did I interrupt something important?
N-Not at all.
This boy saved me.
I'm sorry!
I-It's nothing.
Whoa, what a pretty woman.
And what’s more...
she smells nice.
There's not much room on this train,
so I guess we'll have to stay
like this for a while, okay?
O-Okay!
Oh, crap.
Huh?
It's nothing.
Toukoku Preparatory School
English Department Lounge
This is the place.
Excuse me.
You're late!
I'm sorry.
Um...
What time do you think it is,
Nagasawa Misaki-san?
Look at the clock.
Oh, phew.
I'm exactly on time.
Look closer.
No way.
A measly thirty seconds?
Silence, fool!
Thirty seconds or not, tardy is tardy!
Yes, ma'am.
I apologize for the late introduction.
My name is Morinaga Ayako.
I'm also an English teacher.
The school told me to teach you
everything you need to know.
But I didn't expect that you'd
be late on your first day.
I apologize, ma'am.
You will have a position of power
over the students you teach.
Show a greater sense of responsibility!
Yes, ma'am.
Your voice is awfully quiet!
Do you expect to conduct
a lecture at that volume?
No.
I still can't hear you!
Morinaga-sensei, we can hear your
voice all the way down the hall.
Ebina-sensei...
And besides, if you yell at a young
teacher so harshly on her first day,
she'll quit right away.
It was my fault!
Never mind that.
I understand you banger over
your plans falling through.
Allow me to take her on a tour
of the campus instead.
Will that put a smile back on your face?
Fine. Do as you wish.
Toukoku Preparatory School
Thank you very much!
Um...
I'm Ebina Yukie.
You may have noticed she called
me "sensei" back there.
However, I'm not a teacher.
I work in the infirmary.
So you're a doctor?
Nothing that glamorous.
You really had bad luck today, huh.
No, it was my fault for being late.
But I wonder if Morinaga-sensei
has a bad sex life.
D-Don't say that!
She may wear glasses, but she's got
a really pretty face under them.
And her proportions are killer, too.
However, she's still single at 30.
If she even lifted a finger,
she could seduce lots of men.
S-Seduce?
What?
You shouldn't say something so vulgar.
Aw, I see no problem with it.
It's not like I'm saying it to her face.
Or are you uncomfortable talking about this?
Well, I...
That's really cute.
Hey, Nagasawa-sensei, wanna come
hang out in the infirmary?
S-Sure.
Infirmary | Ebina Yukie
This prep school is really impressive.
I wouldn't expect it to have an infirmary.
It gets pretty busy in here, too.
Oh, do the students injure
themselves that much?
Not just injuries...
Lots of other stuff goes on here.
"Lots of other stuff"?
Counseling and the like.
You're credentialed to do that as well?
I suppose so.
Many boys in this institution
are becoming men,
so I give lots of sex talks.
You don't need to act so surprised.
Boys always have that on their mind anyway.
Is that true?
You really don't know anything, do you?
Every girl that walks past them is
judged purely on her sexual merit.
They even bring dirty magazines to school.
And you know what they
do when they get home.
Say, do you know how many times a day
a boy thinks about sex, on average?
No.
Those are the types of students
you'll have to deal with.
You'd better do some research.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Am I wrong?
I thought so.
It’s a handicap to be inexperienced about
something your students know really well.
Well. Let me give you a little lesson.
I'll teach you many things.
Um, I have to leave!
Huh?
You should take a nice rest.
Yes. Stay just like that.
What am I...
You don't need to worry about anything.
Leave everything to me.
Leave what?
What a pretty body.
No!
Why not?
Doesn't it feel good?
But...
Didn't I tell you?
You need this to be a good teacher.
This feels great.
You really are pretty.
Please, don't look at me down there.
No way.
You're very sensitive, I see.
I'll make it feel even better.
Well? Does it feel good?
Yes. It feels great!
Then make me feel great too.
Th-This feels good!
Do me too.
You know what I mean, right?
Y-Yes! Right there!
Ebina-sensei! I'm gonna...
Misaki, don't call me Ebina-sensei!
Call me Yukie!
Yukie-san...
That makes me happy, Misaki.
I’m gonna...
Well? Was that study helpful?
I was wrong.
Why were you wrong?
There was no reason to resist.
Um, don't tell...
Of course I won't tell anyone.
I'm leaving.
See you later.
So you're a student here.
Yes. I'm Nitoh Sakaya.
Why were you in the infirmary?
Are you feeling ill?
Uh, no, it's not that.
Huh? Yeats?
Yeah. I've been reading it.
But there are still many parts
I don't understand.
I guess I need to study more.
When I was in college, I read that a lot.
I wanted to be able to read more
and understand it more.
So I studied English really hard,
Until my English was so good that I
could become an English teacher.
Is that so?
I guess the two of us are quite similar.
What a strange first day.
That felt really good.
Wh-What am I saying?
What I did back there was wrong.
I'd much rather do it with a man.
Nitoh-kun, huh.
Oh, no.
I mustn't think about a
student while I masturbate.
Nitoh-kun!
I couldn't sleep a wink.
I'm sorry!
Nitoh-kun.
Sensei.
Why are you on the train today?
Even on days when I don't have class,
I still go to the library to study.
Even though it's just a library at a prep
school, it has a lot of books in English.
Is something the matter, Sensei?
No, nothing.
I know!
Hey, can I ask you for a favor?
When I'm on this train,
I want you to guard me.
Guard you?
Yes. I don't want what happened
yesterday to happen again.
Is that okay?
Starting tomorrow, every day?
Yes.
Which means...
Every day, Sensei.
I'll get to feel this every day.
Not bad.
Nitoh-kun?
Yes, it's fine.
Let's go to school together every day.
I'm glad!
Well, time to start class.
I mustn't be timid.
Good morning!
She's really cute.
Awesome.
Are you freaking kidding me?
I'll be in charge of this class for the next year.
I'm Nagasawa Misaki.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
Sensei!
I have a question.
A question?
Very well.
What is it?
What are your measurements?
I won't answer that!
Okay. Then what about the
color of your underwear?
Hey, you!
Now, you mustn't get angry, Misaki-chan,
not at such an innocent question.
We're not kids anymore, after all.
Unless you’re still a virgin or something.
What are you...
Then when was your first time?
And where did you do the deed?
A hotel?
How many guys have you fucked so far?
Stop it.
Aw, don't be so reticent.
You're only one who can do something
about this throbbing thing in my pants.
You get it, right?
Please accept my overflowing libido.
It'll be really hard tonight if I can't fuck you.
This is exactly what Yukie was talking about.
Boys really are perverts.
Oh yeah, did you have sex last night?
How many times a week do you masturbate?
What's your favorite position?
G-Go back to your seats!
Just answer our questions, Sensei.
But I...
Just leave her alone already!
Stupid boys.
Won't you ever grow out of
your pre-adolescent ways?
Are you fucking crazy?
Bitch...
Just drop it.
This is getting boring.
Let's go somewhere to party.
Hey, you boys aren't supposed to...
Sensei, I'm Sayama.
See ya later, Misaki-chan.
Thanks for that, um...
Kurisu.
Inogawa Kurisu.
Thank you, Inogawa-san.
You don't need to thank me.
They were just pissing me off.
If you're a teacher,
use your authority and stop them from
saying things like that in the first place!
Or is that the way you lure men to you?
In that case, I'm sorry I got in the way.
It's not...
Listen, I hate stupid guys like
that just as much as you do,
but women like you really piss me off, too.
It's really tough being a prep school teacher.
My first day was a total flop.
I wonder if I'll be able to keep this up.
Nagcisawa-sensei!
Sorry about that back there.
You're just so cute I got a little carried away.
A-Ah, don't say that.
I really am sorry.
It's okay now.
You've apologized.
Just be sure to be serious in
class for the rest of the term.
Ah yeah, about that.
I missed the first day, right?
And I'm worried I'm falling behind.
So I was wanting you to
teach me today's lesson.
That's why I’m here.
Oh, I see.
Sensei, I'm begging you.
Can you make some time for me?
Aw, I thought he was scary at first,
but he's actually pretty sweet.
That's fine.
For real?
Yeah, but this hallway...
I know a great place!
This room is old, and no one ever uses it.
I'm sure no one would mind if we used it.
What?
What's wrong, Sayama-kun?
It's time to study.
No! Stop it!
Didn't I tell you?
This room isn't used.
No one will come, even if you scream.
No.
So stay quiet and behave!
No!
Well, what'cha gonna do?
No! Stop it!
It's your fault,
because you flaunted yourself before a
bunch of boys who're horny all the time.
Did you really think you'd get away with it?
It's too late for that now.
If you wanna blame someone, then blame
ourself for having such a hot bod.
You're so soft to the touch!
Stop this!
We're a teacher and student!
We're not supposed...
Stop babbling!
No!
Stop it!
Beautifully shaped.
And your nipples are a nice pink, too.
Don't look!
Well? Does it feel good?
Of course it doesn't.
Oh, really?
But you feel it, don't you?
Your nipples are so sweet and yummy.
No...
My nipples...
So you do like it.
No!
No?
Isn't it a teacher’s job to teach her students?
Then teach me about sex!
Just think of this as another lesson!
No!
Shut the fuck up!
Eat this, why don't you?
Your pussy is also a nice pink.
Looks like you're ready.
Time for me to come in.
Just relax. Here I come.
You're so nice and tight , Misaki-chan.
Why?
This can't be!
I'm being raped by my own student?
I'm cumming!
Oh, you really were a virgin?
No wonder you were so tight.
That was really good, Misaki-chan.
You'll give me another lesson soon, right?
English Department Lounge
The Police?
No, he's a student.
That's right! I'll ask Morinaga-sensei.
English Department Lounge
Ah, you mustn't!
Oh, a student can't be doing this to a teacher.
I need to help her!
What's wrong? I didn't tell you to stop moving.
Sorry.
It's locked!
Not like that!
You aren't moving your hips properly.
I'm sorry.
See?
Get it all the way inside,
and swirl it around.
Okay.
Yes. That's right.
What’s happening?
Sensei, I’m gonna...
Not yet.
Hold back a bit longer.
But..
Dammit. You're so pathetic.
Sorry.
If you want to fuck me again,
go do some research first.
What's happening?
Did Morinaga-sensei seduce a student?
Is... this place...
What the hell...
is wrong with this place?
This prep school...
Next Episode
Spring.
April.
A season usually-filled with
hope and expectations,
until despair washed over it.
For the new female teacher at the school,
the dark, gloomy, and
depraved days continued.
Eventually, these dark
experiences change her,
and she transforms into a different creature.
How far will that new form take her?
Onna Kyoushi Nikutai Jugyou, Part 2.
On sale in spring 2004.
On sale in 2004.
Translation:
Voldemort
Snake
Edit:
Collectr
Timing:
v1touch
Typeset & Encode:
ShocWave
Quality Check:
Morpheus_Stiltzkin
Presented by:
Erobeat
http://www.erobeat.net
#erobeat @ irc.rizon.net