And... there.
Hey!
You there!
Yes?
D-Demon Queen?! Why are you here?
That doesn't matter!
R-Right here and right now...
You're going to shoot your semen into me!
Huh?! Wh-What did you just say?
I-I'm telling you...
...that you can use my body as you please!
You'll shoot your semen into me!
Demon Queen Melissa's Erotic Adventure Record
(Onna Maou Melissa no H na Boukenki)
A Lewd Demon Queen Collecting Semen
Wh-Why are you doing something like this?
Soliciting for sex...
Shut up! E-Enough of that...
Hurry up and shoot your semen instead.
I-If you squeeze me so tightly...
Y-Your cock...
H-Hurry, right at the spot that always feels good...
My womb... You're reaching my womb!
That's good...
Good...
You're doing great... Good...
I'm going to come... Your cock is amazing!
Someone like me is now doing such a thing...
Such a thing... Such a thing...
Y-You're coiling around me!
Y-Your Highness, it's gonna
come out! I'm coming already!
C-Coming... I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
Do it more... I-I'm already...
Coming... Coming...
I'm coming!
Good...
Th-That tongue technique of yours is captivating!
Hey, hey, hey... W-Will this really be alright?
Share some of it to me.
I want to have your semen!
I'm hoping for your cooperation.
I can't get enough of this!
Come on, keep sucking it even more!
His penis is throbbing and keeps getting hotter!
This is so nasty!
A very beautiful maid like you is asking for semen!
That's right, this is all for the sake of obtaining semen.
I won't let the demon queen go
through such humiliation by herself.
Aren't you quite skilled?
Hey there, gobble more of the whole thing!
That's good! Yes, yes!
I can't breathe!
But, I-I'm getting off from this!
I'm already mushy down there!
Oh... Good!
Y-You knave!
I don't care about any of that, so come already!
Shoot your semen... Shoot it into me!
Th-That's great!
Hey, how are they?
Do my tits make you feel good?
Yeah, they're the best!
Who would've thought that the
heroine herself will ask for semen?
I-It's not like that!
I have my own reasons for doing this.
S-Semen...
I-I'm in urgent need for some baby batter!
You say that, but aren't you
actually feeling good from this?
Your nipples are as hard as nails!
P-Please don't say that!
This isn't...
This isn't what I had in mind, but I...
I-If you keep stimulating me like that, I-I'm gonna...
Yes, that's good!
No! Th-This feels good!
N-Not so rough...
Yes, yes!
I'll spray my semen onto these lewd tits of yours!
Thank you!
Sh-Shoot it out!
Please shoot plenty of your semen out!
P-Plenty of it!
Y-You come with me as well!
L-Let's come, Miss Heroine!
Y-Yes... I will... I will come!
I'm gonna come!
Good... It feels good!
Coming... I'm coming!
I can't take it anymore!
No, I'm coming!
Coming... I'm coming!
I'm coming!
Ho-ah!
We all kept gathering semen that way.
However, there's actually a certain reason behind this.
We're surrounded.
Seems like it.
Jeez!
Are we going head-on?
Yeah!
Thunder!
Eat this!
We won!
What a bother.
We did it!
Well, if we can only use our original powers,
having a close fight with monsters
of this level would be unthinkable.
That's right...
If only someone didn't mess up using a divine magic
and got the magical powers of all three of us sealed.
F-Forgive me.
This is all my fault.
Even so...
We need to receive semen
in order to replenish our mana.
What an absurd seal this is!
B-But lately...
I'm kind of got hooked in asking for semen!
Are you stupid?!
Your Highness!
Huh?
Wh-What are we gonna do now?
We got surrounded!
Y-You wretch! Impudent!
H-Huh?
Your Highness, our mana already
got depleted from the earlier fight.
Wh-Whaaaaat?
Then, that means...
H-Halt! Stop that!
Y-You vile thing... Th-That's my...
Y-You sneaky...
Th-This bastard...
I think this is bad!
I-I have a bad feeling about this...
S-Stop!
W-Wait, something such as tentacles are...
Th-That spot is...
S-Stop...
Jeez...
There's no way...
Y-Your highness!
I-I beg of your forgiveness!
D-Despite of me accompanying you...
Th-This still happened...
This is so intense!
No... Stop this!
Th-This can't be!
Y-Your highness...
This is bad! I don't have any more strength left to resist!
I-If this goes on...
I-If I kept getting violated like this by these tentacles...
I-It's going to break me!
Stop being too reckless on me!
I-I shouldn't say that!
Stop speaking of such obscenity!
No... No!
No, I shouldn't!
I'm getting pleasure from something like this!
I'm feeling horny from this!
N-No! The tentacles are...
No! No! No way!
D-Don't tease me there!
Th-That place is dirty!
I-It went inside!
B-Both of my pussy and ass are
getting stirred up at the same time!
No... No!
The likes of tentacles dare do this
to me who's a demon queen!
N-No way!
D-Don't you get carried away!
Putting me in such a dreadful position...
Th-This is giving me non-stop pleasure...
Y-You need to stop!
These phalluses are scraping my pussy and ass.
Th-They're scraping both of them!
E-Enough of this...
Enough of this already!
Any more of this and I'm... I'm gonna...
No!
Wow! This is amazing!
They're squirting! They're filling up my insides!
Y-Your highness!
I-I'm already at my limit as well!
The tentacles... The dicks...
They're making both my pussy and ass feel good!
N-No, they're gonna come! It's spurting in my pussy!
Th-That thing got all three of us...
Y-Your highness, please forgive me!
B-But with this,
we've got ourselves replenished with semen again.
Y-You critter, you'll see!
I definitely won't lose next time!
Th-This strange seal!
I'll undo this strange seal without fail!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization