No. I'm going home. I'm fine.
Professor Hayama fell Into the trap set by Gondo and Vlce Principal Ishiguro.
She's being brutalized every day In the basement, or at the school.
You're our sex slave.
What happened?
I'll tell you if you let me fuck you.
What's wrong?
What... What am I supposed to do?
HOT FOR TEACHER
Episode 2
We're going to have a lot of special guests today.
They're all very special, so make sure you cater to their every need.
I didn't hear an answer!
Yes... As you wish...
Why hello, you're here so early. Seems as though you couldn't wait.
She's the one I was telling you about.
They're from the prefecture's Board of Education.
And these people are the ones who give huge donations to the academy.
Someone's late.
Long time no see, Yumi.
Matsunaga!
I was worried that you started without me.
We wouldn't kick off tonight's party without you.
Please... anybody but him.
Look how spunky she got all of a sudden.
He's the one who took Yumi's virginity, right?
It's been getting boring lately, so we thought we'd spice it up.
Yumi, how dare you embarrass me by breaking off our engagement.
I wasn't expecting you to be doing extra curricular activities like this.
You're wrong. There's a reason for this!
No!
What is this? You were such a prude, but now you're just an average whore.
I know you want this instead of that.
Stop... Please turn back into the Matsunaga I knew...
What are you saying? It's been so long since you've seen each other.
Your pussy is crying with joy.
Everyone, please help yourselves.
We'll make copies of the video later and pass them out.
I hope you enjoy it; please keep it as a part of your secret collection.
Please don't hold in it. Please cum on her as much as you want.
All right! I'm going to cum inside her.
No, not inside!
Come on. Who cares if you give birth to our child...
I'm going to cum.
Look how dirty you are... Let me clean you.
Everyone, may we have your assistance?
Professor Hayama!
There's something I want to tell you.
I really didn't know they'd do this to you.
What are you doing?
Stop!
What are you saying? This is what you came for.
You're wrong!
You say that, but your cock is honest... It's so hard.
I said stop!
Forgive me Professor! I want to help you! I really want to help you!
But I have to obey them. If I don't, it'll put Keiko in danger...
I'm being blackmailed...
I want to help you, but I want to protect Keiko... What am I supposed to do?
It's fine... things can stay like this...
It's fine?
I don't care anymore. Protect Keiko.
Don't think about trying to save me.
I can't! I can't watch you like this. I'll save you. I swear...
I think I can go on, just knowing how you feel.
I won't forget your kindness...
Katsutoshi...
Yumi!
Just for a moment... Let me forget everything...
I... I'll do anything for you... For you I'd...
You make me so happy.
Yumi...
Katsutoshi!
I'm going to save her! I swear I'm going to save her!
I'm going to protect him... I'm going to protect them both.
It's best to stay away from me, Professor Tachikawa.
Why? If you're having a rough time I want you to tell me.
You can talk to me about anything.
Why are you so kind to me?
Well... I'm worried about you...
You've completely changed. What's happened to you?
If you found out the truth, you'd despise me.
Something to do with the Vice Principal, right? Keiko told me.
Keiko did?
I figured you'd betray us someday.
Anyway, I'm sure you know the consequences of betraying us.
This is for needlessly trying to stick your nose in our business.
She got herself into this mess.
What are you doing? Please stop!
Mmm... It's the smell of sweet honey.
Then, I wonder what flavor her breasts are?
You have a baby face, but you've got nice breasts.
Stop...
Then do you prefer this?
A young girl's skin feels so different. It's so nice and tight.
She's really sensitive, too. Her nipples are perky already.
So she has sensitive breasts, eh?
Let's make her feel even better.
No!
You idiot. We've only just started.
That's right. Your untainted pussy...
Please, not there...
Show your dear Katsutoshi everything.
Look at her!
Don't show Katsu!
Take a good look. See how wet she is?
Yumi... Keiko... They're all whores inside.
I want you to be even sluttier.
Isn't it exciting when people are watching you be a pervert?
This position is more perverted.
Well? How does her pussy taste?
Please! Move his head!
What are you talking about? He's kissing you...
But I need to pee...
There's no need to hold it.
Katsu, I'm so sorry...
Now it's your turn to make us feel good...
I'm going to tape this, so be good!
No! No! No! No!
Noooo!
You bastards!!
Professor...
It's okay. Go to Keiko...
Are you sure you want to call the police?
Of course I'm going to call them! You have no right to be an educator!
If you get us arrested, you'll be embarrassing them too.
I'm the one who's going to the authorities.
I'm going to take all these tapes and go to the police.
Except for this tape...
Take this and go!
Hurry! Leave, you two!
Why are you doing this, Professor?
To protect both of you. I'm your teacher.
From now on, you need to protect Keiko. Okay?
I promise. I swear I'll protect her.
Hurry. Before the police come...
Are you really sure?
I'm sure. But I doubt I'll be able to remain a professor...
I'll be by your side.
No matter what happens, I'll always be on your side.
That bastard!
Let go of me!
I'm not letting you go!
Professor Tachikawa!
I'm not going to let you get away...
Vice Principal Ishiguro and Gondo were both arrested...
...and all their evil deeds were made public.
Professor Tachikawa was paralyzed from the waist down because of the fall.
He'll be In a wheelchair for the rest of his life, but at his side...
Yumi said It herself. She'll never leave his side until she dies...
They're going to be together forever...
Yumi looked so happy when she told us her decision.
A FEW MONTHS LATER...
I, on the other hand...
Don't you know how to knock?
Is it true you were accepted?
I wanted to be an admlrable person...
...like Yumi and Professor Tachikawa.
That's why I put my mind Into my studles.
Katsu, congratulations! I'm sure Yumi will be proud too!
Keiko...
A reward... For working so hard...
I love you...
Be gentle.
I'm sorry... I don't think I can. I'm too nervous.
It's okay. Relax...
See? It's hard.
Thanks to you.
It hurts!
Stay still. It'll feel good in a minute.
Katsu, it feels so good.
I think I'm going to go crazy.
Let's cum together.
I can't anymore...
Katsu...
Let's stay together forever...
FOUR YEARS LATER...
Here's your lunch, honey.
Off I go!
Good luck, Professor Yoshioka!
A professor...
I became a professor, because of one fateful encounter.
This all happened because of my encounter with Yumi.
Thank you so much, Yumi. Until we meet again...