Cute Boy Hunter
Oh wow, it's so rock hard. I'm so happy!
You look even more beautiful today, Ayano.
Did you meet a new lover?
It's not that.
I'm trying to be beautiful.
So cute.
This is my favorite position.
Oh more, fuck me more!
If It'll make Ayano happy, I'll fuck you with all I have!
Good, good! More, more!
Oh, it feels good.
Oh, no more. I'm cumming.
Ah, cum. Cum over my face.
I'm happy.
You're wonderful Ayano.
Beautiful.
Hey, I decided on my tutoring job.
That's good.
You wanted to be a teacher in the future.
It'll be a good experience for you, Ayano.
Yea, but sometimes, teaching someone is harder than studying by yourself.
I hope I can do it.
I'm a little worried.
Dont worry. You can do it Ayano!
Don't worry about anything.
Oh, I'm leaving now, so be sure to lock up.
Okay, take care!
Yoko, I love you Yoko.
Me too, Yuji.
Ah, feels so good.
Yoko, tighten, can you tighten more?
I don't know what I should do.
Ah, there. Try to squeeze it.
Like this?
Oh, yea! Yea, ah, good.
Ah, Yuji, I'm, I'm embarrassed doing this.
Don't be embarrassed.
Move your hips, move it up and down.
My hips? Like this? This?
Oh wow, wonderful, Yoko.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too Yuji!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
Me, me too! Cumming!
Yuji!
Hey Yoko,
you're not going anywhere even during summer break?
Yea, I'm planning a lot.
But it won't be fun if you're not coming along.
Hahaha, I can't go because i'm a drop out student.
Maybe as recreation, I'll watch movies, that's about it.
Plus i got a tutor starting today, so nothing can be done.
Hey Yuji, let's go to the movies together.
There's a lot of movies you want to watch right?
Umm, yea. Let's go.
But is it okay for you not go to the beach or the mountains?
Yes, who is it?
I came from the Tutoring center. My name is Ayano Yamamura.
Oh shit, it's the tutor.
Oh no, clothes, clothes!
Well well, thanks for dropping by on this hot day.
No problem.
Please step inside.
Yes, excuse me.
I'm sorry Yoko. You dropped by in spite of all your busy schedule.
No, I'm sorry for bothering Yuji's studies.
Excuse me.
Now, try this problem.
For this, can I do this, and this?
Yes, yes. You're pretty good.
This is pretty difficult.
Then next, this one.
What a cute boy.
I'll make him mine someday.
I didn't think teachers were this beautiful.
Her long hair smells good.
You're always a good pussy eater.
More, make me wet!
Ah, good!
Lick all the way up my ass.
It feels good!
How is it Ayano? Do you like it?
This is new to me!
It's great, great!
You have a nice butt, Ayano.
Good, good, make it tighter!
Excellent,
Ayano. Good, very good!
There, next, will be this position!
There Ayano, you can see it too.
Ah, it's so dirty.
There Ayano, Look at it. Look at it more.
I see it.
It's going in and out of my pussy. Good, very good! More, more!
Yoko, what's wrong with you lately?
You're acting strange today.
Cause the tutor last time was very beautiful.
What are you saying? That doesn't matter at all.
Really? You won't start liking her, Yuji?
Of course!
She is just my tutor, and Yoko is my lover.
You understand right?
Here Yoko, this is proof that I love you.
Yuji, I'm so happy! I'm happy!
Fuck me more!
Yuji, Yuji!
There Yoko, how's this?
Great! I'm so happy Yuji!
Come one Yoko, you're forgetting to tighten your pussy.
Yes, tighten more!
Really Yuji?
More, tighten it more!
What happened Yuji? You're so aggresive today.
It's because I love you.
Oh my, Yuji! More, more!
Cumming, cumming, I'm cumming!
Me too!
Cum Yuji!
Cum, on my face like I like it!
Yuji...
Umm first, for this one.
It's wrong.
First you apply this equation, and like this.
Oh, I see.
Then this becomes this, and this, and like this.
Ok. Try this problem next.
What's wrong?
Is this problem very hard?
Umm, I don't know.
Help me!
Yuji.
Yes?
What's bothering you?
If it's okay with you, you can talk to me.
About anything, anything that's bothering you.
Talk to me.
Well, it's not like I'm suffering or something.
Lier. Something's weird. Something's up with you today, Yuji.
Well, the truth, the truth is that.
I...
Yuji.
Shut up.
Ah, wow. It's so big.
Here, insert it here in me.
Ready?
Ah wow! Yuji, it's great!
Your penis is fat, long, and strong... Oh wow!
Your breasts feels so good!
Ah, yes! Fuck me doggy style next. Hurry, hurry and stick it in!
Ready?
Oh wonderful, Yuji!
I love you, love you a lot!
Me too, me too Yuji!
I, I love you!
I can't bare it anymore, I'm cumming!
Okay I'm cumming too! Cumming, cumming!
Did you cum?
Can I cum over your face?
Yea, cum all over my face!
Can I ask you one thing, Yuji?
Yes?
The girl that was here last time, is that your lover?
Huh?
Yea, kind of like a lover, a girlfriend.
She's an underclassmen.
Are you two going out?
Yea, we're going out. But...
But what?
I do like her, but recently she's been a heavy load.
Of course I'm happy when she stops by sometimes.
Oh.
For now, I need a person like you.
Am I being selfish?
No, you're not like that at all.
I want to be your support, not only for your study, but also for your heart.
Yuji...
No, stop, why are you doing this?
Hey hey hey, Do you feel this you horny bitch?
I'll do this to a girl like you.
There, there, look at it, you're dripping wet.
It must feel good.
I bet you want to do this everyday.
Stop, stop, please forgive me!
Now I'll do this!
It went in. Doesn't it feel good?
No, forgive me!
What are you saying?
Even though you like this?
Ah no, no!
What, you want me to go stronger?
All right, then like this!
It's starting to feel better right?
Don't persevere this feeling, just cum.
Ah no, I'm cumming!
Next It's your turn to make me cum.
Use your tongue to lick.
Ah, yes! Yes, yes, you're doing great!
More, licking you bitch!
No!
More, lick me more!
Please...
Do you get it?
If you had enough, don't ever go near Yuji.
He doesn't need a girl like you.
You're just disturbing him.
Huh? What was that dream?
Oh too early? Sorry.
Yea, can you wait in the next room.
I'll be done soon.
Okay, I'll wait. Hang in there!
My bad.
Yuji, what's the meaning of this?
Oh, man, what is it all of the sudden?
Yoko's in the room next door.
This won't be good.
Be quiet, just lick here.
I'm putting it in.
Ah,
It's great!
Isn't this great? There, fuck me more, fuck me harder!
It feels so good!
Me too, It's great!
Ah, Yuji, my Yuji.
Great, It's fucking great! More!
I'll cum if you tighten even more.
It's okay. You can cum.
I'll make you cum even more!
Together, let's cum together!
Ah, sure, together, together...
More, Yuji, fuck me more!
Ah, what happened?
Don't stop, I was about to cum.
Want me to continue?
Don't play with me!
I want you to continue.
Okay, I'll continue.
But understand that the one you need now is me.
I understand, I understand.
I'm about to cum, so hurry and continue!
So you understand.
Then you won't go out with Yoko anymore?
Huh?
What's your answer?
Okay. I only need you.
So hurry!
Good, good! My cute Yuji.
You can cum now, cum in me!
I'm cumming, Aah...