Due to a failed divine magic,
our magical powers got sealed.
In order to replenish our mana,
we somehow need to ingest semen.
We beg men in town for their semen
as we look for a way to undo the seal
in our ongoing journey.
But due to us pretty much asking around,
our bodies have gradually started getting strange.
Demon Queen Melissa's Erotic Adventure Record
(Onna Maou Melissa no H na Boukenki)
A Lewd Demon Queen Collecting Semen
Hey, are you really sure about this?
I mean, saying you want my semen...
Y-Yes...
May it be gulping it down from a blowjob
or a pussy creampie from bareback sex,
I want you to shoot it all inside me!
Is this for real? I'm all in!
What should I do? My nipples...
They're now perked up stiff!
You're sopping wet down here as well!
Y-Yes! My pussy and tits...
My whole body feels so hot!
Here, isn't this what you want?
Yes, I want this!
A cock... A cock, it's a cock!
It tastes good...
His cock is hard, hot, and it smells lewd!
I... I'm already...
I-I'm teasing my own pussy
while slurping on a cock!
I'll suck it airtight, then stroke it using my lips!
I'll lick the tip and neck part just like this,
then vacuum suck the glans next!
And then slurp it again!
Hey, doesn't it feel good?
Whoa...
Good... That feels so good!
More, more... Oh...
Yes, I'm feeling it...
I-It feels good!
I'm about to come, I'm coming!
Oh, your pussy is sopping wet already!
Then, I'm going to fuck you now!
It' went in! It went inside me!
Oh... Yes, that's it!
Ah... Isn't that a nice tongue
technique you have?
Yes, your cock is hard and huge!
It's going wild all over inside
my mouth, and it feels good!
She's squeezing me hard down here!
This feels good! Very good!
I feel like I'm about to come!
H-His dick is going so wild
inside my pussy!
Wow, I'm feeling it so much!
It feels so good!
It feels good here too! That's it!
I'll fuck you hard and come!
Yes, I'm coming!
I'm in the bathhouse with men
whose names I don't know,
and I'm having bareback sex with them!
I have to fill you up with semen, right?
Make sure to take it all in!
My pussy is squeezing tight deep inside!
I'm gonna get filled deep inside my mouth!
Here it comes in my pussy as well!
I still can't believe that
this erotic lady is a heroine!
Damn it!
Forgive me! I'm sorry for being
such an indecent heroine!
We're going to punish you plenty today,
so brace yourself!
O-Okay!
Please... Please, punish me!
Y-You can go rough on my body!
M-More... Mess me up even more!
Ohh... You're squeezing me tight!
I'm going to come!
Come! Come!
More, more, more!
I-I'm sure that right now...
...I am ovulating!
My womb wants to get knocked up
from having sex right now!
I-I'm about to come already. I'm gonna come!
Come! Shoot your baby batter!
I'm coming!
Hey, hey... Are you serious?
Yes... You may find it lacking,
but feel free to use this body
of mine as you deem fit.
You may rough me up like you're raping me.
You may also order me to
indecently shake my hips for you.
I will do anything as you please.
So, that rumor turned out to be true!
Rumor?
Wh-What's this?
There has been a rumor going
around this town lately,
that there are women blindly
begging any men for semen.
Weren't they you and your group?
Wh-What are you planning to do with me?
We'll only be enjoying ourselves.
However, we'll do it our own way!
How is it? Aren't you feeling good?
Take this! I'll bet that human
cocks can't compare with this!
Y-Yes!
It feels good... It feels good!
Your cocks feel good!
Doesn't it feel good to be roughed up like this?
Yes, even though I hate to admit it!
How about this?
You're perverted just as the rumor says!
No, I don't want to feel good from this!
But my body is getting hot
and I can't help it anymore!
Why?
Why is my body this obscene?
Good... It feels good!
I'm becoming an indecent woman now!
E-Even though I am suffering right now,
my pussy feels thrilled with excitement!
I'm feeling good!
His cock is throbbing! He's coming!
He'll shoot his semen inside me!
All three of them together!
They're coming! All three of them at the same time!
I'm going to savor your ass hole this time!
N-No! Stop!
M-My ass is sensitive!
Why are you saying that now, of all times?
Aren't you also...
Aren't you also loving this?
No, don't do that!
She's so slippery down here,
and it keeps on tightening!
I knew it, this woman is loving it!
W-Wow, our cocks are hitting each other inside!
I-Incredible!
This is great! Good!
No...
No, don't! Your cocks...
They're rubbing so hard against my insides!
Wow... It's incredible!
Being scraped this much
by your cocks feels good!
Coming... Something's coming!
It feels tingly! I'm gonna get
shredded down there!
No... No, I'm begging you!
Stop... Stop this! If this goes on...
What are you saying after all this time?
Aren't you also feeling very good? Here, take this!
If you keep doing this to me,
I'll really break down! I'll go crazy!
This is bad! I'm coming again! I'm gonna come!
How about it?
Don't you two want to use those burly cocks
to ejaculate in my petite body? Hmm?
H-How outrageous!
Yep! You may wedge my pussy
wide open using your cocks!
I also won't mind you shoving it
in my mouth up to my throat!
Oh... What wicked things
are you talking about!
Th-That's it!
Exorcism! We have to perform
the purification ceremony!
Oh, exorcism?
H-Hey!
All of you, what the hell are you planning to do?
It'll be alright. Leave everything to us.
We'll exorcise the wanton demon
that is possessing your body.
Wh-What kind of joke are you
talking about, old geezer!
Stop, don't touch me!
You geezer! Do you have an idea who I am?
This is the power bestowed to us by heaven.
This is the purification ceremony that us
from the holy orders shall perform!
Cut that out!
S-Stop stirring up my insides with those fingers!
That scream just now was the demon shrieking!
The purification is proceeding as expected!
Wh-What are you saying...
No... Stop it already!
D-Don't do that! If you'll
keep on touching me there...
This should be about right.
I'll start this by purging you using my holy sword!
Th-That's... D-Don't tell me...
There is quite a powerful demon
possessing you down here!
Y-You're wrong!
Your cock won't work on demons...
Your crotch is overflowing
with the demon's tears!
It won't be long now!
No... Don't do that!
If you keep going that hard...
N-No way!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'll lend my powers for your purification as well.
There! There! There! There!
Stop that!
There!
What purification are you talking about?
There! There!
Y-Your cock is so big!
Y-You'll tear my pussy!
You talk about that purification,
when you're all just gonna rape me!
It appears that the demon is possessing
even your mouth this time.
How's that, lowly demon?
We'll purge you using our holy swords!
Th-These people are using my body as they please!
Oh, God Almighty!
May you lend us your power to purify her!
H-He shoving it in my mouth!
The demon is far from being exorcised yet!
Yes...
Not yet! Not yet!
There! Take that!
H-His dick is getting snugged inside!
It's throbbing!
They're coming! They're coming out!
They're coming while still moving!
This one's coming too! It's coming out!
By the powers of all of us priests who are here,
we will have you purified!
No way...
I-I already have enough semen!
Enough of this already... No... No!
Oh, God Almighty... God Almighty!
May she be purified! May she be purified!
Th-This is bad... I'm already...
I'm starting to feel good deep in my throat as well!
Amazing!
My pussy too, and even my ass hole as well!
They're scraping me...
The cocks in a tight squeeze
are rubbing against each other!
N-No!
It's coming! There's plenty
of it coming in my mouth!
Each of my holes...
Th-They're all being banged!
They're all getting raped!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come!
Well, a lot of stuff happened
but we collected plenty of semen!
We should be able to go through that forest now.
But, Miss Demon Queen...
Huh?
There might be monsters
waiting for us in the forest.
I think that we should collect a bit more
semen and increase our levels first...
Th-That's right...
If we gather more semen and earn funds,
we'll be able to upgrade our equipment and items.
It can't be helped, then.
Then, shall we head to a nearby
town and gather some more?
Some more... Semen...
Okay, Miss Demon Queen!
Yes, Your Highness!
And with that being said,
our adventure still has a long way to go!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji / Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization