Original doujin anime created in 1983-1987
O-Parts: OMAN
Producer: Morino Usagi
Director: Asari Yosito
O-Parts:
O
M
A
N
Have you heard? It showed up again last night.
Really?
It was fifth time. Now at sophomores.
And already 4th victim in this month, eh?
Uh-huh... They say it's some kind of robot.
It can't be!
But there's witnesses!
Is that so?
There's something interesting in our school.
Moreover, this "something" is a very powerful combat mech.
And it's always ready for action!
Enhanced exoskeleton suite on basis of O-Parts technology:
OMAN
Wha?
Help me!
Here you are...
Help!
That's all.
It's here!
Let's go.
Where's it?
N-No!!
Why you did that?!
You are thinking about others, are you?!
But I...
I just wanted to have friends!!