This is...
This is what I've wanted.
Ryuuya, your penis is so hard.
You're excited, right?
I thought I could be the one to feel good today.
Ryuuya.
I'm turned on while I'm doing this to your penis.
Are you hoping to feel good?
Ryuuya, will you use your penis to fuck me?
Ryuuya.
It's coming in.
Please, more~!
Wait, I'll fuck you good.
It's coming in~
It's coming, Ryuuya's penis is going inside.
What's this?
It feels good-
Your penis is making my whole body feel good.
Hmph... you really like boobs.
No, you can't grab them so hard.
You beast~
It's great.
Your penis is getting bigger.
No, please give it to me.
Please squirt your beast milk into my vagina.
Okay, I'll give you a lot.
I'll get pregnant from your beast milk.
The beast's milk is coming inside~!
Ryuuya, you're such a bad boy.
You are really the demon king of boobs.
Please don't call me a demon king!
Geez, let's get out of here.
It would be terrible if someone came here.
Please wait!
Geez.
How can you just go away and leave the girl that had sex with you just now?
Okay... okay, let's hurry.
You're really cold-hearted to all the girls except for Miya-senpai.
Hmph, I'll make sure you pay for this.
W
Oppai Heart
Big Boobs Cheerleader - Matsuri ～Dyeing within the sticky beastly milk～
There, look at this!
You're late, Ryuuya.
No, wait.
Hey, if you do it so rough-
What are you doing all of a sudden?
Now there's no way for you to run away from this.
So, how is it? It looks good, huh?
It's a boy's dream, right?
Are you hard yet?
What are you doing?
What?! You're no fun!
Here I am showing off my charms for you.
I wondered why you called me here.
I'm well aware of your charms.
Eh? Really? No way.
What should I do?
Your charming point is this!
Boobs?
Yes, this is your most charming point.
That's what I love.
I see.
Boobs, eh?
So, I have to go to help Miya.
Bye.
Geez... Ryuuya.
Where are you going?
You've got a cute girlfriend like me in here.
Your penis got hard from seeing me, right?
Matsuri, this isn't good.
It's no good for you to hold back here.
You've gotten bigger there.
When did it become like that?
Ryuuya~! Is it okay?
I want your penis, Ryuuya.
It's hot.
Ryuuya, your penis is hot and hard.
Ryuu-kun.
Oh, no!
I found you, Ryuu-kun!
Don't come here!
R-Ryuu-kun.
Why are you putting up cloth?
Don't, please don't come here.
I'll be there soon, so wait for me.
Ryuu-kun, you look so serious.
S-Sure, I'll wait for you
Wow, that was close.
Ryuuya, you did that so suddenly.
I had a hard time breathing under there.
What are you talking about?!
What if someone had seen what we were doing?
Then you should hurry up and cum inside me!
My boobs feel good.
Your penis is great.
Matsuri...
Ryu... Ryuuya.
It's such a waste for you to cum inside my mouth.
You can do your best next time, right?
No, it's great!
My vagina is being fucked so hard!
Ryuuya, please more... more!
Please come inside some more!
Please let me feel more of your penis!
Please let my whole body feel it!
No, it's making my vagina feel so good!
Your penis is reaching into my uterus!
Ryuuya~
Please give me your milk!
Please give your beast milk and make me pregnant!
Matsuri, you- Not in here...
This is great!
Ryuuya's penis...
So much...
This is wonderful!
My boobs are being squeezed!
It feels good!
No!
I'm going to-
Ryuuya, I'm going to...!
It's coming!
There's so much beast's milk~
I'll get pregnant with your child...
It's so late already.
I thought that I could go back early since there aren't any club activities.
It's your fault for touching my boobs.
Idiot!
Your boobs are not only huge, they lactate.
Aren't they huge treasures?
It shows you're stupid.
Hey, you...
Go to your Miya-senpai quickly.
She's waiting for you right?
No, it's fine.
It's about time to take you home.
And I sent her a text just now.
Then I'm your boyfriend.
I have to think about what I should do in these circumstances.
Ryu... Ryuuya.
'Boyfriend', he said.
Ryuuya is such an honest person.
Owww...
No... No way.
Oh, what a relief.
But why are they going back to normal?
Ryuuya~!
Can't you show up like a normal person?
That costume?
I think that I'm going to be revived today.
I think I'm in good condition today.
I don't think it's okay for you to wear something so raunchy.
It's fine.
I'm used to training in it.
If I do this...
See? You still respond to it.
It's still dangerous.
Idiot.
You shouldn't have taken it out.
What should we do now?
Please wait, this is a bad place.
Ryuuya...
Ryuuya's gotten bigger...
It feels good to be touched by you, Ryuuya.
Something's coming from your tip.
Mat... suri.
There's so much love-milk.
Yes...
I'm full of the beast's penis.
The beast's penis is big!
Great...
My insides are getting wider...
This is wonderful!
It's going inside and out.
It's fucking my vagina.
My boobs!
It's cumming!
Ryuuya, you'll suck out all my milk.
You can suck all of my milk?
Please give me your beast's milk too.
It's reaching inside.
Please, go deeper.
No, this... it can't be.
The people down below can see us.
Ryuuya!
They really will see us from down there.
They can't see us.
No... you're lying, right?
It's too rough-
Your penis is teasing me.
It's messing up the inside of my vagina,
and covering it in beast's milk.
Give it to me, please give me the beast's milk!
Ryu-
It's spurting...
The beast's milk is coming inside of me!
Stupid Ryuuya, you pervert!
I'm sure someone saw us!
Geez.
I'm sorry, I was too excited.
I can't get married anymore.
You'll have to take care of me forever.
Okay, fine.
I'll take care of you forever.
Are you right in the head?
Hey, is that how you respond?
Are you saying I'm not qualified to take care of you?
No... no... no.
That's not what I mean.
I don't mean you're not qualified.
Let's just go home, since tomorrow we have a date.
Okay!
Why did the date become like this?
I-Idiot, that's because you seduce me wherever we go.
Because it was beautiful, right?
All the girls love that sort of thing, right?
Well, let's put that thing away.
Ryuuya, hurry up and give me your pen-
I-Idiot!
What are you going to do if somebody comes?
Please wait.
Matsuri, you can't...
Ryuuya's penis is also hard and thick today.
I want your milk quickly.
Ryuuya,
please fuck my vagina quickly.
For the sake of love,
I'll do what you want.
Today your penis is also great,
it fits inside of me perfectly.
Please control your voice.
We never know when someone might come by.
I know that.
I'll control it.
Please go deeper.
I'm happy that your penis is coming inside of me.
Your penis...
Please calm down and keep it down.
Your penis isn't coming.
Ryuuya.
I-Idiot, don't move.
This is good.
The vagina and penis are rubbing each other.
There's no one here.
Gosh, I told you to be quiet.
Nyaa~
Inside there-
It's deep.
No, it's too rough.
If you do it so hard I'll-
This is your punishment for not listening to me.
No, Ryuuya...
Are you going to cum inside?
Will you fill me up with your beast's milk?
I like it big!
I'll be fucked by this hard beast penis.
No...
There's so much cum.
Ryuuya, you were way too rough!
It's always all about you, isn't it?
I couldn't help it.
And come on, you were really into it.
How could I get so horny at a time like this?
I hope I change phases quickly.
I can't date properly or do club activities.
If this keeps going on, what should I do?
It's okay.
I'm with you.
I'm sure I'll get you pregnant.
Oh my god!
How you could say something so weird like that in public?!
I wonder when the change will take place?
There's also the possibility it won't happen.
It wasn't the pregnancy, but also...
Ryuuya said I'd be okay.
But what if I'm not?
What will Ryuuya do?
Huh? Ryuuya and Natsuki-senpai...
Why? Why does he look so serious?
Hey Ryuuya, how about having lunch-
I'm sorry, I have some work to do.
Sorry.
He's together with Natsuki-senpai
He also said couldn't go to school together this morning.
What's going on?
First he disappears without telling me why, and now this?
Am I just being stupid?
So I'll tell Matsuri.
Although I feel sorry for her.
Ryuuya-kun...
No way, Ryuuya...
Natsuki-senpai, I don't want to bother you anymore.
No.
It can't be...
Ryuuya and Natsuki-senpai, it can't be...
It's a lie, a lie.
It will make her cry!
Why me?
Hey.
Huh?
M-Matsuri-chan, what's wrong?
Miya-senpai.
Matsuri?!
Aiba-san.
I'm not really sure what's going on.
If it's okay with you, would you please tell me?
Isn't it you two who have something to tell me?
Eh?!
I'm ready to hear it.
So...
Aiba-san, do you mean...
So you heard us.
I see, okay. Matsuri.
I know it will make you sad.
But I still have to say it.
Matsuri... Matsuri, you can't...
You can't have an early lun-
No, I don't want to hear about how-
You don't want me to have an early lunch...
Huh?
"Early lunch"?
Is that really so important to you?
But the teacher said that it's important and that we should inform the student council.
Matsuri, your habit of sneaking in an early lunch was turning into a big problem.
If only I had been stricter when mentoring Aiba-san...
It wouldn't have to come to this.
It was my fault too, I'm with her all the time and I didn't try to fix it.
But you need to stop the early lunches.
It can't be forgiven if this keeps on.
Umm... was early lunching the thing you wanted to talk about?
Yeah, what else would it be?
Sure it would be.
M-Matsuri-chan, what's going on?
Suddenly laughing, then suddenly crying...
Today's agenda
- fixing the problems of
sneaking in early lunches.
You thought I was gonna break up with you?!
Geez, first you eavesdrop, then you completely misunderstand what you heard...
What made you think something was going on between Ryuuya and me?
Well, because...
Whatever you're thinking,
I'm 100% sure it would never happen.
You don't have to say it so bluntly.
What's up?
Akino is cheating on you?
No, I don't mean that-
Well... since you say it like that, it wouldn't happen right?
Aiba, thank you for waiting
The change is finished.
Th-That means?
Yes. That's right. You're pregnant.
Eh?!
It shocked me...
Back then...
I was the one in shock.
Angry, crying, and laughing.
Because I misunderstood.
Good!
It's reaching so deep inside of me.
Your penis will make the baby come out.
This is great...
Ryuuya's penis...
It's kissing the baby
That place-
It feels good when it's touching there.
I won't let Ryuuya's milk drown the baby.
No...
Please cum!
It came!
Ryuuya's milk~!
So much!
A lot came out...
Ryuuya...
I'm so happy.