I'm not really a member of the photography club.
I just really like cameras.
They're cheap!
I want to take pictures of people.
That was the first time I thought of it.
I was so focused on it that I just happened
to stroll by the marching band club,
and started taking pictures.
However, I wasn't able to do anything about their
accusations of me taking pictures in secret.
Hey Mister!
They broke my camera,
I said Mister!
and this bunny girl here is obstinately trying to sell me something.
Are you listening?
Just for a minute, okay?
H-Hey, what are you...?
What?
What is this?
Is this a dream?
When I came to my senses,
the bunny girl had already replaced my camera.
Academy Marching Band Club
The Days Of Active Recorded Sex and Arousal
Breast
# 1 Camera + Girls = Orgasms
I wonder what that was yesterday?
I want to take a picture of something
with this camera already, though.
Anyway, who the hell was that bunny girl?
Hey~!
Minamo, is that the peeping camera guy from yesterday?
I don't think any peeping tom would just
walk up and expose himself like that.
She's right, Natsumi-chan.
The groupies yesterday suddenly caused an uproar about it,
breaking his camera in the end.
We have to properly apologize to him.
I'm sorry!
We broke your precious camera.
We should have stopped the ruckus sooner.
I-I'm fine as long as the misunderstanding's cleared.
Oh, planning on laying a hand on our Minamo,
Mister peeping camera man?
Jeez, Natsumi-chan, Yuuji-kun isn't a bad person.
Oh yeah, Yuuji-kun.
Can we do anything to make amends
for what happened yesterday?
Amends?
Yup, say anything that you want.
Pictures.
If it's alright with you, I'd like to take some
more pictures of the marching band club.
Here we go, Natsumi-chan!
I get it already!
Something feels odd...
I don't hate it though...
I feel something within me...
It feels good.
I feel hot, like when we were in that tournament.
Yeah, that exact feeling.
Amazing.
Those two are starting to get drenched in sweat.
It looks erotic.
That girl's name is Shirley, right?
W-What is this? I'm...
Whenever I tap, my body feels extremely tingly.
Something feels hot, Natsumi-chan.
No, it's reverberating throughout my body...
This is really strange.
Whenever I snap a picture, they appear to get aroused.
Whenever you take a picture of a girl with this camera,
that girl becomes aroused and will start to crave for sex.
A present for the depressed you.
How you use it is entirely up to you.
It felt great earlier, I felt like I was performing at my best.
It felt like I was really passionate earlier,
or filled with tension, like the kind
I felt during the last tournament.
F-For me, it felt like our performance was
reverberating throughout my body.
But, why was it different from usual?
Maybe the tension that we felt is connected
with how he took our snapshots.
That just can't be, right Shirley?
No, I think it's possible.
If we continue practicing while getting our pictures taken like that,
then we just might be able to improve.
Take care of us, okay? Club exclusive camera man!
Eh, eh...
Eh~?!
And so, my days as their exclusive camera man, has begun.
Next day
Thank you for the hard work!
I'll sit here, okay?
Y-You sure worked hard earlier.
Your performance was really good earlier!
Really?
I've actually been on a roll these past few days.
It's all thanks to you, Yuuji-kun.
I'm happy to hear that.
Oh yeah,
if you're free after this...
You're going to take a picture of me in this pose?
Y-Yeah.
O-Oh no...
I feel really aroused, whenever you take pictures of me...
Yuuji-kun, lately, my body's been feeling
hot whenever you take pictures of me.
It's starting to kill me!
Once you make them feel aroused,
make them do a tit fuck to let them feel better.
I-In that case,
w-wouldn't a tit fuck make you feel a lot better!
Tit fuck?
I'll feel better if I do it, right?
Can you tell me how to do it?
T-Then...
I want you to expose your breasts.
Is this okay?
Yuuji-kun, are you alright?
Your thing is really big and stiff.
It's the same as what you're feeling Minamo.
I feel aroused whenever I take those pictures.
I-I see.
Then I'll have to do something about it for you.
What is this, Yuuji-kun?
I can't hold back anymore.
My voice is...
What is this?
Yuuji-kun, I suddenly felt very strange as
you rubbed your thing on my breasts.
It's called a dick.
Your dick is rubbing against me.
What is this?
My body is shaking all over.
Minamo-chan!
It feels hot.
It's pumping out all this hot and sticky stuff.
What is this?
It's cum.
And it's used to make babies.
So this is cum.
Your cum...
It feels really hot.
C-Can we do it again?
Is your dick alright?
It's rubbing...
It feels like its heat is getting transferred to me.
I feel hotter every minute..
It feels hot, my breasts feel hot...
Your dick is really close to me.
Its smell is really something.
This feels strange.
My body is tingly all over.
I'm cumming!
I think I'm going to cum again.
I think...
That felt really relieving.
Hey, you pervert.
Come with me for a bit before practice.
Something feels strange after you came to our club.
The air feels somewhat restless.
So as punishment,
I want you to help me relieve my stress, okay?
This is a reward!
Whenever you're there,
our practice goes a lot better than normal.
But more than that, there's just something
that I can't wrap my head around.
Doing this, and shaming you like that,
relieves some of my stress, and makes it feel good for you too.
So it's not that bad of a deal, right?
Thank you very much.
Why does it feel so good? I'm just rubbing my foot on his dick!
Well? Feels really stimulating, right?
Yes, very.
It got bigger!
It's twitching.
It's also quite flexible, and can get stiff like this.
I guess you really are a pervert.
I think any guy would get a boner in a situation like this.
Your dick is really twitching, does it really feel that good?
Yeah, it feels good.
Oh, so it does.
Do you want to cum then?
Do you want to cum inside me?
If you keep doing that, I'll really cum!
Eh?
Okay then? Why don't you try pumping it all out?
Let it all out from your dick!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
The hot and thick thing is tiling me up inside!
That was refreshing!
Well, I can't deny that our practice
is going really well thanks to you.
You already know what to do
when I build up stress again, right?
Please.
My body feels hot, and it's wet.
Please do something about this.
Are you okay with me doing something about it?
Yes, do whatever you need to do,
so hurry...
Fluids are dripping...
Don't worry, I'll be sure to plug it up.
Huh? Yuuji-kun, what are you...?
Something's entering inside me.
I-It hurts.
So, this is a dick?
Shirley...
My insides are getting forcefully opened.
A-Amazing...
My breasts are being fondled...
It's hitting me inside.
Going deep inside me.
If you keep moving like that I'll...
This... your cum is pumping into me.
I'm going to get pregnant.
You're too quick.
Too quick!
Sorry, but I just can't let it rest.
It's making lewd sloppy noises.
Shirley, your insides feel too good that I can't stop.
Oh no...
Oh no, I'm feeling really aroused by it too.
I'm going to cum again, Shirley.
Okay, but please cum inside me again.
I'm going to be cummed inside again.
I'm going to get pregnant!
Shirley!
Don't stir me up too much,
or I'm going to go crazy.
I'm going to cum it all inside.
It's too full already.
You mustn't cum inside, and yet...
Cum is pouring inside me again!
Jeez, Yuuji, you're such a pervert.
I think I really like you....
Eh?
Getting my picture taken like this makes my body feels hot,
and I start to think of nothing else but you.
That's why...
Her feelings, are all because of this camera.
Please, Yuuji-kun.
Minamo-chan.
When you fondle me like that,
I feel like wanting to be fondled even more.
Oh no, sucking my nipples like that...
It's starting to feel really stiff.
You're quite slutty, aren't you?
Don't...
If you play roughly with them like that...
Something's coming!
It's coming, it's coming!
Minamo-chan, I can let myself do it already, right?
Don't worry, I'll be gentle.
Yuuji-kun, I want you.
Minamo-chan, I'm putting it in.
It's widening my insides.
Yuuji-kun, your dick...
It's now inside me.
I'm happy.
I can feel you inside, Yuuji-kun.
It's going deep inside.
Minamo-chan, I'm going to cum all the way inside.
Inside?
But I might get pregnant if you do that.
I'm cumming, Minamo-chan.
I'm scared, but cum inside me.
Your hot cum is getting pumped deep inside me.
Oh no...
I'll...
It's already wet with cum.
And it's making sloshing noises.
I'm going to cum inside again.
I'm getting cummed inside again.
I'm going to cum too!
Cum, Yuuji-kun.
Oh no, I'm going crazy with your cum.
I can't stop this tingling feeling.
It feels good.
My insides are getting filled with your cum.
Yuuji-kun, I...
I love you...
Are you okay, Minamo-chan?
Someday, I'll confess all these feelings to Yuuji-kun.