C-Chika, you can't!
Naoto, you hold it in
pretty well, don't you?
Okay...
Chika, you can't do
something like this.
No way...
No, wait...
There's no way Chika would...
But...
Naoto...
Naoto!
Chika!
Your father doesn't remember
raising you to be like...t-that!
How is it, Naoto? Feels good?
C-Chika, l said no...
Why ''no'' even though
you look so happy about it?
Here! Here!
lf you do such a thing,
l'm going to become useless...
Become useless?
l'll become useless with you.
Together...together...
You already betrayed Aya!
You already betrayed her!
Naoto, yours is getting bigger.
ls it about to come out?
lt's going to come out, right?
lt's flying up like a
dragon inside the penis.
The special milk blend...
The special milk blend is going to come!
lt squirted out!
Encode by Jan55 for www.world-of-hentai.to
Booby Life
Episode 2
Naoto-flavored...
l know it's bad, but...
But...
Naoto, l have no intention
to tell Aya about this.
But, l just wanted to...
Become one with you...
lf it was no, that was fine too.
But, that time you...
...brought Aya with you...
You showed me that
l wasn't part of the group.
That is worse than knowing you're
happy somewhere else l don't know.
That's why...
l'm sorry, Chika.
Naoto, you are kind.
No, l'm not kind.
lf l was really kind...
...l wouldn't make you
feel this way, Chika.
No...
You are kind.
Don't try to cheer me up the way
you used to when we were young!
Was l like this since back then?
Yeah.
Hey, could we do it one last time?
Naoto, come...
l'm already soaked.
lt should go in right away.
Since l licked your baby juice...
...the back of my uterus
has been quivering.
So please hurry!
Naoto, yours is
reaching the back so easily.
But when it rubs against
the entrance, it's so good!
Naoto...
l, l...
l really...
...love you, Naoto!
l don't want to
separate from you, Naoto.
l want to stay as one forever...forever!
When l squeeze your body,
my breasts get squeezed too...
...it feels so good!
And my nipples get
squeezed and stimulated, so...
...it feels so good for me
l feel like l'm going to let it out.
No Naoto, don't rub my breasts.
lf you rub my breasts that much...
...l can't tell where l am
because it feels too good!
That feels so good!
No, l'm going to torture
yours by squeezing it!
N-No!
l'm going to drink the milk!
l'm going to drink the milk that
you squirt out like a little baby!
Miss Ayane.
Yes?
U-Um...
Aya...
l have some business to
talk about with Miss Yukishiro.
Oh, her?
She's out today with a cold.
Oh, really?
''l really like Naoto too,'' huh?
Aya is most likely the same too.
No, no, don't think like that!
Aya is your enemy! She's an
enemy you're supposed to hate!
lt would be easier if
l were able to think that way.
Then what was l supposed to do?
So what business
do you bring to me?
l'm in the position of getting
ready for the entrance exam.
So Aya, even if it's you,
l can't be hanging out too long.
l am...
Well...
lt's nothing with Naoto and me.
So you don't have to worry
about anything, okay?
Because...
...Chika, you're a student
preparing for the exams, right?
l thought l shouldn't make you
think about this too much.
So l thought l should
tell you as soon as l could.
Aya, are you okay with that?
What are you talking about?
l slept with Naoto.
He told me that you
are his girlfriend too.
Well, do you hate me?
Then don't just sit there.
Don't just sit there!
l'm sorry, Chika.
lt would have been better
if your confession were earlier.
But...but, Aya, are you okay with that?
l'm fine.
Because l know how you've felt
about Naoto since back then.
That's a lie!
lt's not a lie.
lf you say that l knew about your
feelings to Naoto back then too!
Look, you can't say anything!
W-What?
Then what are you telling me to do?
Yesterday, l totally knew from your
facial expression what you were thinking.
And if l went with you guys...
l would have been able to stop
the two of you from having sex.
Yes, so you say that
would have solved everything?
No, right?
That's...
l found out your feelings.
But my feelings are important too.
A-Aya?
What am l supposed to do?
Well that's...
lt's most likely l'm just the idiot, but...
How is it, Naoto? Feels good?
ls this your first time using this room?
There is no guy that can
deny the both of them like that.
But l have to give an answer.
lf l don't, l would be
no good as a human being.
Right?
Hey, Aya...
lt's kind of embarrassing here,
so let's go outside.
l'm the villain? That's impossible!
Okay Chika, let's talk
this over thoroughly.
Before involving Naoto
into this conversation...
...l think it's better to come
to a conclusion ourselves.
What is this?
Was Aya this kind of character?
Both of you, are you
sorry about what you did?
Yeah, she was this kind of person.
Chika, what's funny?
Well, l just thought that when you
were mad, you were always scary.
What do you mean by that?
l get it!
What?
That you really like Naoto too.
O-Of course l do...
l like him and it's not just that...
But l don't think this is a good thing.
lt's from Naoto.
Mine is from Naoto too.
Because l'm a no-good guy...
...l did something to
Chika and Miss Ayane...
...that will never be forgiven
regardless of how much l apologize.
l feel that l seriously need to face
and come to a conclusion about this.
So l want you to come to my room.
Hey, Aya...
What is it, Chika?
Naoto is trying to seriously face us.
That's right. We need to be prepared.
But if neither of us are chosen,
what will you do?
Even though Naoto looks like that,
he definitely has a strong sense of duty...
...so that is possible.
l'll be sad if l'm not chosen, but...
l don't want to see Naoto being
with another girl besides you.
lf that happens...
lf that happens?
Hey both of you, please come in...
F-First of all...
What is it?
l have to break up with Miss Ayane,
but l can't go out with Chika either.
l-l, you know, had sex with Chika.
That was because l'm a no-good guy.
Even saying that,
l don't have the option...
...of breaking up with Miss Ayane
and start going out with Chika.
So please forget about me!
So, Naoto, your decision is totally set?
Y-Yes, set like a stone...
You don't have space
to listen to our idea?
Of course!
N-No, l don't think l can
give an answer right away.
l mean it's very rude to give
those two this kind of attitude.
Plus, it's impossible
to choose one of them.
l've known both of them since
l was little and l like Chika's cute parts.
Plus, l like Miss Ayane's sexy parts.
Meaning, to say my feelings...
...l can't choose between you two.
No, no, not in that meaning.
ln the meaning of good faith...
Then, why don't you
just make it both of us?
Right, Aya?
T-That's right.
As an option, it's possible.
Both of you? That can't be possible...
Wait, what!
Both.
As l thought,
something like this isn't good.
lt's fine!
This is the best option that
the two of us came up with together.
Naoto, you just
need to keep on smiling.
l think this is the best way too.
How it used to be
since back in the day.
Look, even Aya is saying that.
But ethically...
Even though you're saying that,
you're about to come.
Right, Naoto?
Naoto, what's wrong?
l'm all talk.
Even though l said something big,
l came lavishly.
Man, you're still
saying something like that?
Naoto, you're not being a man.
You're okay with this?
Yeah!
You too, Miss Ayane?
Okay, the switch has been turned on!
This could pass as a dream.
This isn't a dream. lt's...
...reality.
The amount of precum
feels like it's special.
Next is your turn, Aya.
How is the mixture of
my saliva and Naoto's precum?
lt's delicious.
Aya, you are horrible!
You should tease
someone older than you.
Yes...
l came up with a good idea.
N-No...
L-Let's not do something like this.
But Chika said...right?
That's right, Naoto. lf you don't do it,
something horrible will happen.
That's what she said.
But...
N-No...
Aya, it seems so rough.
l'll lick it for you.
Wow, your clitoris
has become so big.
l'm going to pinch it.
No, no!
Don't pinch there!
Okay Aya, here we go.
Deeper...a little deeper...
lt's about to hit that really
good spot, right, Aya?
This is so good!
lt's hitting a really good spot.
My stomach!
lt's rubbing against the sidewalls.
lt's agonizing!
My stomach is really in agony!
No! l'm coming with anal!
lt's a zombie!
Chika, l'm going to
share the gift with you too.
What if l say l want to hold off on it...
You think something
like that is going to fly?
lt's rubbing the backside!
lt's rubbing the
backside of my uterus!
Chika, every time
your butt is being rammed...
...you are being filled with
urine and it's pouring out.
How cute.
Aya, don't say such
a perverted thing.
Because...because...
When Naoto scratches the wall,
that's the backside of my uterus.
l want to come!
My uterus wants to come,
and l can't hold it in anymore!
No!
l'm coming!
No, you have to come at
the same time Naoto ejaculates.
Okay? You can do it, Chika.
l'll do my best...
l'll do my best,
so please let me come fast!
Do it faster!
More! l, l...
l want to drink
your thick milk, Naoto!
You're going to milk
Naoto with your butt!
l-l'm going to come with my butt!