The first time...
I fell in love.
But that was...
An unusual love.
Is it wrong?
For me to fall in love with someone...
The student council president, Mikisaka Haruka-san.
She is so beautiful,
her grades are perfect,
and she excels at all sports.
She is the person I adore.
Good morning!
Have a good day, everyone!
Even though we are both girls, my feelings won't change.
And for the first time in my life, I wrote a love letter.
So annoying.
No way... she's reading it...
"At that moment, a flower of love sprouted in me."
My whole body shook, and my mind went blank.
Why? Why?
Such unskillful writing... idiotic.
You probably got some self-satisfaction writing it,
but you didn't think about how
I'd feel while reading, did you?
Haruka-san... why?
You say that you are in love with me, but that's a lie.
You are mistaking admiration for love.
That's not true!
I'm really in love with Haruka-san!
You're disgusting.
There's no way a girl would fall in love with a girl!
You've got to be seriously defective as human.
No!!
Stop it... No!
No... Please stop!
Don't tease... my boobs so much...
It's soft and sticks to my hand!
No!
What slutty boobs you have.
They're worth the teasing.
Please don't say something like that!
Woah, the nipples are getting hard nicely, too!
No! No more...
Such large nipples ready to be played with!
No more! It's embarrassing!
What? Are you wet already?
N-No!
Hmm? What's wrong? it's getting harder!
Don't rub it!
No...
You're dripping so much of love juices...
Such a slutty pussy.
That's not true!
It's just... disgusting!
That's... my clitoris... don't tease...
You're fingers are... deep inside... No more!
That's quite some squirting!
Please... Please wait...
It's... my first time...
Oh really?
Then, I'll be by your side for your
first experience with sex.
This is quite a plump pussy!
Hey hurry and put it in!
No!
She's nicely wet!
A penis... is all the way inside my... my pussy...
Please... slow... slow down...
Amazing boobs! They wobble as I thrust!
It's embarrassing...
It’s your first time doing fellatio too, right?
I'll teach you well.
Ha, so warm inside her mouth!
Her pussy has loosened up!
That's right, move your tongue inside
your mouth like licking a candy.
No... How did this happen?
Haruka-san, I loved you! I trusted you!
This is bad, I'm going to cum soon!
Be sure to cum outside.
Me too!
It’s coming out!
Cummingi
No... A man's semen is...
That felt great.
It's my turn now.
No!
Are we still going!?
C'nom!
Shake your hips more, it feels good right?
Too rough!
You're shaking that huge ass around...
Everyone is clinging tightly onto Miu-san...
Is it because she's got a body worth teasing?
Haruka-san, she's a true masochist!
Miu-san, is having sex while being watch that good?
No! That's... that's not it.. I... I'm not...
Wow! When she talks to Haruka-san... her
pussy squeezes real tight... amazing!
You're quite the masochist sow, aren't you?
Alright, I'm cumming!
Again... cumming again!
We re covering your body with our semen!
No! Don't! Don't!
That was quite the climax.
Miu-san, you've squirted so much.
From now, everyone will love you more and more, okay?
There is no way... such things will be forgiven.
Day after day, I was violated by the male students.
Down there... and my butt... over and over again.
But, the fear prevented me from
talking to anyone about it.
Haruka-san enjoyed herself as
she watched me being raped.
I never thought she was this kind of a person...
My feelings towards the president
changed from admiration to hate.
One day, I suddenly noticed changes in Haruka-san.
Love juices dripped from her crotch down her legs...
And the president's expressions were in trance...
So one day I followed president as she
walked alone without being noticed.
What is she doing at a place like this?
Haruka-san, please accept my love letter.
Good morning, President.
Good morning, everyone.
Uh, good morning...
The atmosphere is strange... is it just me?
Miu...
Be sure to come to the council meeting
today after sorting out all the files.
What's with that girl?
Such a nasty smile.
Is she trying to gross me out?
C'mon, c'mon!
Hurry up and strip and get naked!
Don't you know your position!?
It's Haruka-san that doesn't know, isn't it?
What do you mean..
No!
Hey... what are you doing!? Stop it!
Well you shouldn't want us to stop right, Haruka-san?
Woah, her thighs are so slippery, this is great!
This is disgusting!
I'll call for someone!
Sure you can call. But only if you want
more people to see you like this.
What are you saying? What did you do?
Why don't you ask yourself that?
No! Wait, what are you doing!?
Wow! Such erotic panties!
You were planning to masturbate watching
me being violated, right?
Stop it already!
Take your hand off!
Just rape this girl like usual!
If you do that, I'll forgive you...
What? You still think you're in charge!?
Stop... stop it, don't...
No!
Woah! Haruka-san's boobs that I've been dreaming of!
I can't hold back anymore!
Woah... right now I'm... having sex with Haruka-san!
Why is... this happening...
I won't let you say that you don't know about this...
What is... that?
Looks like you hid in the sports equipment room
and masturbated every time I was raped.
I wanted everyone to know, so
I uploaded it to the internet.
How, how dare you!
This is a love letter from me. Please accept it this time.
Hey, Haruka-san! Concentrate on my dick!
No, no...
Are you turned on, Haruka-san?
You're dripping slutty juices!
Woah, so she moans in such a cute voice! Amazing!
Haruka-san is so beautiful as she is loose and slutty...
You're... you're mad!
Haruka-san is the one that is mad.
You blackmail all the girls that confess to you,
and get off watching them being humiliated.
How do you know that?
You guys... you betrayed me!
We're not gonna be ordered around forever!
Woah, cumming! I always wanted to creampie
this prideful bitch of a president!
No, don't! Not inside, don't cum inside!
Haruka-san's butt... it's so soft and amazing...
You guys... you'll never be forgiven...
for something like this!
Your ass is great, too.
This softness... could it be that you
masturbate in your ass, too?
No... there's no way that I would do that!
It's well loosened already.
We should be able to have anal sex.
Like I thought, it's a soft, squishy anus!
A penis... in both my pussy and
my asshole... at the same time...
Feeling good from your butt? You're
so much more a pervert than me.
You really think... I'd feel it... from something like this!?
The Haruka-san pretending to be strong, is very cute!
You actually feel good, don't you?
You actually wanted to be forcefully raped, don't you?
You thought of yourself as you watched
me being violated, right?
No... that's not...
Haruka-san... you're so gross.
C'mon, the perverted president who feels it from her ass.
Clean up my dick, too.
What's wrong? You stopped struggling suddenly.
Does that mean you've become honest?
You've finally accepted your true self!
C'mon, c'mon, Haruka-san! This is
the rape you've always wanted!
N-No!
No!
Woah, your pussy is squeezing really tightly!
Are you cumming? Cum!
Both my pussy and my butt are being violated by dicks...
This is so good!
C'mon, cum, bitch president!
Cumming, cumming!
Cum!
Wow... Amazing, the prez is so erotic!
Cumming so hard with such an ahegao.
But it's not the end yet.
This time...
Oppa Infinity
Amazing! The prez's pussy feels so good!
Amazing!
I came so much.
What does it feel like?
It must be horrible to become a plaything for
the guys, and be covered in dirty semen.
But, I was in much, much more pain.
They often say that love and hate are
the same thing, turns out it was true.
Once you're used to it, it's quite good.
Wanna try it, too?
Haruka-san has become a dump for the guys lust,
a miserable woman only for disgusting semen!
You're a cumdump!
Um...
I... um...
I've always... always had a crush on Haruka-san...
Well then, your next partner is this guy.
You pair of pigs enjoy yourselves.
It's great you came.
I'll squeeze out the stored semen from your virgin balls.
Haruka-san?
Amazing... you're pre-cum is overflowing...
What a lewd dick...
Haruka-san!
You want to have sex with me already?
But no... first you have to shoot lots of your
virgin juice into my perverted mouth!
Woah!
Amazing... there's so much...
Such a bitter stink...
The muscles are so stiff, too!
Haruka-san is... sucking my dick!
Haruka-san's fellatio is... so warm...
wrapping around... so wet...
I'm gonna... gonna cumm!
Woah... cumming, again! Cumming
more into your mouth pussy!
You came so much! It was so thick and tasty!
Well then, stick it in here this time,
and let's feel even better!
Yes! More! Thrust your dick more!
What's with this!?
She's being humiliated... her body and
her heart both violated... and yet...
If this goes on, I can't calm my anger or hate!
Everyone, thank you for gathering here.
I'm the student council president, Mikisaka Haruka.
As congratulations for the baseball
club winning the provincial league,
I'll become everyone's sex slave.
This is a special service today, please us me well.
What, what is this?
What is happening!?
Really!? We can really fuck!?
Mr. Captain, your crotch is already bulging.
Would Captain please take me to the National
League with your hard and sturdy bat?
It's fine if everyone messes me up!
Woah! Haruka-san!
Captain! No fair to leave us out!
Woah, we're doing it! It's happening!
Haruka-san is right in front of me!
Thank you so much!
Everyone out of the way! As captain I...
What are you talking about!? In the
order of batting, I should go!
What do you say!?
With this, Haruka-san will lose her position of president,
and be looked down upon by everyone. In your face!
With this, my revenge...
H-huh?
Why? Why am I... crying?
Didn't I want this ending for Haruka-san?
No! I didn't wish for such an ending!
It shouldn't have been like this...
I just wanted to play a small prank on Haruka-san...
Haruka-san is going somewhere I don't
know... somewhere far away!
There's no way I want that!
Haruka-san is the president admired by everyone, right?
I finally, I finally know now.
The lonely one... the one that was
singled out... it was always me.
What's wrong, Miu?
Don't you want to feel good together?
I... I love you, Haruka-san!
I want to say good mornings... and study together...
and do student council work together again!
I want to feel Haruka-san nearby just like before!
I know I can't bring back anything
saying stuff like this now... but I...
It's fine now, Miu.
I won't go anywhere. Because, thanks to Miu,
I've having such wonderful experiences.
Haruka-san...
Miu-san is erotic with those huge boobs, too!
I'm having sex with Haruka-san!
More... thrust your penis more!
This is bad... group sex is so exciting!
This is so good!
Prez's pussy feels really good!
I can't wait! Hurry and switch!
Wait up, I'm not done yet!
Haruka-san, please take care of me!
Haruka-san your fellatio face is too erotic!
Woah! It's so warm inside your mouth!
Titty fuck feels so good!
My whole body is catching the stink of semen!
Thrust your penis lots and then spurt onto my face!
Everyone, please spurt lots of semen onto my slutty face!
I can't... Cumming!
Prez, please face this way.
So warm...
My face is decorated... with everyone's semen...
This could really become a habit...
My entire face is soaked with such a full, slutty smell...
It's so warm and comfty...
Geez, Miu...
Haruka-san...
It feels good...
C'mon, everyone, you can use my butt, too!
Two dicks are thrusting inside me!
Amazing! Both the pussy and the
ass are squeezing on dick!
I... I'm going to cum!
Cumming! Together! I want to
cum together with Haruka-san!
This is bad... my hips won't stop!
Haruka-san, your pussy is pulsing.
We'll cum too when everyone cums!
Let's all cum together!
Cumming, cumming!
No, I... together with Haruka-san!
Here we go!
Cumming!
Amazing, that was great!
I came three times.
Both Haruka-san and Miu-chan were too erotic!
Miu... you will become the next student council president.
Haruka-san... I'm so happy... really...
Miu, congratulations!
Congratulations!
A present to the new president.
Thank you, Haruka-san. I'm so happy!
The student council president, Sudou Miu.
Will you accept my love letter?