Who is it?
We, the Trident Foundation,
control all the back alleys.
But our organization
is going down the drain because our new
drug, D-99X,
is being so easily seized by someone.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
So if you are saying
it is all your fault,
then take your responsibility,
right here, right now!
Boss!!!
Rei-Lan has entered
in today's Super Grapple.
Interesting... Make sure
the opponent is Machine Gun Joe.
How long you going to let
that criminal remain at-large?
I've waited for four years.
It would be such a waste if
I don't enjoy it, at least a little.
Don't you think so, Ryu?
Okay fight fans,
let's-get-ready-to-rumble!
Now for today's featured bout:
This is
a Super Grapple Open-Class Battle!
One Orchid has bloomed
in Super Grapple...
She has had nine fights,
she has had
nine wins, she has had nine KO's!
Our undefeated challenger,
The Genocide Queen, Rei-Lan!!!
Our greatest champion,
belonging to the Trident camp.
The one! The only!
Machine Gun Joe!!
The odds have gone up.
How much?
It's Joe vs. Rei-Lan
and the odds are...
1:36, 1:22, 1:15, 1:30, 1:125,
all in favor of Machine Gun Joe.
Let's make it an even bigger spread.
Huh? You think Rei-Lan's going to win,
not Joe, Boss?
Of course.
I'm going to take care of you,
little kitty cat.
Meatball!
Ah, she's deceptively quick.
She blocked my kick?!
You're so slow!
This is how you snap a kick!
The winner... Rei-Lan!
Tojo!!
Rei-Lan wins
by a knockout in 30 seconds.
– The odds on this fight
were 36-1 against her.
Boss.
Read it.
I am in possession of D-99X.
Come to airport runway 2, at 2:00 AM,
tomorrow morning.
Yours, Orchid Emblem.
I've been waiting
for your return for four
years,
believing in the Rising Dragon Tattoo.
Congratulations, Rei-Lan.
You've won ten in-a-row, Rei-Lan.
I knew you were going to win!
Thank you Emi.
What's this?
Today's victory purse.
Take it.
No, Rei-Lan, I cannot take
such a big amount of money.
Don't worry.
It's my way of saying "thank you"
for letting me stay in your room.
No, no,
it's I that should be thanking you.
I would have been sold to a pimp if
you had not rescued me
from those punks...
So...
Okay, then why don't you consider
that money to be for our living costs.
Rei-Lan... Rei-Lan...
I like you.
I like you Rei-Lan.
Wait... Emi...
This is the least I can do for you.
You naughty girl.
Don't... Emi...
Don't do that!
Stop it Emi...
Emi. Not there...
Leave it with me.
Emi, it feels so good...
Please, mine too.
So good...
It's more powerful than cocaine
and it requires a
smaller dosage
and the high lasts twice as long.
If you take a really big hit
this drug can bring out
a person's dark-side,
turning him into a murderer.
Interpol is desperately seeking
the source.
D-99X, the phantom
which has never been seized.
It sounds scary,
why don't you report it to the police.
It's no use,
there are a lot of Mafia operatives
stationed in the Blue City police force.
Anyway, this is the bait,
this is how
I will reel in Trident's boss, Tojo.
Are you going to kill that bastard?
Yes, tonight.
You are putting yourself in danger.
Even if you are so strong,
you can't defeat him.
Let's runaway together,
I'll go anywhere in the world with you.
I'll follow you anywhere.
I'm sorry,
but this has been the driving
force in my life
for the past four years.
No, I can't go anywhere
until I've defeated Tojo.
Good-bye, Emi.
Rei-Lan, I'm really worried about you.
Who is it? Rei-Lan?
It's Tojo I cannot forget,
even if I wanted to...
My life has been ruined because of him.
There is a dealer and three others.
Rei-Lan is coming with me.
Kato and Ryker,
you cover the back door.
Okay.
We are in position.
We are ready, Doug.
Doug?
What happened to you, Doug?
You seem very strange, today.
It's been a difficult investigation.
Rei-Lan, once this over, let's take
a vacation, just the two of us, okay?
Да.
Okay, we're going to break in.
Let's go Rei-Lan.
As I said, if you want to continue
doing business with us,
you'll have to bring in another million,
by tomorrow.
Okay.
Okay. We're leaving now.
Freeze! D.E.A.
Oh? Drug Enforcement Agency's
Special Services.
You are under-arrest.
The charge is "drug dealing."
Shit!
Die!
This is the end for you, Tojo.
The end?
You mean, the end... of you!
Oh shit!
Doug!
Pull yourself together, Doug.
As I expected,
you're a fine-looking piece of meat.
What shapely breasts you have.
We're going to bring those two back.
This is going to be interesting.
Where's Doug?
What's this?
Are you awake now?
So, D.E.A.'s expert, Miss Rei-Lan.
My name is Tojo.
I am the owner of this ship.
What are you going to do with me?
Where's Doug?
What has happened to Doug?
Are you worried about your boyfriend?
I'm going to let you see him?
But before that... Start it!
What are you going to do?
Stop it!
Don't come near me! No!
No! Stop it!
Please... No!
Stop it!
No! Stop it!
Please, stop it!
So you are highly sensitive sexually?
So, were you trained by that guy?
Please, Mr. Tojo.
If you go on, I...
I mean...
So what's going to happen
if it goes on any further...
Please stop doing this... Stop...
Yes, then why is your pussy
quivering with desire?
It's about time.
Admit it, you want this!
If you want it, you're going
to have to clean it with your mouth.
But...
What's the matter, don't you want it?
Suck on it. Quickly!
Oh, yes, that's good.
That's very good.
Okay, now open it!
Okay, Rei-Lan, now say,
"Please stick it in."
Aren't you sucking it
because you want me to stick it in you?
Yes, please stick it in.
And plunge it all around.
Except...
It's my first time, so...
What?
You're a virgin?
Yes.
Ah-h... I see.
He's such a fool.
He hasn't even done her.
Okay, well I'm going to pop-her-cherry!
Rei-Lan! Rei-Lan!
Doug?
So what did you think
after watching all of this, Doug?
Did you even know she is a virgin?
Don't look at me Doug.
Please, don't look.
Even if you look-away, you can still
hear your girlfriend's moans.
You know Doug,
Rei-Lan's tits feel so fine.
What's going on down here?
She sounds good, doesn't she, Doug?
Rei-Lan, what don't you tell Doug
what you really want.
I'm sorry, Doug. I'm sorry.
But I can't take it anymore.
Stop...
Oh what's the matter, Rei-Lan?
Let him hear.
I want you to stick it in.
Please!
With this I want you
to fuck every inch of me.
And you want me more than Doug?
Yes, yes. I want yours,
I want yours more than Doug's...
Yes, yes, I want you to make
me a woman. I want your penis.
Do you hear this Doug?
Okay, I'll make you a woman.
Oh, please, please...
Stick it in quickly. Oh, please!
But before that,
you tell him to watch it.
You tell him to watch
the moment you become a woman.
What's the matter?
Don't you want mine more than his?
Doug, please watch me.
Please watch me, Doug.
Please watch the moment
I become a woman.
Please watch me making love to him,
Doug...
I'm going to be held by him...
I'm going to make love to him...
Why don't you watch her? Why don't you
watch your girlfriend being raped?
Watch carefully, Doug.
Please give it to me...
It feels so good! It feels great!
Hey, Doug.
Rei-Lan's got a tight pussy.
And she squeezes so good.
You're losing it
in front of your boyfriend,
don't you feel embarrassed, Rei-Lan.
Embarrass me more.
Fuck me more. It's incredible.
Oh my God.
Fuck me. Fuck me more...
You're a natural Rei-Lan. You feel
so good, and you squeeze me so tightly.
You make my pussy feel so good.
How does mine feel?
It feels so good. It's so hard...
It's so big. Keep plunging!
Move it around in my pussy...
Let Doug hear that...
Doug, watch it... It's so hard...
It's so big... It's inside my pussy.
Oh, Doug, watch it go in and out
of my pussy... Watch it! Watch it!
Look, look! He's got an erection from
watching his girlfriend being raped.
Why? Wow!
It's unbelievable!
Mr. Tojo, he's got a hard-on
watching his girlfriend being raped.
Why not?
It feels so good!
Harder! Faster! Faster!
Oh-h-h... that's the spot.
You're hitting the spot.
It feels so good. So good...
Okay, well,
I'm going to blast inside you.
Yes, yes... Oh-h-h.
Cum! Cum! Cum inside me!
Doug, I made your girlfriend a woman,
without much resistance.
You missed your opportunity, Doug?
Do you feel vexed?
But this is my organization's way
of punishment.
By the way, I do have one thing
to thank you for...
That you have never done her!
Good-bye, Doug.
Tojo?
What's the matter?
Where's Doug?
What have you done to Doug?
I let him go. He's probably returned
to the D.E.A. By now.
Take off your clothes, Rei-Lan.
Are you going to shame me again?
No, we are going to make love.
But you had me bound
so I couldn't resist your rape.
Yes,
but I gave you life's highest pleasure.
But you didn't have to do that
in front of Doug.
Take off your clothes, Rei-Lan. Now!
That's good... You are my woman.
Okay.
Deeper! Deeper!
I envy Rei-Lan.
She's getting it everyday...
Saki, forget about it.
Face it, we're just seen by Mr. Tojo
as his pets, after all.
Day and night he wanted me.
He did not allow me to wear clothes.
Even though I was held by him so much, I found myself wanting him more.
I found such great pleasure
to-flesh with him.
I felt such great pleasure
with his penis inside of me.
It's so good. Fuck me.
Rei-Lan is so beautiful,
I want her to sleep with me, too.
What are you talking about?
You have me, don't you?
Yes, I'm just being stupid.
Mr. Tojo, High Priest Chin has arrived.
I have not seen you for awhile, Tojo.
Welcome High Priest.
So you found the one?
You found the one worthy
of the legendary Dragon Tattoo?
Yes. It's the woman
I want to have tattooed for me.
Oh, this one.
Oh, this one has such beautiful skin;
and the muscle tone...
It's a miracle, she's so perfect.
On top of it,
she was a virgin just two weeks ago.
Ideal. I have no complaints.
Very good! I'm going to tattoo her.
I will tattoo her with the dragon,
the legendary Dragon Tattoo.
However, this tattoo
can only be inscribed on a woman
while she is engaged
in the act of sexual intercourse.
The inscription will take
three days and three nights,
and you must have intercourse
continuously.
Can you do it?
Are you ready, Rei-Lan?
I am!
This is...
Due to the sharpness of the needle, the
woman will squeeze the man so tightly,
it will seem as if he is being wrapped
in a vice by her.
Also, the shape of the male lover will
be put into the shape of the tattoo.
Rising pleasure will continue like
the ascension of the Rising Dragon.
However, once the act is completed,
neither the man, nor the woman
will ever again be able to reach ecstasy
without being with the other.
That is the legend
of the Rising Dragon Tattoo.
The only thing left for me to do is to
complete the eye-pupil of the dragon.
The two of you can cum now.
Okay, Rei-Lan.
I'm going to cum inside you.
Oh please cum inside me.
Please! Oh, more! More!
The dragon, by acquiring male sperm,
is on its way to heaven.
Simply great!
I've never seen a woman burn through
the Rising Dragon Tattoo like this.
The dragons are calling each other.
Thank you, Priest.
No, it is I that must thank you.
You did a great job in finding
such a woman. I must thank you.
Miss Rei-Lan! Miss Rei-Lan!
Miss Rei-Lan!
You are troubling me.
You were told by Mr. Tojo
not to go in here.
But this place has bothered me
for a long time.
But we will be in trouble if something
happens while Mr. Tojo is away.
Go back to your room, please.
Wait a minute.
What's that?
Doug?
Don't! Don't Miss Rei-Lan.
Let go! Let go!
Don't Miss Rei-Lan.
Just go back to your room, please.
Let me go!
Doug!
Doug, what have they done?
Oh, I let him go.
He must be back with D.E.A. By now.
I didn't know, Doug!
No. NO!!!
I didn't remember how I ran away,
but all I wanted to do was run away
from that place, that ship.
I just couldn't forgive myself
for giving my heart and body to Tojo.
It hurt me more
than it hurt Doug to be killed.
I am not going to go back.
Everything is going to be over tonight.
You are... Ryu!
Well, I've come here
to extract my revenge against Tojo.
I will play with you
until The Boss comes.
Don't be silly. Ugh!
Wow, he's strong. But after all,
he is Super Grapple's strongest man.
Welcome back, Boss.
I have a gift for you.
She's so cute.
Yeah, but she's a little dirty though.
Well, we'll bathe her and make her up.
She'll look fine...
Well, this is the first opponent that is
actually causing me to break a sweat.
It's a damn shame it's woman.
What am I going to do?
I'm losing right now.
Rei-Lan, you have become so strong
over the past four years,
and you have become
even more beautiful.
Well, it's either...
"Kill! Or be killed!"
Tojo!
You've even defeated Ryu.
That's all right.
You've come back to me.
In order to kill you!
I am the man who made you a woman.
You can't kill the man
who introduced you to female ecstasy.
I finally arrived here, yet...
You just pretend to be strong.
Oh, she's so good.
She's really good.
She's really good at it.
I can't take it any more.
Please stop.
Mina, she seems to like it.
Do her more!
Mistress Saki, Mistress Saki...
Oh, her pussy is squirting.
She's so cute. She's so horny!
I'm so sorry. But it felt so good!
Don't worry...
Where is it?
I was defeated?
You are awake, Rei-Lan.
Tojo!
You're now revitalized after sleeping
for three days and three nights.
Shut up!
What, do you hate me?
Yes, I hate you!
You have taken everything away from me.
You killed Doug, you toyed with me,
you must have had fun!
Oh, that guy... That guy was one of my
spies sent in to infiltrate the D.E.A.
That's a lie!
I'm not going to be deceived.
Then do you remember this?
That is!!!
This is my organization's
customized device.
It has a built-in transmitter.
I knew your every move.
Doug reported everything back to me.
Then why did you kill him?
It was punishment.
He had become a double-agent.
It's one of the Golden Rules:
The only punishment for betrayal
is death.
Rei-Lan, once this over,
let's take a vacation together, okay?
Oh look, he's got an erection
watching his girlfriend being raped.
Oh, Doug! Watch me, Doug!
I cannot believe it.
I cannot believe anything, anymore.
Don't expect me to be a good guy.
After all, I am a Mafia boss!
But I am the only one worthy
of loving you.
I told you, you are mine!
What have I been doing
for the past four years?
With how many men did you sleep
during that time?
My body wanted only you.
What about your heart?
My heart too.
I've wanted you from my heart.
The reason I came here, probably,
was to confirm my love for you.
Have you confirmed.
Yes.
You are mine, yes?
I am yours.
I've always believed
in the Rising Dragon Tattoo.
You don't know how long I've waited
for this day.
Touch me. Touch my body.
Confirm your belief. Touch me.
Touch me more.
Touch me there. Yes!
It's already so big
How do you feel, Rei-Lan?
Oh yes. You can cum in my mouth.
Let me swallow your sperm.
Okay, I'm going to explode!
Does it taste good?
Ah, yes. It tastes so good.
Now stick it in my pussy.
Stick it in! Stir it around my pussy!
Please!
It feels so good!
Tojo! Tojo! Please cum again.
I want to be yours.
I want all my body to be yours!
О, нет!
I will show you something good.
Rei-Lan?
That's right.
She came back to us, like before.
That's right, it's inside me.
Stir it around more!
Онэ-сама!
You know, Emi,
we have to do it once more.
Tojo, it feels so good!
So how do I taste after four years...
It tastes so good...
And my pussy... Give me more!
Fuck me more! Fuck me!
Rei-Lan it feels so good,
it feels so good.
Introducing, the challenger,
Dynamite Bob.
As you know, he is the big brother
of Machine Gun Joe.
Shall we go, Rei-Lan?
Yes. Boss.
Miss Rei-Lan.
Good luck!
That's not fair, Emi.
No favoritism or you will be punished.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Our undefeated, female champion,
Rei-Lan!