I kinda ran away from home...
Let me stay at your place.
Also, did you send Daddy the present?
Make sure it says that it's from me, 'kay?
God damn it, this girl is always so...
Hey there!
Welcome back from work, Uncle!
Rinka, you know what...
Just cut it out already.
You're always just randomly inviting yourself over here.
I have my own life, you know...
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry.
Anyway, let me in already! I'm beat!
Thanks for having me!
Hey, take your shoes off!
Wash your hands before going in...
Get out! That's my room!
Geez, can't you just wait for one second?!
Original work: Yakisaba Teishoku
The reason I rape my niece
First day: The Day He Acquired Her
First day:
The day he acquired her.
So, like, Daddy was getting on my case
for getting home just a little bit late.
But it's not like I'm a little kid or something!
My brother's just worried about you.
You're his cute little daughter after all.
Wow.
Cute? Compliment me much?
And you're not a kid, right?
Cover yourself up a little... have a little shame!
Hmph. Why should I care?
For crying out loud.
I've always thought of her as a little kid,
but she's already got a woman's body.
My brother's fiance, Haruka-san,
was his girlfriend from back in his schooldays.
She came to our house fairly often,
so I found myself drawn to her.
But, I was still just a kid back then.
Just thinking back to that time makes me so pissed.
Haruka-san!
I've loved you more than my stupid
brother has ever loved you!
Why are you with him?!
Hey, Uncle, are you listening?
I'm thirsty. Can you bring me something?
Oh, clothes too.
I don't have a change of clothes.
Fine, fine.
Just stay put.
Don't order me around with
that face... with Haruka-san's face!
Do I even have clothes that she can wear?
Oops.
I-Isn't this...
This is something I got during
one of my foreign business trips.
It's an aphrodisiac.
It was an incredibly powerful aphrodisiac
in small doses, but with more exposure,
there's a risk of turning that innocuous
sexual arousal into full blown stupor.
I got it from a friend as a joke, but I saw what it could do
firsthand and I hid it away, scared of what it could do.
Hey, wait a second, you crazy bastard.
You want to use this on Rinka?!
Get real.
She's my niece and I've known her since she was a baby!
I know she's gotten a little full of herself lately, but...
But... she's getting even closer to...
Looking like Haruka-san.
I see. So this is what it feels like
to be drowning in temptation.
Hey, your clothes.
Oh, and this...
Juice for you.
Thank you.
Oh, this is my favorite!
You know me so well!
Huh? Is it hot in here?
Hey, Rinka, do you remember?
I used to hold you in my arms just like this.
What?
I'm not a kid anymore!
That's true.
You have a woman's body now.
What?!
U-Uncle?! Sto...
You got so wet, so easily.
Do you play with yourself a lot?
You really grew up!
But I guess these are still not grown up yet.
Why should you be the only one feeling good?
Come on, do me good too!
Sto...
Rinka! You're the spitting image
of Haruka-san back in the day!
It feels like I'm doing her!
That feels great, Rinka!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum right in your mouth!
Hey, really?
Don't faint already!
We're going to do something
even better, so let's go to my bed.
Rinka, take a look. You know what that is?
That's Daddy and... Mommy?
Why... Why do you...
Why do I have this video?
It's thanks to your "present" to Daddy.
There's a camera in here.
He was so happy when he received this "from you".
He put it right next to his bed!
Thanks to that, I get to watch videos of
Haruka-san having sex whenever I want!
Daddy...
Huh?! You're getting off from watching your dad?!
Oh is this one of those Electra complexes?
You're a total pervert!
Well, whatever.
The woman you're seeing right now,
was supposed to be mine!
But now she's unobtainable.
So now, you're all I have left.
I'm going to give you the same thing she's getting.
N-No! I don't want to!
N-No! It hurts!
Stop! Uncle!
Don't make a face like that!
It just turns me on so much more!
No! No!
I don't want this!
Uncle! Stop!
Daddy! Save me!
Look at the screen.
Look at how your Daddy's moving his hips.
Who's he fucking right now?
Who's fucking you from behind right now?
Daddy... Daddy!
I'm having sex with Daddy!
Daddy!
I love you!
It's seriously like I'm fucking Haruka-san!
Okay, Haruka, I'm cumming!
Haruka!
Wait, no! No!
Daddy... Daddy...
After that, I kept fucking Rinka through the night.
Daddy! It feels so good!
Daddy! More! More!
There's so much of you inside me, Daddy!
It feels so good!
So good!
After a while, the aphrodisiac wore off.
I think we'll be able to do
even more fun things next time.
Huh? Yesterday, I...
That's right, I was raped by...
Hey.
Finally awake, Rinka?
Last night was intense, huh?
Oh shit, I came that much?
Yeah, you're definitely pregnant now.
Pregnant?
Oh, now that I think about it, I might still have those,
what do you call them... morning-after pills?
The ones that if you take them
within three days of doing the deed,
the chance of you getting pregnant goes down massively.
Are you serious?
Uncle, please!
You know what you have to do if you want them, right?
Please give the pills to me.
You can do whatever you want to my body.
Looks like we're gonna have
a fun weekend together, huh, Rinka?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editing: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч