I put my bratty niece in her place with her body.
It'd be a shame to end things here, though.
Let's keep the fun times rolling.
Now then, what should we do today?
Original work: Yakisaba Teishoku
The reason I rape my niece
Second Day: The Day He Played with Her
Good morning. This is the national news.
First, the traffic.
There is a traffic buildup due to a chain
of cars colliding with one another.
Oh, that looks good on you.
Wh-Why do you even have this uniform?
Oh, it's just something one of my exes left behind forever ago.
She said I could keep it.
Pretty cute, isn't it?
Y-Yeah, it is...
But still, it's kinda weird for a guy to have a girl's uniform.
You'll be wearing that all day.
Why do you get to decide that?
What're you going to make me do?
Well, I do have some ulterior motives...
Look, they're already at it, first thing in the morning.
I'll make you feel good too.
N-No! I don't want to do anything like yesterday!
Don't think you can fool me with those eyes of yours.
Only good girls get the pill.
Now shut the fuck up if you don't wanna get knocked up.
I-It hurts! It hurts so much!
Shut up.
If you don't want it to hurt, then get wet!
I can't...
It hurts! It hurts!
Please stop!
It's because you're not that experienced yet.
At least you're nice and tight.
I'm begging you...
It really hurts!
No!
Stop!
You just keep blabbering on and on. Do you ever shut up?
Be quiet for a second.
U-Uncle, please...
Damn, you're even tighter now!
I've learned something new about you!
That's good! Get tighter!
Yeah, this tightness is the best!
I'm cumming!
Damn, you look like you're in pain.
I'll make you feel better.
Uncle...
I'm...
No! Don't!
Stop!
You're more sensitive than you were yesterday.
Looks like you're getting used to the aphrodisiac.
No, I don't feel anything!
It doesn't feel good at all!
You're not convincing anyone with all that moaning.
Just be honest with yourself.
No! Don't put in in anymore!
Don't move it!
No! I don't like this!
Come on, it feels good, doesn't it?
Show me how good it feels!
No!
Daddy... Daddy's having sex...
Daddy and I are both having sex!
Daddy! Daddy!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Oh? I'm cumming too!
Daddy, I'm cumming!
Daddy...
Now then, how about some breakfast?
Clean this all up, okay?
Okay...
C-Coming!
I'll be right there!
Thank you for waiting...
Th-Thank you for the delivery.
Let me get some money...
S-Sorry, please wait just a little.
U-Um...
I see. So fingering you isn't enough, huh?
What am I going to do with you, Rinka?
Uncle?
What are you doing?
N-No, that's...
It's making me feel weird!
You're already this wet from your first anal beads?
I'm proud of you, Rinka.
Or maybe this isn't your first time?
You're really hanging in there.
Here's your reward.
Sorry, I'll give you the money now.
Sorry to play with you like that.
I'll put it in now.
N-No! Not now!
Stop! He's gonna find out!
Not here!
Are you listening?
Don't worry, he already found out. See?
Sorry, this girl's a bit of a freak.
She'll suck your dick, so just forgot this ever happened, okay?
R-Really?
Huh? Are you serious?
How does it feel?
Does it feel good?
Attagirl.
I'm gonna record every second of you
sucking off a random stranger.
C'mon, you gotta do better than that,
you fucking little slut.
Or else you won't get that tasty cum you love to guzzle.
No! I don't want it. I don't want it at all!
So good... Damn, I can't hold back any longer!
My pussy can't take anymore!
Take it out!
I'm gonna blow my load.
Take every last drop inside you.
I'm cumming too!
Good job, Rinka. You're not a kid anymore.
You're a full-grown slut.
No more!
Let me go!
Don't you want the pill?
Now be a good girl and listen to what I say.
translation: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
edit: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч