I taught my cheeky niece a lesson using her body.
But her body is just too good
that I can't just let it end here.
There's still a long way for me to enjoy this.
Well then, I wonder what should I do today?
Ore ga Mei Kanojo wo Okasu Wake
That's (the reason) Why I'm Going To Rape my niece Her
Original Work : Yakisaba Teishoku
Original Animation
Day 2: The Day He Toyed with Her
The second day: the day he toyed with her.
Good morning! Here is the nationwide news.
Let's start with the news about traffic.
Witnesses are giving statements about
the pileup caused by reckless driving.
Oh... You look good in those.
U-Uncle... What's with these clothes?
Hmm? Ah...
My ex used to own those but gave them to me
saying she doesn't need them anymore.
Aren't they cute?
I-I see that they're cute.
But it's weird for a man to own girls' clothes.
You're going to spend the rest
of the day wearing those, okay?
Huh?
Don't just decide things on your own!
What are you planning to do, making me wear these?
Well, of course! You're not just
wearing those for nothing.
Take a look.
It's still morning but those two are already at it.
You should also make yourself feel good like them.
N-No!
I don't want to do anything like that from yesterday!
You can't fool me with those eyes!
If you won't listen to me,
then there's no pill for you.
Shut up and get raped if you
don't want to have a child!
O-Ouch... It hurts!
You're annoying!
Get yourself wet now if you don't want it to hurt!
I-I can't just do that even if I wanted to!
It hurts, it hurts!
No... Stop!
It's because you just lost your virginity yesterday.
Your tightness is great, Rinka!
I'm begging you!
It really hurts!
No—!
Stop this already!
You just keep on running your mouth.
You're really pissing me off!
Won't you shut it up a little!
U-Uncle... You're kidding...
This is amazing, Rinka! You're insides
are way tighter than before!
This is a new discovery!
That's good... Come on, squeeze me tighter!
This is it, this tightness is the best!
I'm coming... I'm coming, I'm coming!
Oh... Looks like it was excruciating for you.
I'll make you feel better now, okay?
Uncle... that thing again...
No, no way... Stop that!
You're more sensitive than yesterday.
Have your body gotten used to the aphrodisiac?
No... I'm not feeling it!
This doesn't make me feel good!
Your don't sound convincing
when you moan like that.
Just admit that you feel good.
No, No! Don't put it inside me anymore! Don't move!
No, don't! I really don't want this!
Hey, hey, come on! Aren't you feeling good?
I'll let you feel even better!
No!
Papa is... papa is having sex!
Me too... I'm having sex with papa!
Papa, papa! I'm coming!
I'm coming too!
Papa, I'm coming—!
Papa is...
Well then, we should have a breakfast.
Make sure to clean that up.
O-Okay...
Y-Yes!
Just a moment, please!
Oh, thanks for the purchase! Sorry for...
...waiting.
Y-You're welcome....
I'll just get the payment...
S-Sorry... Please wait a moment.
U-Umm... well...
I see, my fingers aren't enough for you.
Jeez... you're such a helpless slut, Rinka.
Uncle... What are you doing?
Not that! It's gonna make me turn weird!
To get off this much from your first anal play...
Just as I expected from you, Rinka!
Or was it because you're usually
teasing yourself down here?
Aren't you hanging in there?
Here's your reward then.
I'm sorry...
I'm gonna get the money now...
I'm sorry for teasing you, Rinka.
I'm now going to shove it inside you, okay?
N-No way... Not now!
No... Uncle, we'll get seen!
We can't do it here!
Listen to me, uncle!
Don't worry, we have already been seen. Look.
H-Huh?!
Oh... I'm sorry. This girl is actually a pervert.
She'll make you feel good down there too
so can we just keep this to ourselves?
S-Sounds good to me...
Eh? No way!
How is it?
Does it feel good?
That's good, Rinka!
I'll make sure to record you
suddenly sucking a stranger's cock!
Hey, come on. Make sure to do a proper job,
Rinka-chan the pervert.
You're going to be rewarded
with the sperm that you love!
No... I can't take this much!
This feels good... I can't hold it in any longer!
Wait... Stop moving!
No... Stop moving!
Here I go... I'm coming, I'm coming!
Make sure to catch all of it without spilling any!
I'm coming too!
Here you go...
That was great, Rinka!
You sure aren't a kid anymore!
You're a full-fledged pervert!
I don't want this anymore...
Spare me already!
Don't you want the pill anymore?
Just shut up and do as I say.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization