I made my brat of a niece understand with her body.
But it'd be a shame to end things here.
Let's keep the fun times rolling.
Now, what should I do to you today?
Original Work: Yakisaba Teishoku
Day three.
Third Day: The Day She Closed Her Heart
The reason I rape my niece
The day she closed her heart.
Oji-san, I'm at my limit...
I wonder what the neighbors will
think of you if you pee yourself here.
You're a smart girl, Rinka. You should know.
You're going to wear these for the entire day.
D-Do you really think that scares me?
That's nothing!
Oh? I'm impressed.
Then how about we go for a walk
while you're wearing these?
Wha...
Oh, and starting now, you can't use the bathroom.
You're a big girl now, Rinka.
You wouldn't pee yourself, would you?
Y-You pervert!
Watch how you talk to me.
Or maybe you don't need the pills?
Come on, hurry it up.
I will! Just turn it down a little!
Please!
You must be tired.
Let's take a break.
Oh? Rinka-chan...
You can't even hold your pee in?
Poor girl. Come on, up.
Why are you laughing?!
Forget what happened!
I don't think I can forget that.
Take off your panties.
Not out there.
Do it right here.
Huh?!
I'm going to drill in some exercises
so that you'll never fail again like that.
I'll even record it for you.
C-Cut the crap! Why would I do that?!
Speaking of recordings... look at what I have.
What'll happen if this gets uploaded?
Th-That's not fair!
This is a video. Let me get a shot of those dirty panties.
Make sure you say who you are and how this happened.
Oh, and don't forget to smile.
I'm Ooki Rinka.
My uncle didn't let me use the bathroom...
Try again!
I was trying to hold in my pee, and I...
I couldn't hold it in.
S-So I peed myself!
Do you even know what you're doing right now?
You just smiled into the camera, pantieless,
while showing your dirty panties to the camera!
Is it normal for people to go so far just for some pills?
You're such a pervert, Rinka.
But let's be real, pee's not the only thing
dripping down your legs, is it?
N-No, this isn't...
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for making you wait.
Well since that hole's occupied, the only other option is...
N-No! Don't!
Stop! I'm gonna break! I'm gonna break!
Come on, the camera's rolling.
Give me your best smile, Rinka!
More! Just let it happen! Come on!
No! Stop!
I'm really gonna break!
What? This isn't enough for you?
Then I'll move this for you too!
Stop! Don't!
I-It's making me go crazy!
What's the matter Rinka? Where'd all that energy go?
Almost at your limit, huh?
Let me finish up then!
Here I go! Here I go, Rinka!
Take it all in!
Keep your voice down.
You know what'll happen if you're exposed here, right?
Fine. Come.
No! No!
What? Your nipples were being teased so much
that you couldn't hold on any longer, right?
N-No!
I don't want to do this!
Don't try to act tough now!
You're not very convincing when your pussy's cumming!
No, this doesn't feel good!
Wait! No! Don't go faster so suddenly!
I'm not even close to being done!
Come on, squeeze tighter!
No! Stop! Seriously!
I-It's too strong!
Oh, that's really tight!
Keep it good and tight like that!
Sto... Stop!
I... can't...
Oops, I came inside you again.
W-Wait, no!
W-What are you two doing?!
Seduce him, Rinka.
It's bad for both of us if we're caught.
B-But I...
But...
Officer, she's a loose girl who will take anyone's dick.
Would you like to try?
W-Would you like to have sex with me?
What are you thinking?!
You're threatening her, aren't you?!
P-Please fuck my pussy!
You're going to tell me everything!
Hey, hey, this is getting real!
Ow!
Doing these indecent acts...
In a place like this...
You're such a naughty girl.
Criminals deserve to be punished.
They need to be...
N-No! Stop!
Indecent exposure.
Disturbing the public order.
I need to crack down on this criminal!
Stop! Please!
No!
That's great acting, Rinka!
It looks like you really don't want this!
S-Stop!
Stop recording!
Cum! Rinka, cum!
Cum from a complete stranger!
Good for you, Rinka.
The officer understands how lustful you are.
You probably can't even go outside anymore.
A stranger made me cum...
There are a lot of videos of me too...
Nothing makes sense anymore...
I... don't care anymore...
translator: hikarucon
timing: kurousagi
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч