I taught the cheeky girl Rinka
a lesson using her body.
But her body is just too good
that I can't just let it end here.
There's still a long way for me to enjoy this.
Well then, I wonder what
should I make her do today?
Ore ga Mei Kanojo wo Okasu Wake
That's (the reason) Why I'm Going To Rape my niece Her
Original Work : Yakisaba Teishoku
Original Animation
Day 4: The Day He Laid His Hands On Both Women
The fourth day: the day he laid his hands on both women
Good morning! For today's weather
in the Japanese islands,
there will be a wide high-pressure area
and it will be a clear sunny day.
Uncle... More...
Push it in deeper!
Ever since then, Rinka has been a slave to pleasure.
Come, come... Papa!
It's coming... The first semen of the day!
Well then...
I wonder what should I make her do today?
Stir my womb up!
It feels so hot!
Uncle, your cock...
It's hotter than the bathwater!
Even when I intentionally avoid using aphrodisiac...
No matter what I say...
It feels so good while we hug!
...she will readily offer her body to me.
Uncle, uncle!
Amazing... It feels amazing!
When doing it with strangers, she insists
to make me use the aphrodisiac.
She says that it puts her in a trance and
stop worrying about everything.
Both my pussy and ass...
Stop shoving both of them inside!
My body can't take this!
Coming... They're so deep in me! So deep!
Come! Shoot them all out!
Pour your slimy semen in my belly!
Shoot them all out!
It's coming... again... it's coming again!
Rinka has already become my toy.
I'll play with her until she's broken.
Don't get so impatient!
I'll make sure that you'll be able to come!
Yay~!
Look here, look!
I am Rinka-chan the pervert!
More cocks...
Well then, Rinka. Isn't it about time...
...to go back home and see your parents?
Why don't we show your papa and mama
how you look now that you're a grown-up?
Ooki
I'm back!
Rinka!
What were you doing up until now!
I've been trying to contact you!
I'm glad that you're alright!
I was worried that you might have
gotten caught up in some trouble...
Yeah, yeah! Sorry!
I'll go up and change so save that for later.
Hey, brother. Don't get so angry with Rinka.
It's a good thing that she stayed at my house.
But I was busy with work too that I
haven't been able to spend time with her.
I told her to get in touch with you, though...
I'm sorry.
Nah, stop bowing down.
I'm sorry for my daughter causing you trouble.
I'm really glad that you were there for her.
Hey, darling...
Let's have Ryuuji-kun eat dinner with us!
Then... I think I'll accept the offer.
It's been a while since I had Haruka-san's cooking.
Okay, welcome yourself inside.
Even if you don't invite me,
I'd be feasting myself on you, Haruka-san.
Jeez, Taichi-san is so helpless.
Rinka never went down for dinner too...
I'm sorry, Ryuuji-kun.
Everyone is being a handful.
Please don't worry yourself about it, Haruka-san.
I'm sure that my brother was worried
all this time. The same goes for Rinka.
Your mind should be at ease now.
You really are so kind, Ryuuji-kun.
Hey, Taichi-san...
Ryuuji-kun?
What's the meaning of this...
Haruka-san...
Do you have any idea about the feelings
I've been keeping inside myself?
Do you have any idea on how I felt
whenever I see your family up until now?
I always wanted to make you mine!
I wanted you to choose me over my older brother!
But all of those gloomy feelings will end now.
I'll have my first shot for now.
Swallow it just like this, Haruka!
That's a nice face you're making, Haruka.
From today onwards, I'll shower
you with my affection!
Uncle, sorry for the wait!
So, you already started.
You see, this apparently was mama's
school uniform in the past!
Uncle, won't it be fun if we do it like this?
Good job, Rinka!
I have to give you lots of creampies as a reward!
More! More!
Uncle! Uncle!
Rinka?!
More, thrust it in more!
What...
You're awake, brother!
Oh... You really raised Rinka
to become such a fine woman!
Keep sliding your cock inside!
Rinka...
No matter how much we do it,
she's still squeezing tightly down here!
And Haruka-san too, she's still in
good condition despite her age.
Should I get another one of them
pregnant and make your family bigger?
Ryuuji, do you understand
what you're doing right now?!
I wanted to rape these two
and I'm doing it right now.
Don't worry, I'll give them back
when I get tired of them.
Come on, Rinka.
Let's greet your papa properly.
Huh, papa?
I now belong to uncle.
I get uncle to violate my pussy...
...and he squirts semen inside!
Yes! Well said, Rinka!
Here's your creampie as a reward!
Creampie! Creampie!
Uncle's semen will pour in my perverted pussy!
Hey, come on! Haruka, stop
being dazed down there!
Let my brother hear about
what you were saying earlier!
Forgive me, darling!
Ryuuji-kun's cock is incredible!
Now I can't have anything else but his!
Hey, uncle...
I want you pamper me too, not just mama!
You're sucking my nipple!
Ryuuji-kun, I'm coming... I'm gonna come again!
I'm gonna come as well!
I'll shoot it inside you, Haruka!
It's going in... Uncle's cock is so deep!
I just remembered...
Isn't it almost seventy-two hours since we first did it?
Rinka, do you want to have the pill?
Enough of that already!
Come on, make me pregnant!
Did you hear that, brother?
Make sure to watch the moment your
daughter gets pregnant with my child!
Uncle! Uncle!
Stop... Stop that!
Here, I'm coming! Get knocked up!
Get knocked up, Rinka!
Papa, look...
I'm filled with semen!
Ryuuji-kun... I'm next...
Me too...
More... More!
Haruka...
Rinka!
My life has now been thrown into a chaos
by a sense of satisfaction in an
amount that I never felt before.
I'm looking forward to what's yet to come!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization