I put my bratty niece in her place with her body.
It'd be a shame to end things here, though.
Let's keep the fun times rolling.
Now then, what should we do today?
Original Work: Yakisaba Teishoku
The Reason I Rape My Niece
Fourth Day: He Obtained Both Of Them
Good morning. Here's today's weather forecast.
The stormy weather has died down, and we're
expecting sunny skies throughout the week.
More... More...
Push it in deeper!
Rinka has completely succumbed to pleasure.
Cum! Cum!
The first cum of the morning!
Now then, what should we do today?
Shoot it into my womb!
It's so hot!
Your dick is even hotter in the bath!
I don't even have to use the aphrodisiac anymore.
She listens to whatever I say now.
It's going in and out of me so fast!
She's always asking for it now.
Uncle Ryuji!
It feels so good!
When she fucks other people, she asks for the aphrodisiac.
She says it makes her head hot
and helps her lose her mind.
My pussy and ass!
Both at the same time...
I feel so stuffed!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Fill me up!
Shoot your cum inside me!
I can feel both of you cumming!
Rinka's my toy now.
And I'll keep playing with her until she breaks.
You don't have to be so forceful.
I'll keep sucking till you cum.
Yay!
Look! It's me, Rinka, the world's biggest slut!
I need more dick...
Okay, Rinka.
Don't you think it's about time you visit your parents?
Let's show Mommy and Daddy just
how much you've grown up.
Ooki
I'm back.
Rinka!
Where the hell have you been?!
We've tried calling you dozens of times!
Thank goodness you're all right!
I thought you were in an accident or worse...
Yeah, whatever. Sorry.
I'm going to change.
Save it for later.
Don't get too mad at her.
She was staying at my place.
I wanted to talk things over with her,
but I was just too busy with work.
I tried calling you, but...
Sorry.
Don't be.
Sorry she caused you so much trouble.
I'm really glad you were there for her, Ryuji.
I know!
Why don't we have him over for dinner?
Well, I'm not gonna turn down a home-cooked meal.
It's been ages since I've had your cooking, Haruka.
Come on in.
You don't have to tell me twice.
I'm definitely going to get my fill today...
Of you.
Oh, what am I going to do with you, Taichi?
Rinka didn't come down either...
Sorry, Ryuji.
Everyone's so impolite.
Don't worry about it.
He probably hasn't been sleeping well with Rinka missing.
I'm sure Rinka is doing better, too.
You're always so kind and thoughtful.
Hey, Taichi...
Ryuji?
What are you...
Haruka...
Do you know how I've felt about you?
Do you know how hard it was to hold back
whenever I saw you or your daughter?
I've wanted to make you mine, all this time.
I wanted you to choose me, not my brother!
But today's the last day I have to feel that way!
Here comes the first load.
Swallow every last drop, Haruka!
I like that look on your face.
Fill take very good care of you from now on.
Sorry for the wait, Uncle Ryuji!
Oh, you've already started!
Look! I found Mommy's old school uniform!
Don't you think it'd be fun to do it in this?
Nice idea, Rinka.
I'll give you lots of cum as a reward!
More! More!
Uncle Ryuji!
Rinka?!
More! Give it to me harder!
What the...
Oh, you're up?
You really raised Rinka to be a fine woman.
Your dick feels so good!
Rinka?
No matter how many times we do it, she's still tight as hell!
Your wife isn't too bad either for her age.
Maybe I should put another one in
her and make this family bigger?
Ryuji! Do you know what the hell you're doing right now?!
Yeah, I'm fucking your wife and daughter 'cause I feel like it.
Don't worry, I'll give them back to
you when I'm bored of them.
C'mon, Rinka. Say hi to Daddy.
Daddy, I'm giving myself to Uncle Ryuji.
He can play with my pussy all he wants.
He's gonna fill me to the brim with cum!
Good girl.
Here's your reward!
Cum! Cum!
Pour your cum into my slutty pussy!
Come on now, Haruka. Stop spacing out and
tell your husband what you said earlier.
I'm so sorry, Taichi...
Ryuji's cock is amazing!
I don't think I can live without him!
Hey, give me some love too.
You can't just give it all to Mommy.
My nipples...
You're sucking them so hard!
Ryuji... I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Yeah, I'm gonna cum too.
I'm gonna cum inside you, Haruka!
It's in! Uncle Ryuji's dick is inside!
Now that I think about it, it's been three
days since I've started fucking you.
Do you want the pill?
I don't care about that!
All I want is your semen!
You hear that, bro?!
Witness the moment I knock up your daughter!
Uncle Ryuji!
Stop! Please stop!
Here it comes!
Get pregnant! Get pregnant, Rinka!
Look, Daddy... So much cum...
Ryuji, do me next.
More... More...
Haruka...
Rinka...
My life suddenly feels so much more satisfying.
I can't wait to see what happens next.
translation: hikarucon
timing: kurousagi
typesetting: hybrio21
editing: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч