I taught the cheeky Rinka a lesson using her body. But...
Her body is just too good that I can't just let it end here.
There's still a long way for me to enjoy this.
Well then, I wonder what should I do today?
Ore ga Mei Kanojo wo Okasu Wake
That's (the reason) Why I'm Going To Rape my niece Her
Original Work : Yakisaba Teishoku
Original Animation
Day 3: The Day Her Heart Fell Into Despair
The third day: the day her heart fell into despair
Uncle, I'm already at my limit!
If you peed right here,
I wonder how the neighbors
will look at you afterwards?
Rinka-chan the smart girl understands, right?
For a whole day today,
I'll have you use these.
Do you think you'll scare me from just that?
You won't outwit me with those!
Just as I expected from you!
Then, for today maybe we should stroll
outside while you're wearing these.
What—?!
And you're forbidden from going in the restroom.
The matured Rinka-chan has
no need for peeing, am I right?
Th-This pervert!
Be careful of what you say.
Don't you need the pill anymore?
Come on, get on it already!
I get it already,
so turn it down a little! Please!
You're tired, aren't you?
Take a little rest.
My, oh my! Rinka-chan...
Were you unable to hold your pee in?
It can't be helped...
Come on, hey!
What are you laughing at?
Forget about that!
Nah... There's no way I can forget about that!
Take your panties off for now.
Not right there.
You're taking them off here.
Huh?!
To make up for that failure you had earlier,
I'll have to teach you a lesson that you'll never forget.
We have to record this.
Stop messing around! Who would
do something like that?!
Speaking about records,
we also have something like this.
If this video gets published online,
I wonder what will happen?
Th-That's not fair!
Come on, it already started recording
so show your dirty panties over here!
Properly state your name and
the reason why that happened!
And do it with a smile.
My name is Ooki Rinka.
My uncle told me to hold my bladder...
Not like that!
I had to hold my pee in...
But I couldn't hold it in...
And then I...
urinated outside in public!
Do you have any idea about
what you're doing right now?
You're showing your pee-soaked panties,
and being recorded while you're smiling at the camera!
Even if you wanted to get a pill,
you normally don't go this far!
Just how much of a pervert are you, Rinka?
By the way, those stuffs dripping from your groin
weren't actually just pee, right?
Y-You're wrong! This is—
Yes, yes. I understand.
I'm sorry for teasing you!
Well, you already have that one on the front,
so you'll have to take me in using the one instead!
Th-This can't be! No, no! Wait—
Stop, you'll tear me apart!
Come on! I'm filming you again
so you have to smile, Rinka!
Loosen it up, here, right here!
Stop! You'll really tear me apart!
What, having only your ass fucked isn't enough?
Then I'll have to thrust this one as well!
No! I don't want that!
You're stirring me inside, it's driving me crazy!
What's the matter, Rinka?
That grit you had earlier is now gone!
You're about to reach your limit, huh?
Then let's put an end to this!
I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come, Rinka!
I'm gonna fill you up a lot!
Don't let your voice out.
If you get found out in a place like this,
you know what's going to happen, right?
It can't be helped. Follow me!
No... No!
What's with that "no"?
Weren't you at your wit's end from having
your nipples teased all this time?
You're wrong! I don't want to do this sort of thing!
It's too late for you to be acting tough!
You say that while your pussy is this drenched.
You don't sound convincing!
No... I'm not feeling anything from this!
Wait... don't! What? Not that fast!
This is still nothing!
Look, I'll do it rougher on here as well!
This is bad! This is really bad!
The stimuli are too strong!
Oh, aren't you squeezing me tightly!
Keep tightening your grip just like that!
Stop... Stop this!
I can't take it anymore!
I poured it inside you again!
Wait, no way...
B-Both of you!
What are you doing?!
Rinka, you have to seduce that guy.
Won't it be bad for both of us if we get arrested?
Th-That would be...
But...
Mr. Patrolman...
This girl is a slut who'll take anyone's cock in her!
Want to try it a for a bit?
U-Umm, would you like to have sex with me?
You... What the hell is on your mind?
You're threatening that girl, aren't you?
Please screw my pussy!
You'll have to explain yourselves!
Hey, hey! This ain't a joke!
Ouch!
In such a place like this...
To be engaging in lascivious acts...
You are a bad girl...
I should punish offenders...
...like yourself!
N-No way... Stop!
Lascivious acts in public is against
school regulations on right conduct!
I have to reprimand any offenders!
Stop this! I'm begging you!
No!
That is such a realistic acting, Rinka!
You really look like you don't want it!
S-Stop that!
Stop taking pictures!
Come, come, Rinka!
Let a complete stranger you just met
forcibly make you come!
Isn't it great, Rinka?
Seems that you even taught the
patrolman about your fetish!
You can't walk outside alone anymore...
A stranger made me come!
I got filmed a lot as well!
I don't know what to think of anymore!
I don't care whatever happens anymore...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization