Rinka
I ran away from home
let me stay tonight
and also, have you already sent
the gift to papa? ( `^´)
tell him that it was
from me, okay?
I ran away from home. Let me stay tonight.
And also, have you already sent the gift to papa?
Tel him that it was from me, okay?
Jeez! She always acts like this...
Yahoo!
Uncle! You must be tired from working hard!
Jeez, Rinka...
It's about time you stop that, always
suddenly coming here by yourself.
Even I have my own things to worry about—
Yeah, yeah! Sorry!
Enough of that, let me in already.
I'm tired, you see.
I'm barging in!
Hey, don't just kick your shoes off.
Wash hands before entering the room.
Hey there, that's my room!
Darn it, wait for me like a good girl.
Ore ga Mei Kanojo wo Okasu Wake
That's (the reason) Why I'm Going To Rape my niece Her
Original Work : Yakisaba Tekishoku
Original Animation
Day 1: The Day He Laid His Hands On Her
The first day: the day he laid his hands on her.
And then,
papa is being annoying just
because I got home a little late.
I'm not a kid anymore, you see...
My brother is just worried about you.
That's because you're his only cute daughter.
Oh jeez...
Uncle, calling me cute is a
bit too much of a praise.
And didn't you say that
you're not a kid anymore?
Have a little more modesty,
you're being too sloppy!
I dunno about that!
Damn, I always thought of you as a brat,
but doesn't she already have a woman's body?
My brother brought her fiancée home.
She was his girlfriend from college, Haruka-san.
Right after coming in our home,
I opened myself up on her.
But... I was still too young back then.
Even now, it makes me feel bad
whenever I remember about it.
Haruka-san...
Even when I loved you way more than my brother did,
why did you end up with him...
Hey uncle! Are you listening?
I'm parched so why don't you get me something?
Oh, and lend me some clothes.
I never brought any with me.
I get it , so behave yourself there.
Shit! That face...
Stop showing me a face
that looks like Haruka-san!
Do I even have any clothes that she can wear?
Oops.
Isn't this...
This is something I got when in a business trip abroad.
It's some aphrodisiac I got from a local shop there.
I bought this drug that has
an instant and extreme effect.
If enough is used, it results from severe intoxication,
and it will pull a woman's deepest
desire out, or so I was told.
I just took it as a joke at that time,
But when I saw it's actual effect, it scared me
that I put it away and forgot about it.
Hey there... What am I thinking?
Use this on Rinka? Who am I kidding?
She's my niece, and I knew her
since she was still a baby.
She's started to be cheeky lately, and then...
And then, she's becoming more and more...
like how Haruka-san looked like...
I see... So this is how being
'possessed by a demon' feels like.
Here are the clothes. And this as well...
Your juice.
Thank you.
Oh, it's the one that I like.
You really know me, uncle!
Huh, did it get hot in here?
Hey, Rinka...
Don't you remember? Not long ago
we both sit down like this,
and then I always hug you.
So what?
I'm not a kid anymore!
That's right, you already got a grown-up body.
W-What? U-Uncle, stop!
You got so wet easily.
Are you usually doing things like
this by yourself? You really grew up!
Though you still have a kid's size up here.
Why are you feeling good all by yourself?
Here, make mine feel good as well!
S-Stop—
Rinka...
You really look like Haruka-san way back then!
It's like I'm raping her as I do this.
That feels good, Rinka!
I'm gonna come... I'll come just like this, okay?
Hey, hey!
Don't get worn out after only that.
We'll be going to do more amazing
stuffs so let's get on the bed.
Look, Rinka. Can you guess
what is playing on the screen?
Huh... Papa and mama?
What... Why...
You mean why I have this footage?
It's from your 'present' to your papa.
I had a camera put inside it.
My brother was so happy when
he saw your name on the gift.
He put it in front of the bed as a display.
Thanks to that, I've been able to watch
some porn starring Haruka-san every night.
Papa...
You... Did seeing your father arouse you?
You have a father complex?
Just how perverted are you?
Hey, Rinka. See the woman being shown
in the video that looks just like you?
That woman should have been mine.
But now I can't get her for myself anymore.
So there's no other way but
for you to be mine instead.
From now on, I'll do on you
the same things he does on her.
N-No way, I don't want that!
I-It hurts! It hurts!
Stop... Uncle!
Hey hey, stop making a troubled face like that!
It'll just get me even more aroused!
No... No...
I don't want this!
Uncle, stop!
Papa, help me!
Look over there! Your papa is humping his hips!
Who's the one he's making love with now?
Who's the one thrusting behind you now?
Papa... Papa is...
So deep... Papa is thrusting inside me!
Papa!
I love you!
It really feels like I'm raping Haruka-san!
Haruka... Haruka, I'm gonna come! Haruka!
You can do anything you want!
Papa... Papa!
After that, I continued raping
Rinka for the whole night.
Papa... it feels good!
Papa... more... more!
It's coming out... Papa's sperm... A lot of it!
It feels good!
You're scraping me there!
I still have some time before the drug wears off.
Looks like I'll be able to do it as much as I want.
Huh? Last night, I...
That's right, uncle did...
Hey...
You finally woke up, Rinka!
Last night was pretty intense...
Did I really come that much?
You'll most likely get pregnant with that.
Pregnant?
Oh yeah, I still have those...
The 'morning after pill'.
From what I recall, if you take one
within three days after sex,
won't the chance of pregnancy  drastically decrease?
I-Is that true? Uncle, please...
If you want one, you know what to do, right?
I'm begging you, please give me a pill.
You can do as you please with my body.
This is gonna be a wonderful
weekend. Right, Rinka?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization