Hey, Minokyuu!
Bring my usual coffee here already!
Okay, I'll bring it already!
I'm Minoda Kyuutarou.
I'm working as an AD at Maru TV.
I only ever do minor stuff though,
But I'm somehow getting by
In the middle of my troubles,
The popular TV announcer whom
I get to work together with lately.
Is Nishio Aya,
Because of her, this supposed AD somehow
gets frequently exposed on TV,
becomes the laughing stock of the audience,
forces me to eat oden on public television,
made me do bungee jumps,
threw me into a lion's cage,
and even treats me like her slave.
If I was with the newbie announcer Miyase Kaori instead,
I would never have suffered like this.
What the hell is wrong with her?
Ordering me to get coffee like I'm some dunce...
A little sugar and lots of milk you say?
If this is how things are going to be,
I'll just have to jack off to Aya-san's erotic image,
And give her lots of my own cum milk!
Please
wait a moment
The blend that I like.
Low in sugar, high in my very own "milk".
Aya-san, I haven't been jacking off lately
so this milk is very thick you see.
Wait no!
W, wh, what have I just done?
I have to get her another cup of coffee immediately!
Hey, Minokyuu!
What are you doing?
Yes?!
Just how much time are you going to waste for my coffee?
Well, ummm...
Stop making excuses.
Oh, so you already have it there.
No, that's...
What? Do you have anything to say?
No, not really.
Aya-san, the popular announcer is drinking my cum-filled coffee!
Wait, that tasted a bit different than normal.
Why are you slouching like that Minokyuu?
It's nothing.
Sucker Announcer
If you make me drink that much... I'll start craving for sex
#1 The Magic Semen
Waiting Room
The manager of the Announcer Department commended
me for reading the script perfectly.
Oh, that's great then.
Somehow, the coffee that you gave me last
time really helped me to speak well.
I see, all because of that coffee so...
Wait, was there something wrong with that coffee?
Was that really the same as my usual coffee then?
I wonder...
Minokyuu!
Give me the exact same coffee that you last gave me.
I'll be having a recording session again shortly.
I want to clear my throat up with that coffee.
But...
What are you slacking for?
Get on it already!
Roger!
Please
wait a moment
Minokyuu!
Jeez, I thought something was odd so I tried following you.
Wait...Aya-san?
So I was actually drinking coffee with your cum eh.
I'm really sorry.
But this is quite an interesting phenomenon.
Something worth testing.
Hey, Aya-san...?
Anyway, just concentrate on making yourself cum.
Hurry up and release it already.
You sure are surprisingly well-endowed down here.
Just cum whenever you want to.
I'm already doing this just to get you to do it you know.
Just cum and let me drink it already.
Give me your thick cum milk already!
This...the sensation as it wraps around my throat...
Thank you for the meal.
Yep, it's as I thought.
My speech becomes very clear when I drink your cum.
What?!
Minokyuu, you're going to let me drink
your cum milk from now on okay?
Eh?!
Your cum milk is critical for my career as an announcer!
Do you understand?
I understand.
If that's what you want.
From that time on,
She calls me whenever she wants to,
Squeezing, and sucking it out like I'm some sex toy.
Your dick is very big, and its veins are pulsating.
It really wants to be teased by me eh.
How cute.
Aya-san, the next program will be broadcast live.
So what?
Your job as an AD is to condition me
perfectly for the upcoming program.
And before that program, I need to suck on this first.
I need to drink your cum first.
Be thankful that I'm doing this to an AD like you.
So just cum and give it all to me already.
I'm already sucking your stiff dick for you.
I'm cleaning a lowly AD's dick.
Some clear liquid is starting to overflow at the tip.
So, you're slowly unable to hold it now?
Just release already!
The live show is about to start.
Let me drink your cum now!
No more? Cum some more if you want to.
Thanks for the meal.
Now the next session will be perfect.
I'll be expecting the same again next time Minokyuu.
You're late.
I told you to come here in 30 minutes!
That's just impossible...
Oh well, just hurry up and pull your dick out.
What, again?!
We don't have time!
I still have an interview with  *censored*
I really can't mess this up so I need your cum badly.
What...
Hurry and make me drink your cum.
*censored* is about to arrive.
Whether I perform well in the interview lies in your cum.
Release it all out now.
I'm going to get really busy soon.
Here, cum already.
It's not coming out.
Oh well, I'm doing this for you. I'll have to make you cum quicker.
Okay then.
Then how about this?
I'm doing this exclusively for this occasion, okay?
I'm exposing my embarrassing part to you.
You need to understand that I'm only doing
this just to make you cum faster okay?
Your dick is starting to bulge out more
as soon as you started staring at it.
I'm doing this for you, even if you're just an AD.
Be grateful.
Just a little okay?
Just fondle me a little there okay?
No, I said just a little!
You’re just Minokyuu, so don't start getting all rough there.
If you do it intensely like that, someone will...
Just release it all already!
Here...
I'm already doing all of this for you.
Oh no, I'm really going to cum.
I'm going to cum because of you...
No, I can't cum now because of you!
I'll be having an interview shortly!
Now, I'm heading over for the interview Minokyuu.
Be sure to watch it later, okay?
Yeah...
See you then.
Oh, Aya-san.
How was the interview?
I want you to take me to my home today.
Oh really?
Then that means it's been made especially for this show?
Minokyuu, thank you.
It's all thanks to you that the interview was a success.
So, I'm going to give you a treat.
Don't just stand there, turn the lights off.
Even I'm embarrassed with this you know.
Minokyuu, don't suck my nipples like an infant.
But, suck my breasts properly.
My nipples are starting to get stiff.
It's starting to feel good.
No...Don't...
I said don't.
You're just Minokyuu, don't just go touching my delicate parts.
Now you're licking me down there.
If you keep doing that, my love juices will start to flow out.
Hey, Minokyuu, I think that's enough.
That's enough already.
That's okay now right?
Hey, don't just finger it like that.
I think, I'm ready now.
See, it went all the way in.
Your dick is now going inside me.
Your dick feels hot.
What's wrong?
No need to hold back, just rub it inside of me.
The way it shoves up inside me.
You're still not thrusting that hard, and yet the
sensations inside my womb is going wild!
Umm...please don't wrap around me tightly like that.
Why?
Because I'm going to cum quickly.
What? You're about to cum already?
What a helpless dick.
Well, that just means that it feels really good inside me though.
But, not yet.
It'd be boring if it ends too soon.
Even if I did say this is a treat
You still need make me feel good okay?
Though, you’re still pushing it in way too deep!
But, push inside my womb more anyway.
There, that's amazing.
This feels great.
I'm already tired due to work, but it still feels amazing.
Does my pussy feel good?
Hey, does it?
Your soft flesh is the best.
Okay, that's good.
My pussy is here as your reward, got it?
Take it as you please.
Wait, it just pierced inside.
I think the tip of your dick just entered my womb.
Your dick is getting really cocky now, eh?
There, there!
The thick thing is going right in!
Push it in more.
Just push it in the way you want to.
Your dick feels great.
It's going very deep inside.
And my pussy is feeling pleasurable too.
It's sweetly taking in your dick.
Minokyuu, I think I'm about to cum.
You're going hard.
You're going too hard.
I'm about to break.
My pussy is about to be molded.
About to be molded into the shape of your dick!
Don’t release that cum anywhere else.
Release it all inside me.
Pour it all in.
Oh no, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
Minokyuu, wake up already!
How dare you sleep peacefully like that on someone else's bed?
Why do I have to wake up my own AD?
You're the one who's supposed to do the waking for me you know!
I'm sorry!
How long are you going to lie down there?
Come, we're going to work now!
Got it.
Get up and go!
Roger!
And that's it for our program.
This was Nishio Aya.
Aya-san, thanks for the hard work.
Oh, Minokyuu.
Perfect timing.
Lend me your body.
Your dick's going inside me.
And it's firmly in because of its thickness.
It's too thick, and it feels too good.
Maybe we're really compatible with each other if it feels this good.
You're getting too intense already.
Rub inside me more.
Make me cum with it.
Whenever you rub it inside me, my insides tingle.
There, rub it in further at that spot.
Push it through with your hard part.
Push it, push it more!
Make me feel it more.
Your dick feels great.
It feels so great to be fucked like this!
Make me feel more!
Make it feel so good that my mind goes blank.
I don't want to think of anything else, I don't want to!
What's wrong, Aya-san?
Aya-san?
Minokyuu, would I be a successful news entertainer?
Aya-san...
Just earlier, I had to wear that laughable and humiliating costume.
I don't intend to be picky about my work, and
I actually like that kind of presentation,
but what I really want is to be in the news business.
The jobs that I always get are these variety types.
I know It's already great that I even got a job at all
I thought that if I do well in whatever they give me
I'd eventually be recognized.
I tried my best...
Hey Minokyuu.
What do you think of me lately.
I think you're doing very well.
You're very popular.
Hey, try to move while saying your opinion of me.
I want to erase these bad thoughts with good pleasure.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Minokyuu, I'm really quite grateful to you.
The scope of work that I do started to get
wider ever since you were with me.
No, I think it's all because of your capability.
No, I don’t think so.
I said that it's all thanks to you, so it's all thanks to you.
That's why, make me feel great like you always do.
And then make me cum.
Lift my spirits up high.
Aya-san, your expression is very erotic.
What, I'm not making such an expression.
You are, look.
Just forget about my erotic expression.
Do you really think I can become a news entertainer?
I think you'll be able to easily work as one.
That's, that's my softest spot!
Don't push hard in there.
I think you'd become even more famous if you
try to read your news script in that loud tone.
Jeez, you idiot, stop telling me the obvious!
But, thank you.
I don't know why I feel relieved just by you saying that to me but...
Hey, no slacking, thrust your hips too!
I want to feel the pleasure more!
There, that's good!
Your hard and stiff dick is going wild inside my pussy.
It's getting caught inside by my soft flesh in many spots.
No, don't push it inside any further.
It's pushing against my shameful flesh from the inside.
That's enough, because I can't stop anymore.
This feels great!
Do it more.
Rub it back and forth more.
Your dick feels good.
Oh no, this stiff thing is trying to fill my womb!
It's pushing and filling me inside!
Oh wow, my pussy feels like its stuck on
to the dick and is getting pulled out.
It feels so good, that it feels like my pussy
is about to get torn inside out.
Oh no, I’m cumming, I'm cumming!
Minokyuu, stir me up more.
Rub your stiff cock inside me more!
Just cum.
Please give me your warm cum.
Violate me deep inside!
I'm also about to cum.
Let's cum together.
I'm about to cum by being fucked by an AD!
Cum.
Hurry up and let it all out.
Come on and cum already!
Cum inside me!
I'm going to take it all.
You're late Minokyuu!
I was planning to drink your warm cum
before going to work you know!
The meeting's about to start already!
I'm sorry.
Just forget it.
I'm just going to drink it during the meeting,
so go and prepare my usual coffee.
Huh?
Low in sugar, high in thick milk.
The usual one, get it?
Please, okay?