My name is Shimohei Joutaro.
I work here at Mitsuishi Municipal Girls School.
I'm the Admissions Secretary.
I need “it”!
Then say it.
Even though classes have not officially started, there's a reason that I'm here.
That is…
No! No!
That reason is to make each and every student scream in orgasmic ecstasy.
SubDESU-H Presents
Harsh Discipline
Mission to Pacify the Bad Schoolgirls
Faculty Room
Now that you've persuaded me, I understand…
Todo Mitsuki, you will not be skipping class any more, correct?
Shinohei-sensei…
There's your cheating problem as well.
Sensei! That's just a rumor going around the school, whoever spread it has really upset me!
I see, you're upset?
Unfortunately I can’t just let this go on like this.
Is there anyone that can name all the transition elements for me?
Yes, me!
From the top:
Gallium,
calcium,
natrium,
magnesium,
calmenium,
zinc,
iron,
nickel,
cesium,
lead,
copper,
mercury,
silver,
palladium,
gold.
Ah, give ME some of that to eaaat...
Oh dear, I'm going to have to discipline that young lady as well.
I said no!
But your nipples are becoming so hard and pointy.
I see…
That’s why she's so sleepy today.
So you're sleepy because you’ve been practicing hard everyday in the school sports team, huh?
Falling asleep in class is unacceptable, though.
I’m very sorry.
Hm, I understand, Mitsuki.
You're a very kind person, but you’ve been teaching your friends some very naughty things, haven’t you?
If the other students find out what you’ve been doing it won't be good for the school.
I can't discipline you in front of the other students, so I'll have to teach you privately…
Will you be able to help me?
Yes.
If you only watch all the time you'll be unhappy, why don’t you come and swim with me, Mitsuki?
Well, I didn’t bring my swimming costume.
Just jump in naked, no one will come in here.
I'm not really afraid of that, but I think you and I should stop doing “naughty things” together.
Well, we're sisters so there's nothing wrong with it, right? You're the one who asked me to do it, Mitsuki chan.
Well, that was…
Hello girls, good evening.
Jou-sensei, good evening! Mitsuki… our last conversation is finished for now, okay?
Are you satisfied with the outcome of your discussion?
I don’t know what to doooo!
S-Sensei… Ah...
Wh-What are you doing?
Sensei, don’t let my sister see us…
Mitsuki… what are you doing over there?
This… this is…
Tell her, Mitsuki!
Shimohei-sensei’s…
He's touching my breasts right now…
He's squeezing and making my nipples hard…
And he's teasing my pussy…
Mitsuki, does it feel good?
D-Don’t look!
I'm so ashamed.
Wow, it looks like it feels so good, her vagina is making more sounds than when I was touching it!
Don’t say that!
Mistuki, you know there's something that feels even better waiting for you when I'm done with touching you,
don’t let that escape your mind while I'm playing with you.
Feels even better?
Wow, inside Mitsuki's… Sensei…
Sensei… is…
Tell your sister what's happening to you!
Sensei… Sensei’s cock is…
Is… inside my pussy!
His penis is penetrating me from behind, it's moving in and out... in and out…
Wow, Mitsuki's sex is giving me goosebumps!
No, don’t say that!
Jou-sensei, I want your penis inside me too! Its okay, right?
Of course, young lady, but first I have to satisfy young Mitsuki completely.
Don’t be surprised… She'll suddenly start screaming in pleasure before I'm done.
There…
No… Stop… stop… I'm cumming… I'm cumming… I’m... cumming!
This is so different from when Mitsuki touches me!
How is it different?
I don’t know, but when Jou-sensei touches me, I get nervous and excited.
That’s very good, because in the future you'll do this with many men, not just women.
Oh, really? Is that true?
How does that feel?
Good, it feels good… Jou-sensei...
This is where it starts to feel good.
Ah, my pussy is making such strange sounds!
Jou-sensei, please touch my pussy, don’t touch me through my costume…
I can't do that,
because I am teaching you.
You can't touch Mitsuki like this, can you?
Why?
You selfishly made her play with you to make yourself feel good, didn’t you?
Yes, that’s probably true…
You can't be that selfish, just like you can't be that selfish in the classroom.
Yes, I understand, I'll be careful.
No, you don’t understand.
Jou-sensei, you can't stop touching me!
Please, Sensei, please touch my pussy…
Put your dick into my pussy just like you did with my sister!
Well… If I must…
Wow, it feels so good to be touched by a man!
It's not just because I'm a man, it's because you've been touched by everyone…
Yesterday, how was it when Mitsuki was touching you?
Oh… that was…
That was nothing like this…
It hurts, Jou-sensei… It hurts… Jou-sensei!
Of course it hurts.
That’s because this is a punishment.
Oh, I see.
You and I cant force Mitsuki to touch you anymore, so I must discipline you and teach you a lesson.
Mitsuki wont be touching you either from now on, right?
Mitsuki, you've learned your lesson, right?
Yes.
It feels so different, Jou-sensei, your cock feels so good.
That’s because Mitsuki is giving me a helping hand.
I never knew that a cock could feel so good stretching my pussy like this.
Mitsuki, did your pussy also feel like this when Jou-sensei had his cock in your pussy?
That’s right.
Move more, Jou-sensei, it feels so good, move more!
Yes.
Mistuki… Jou-sensei…
It feels so good!
Yes, that’s right - it feels so good because it's my hard cock teaching you a hard lesson.
Now there's only one for me to take care of.
Thank you for such a wonderful class today, I enjoyed it immensely.
Yes, you were such a good student today, you paid attention wonderfully.
How can I be as wonderful as you, Sensei?
It's easy.
Without looking away from your student's eyes, look deeply into their hearts and give them heartfelt advice.
Yes, I'll try, but right now I'm still new and inexperienced.
For me to teach you, we should start from here.
That is…
Yes, I took a look at the contents of your cell phone… and all the mail you sent…
No! No, you're wrong, that’s not me!
Shimohei Jou-sensei, what are...?
Stop.
I heard everything from Mahiru.
No, no she’s lying!
That’s too bad, because today there's one more teacher that I have to teach.
Teach?
Stop! I'll scream!
Everyone's gone home.
No matter how hard you scream,
no one will hear you.
No, stop, I'm still a virgin!
Make sure you tell your sister exactly how this feels.
Oh, no, this means that there might be a little bit of trouble….
You're awake.
Shimohei-sensei, what is the meaning of this? Why did you do this?
I did this because I'm a teacher.
Because you're a teacher, you helped your sister to cheat, didn’t you?
Well… that was…
Big sister…
Mahiru...
You should be honest and tell Shimohei-sensei everything like I did…
Then you'll feel much better…
Just relax and let Shohei-sensei make you feel good, sis, just like I did.
B-But...
Trust me… You'll be changed forever.
Sis… Let Shimohei-sensei put himself inside you.
Mahiru made you feel good, but you telling her the answers to the test was wrong, was it not?
But…
You should have been teaching her to enjoy her school subjects, shouldn’t you?
Sis, right now Shimohei-sensei is teaching you a lesson, because learning lessons is fun.
Sis, are you crying?
I'm sorry, Mahiru, please forgive your big sister.
Of course I forgive you, sis, how can I not forgive you?
I'm sorry I asked you to tell me the answers to the test,
it's all my fault, can you forgive me too?
I've taught you both well, you've not only learned about school, but you've grown as human beings as well.
Shimohei-sensei… move more, please, and make my big sister feel even better!
Yes I'll do that for you.
Sis, touch me too, please!
Yes, sis, it feels so good, I feel so happy!
No… it feels too good!
Mahiru, it feels too good!
It's okay, sis, don’t hold back, let it out!
Yes, I can see my work here is done…
Ah... What...
What is the meaning of this?!