My name is Shimohei Joutarou.
I'm a newly transferred teacher at the Mitsuishi private academy.
Mahiru...
Say it.
There is a reason why I tranferred in the middle of the year.
And that is...
No!
I must fix the students who disturb the order of the academy, by using any means necessary.
Mitsuki! Teacher!
I've already punished three students and a teacher, fixing them.
But when I thought my work would be over...
What is this?!
The students boycotted my class.
Punishment
Plan to fix the school's princess
I bet this is Homareko's doing.
I think so too.
Homareko? You mean Kanegasaki Homareko?
You shouldn't say such accusations without any proof.
But...
Teacher!
The culprit aside, I think the first priority should be
making everyone return and continue with the class.
Mitsuki, very well said. That is correct.
But do you know where everyone is?
If they've left school, we have no way to find them.
I have an idea.
Listen, everyone.
The important thing is to understand "molar property" here.
If you understand that, you can solve this problem.
She's good at teaching.
Teacher, you're not supposed to be sympathizing!
Sorry.
How did you know she'll be here?
This is the only place where many students can gather without standing out.
You're smart, Mitsuki!
What now? We're going in?
No, we shouldn't do that.
But it's a shame she's using her talent for boycotting class.
Nurse's office
Homareko's taking rhythmic gymnastics very seriously.
She's good at working hard.
She's alone in the gym training.
Yeah. She's studying late in the dorm as well.
I see.
Teacher, teacher!
Hurry up, Sis!
The rhythmic gymnastics club requested permission to use the gym for longer.
Could I help at all?
Yes, thank you, Ms Kuji.
But I went to look into it!
I know.
Ah, amazing!
Can we kiss, Mitsuki?
Yeah.
We won't lose either!
Mahiru, you've changed.
Yeah! I enjoy being in class and the lectures are fun too!
I can talk with Mitsuki and Minami as well.
Thank you! It's all thanks to Mr Shimohei!
Teacher, would you touch my pussy too?
Your finger... put it in...
It feels great, Teacher!
Mr... Mr Shimohei... I'm... I'm...
Your cock feels great!
More...
It feels too good! Too good!
I'm cumming!
Amazing!
So deep!
It's in so deep!
Amazing! Teacher, you're amazing!
My pussy... My pussy can't take it!
Teacher, it feels great!
You look much happier. It's very different from when we first met.
It's all thanks to... you!
No, this is your true self.
I only helped a little so that you could find yourself.
Teacher!
Will you... Will you cum together with me?
Cum together with me!
The next will be my last punishment in this academy.
Mitsuki and Minami? What are you doing here?
Come on, we're just here to see you practice!
I wonder about that.
You're so moody.
Is it your period?
That's not it!
You two are so close to that Shimohei!
Did he send you here to tell me not to boycott classes?
Oh please!
Even if we told you, you wouldn't change your mind.
You get it, then.
Blackout?
Such a shame, it's a blackout.
Shimohei?!
What are you doing here?
Of course to enjoy your wonderful performance.
And to punish you so that your talents and desires will be directed the right way.
Punish?
What's the meaning of this?! Let me go right away!
Please endure this until I'm done talking.
Shimohei Joutarou! You coaxed them into this!
That's not true, Kanegasaki.
We're doing this by our own free will.
No way! You're crazy!
You're all crazy!
You're no match for Mitsuki when it comes to studies
or Minami when it comes to sports.
But you are improving by working really hard.
What's wrong with working hard?
I didn't say it's wrong.
But your hard work is nothing compared to Mahiru's.
It's because you have no joy in your hard work.
You perverted teacher!
On the contrary, isn't it causing you pain?
I've listened to your lecture.
It was really good.
I'm even more impressed by the fact that you held a class at all.
Normally students would have tried running away, but no one did that.
Your leadership skills and sense of responsibility are amazing.
Why... Why are you crying?!
Why wouldn't you use your leadership skills and sense of responsibility the right way?
Instead of just not using them.
Don't!
Why are you abusing them just to make me leave school?
No! It hurts!
Teacher, please pull out!
This is punishment. Of course it hurts.
We'll help so it won't hurt.
Bear with it a little and it'll feel as good as earlier!
Your hard work in academics and sports isn't meant for getting rid of a teacher you hate.
It's meant to be used for leading your class and the school in the right direction.
Listen to what he says.
Homareko.
Kanegasaki.
He tells no lies.
When you escaped with everyone and skipped class, he was praising you.
It feels good! Amazing!
I've just understood it all!
I'm glad you understand.
Teacher!
Mr Shimohei, I'm very sorry!
I was wrong!
There is no need to apologize.
What's important is what you're going to do now.
Yes!
Let's work hard together!
Ms Kuji!
I'll help you with everything!
Kanegazaki, do you feel their support?
Yes!
It feels great! I feel weird!
I feel... weird!
Goodbye, everyone.
I was merely an episode actor.
Now that you're heading in the right direction, I might just hold you back.
Let's part without any real farewell.
You will enter society and pray we may meet again sometime.