Look, look, that’s him.
The new teacher.
Eew, he’s so lame!
My name is Shimohei Joutaro.
I have a reason for entering this school mid-term.
It's because...
Are you okay?
Hey, you!
Don’t run...
My mission is to punish the students who disobey school rules.
SubDESU-H Presents
Harsh Discipline
Mission to Pacify the Bad Schoolgirls
Faculty room
Huh? Someone cheated?
Yes.
I heard something of that sort.
It’s just a rumor.
Let’s just forget it.
Otherwise the students will lose trust in us.
That’s true.
The students can be very sensitive in matters like these.
She is a teacher, Kuji Hinako.
She is a young and passionate teacher.
Oh don’t, Mitsuki.
It’s okay.
No one’s nearby.
D-Don’t!
Here look, your nipples are so hard.
Oh, stop it!
Down here too, it’s so wet.
Minami, does this feel good?
Yes, very.
Oops.
Good afternoon.
We know who you are!
You’re the new teacher.
Yes.
I am Shiwa Minami.
And this is my sister, Tono Mitsuki.
Sister?
We’re twins.
When we were little, my parents took her in.
So that’s why your surnames are different.
I am Shimohei Joutaro.
I’ll be teaching chemistry.
Oh, so you’re a pro!
That sounds too cool.
That’s okay, no one will mind.
Oh, I see.
It’s food in pill-form.
It doesn't make me gain weight.
That was such a shock.
I mean, Mahiru-chan just suddenly started getting perfect scores!
Until then, we used to be neck-in-neck for the top.
Have you heard any rumors to this affect?
Rumors? About cheating?
But Mahiru-chan would never do that.
She’s a good girl and her sister is a teacher.
Teacher?
Yep! Kuji-sensei.
Kuji Hinako-sensei!
Oh, you mean her.
Kuji Hinako... Kuji Mahiru...
Infirmary
Onee-chan!
So you are Kuji Mahiru-chan.
I heard my sister was sick.
It is a lie that Kuji-sensei fainted.
Wh-Why?
I've heard rumors of your cheating.
And so I investigated the grades of all students here.
I... didn't...
Mahiru... Mahiru didn't cheat at all!
Then let me examine you.
Oh...
Answer my questions and I will determine whether you're lying or not.
Did you cheat?
You don't get it, Mahiru would never...
What a problem.
Every time you answer, you lie.
I’m not!
Then let’s examine a more telling area.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
This can only be done with a female.
I ask your uterus.
My uterus...?
Don’t move it!
Then I will change my question.
You don’t have pubic hair, do you?
Of course I do!
I have pubic hair!
Maybe my methods were flawed.
But just in case...
Allow me to inspect.
Ah I see, you have no hair.
So that was a lie.
And what you said before was also a lie.
You cheated, right?
S-Sensei!
Now, answer truthfully.
Putting your sin into words is the first step towards forgiveness.
No... stop...
What is it?
Did you cheat?
Didn't you cheat?
Fingers inside...
What is it? Tell me.
Your fingers are... touching...
I couldn't hear you.
Mahiru’s pussy... is filled with your fingers.
It’s throbbing.
Very good.
Use this courage to tell me about your cheating.
Now. Tell me.
M-Mahiru did... cheat... she did!
So you finally admitted it.
But you still seem upset.
Sinners must be punished in order to be forgiven.
I'm also very upset with you.
N-No!
Help me... Onee-chan!
Now, pay for your sins.
That pain is your punishment.
And when your sin is forgiven, this punishment will...
This punishment will change to pleasure!
Now promise to never cheat again.
Yes!
If you want good grades, you must study.
Now, let us study.
Sui. Hei. Ri. Bei.
TL Note: The sailor, Libei on my boat = This is a special way to remember the order of the periodic table of elements.
Bo. Ku. No. Fu. Ne.
Now, say it with me.
Sui... Hei... Ri... Bei...
Bo... Ku... No... Fune...
Very good.
Here is your reward.
I’m cumming...
Oh, is that so?
English
Hinako
What a pity. I am truly upset, Kuji Hinako-sensei.
Kuji-sensei.
About yesterday’s cheating...
I thought we weren't going to talk about rumors!
There are more important things.
L-Like...
Tono-san, who often ditches classes, even though her grades are good.
And Shiwa-san, who always sleeps in class.
What a problem.
If only Kuji-sensei would come clean.
As a person, and as a teacher, and as Mahiru-san's sister.
Who’s there.
Oh my, oh my.
I thought I hid my aura well.
Your aura?
Are you sure you don’t need to be in class?
I don’t.
I already know all the answers.
Yes, but, no matter how good your grades are,
we can't allow you to behave in such a way that brings down everyone else’s zeal to learn.
Let’s go back to class and apologize.
Come.
Don’t bother!
But I was hoping to resolve your issues.
I have no issues!
Is that true?
Like perhaps... Shiwa Minami-san...
What’s wrong with my sister?
You are strong, yet weak.
You have a dream of Minami leaving and you living alone with your real parents.
Y-You...
Wh-What’s this?
I can’t move!
Ah, when you threw me just now, I shot you with a muscle relaxant.
And it was laced with an aphrodisiac.
Wh-What?
Stop it!
No!
Wow, it’s working well.
Stop i-
Stop it.
Don’t touch me!
This is your punishment.
You deserve it.
What gives you the right?
Naturally, because I’m a teacher.
Don’t tell me you’re gonna...
Does it hurt?
D-Don’t move!
I can't stop.
You must be punished.
No! Stop it!
Let me tell you something about school.
It is not only a place where you learn from a textbook.
You interact with others, learn from them,
and they learn from you as well.
You understand this, right?
Do you realize how much your absence in class affects your sister?
D-Don’t talk about my sister!
So you agree with me.
You realize what a bad influence you are.
You are no longer your former self.
You no more feel any pain.
I don’t!
It’s very... very exhilarating!
More... Move more!
Sensei, please stir up my pussy with your dick!
Yes! Oh, yes!
I want you to teach me some lessons, Sensei!
I’m cumming... I’m cumming, Sensei!
I’m cumming!
I can’t hold back.
My name is Shimohei Joutaro.
My mission is to punish the students who disobey school rules.
My next target is that girl, I presume...