SubDESU-H.net
My name is Shimohei Joutarou.
I work here at the Mitsuishi Private School, as a teacher and guidance councilor.
I...
Come on, say it.
There's a reason why I transferred here even though it's not the start of a term.
And that's...
No... stop it!
...to punish anyone who breaks the school's rules, whatever it takes.
Mitsuki... Jou-sensei!
I already punished three students...
...and one female teacher.
Thus, making them repent.
But just when I thought my job was done, something happened before my eyes...
What is this...
...the students massively boycotted my lesson.
SubDESU-H Presents
Harsh Discipline
Mission to Pacify the Bad Schoolgirls
This is probably Homareko's doing.
I think so too.
Homareko...
Do you mean Kanegasaki Homareko?
Yeah.
This is no good.
You mustn't say that without any proof.
But...
Sensei, putting the question of who's at fault aside...
...it's most important that everybody return to the classroom...
...so you can get back to your lesson.
Well done, Mitsuki-san.
You're right.
But do you know where everyone is?
If they've left school we can't possibly find them all.
I've got an idea where they might be.
Listen up, everybody.
It's important here that you understand what this chemical is.
If you understand this much, you should be able to solve this problem.
She's not teaching badly.
Sensei, this is not the time to be impressed.
Oh, my bad.
Amazing that you knew they were here.
A place within the school where you can assemble that many without standing out.
That's Mitsuki for you.
What should we do? Jump right in?
No, let's not.
But, what a waste...
...to waste your talent on boycotting lessons.
Infirmary
Ah yes, yes.
That Homareko is doing her best in gymnastics.
She's quite the hard worker.
She often leaves last and trains alone in the gym.
She studies until late at night in the dorm.
I see.
Sensei, Sensei... Onee-chan, hurry.
Y-Yeah...
I've received a message from the gymnastics club to say they wouldn't exercise today.
Does this help?
Yes. Thank you very much, Kuji-sensei.
My.
I was the one who told her to find out.
I understand.
No, wow!
Can I kiss you, Mitsuki?
Yeah.
We can't lose to this.
Mahiru, you've changed, haven't you?
Yup, you see...
...I have fun in lessons and in the classroom now.
I can talk to Mitsuki-chan and Minami-chan now, too.
Thank you so much.
This is all thanks to you, Shimohei-sensei.
S-Sensei...
Could you touch my pussy, too?
Finger...
...he's inserting his finger.
This feels so good, Jou-sensei.
Sensei... Shimohei-sensei... I'm about to...
S-Sensei, your penis feels good.
Dee... per...
That feels too good.
Stop, this feels too good.
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Wow...
So deep...
...so deep inside.
No...
Wow... Jou-sensei... this is amazing.
It's like lightning!
My pussy is cumming like it's having an electric shock!
This feels good, Sensei.
You've really brightened up, haven't you?
You're a totally different person from when I first met you.
This is thanks to you.
No.
The "you" now is the real you.
I just helped a little to turn you from a caterpillar into a butterfly.
Sensei...
I want you to cum.
Let's cum together.
Together, cum with me!
The next punishment will be the last one for sure.
Mitsuki, Minami...
Why are you here?
Oh come on. We're here to see you exercise, of course.
I wonder.
Oh? In a bad mood?
That time of the month?
No, that's wrong.
It's because I know that you girls are close to that Shimohei-sensei.
Did you come here on his behalf because I made the class boycott his lesson?
No way.
It doesn't really matter to you what we say, does it?
You seem to understand.
A blackout?
A blackout, what a shame.
Shimohei?
Why did you come here?
Because I wanted to see your magnificent performance, of course.
And, because I want to punish you...
...so that your talents are being used for the right reasons.
Punish?
What's that supposed to mean? Untie me, now!
Please bear with me until I finish my speech.
Shimohei Joutarou...
...you're manipulating everyone.
That's not true, Kanegasaki-san.
We're doing this of our own free will.
What? You've gone mad!
You've all gone mad!
You can't be on par with Mitsuki-san in terms of studying...
...and with Minami-san in terms of sports.
You are putting too much effort into everything.
What's bad about effort?
I didn't say that effort's bad.
But... this effort is nothing compared to the effort Miharu-san puts in.
It's because you don't feel any pleasure from making an effort.
You perverted teacher!
Isn't effort without pleasure a sad thing?
I was listening to your lesson.
It was splendid.
And above all...
...what deeply impressed me was the fact of your teaching itself.
Normally...
...there would always be some not joining the boycott. But there wasn't a single one.
That shows great leadership and responsibility.
W-Why?
Why are you crying?
Why... aren't you using this great leadership and gift for responsibility for the right cause?
These subs were done by SubDESU-H.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
No, you just can't use them for that.
D-Don't!
Why are you using these skills for low class things such as teasing me?
You are wasting your efforts!
No!
It hurts! Pull it out, please... pull it out!
This is a punishment.
Of course it hurts.
We'll make it less painful for you.
Bear with it for a short while. We'll make you feel good like before.
The effort you put into studying and sports...
...isn't for the cause of chasing out a teacher that you hate, am I right?
It should be used for guiding your class - no, everybody in this school - in the right direction.
Believe in what he says.
Homareko!
Kanagasaki-san!
There is no lie in what he's saying.
When you made everyone join in and escape from his lesson...
...he was praising you.
Feels good!
Now, I feel really...
...happy...I think I’m happy!
You understood, didn't you?
Sensei...
Shimohei-sensei...
...I'm sorry. I was wrong.
You don't have to apologize.
What's important is what you do from now on.
Yes.
Let's give it our best.
Yes, sensei.
I'll help you.
Yes.
Kanegasaki-san...
...will you accept everyone's support?
Y-Yes!
This feels so good. I'm going nuts.
I'm going crazy...!
Farewell, everybody.
My presence is like that of a strong medicine.
And now that you're on the right path...
...it might become a strong poison.
For now, let's leave without saying goodbye.
Hoping, when you all become good citizens...
...that someday...
...and somewhere, we will meet again.