This should be good enough.
My "Cute Hikaru Collection" sure has gotten big.
His maid costume is so arousing!
I just can't get tired of it!
His cute swimsuit is also superb!
Even in the water, it's...
Ojou-sama?
You seem awfully happy, did something good happen?
Oh, Hikaru, what good timing.
We're about to do something good...
Eh?
SubDESU-H
A boy and his mistress!
Hikaru and Ayana's secret collection!
My choice of clothes suits you so well!
Jeez, why are you so cute, Hikaru?
C'mon, Hikaru. Pull up your skirt for me.
B-But, if I do, you'll see...
What do you mean by that?
I'm ordering you to do it!
But I shouldn't show you something so indecent...
If you can't, then I'll do it myself!
N-No! I can't let you do something like that!
This is so embarrassing...
Jeez, I know you don't actually mean that...
Your cock has already gotten so big. It's nearly coming out of these panties!
When I think that I'm being watched by Ojou-sama, I...!
You're not very convincing with your thing like this down here!
Your body is always so honest!
If you rub me like that, I-!
You always show such a cute expression, Hikaru!
Oh! Your huge cock has gotten bigger at the end!
Your cock is like a beast here!
Your dirty juices are dribbling out, and then there's the smell...
You're too lovely, Hikaru!
I can feel your breath!
You're too close!
Then I'll keep doing it!
But, to make sure you don't cum too quickly...
What are you doing?
I won't let you cum so easily.
I'll untie this when you've peaked.
Ojou-sama, if you tie it up like that, I'll...
Are you feeling tantalized?
However, I'm going to keep teasing you!
Cumming after you've been teased the whole time feels so good that you almost faint, right?
Now then, lay down there...
It's not fair that you're the only one feeling good, is it?
Make me feel good too!
Ayana-ojou-sama's sweet juices taste great!
Please use your tongue, Hikaru!
Suck me like you're a baby!
Hey, Hikaru...
You don't feel satisfied just having your cock played with, right?
Huh? N-No, that's not true...
But...
Down here, it's saying that it wants to be played with.
Ojou-sama! It's dirty down there-!
Your cock is throbbing.
You're feeling aroused, aren't you?
Ojou-sama! Y-You mustn't do it that much-!
Are you going to cum?
But, unless I untie the ribbon, you won't be able to cum...
Ojou-sama... I beg of you, please allow me to cum!
Please don't beg me with such a cute voice!
However, untying it so quickly is a bit...
I'll go crazy like this!
Then I'll have you let out a lot!
Your cute expression that wants to cum is so adorable!
I need to put it at ease...
I-I'm gonna-!
A-Ayana-ojou-sama!
Your huge cock looks like it's about to burst from trying to let out your hot semen!
C'mon, let it out like this!
N-No-! I-I-I'm gonna cum!
You let out so much of your thick, hot semen...
And this scent... I can't get enough of it!
You always cum so much.
You even made my tunic sticky...
Ojou-sama...
That felt so good that I thought I was going to faint...
Ojou-sama?
Why do I have to wear this swimsuit just to bathe?
That's because it's boring if you're just naked!
I bought this swimsuit since it looked like it would suit you, so we must use it!
I think your use of it is somewhat questionable...
A-Also, this swimsuit is so tight...
It's a normal school swimsuit!
I've got some frilly ones too. Would you prefer one of them?
N-No! This is fine!
But, having Hikaru written on the front is...
If that wasn't on the front of a school swimsuit, wouldn't it look strange?
I'm a male, so I wouldn't know...
I guess so!
Even though you came so much before, you've gotten so large that it's bulging out!
You're a boy who's bursting with sexual desire, aren't you, Hikaru?
I knew that you wouldn't be satisfied after doing it just once.
You're getting excited from looking at me in this swimsuit, aren't you?
I-I'm very sorry!
Getting so large and having it bulge out like this...
Your cock is too big, Hikaru!
However, this disproportion is also what makes you so wonderful!
Y-You mustn't do that, Ojou-sama-!
Oh my! You're getting so wild under your swimsuit...
You're very energetic here, aren't you?
Even though this is through the swimsuit, I can feel your hard, hot cock!
I can also hear your desires screaming: "I want to cum!"
O-Ojou-sama-! This is too much-!
Letting out such sweet moans... You love breasts, don't you?
Here we go! I'll stroke your cock faster!
Ojou-sama! You're going to crush my cock with your breasts!
Your hard, huge cock can't be satisfied unless they're my breasts, can it?
Y-Yes!
Only Ojou-sama's breasts can satisfy my cock!
That's right!
C'mon! Feel even better thanks to my breasts!
I-It feels great-!
You're making such a lewd face! Your love juices are leaking out, too!
Ojou-sama!
Please rub it directly...
I can't say no if you make that face!
I'll do it with my bare breasts!
C'mon! You should make yourself feel good too!
Make myself feel good?
Your cock's getting bigger between my breasts...
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Ojou-sama! I'm gonna cum!
I-I'm-!
You let out so much, even though this is your second time!
It's like you have an infinite amount of it!
I'm sorry...
Hikaru, did this satisfy you?
Please satisfy me this time!
I've become aroused from watching you, Hikaru...
I'm going to be eaten up by Ojou-sama!
Right then, thanks for the meal!
It's reaching my deepest spots...
Can you feel it kissing my uterus?
Yes!
My cock is deep inside-!
It's like it's biting me playfully!
How does my tight pussy feel, Hikaru?
The layers are clinging to me!
I'm about to cum again!
Is that so?
I want you to drench my insides with your hot semen!
Hikaru's cock is so deep inside!
Please pour your thick juices into my deepest spots!
Yes!
I'll splash my semen deep inside of you, Ojou-sama!
You always cum for me like you're extremely aroused, Hikaru.
Your insides just felt amazing, Ojou-sama...
Hikaru, you're not satisfied yet, are you?
You won't calm down until you let out more, right?
C'mon, I'll let you do whatever you want, so make sure you feel me all over!
I want to feel your body heat, Ojou-sama...
You've already cum so much, and yet...
Even though you're so meek, your cock is such a beast!
I'm very sorry!
When I saw your lewd spot, Ojou-sama, I-!
I couldn't hold back my sexual desires!
It's thrusting inside me! It's carving me up-!
Your big, long thing, it's-!
Your pussy is squeezing my cock, Ojou-sama!
Not so hard-!
Hikaru's thrusting into me! I'm gonna be crushed!
Your insides are squeezing me!
Hikaru's cock is penetrating me so deeply!
Ojou-sama!
N-No-!
Ojou-sama! Please feel more of my cock!
You're digging into me so deeply!
Ayana-ojou-sama!
Ojou-sama...!
I-I'm gonna cum-!
Looks like I've been seeded by you, Hikaru...
My insides are drenched with your semen...
O-Ojou-sama...
If you stare at me like that, it's embarrassing!
I love looking at you after you did your best...
I feel kinda tickled if you say it with a straight face...
It's great looking at you when you're like this...
Ojou-sama, stop making fun of me...