My new life had begun and I was getting used to living here.
Refreshing weather,
the chirping of birds that echoed
through this spacious kitchen.
Perfect taste.
I guess it's time to wake up the Young Lady.
But in this house, there's...
U-Um, Young Lady?
W-What in the heavens are you doing?
Oh, Minato, good morning.
This feels so relieving!
Minato?
Is all the urine going in the bottle?
Y-Young Lady!!
In this house, there's nobody but strange Young Ladies.
Otome Domain
The animation.
After losing my grandmother who I've lived with since
birth, only one person reached their hand out to me.
That was the Young Lady, Kazari.
The house that my grandmother used
to work in was an expensive mansion.
Board Chairman's Office
But I've no clue why the Young Lady of
the mansion is going so far just for me.
Welcome to my school, Mr. Asuka Minato.
I might be a student, but I also work as
the Board Chairman for the school.
My name is Saionji Kazari.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Asuka Minato.
Um...
What's the matter?
Why am I in a girl's uniform?
You need a reason?
Shirosuzu All-Girls Academy
This is an all-girls school.
Is that not obvious?
Yes, I understand that, but...
Is there a problem with this being an all-girls school?
Yes, a big problem!
I'm a guy!
Really?
Your name could be a man's or
a woman's, so I didn't notice.
She's definitely lying!
I don't think there should be any problem though.
Hey!!
I see. Like this, even if the wind flips your
skirt, you'll have nothing to worry about.
It fits you perfectly too, so I doubt
anyone will question your gender.
You also have a feminine voice. It's very adorable.
No, listen, I'm not saying that it'll
be fine as long as I'm not caught.
The board chairman is saying it's okay.
Also, it seems you got fairly into it considering
you brought your own drawers.
You just accepted it, didn't you?
Welcome to the Shirosuzu Academy.
Nice to meet all of you.
So cute.
I'm a girl.
Asuka Minato
I'm a girl!
I want to eat her up!
– Grandmother, from now on, I...
– Wanna try talking to her?
I get the feeling that I'm just going to be constantly
pushed around by Young Lady Kazari.
Young Lady?
It's morning.
Good morning, Minato.
Good morning, Young Lady.
Breakfast is ready.
Breakfast... Now that I think about it, I am hungry...
If possible, maybe you should comb
your hair before your meal.
You can do that much by yourself, right?
What exactly do you think of me?
Well, I'm going to greet the other guests,
so please head to the washroom.
There are other unique girls in the second
dorm of Shirosuzu Academy.
One of them is a girl who I need just a
little bit of preparation to deal with.
Okay.
Ms. Hinata?
Are you awake?
Kukuku. Welcome to my magic mansion.
I am the General of the East, Sarazukstra.
I am one of the four generals of the Demon King's
army, and the bringer of destruction to all Gods.
It's time for breakfast.
Okay! I'll change right now!
Food! Food!
H-Hey, M-Ms. Hinata?!
Please don't get undressed all of a sudden.
Huh? But we're both girls. What's the problem?
W-Well, uh... Nevermind.
You're so strange.
Oh no, I just took a real good look at her!
Ahem, now then.
Let's get back on track. The next girl...
Huh? What's this smell?
It stinks.
It really stinks!
Why is Yuzu-senpai... This is bad.
This is really bad. At this rate...
What are you doing?!
What am I doing? I'm helping out with the cooking.
This... This can't be happening!
I just made that!
No matter what you try to do, it'll be futile.
Kifune Yuzu, she's also known as the
Dark Master of Messing up Food!
She's a Dark element type!
The poisons she births from her abilities are...
What is all the commotion about?
This smell...
Young Miss, run!
I see. So Ms. Kifune is cooking, then?
She threw up!
This is nothing.
It's making you throw up too?!
Oh my, how does it always turn out this way?
This is the every day unfortunate, rowdy
lifestyle that I've become accustomed to.
That was terrible.
W-Why are you...
Naked...
Why are you naked right now?!
I got my uniform a little dirty by accident.
Geez, I'm a guy, you know?!
What I found deep in my geart
Changing Room
I wonder if Young Lady Kazari is
just not seeing me as a guy?
Was a flower bed of memories
The sparkle of smiles
But thanks to everyone pushing me here
and there, every day is really fun.
Makes me blush a little
Every day is indeed very fun, isn't it?
I've seen your face so many times, but
I'm seeing it from a different distance than yesterday
Ms. Yuzu? Was there really a need to take off your bra too?!
I always change into a sports bra for gym class.
I hide my blushing cheeks and look at you
O-Oh, I see.
T-They're huge.
That day (that day), the words we exchanged
Um, Ms. Minato?
Please don't stare at me so intently.
It's making me embarrassed.
It dyed the two of us
Love becomes courage
U-Uh, it's just that I have a washboard
chest, so I'm a little jealous!
Let's go forward!
The melody of tomorrow that we're singing
Thank you very much...
But they're just heavy. I don't think
they're that great to have.
Ties us together for the rest of our lives
Let's continue walking this path in front of us
How about you try holding them?
And ride this new wind by our side
Um, that's... that's nice of you to offer, but...
This kind miracle that you've created
Strangely moves my heart
That was really close.
I want to be by your side forever!
It's so hot!
I'm so thankful that we met each other
You and I will be together forever
I-I can see them!
Calm down. They're just panties!
Compared to what I saw this morning, they're nothing!
Minato?
Emptiness is form. Mind over matter!
Evil begone! Evil be struck down swiftly!
– Cast off the impurities. Mind clear and serene!
– Hey, Ms. Asuka, what wrong?!
Cleaning currently in Progress.
My body's not going to be able to keep up with this!
Just because there are no guys around, they
really let their guard down that much?
We're coming in!
Y-Y-You two, wh-why?!
Yuzu-senpai said that she really wanted to
take a bath right now for some reason.
I sweat a lot today.
Oh, so the cleaning is done already?
Y-Yes, it is.
I always take a bath after the cleaning's done...
Oh, then please allow us to join you.
Oh no, I'll leave...
Please have a good bath.
Onee-sama?
I wonder what happened.
Wait! Just wait a second!
After seeing that, I... I'm in a bad spot!
Minato?
You've been acting strange all day.
Are you alright?
This is the Young Lady Kazari's scent...
Are you not feeling well?
N-No, I'm fine.
I just can't really move right now...
I don't really understand.
What I mean is, um...
It's gotten big...
I couldn't hear what you said.
Um! My dick has gotten big!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to blurt that out.
So that's what this was all about?
Yes...
If it won't go down, then all you have to do is let it all out.
Come on, let me see.
Stop!
This is... it's impressive.
U-Um, Young Lady?
You can't!
You shouldn't be doing this!
It's okay. I'll help you ejaculate.
If you stay big like this, other people
will find out that you're a guy.
But...
If people find out who you really are...
I'll be in trouble too.
So leave this to me, okay?
Her tongue is wrapping around my dick!
What should I do now?
Could you tell me?
Well, try moving it in and out of your mouth.
Also maybe suck it?
That's too sudden... No...
Like this?
Minato, your voice is so cute.
It's twitching inside my mouth.
Young Lady! Young Lady!
It feels really good!
It's coming! I'm cumming!
Let your sperm out.
So this is Minato's sperm?
I've really done it now...
What are you depressed about?
Why did you do that?
Why'd you do that for me?
Good question... Because it'd be a problem
if you assaulted the students?
I'd never do that...
Otome Domain.
So she never really trusted me that much, huh?
Onee-sama, are you feeling alright?
So she only did that because she felt the responsibility
as the board chairman, huh?
Because it'd be a problem if you assaulted the students?
It feels like Young Lady Kazari's been
keeping her eye on me too.
Maybe it'd be better if I just left...
Okay! Let's have a real talk with her.
I can't continue to trouble everyone...
Any more...
The scent of Minato's sweat is...
Uh...
It's a pervert!!
Give them back.
Seriously, Young Lady?!
What in the heavens are you doing?!
Exactly what you saw me doing.
I was sniffing the scent of your sweat.
Are you a bona fide pervert then, Young lady?!
I can't help that I'm interested in
the smell of the person I like.
Huh?
Um... Huh?!
Don't tell me that you hadn't noticed?
You really are such a...
You like... But... Huh?
You just... kissed...
You're so dense that if I didn't do
that you'd probably never get it.
Young Lady Kazari likes... me?
I love you.
But I thought you've just been keeping an
eye on me because you had no choice.
What are you saying?
I've been trying to seduce you for some time now.
Young Lady!
No matter what I tried, you'd never even make a move.
I would never lick the dick of a guy I didn't like.
Your expressions of affection are horrible!
Young Lady, I... I like you too!
Really?
Yes!
I like you. From the first time I
met you, I've always liked you.
I'm so happy.
So that means you desire me, right?
So tell me, what are you going to do to me?
I'm not really sure what to do, but...
I want to try touching your breasts.
That's a little embarrassing, but
you can do whatever you like.
Th-This isn't touching.
Didn't you just say that I can do whatever I like?
I did, you're right.
My head's starting to space out.
I'm beginning to feel anxious.
My panties are already getting incredibly wet.
Me too. Just seeing you like this is making me...
It's making me unable to wait any longer!
That's... going to go inside me, right?
It might hurt.
That's okay.
Come on, put your dick inside me, Minato.
Please take my first time.
Are you alright?!
It hurts, but I finally got you.
Sow your seeds into me.
Minato, does it feel good?
Yes, incredibly!
Kazari!
You finally called me by my name.
Minato, your voice is very cute.
That's... It's tingling!
I... I feel like I'm going crazy.
Minato, I love you!
Kazari!
I... I'm gonna!
Cum!
Have sex with me until the very end.
I'm...
You came so much...
Yeah, the sheets are going to get dirty.
Kazari?
It'd be terrible if Yuzu or the others saw this.
It's fine for me to be here.
Minato?
More...
Minato!
Th-That's... Not there!
Minato, your dick feels great.
Do it more.
My mind's going blank, I can't think straight!
I-I'm cumming!
No, I'm cumming.
Minato... that felt so good.
Geez, Minato won't wake up at all.
That leaves me no choice.
So tasty.
A butt?
What's going on? It feels good!
Kazari?
What are these?
Handcuffs?!
Kazari...
Stop...
Did I do something?
Last night was our first night together.
You fell asleep after just having sex
once on our very important night.
So this is punishment for not lasting that long.
If you resist, I'll stop talking to you.
That's not fair...
Then how about you make me feel good too?
It's Kazari's pussy...
Minato...
Your dick is letting out dirty juices too, Minato.
Let me drink them too.
All of Kazari's love juices are coming inside me!
Your dick's getting bigger inside of my mouth!
I can't drink all of this.
Minato, let's... let's cum together.
I-I'm about to cum!
I'm about to cum inside your mouth!
Minato's cum is making my stomach so warm.
Today, I'll be the one making your dick go inside me.
Um, Kazari, what about the handcuffs?
They're staying.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm going to put your dick inside me.
It just slid in!
Kazari, your insides are so warm!
You're being so rough from the start!
It feels so good. It's wonderful.
I love your dick, Minato!
I want you to become even more perverted, Minato.
Your dick's rubbing against my
womb, it's making me so wet!
Kazari, this feels so good!
My mind's going blank.
Your dick's making me lose my mind!
Kazari!
I'm... I'm...
Minato!
Let's do it together.
I want to cum from you cumming inside me.
Of course! I'll let everything out inside you, Kazari!
I'm cumming while you're cumming inside me!
This much cum might get me pregnant.
You're the one who raped me though.
My body's all yours though.
And your dick is mine.
I won't let go of it for as long as I live.
Beatiful
student:
romance
exposed!!
Who's
her
partner
!?
Shiro
suzu
All-
girls
aca-
demy
News
paper
Find
the
sche-
dule
on
page
What is this about?!
When did this happen, onee-sama?!
Hinata-san? Please calm down!
I don't know what this is about either!
It seemed that the two of you had entered a special
relationship, so I decided to publish it.
The two of you?
What are you talking about...
Who's the other person?! Tell me!
Minato, I love you.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч