SIGN: Student Council room
And so, the retribution begins.
U-Um, you're in here, aren't you?
P-Please don't bully me...
I'm impressed that you actually came with the blindfold on.
U-Um, you're going to return those photos to me, aren't you?
Oh, you mean these?
Well, I guess you can't see them.
Hold out your hands.
N-No!
You're totally exposed in this.
Um, what are you...?
I'm getting ready to violate you.
Huh...
Huh?
No!!
This is what you wanted.
I'll make sure that you can see it.
No! Don't touch me there!
Huh? You want to pee?
T-That's not it!
T-Take it out!
Ordering me around?
You seem to be pretty full of yourself.
D-Don't move your thumb! Please!
I won't... I won't fight back, so-!
That's good.
Lift your ass.
Huh? No...
What's wrong? Were you lying?
N-No!
No!
Your voice is getting more perverted.
N-No! I'm-!
No, not there!
You're a lewd girl, just as I thought.
Huh?
W-What are you doing-?
Isn't it obvious?
Of course I'm going to put it in since we came this far.
N-No! Please don't!
It's tight...
No...
No!
Don't thrust so much!
What a good scream! Let me hear more of it!
No-!
No! Please stop!
Please? Oh, you want more?
No-!
Hey, hey.
Don't tell me that you're getting aroused from being raped by the person who blackmailed you?
What a slut!
I'll do more fun things to you.
N-Not there!
Not there, take it out! It's embarrassing!
N-Not my butt!
Not my butt!
Don't play with it-!
I'm gonna...
N-No! Please, cum outside!
No-!
No, no!
I won't be satisfied with just that...
Huh?
No...
No more...
No more!
I knew you were a lewd girl!
N-No, I'm not-!
It hurts!
You like it when it hurts?
I'm going to break!
Break? Don't you mean climax?
No way!
Looks like you're ready here.
Now then, let's begin.
Higuchi-kun, make sure to be on time.
Yes.
You won't do what I tell you to do?
Like hell I can!
How can I masturbate in front of people?!
I'll help you.
Hey! Stop this!
What's wrong, Higuchi?
You're pretty shriveled up here!
That's good!
If you look like that, then I have to meet your expectations.
Wha-?!
Does it feel good? How shameful.
I know! How can you be feeling aroused with people watching?
You sure are a pervert to be aroused by people watching.
No-!
He's a pervert, alright.
You better watch too.
Huh? Y-Yes...
You actually came!
Hi-Higuchi-san...
Why did you cum so much?
Are you trying to impregnate the floor?
Your embarrassment is the purpose of my revenge.
The other members had just stopped him from assaulting me!
Damn it! Why should I get suspended?
The humiliation they caused me...
I'll definitely get them back.
Cry and scream for me, at least.
Take a photo of yourself masturbating in class, otherwise...
There's no way I can do that!
The retribution has just begun.
My next target is...
This bruise...
Here too?
They're in hard to see places...
I bet it was a girl.
I-It hurts!
Huh? It hurts?
Are you trying to be a high-class lady?
I said don't talk back!
Huh?!
It's annoying, so don't look at me!
Huh? No-!
Hmm?
What a fancy room.
Hey! Stop this!
Kiryuu Misao...
You deserve the utmost humiliation for your doings.
Um, Misao-senpai, if you don't want to...
N-No, I'm just a bit nervous...
If you don't want your secret to be known, do as I say.
You can't refuse.
What are these?
Um, they're nothing suspicious...
My friend gave them to me, so it won't hurt as much...
Is it a stimulant?
I'm gonna take one too.
Hmm? It's the one that's popular now?
Okay, I'll trust you, Misao-senpai.
Takano-kun...
I-I'm going to take a shower...
Let's stay like this for a bit...
They're getting lovey dovey, huh?
That works fine for me.
Have a nice nap...
No!!
You bastard! Why?!
I guess you're still paralyzed...
You shouldn't shout so much.
You're the one who's been blackmailing me?!
That's me.
Hey, be quiet.
Otherwise your sleeping boyfriend will wake up.
Ta-Takano-kun!
Why are you doing this?!
I did what you said!
Oh well. I thought I might as well rape you while I'm at it.
No!
N-No!
What a cute voice!
Is this your first time?
O-Of course! It doesn't concern you-!
Y-You'll crush me!
I don't want this!
What are you...?
S-Stop it-!
You're nice and wet.
N-No, I'm not-!
That voice proves that you're aroused!
I'm not-!
Then how about we take a look?
Huh?
N-No!
Like I thought, you're wet.
No, stop it!
It hurts-!
What a great voice.
It would be a pity for me to be the only one to hear it.
What are you going to do to Takano-kun?!
No! Don't look, Takano-kun!
At least we can let your boyfriend watch you get raped.
N-No!
No!
No!!
No-! Not that-!
Takano-kun, don't look!
No! Don't rub it against me...
No!
I will never forgive you!
Yeah, that's good. Curse me.
Noo!!
She's bending her hips to make me feel better...
I should help out too!
It hurts-!
Don't thrust so much!
It hurts!
I feel really good!
Seeing that you're in pain really helps.
No!
Forgive me already!
So deep!
Don't-!
Don't thrust so much!
You'll ruin me down there!
I'll break!
I'll break-!
No! Not inside!
Why are you crying?
You did this to protect yourself.
How irritating!
I'll teach you what obedience means!
What?
Don't tell me...
No...!
We're not done yet.
You're going to bear further humiliation.
Next is this.
I'll take both of your holes so that you can become a woman.
Huh?
It's uncomfortable!
You sure are tight...
It's entering my butt!
D-Don't look...
Don't look, Takano-kun! Don't look!
Things are getting more interesting with your boyfriend watching!
I'll have to play my part too!
It hurts-!!
Can you feel my penis rubbing against your intestines?
Soon you'll be addicted to it!
No way!
Not my butt, it just hurts!
Not there!
Not there?
You're sucking me in!
No!
No, Don't look!
Hey! Can you hear it?
No!
Don't say such things!
What an excellent reaction!
I-I want to go to the bathroom!
Just let it out!
Your boyfriend and I will watch you!
No!
No! Pull it out already, pull it out!
No, I'm gonna-!
You're getting aroused from losing your virginity
while your boyfriend watches you? You whore.
No! I'm gonna!
I'm gonna-!
No more!
It's gonna come out...
It's gonna-!
I want to go to the bathroom!
I want to go to the bathroom-!
I don't want it in me!
Go on! Push it out!
N-No...
You're leaking like a dog...
We're just getting started... We've got more to come.
That's two down...
My next target...
is you, Shirakawa Mitsuki.
Over here, sensei!
Um, Higuchi-kun, you shouldn't be out here...
I know, that's why I called you here.
Huh?
We can be alone here, can't we?
I got some Blitz donuts, how about we have some?
I've always wanted to try these Blitz old-fashioned donuts,
but why did you...
You're always looking after me during Student Council meetings...
Even though other teachers
wouldn't even bother being a Student Council supervisor.
I just thought you were a fine teacher.
This is my thanks to you.
That's the first time...
Huh?
That's the first time someone said such a thing...
I'm really sorry about this.
I mistook the time of the movie,
and I made you stay out with me like this...
Oh stop it!
You treated me to dinner just for those donuts...
Also...
Also?
I was able to spend time with you, Shirakawa-sensei...
SIGN: Changing room
She's just changing, huh?
This is...!
So good!
Higuchi-kun...
This is honestly a surprise.
Hi-Higuchi-kun...
Higuchi-kun, more...
I shall use you completely, then.
But before that, I have to finish up with Misao...
I guess there's gonna be others at this time of day...
Hey! Don't say it like it's not your business!
If you do it any more-!
Watch your language!
What's up? Why are you so aroused?
How can I be?! Putting such things in me!
You'll be mistaken for a pervert like that.
And who's fault is that?!
I just gave you a present.
You're the one who put them in your butt and pussy.
Wha?! Don't say such embarrassing things!
Embarrassing?
What do you mean?
My butt, don't turn it up!
You're the one who's embarrassing!
There's an office worker watching you from behind.
There's no one there!
Haven't you had enough?
You've humiliated me enough...
It's not like I called you out for you to streak.
Then what?
I'll have you entertain me.
That's good, lick the backside too.
Put it in your mouth, next.
Make sure to use your tongue, too!
What? Then I'll-!
Now, then. We're just getting started...
This is the best!
Misao, doesn't my penis taste great?
She's already become my slave.
Shirakawa Mitsuki and Mimasaka Nanao,
I've still got some fun left for you!