Sign: Student Council Room
No panties or bra...
You've got good intentions. It looks like you've become more obedient.
No way...!
No! It's embar-!
What are you saying?
You can't help but want it, can you?
If you want it, keep doing this.
You're good, keep at it.
I've got a reward for you afterward.
Who would have thought that Nanao and Mitsuki had the same tastes...
I wonder who else she's masturbating?
Well, I thank whoever it is.
That video did look great, though...
Nanao, my revenge has just begun.
That concludes the report for this issue.
N-Now for the next item on the agenda...!
Regarding the old and broken items in the current clubs...!
I-I'm sorry!
I can't hold back now...
So good-!
Mayu, can you do me a favor?
W-What is it?
No... Not there!
You can't-!
I'm sorry, bear with it for a little longer, please...
N-No!
She actually did it!
I can't believe she's actually lezzing out with Mayu...
Make a girl orgasm and upload a picture.
Otherwise, this picture will be spread on the Internet.
Chairman Mimasaka!
Please stop this already!
Sorry, you're the only person I could ask...
Does it feel good here?
Not there!
No...!
Don't hold back, cum!
I guess it's time for the main act.
Nanao, my revenge is only at the level of foreplay.
Sign: Student Council Room
Oh, they're not here yet?
I eagerly came here to catch them...
I guess my plan didn't work out.
What a coward!
Do they think they can hide and control me by blackmailing me over the phone?
Well, whatever.
That composed look. I wonder how long it's going to last?
At least resist a little and make it fun for me.
C'mon! Come out already!
I know you're in here.
Who are you-?!
How unfortunate, your enthusiasm to catch me has gone to waste...
You coward! You have to do this to control one girl?
I looked up some information on you...
You're the type that wants to deal with things yourself.
That's right!
I was going to catch you and give your ass to the police!
Hiding behind a mask? You're such a coward.
Listen here, I'm being kind to you.
If you see me, I might have to take out your eyes or kill you, won't I?
I just don't want to do something so messy...
Then I'll have some fun with you.
What are you-?!
No!!
Hey-! Stop it!
No-!
Don't do that!
Stop it! Stop it right now!
Why would I stop?
Think before you speak.
Why do you think I called you out?
That's enough-!
Can you see?
I can tell the shape of it over your panties...
Don't look! Don't look at me!
Hmm? I can clearly see the shape from your sticky juices...
No way, I wouldn't get wet!
Can't you tell?
You're leaking so much love juice from your pussy...
T-That's not-!
Don't rub it so firmly-!
No need to hold back, you can moan all you want!
You bastard-!
What's with that look?!
You still don't seem to understand your situation...
No!
Don't look, don't look!!
Even if you say that, if you show it like this right in front of me...
No! No...
You're good at moaning, have you taken a liking to it?
Who would?!
Oh really? Then maybe you'd like something a bit more rough?
That hurts-!
Oops, sorry.
Looks like I ruptured your hymen instead of making you feel better.
Well, now that we're at it, how about I completely burst it?
No...!
Don't show me that!
How rude.
This is the thing that's going to violate your vagina, so you better remember it.
No...
Please...
Please, don't!
I have someone I like!
So-!
Please!
Anywhere but there!
Okay, then.
If you don't want to lose your virginity, then I'll do it here...
There-?
What's wrong?
You're taking it back right after saying yes?
Fine then, you can do whatever you want there... So please...
Right then, negotiations are over.
But...
No!
Huh? Didn't you say I could do anything I want?
I'll tell you beforehand, but even if you scream, I won't stop.
It hurts!
Pull it out, pull it out!
That's good.. Shake your butt more. You just couldn't wait, could you?
It hurts... It hurts!
It hurts, does it? It feels really good!
Your asshole seems to have taken a liking to it. It's welcoming my penis!
No! No...
No way!
Don't resist so much.
I don't want you to accidentally go to the bathroom while we're at it.
Don't say such disgusting things!
Disgusting things?
You're the one who wanted me to do this...
It... It hurts, It hurts!
You... you'll ruin my butt! Please!
What an excellent expression. Show me more!
No...
This is good, it seems like you're finally loosening up.
Don't cry so much, I'll slow down...
No more... Don't thrust any more...
Is that because you'll feel too aroused?
You can't allow yourself to get in such a state on your first time.
I-It doesn't feel good-!
Hmm, it won't be fun if you get aroused too easily.
More, scream more!
You're gonna break my butt!
This is good-!
Don't!
Don't thrust such a dirty thing into me!
No-!
I'll start feeling...!
Cry more!
My butt-!
Catch this, Nanao!
No!
It's filling up my butt...
I wonder what your expression will be like... when I reveal the blackmailer and take your virginity next time...
Right, Nanao?
But before that, I need to take Mitsuki-sensei's virginity.
Right there-!
Thrust more!
A matured virgin sure feels good!
Stop it-!
Don't say such things!
Hey, look at the camera...
No!
I've taken the liberty of recording the scene where you lost your virginity!
Wave to the camera or something!
No...
I don't want people to see this!
You're tightening around me all of a sudden!
How would I know that-!
If I'm right about that sensei,
you're the type of masochist who gets excited when she's being watched.
Those clothes suit you.
I bet you're already wet...
S-Stop that!
This is the last time I have to do this, isn't it?
I won't lie, since I've already taken your virginity...
This will be the last time.
But it's really too much for me to have sex with strangers...
You'll be fine, sensei. It's someone you know.
Huh?
Just wait there, they'll come by shortly.
I'll watch from here...
Over here, sensei.
Takano-kun?
Cosplaying? I didn't know you had such a hobby...
N-No, you're mistaken! I was forced to wear this...
Well, whatever.
How about we take a break on the benches, sensei?
You're good at this, sensei...
But don't cum first just because you felt too good.
Don't say such things!
I'm the one telling you what to do!
That's it...
I know, this is your reward...
Don't cry so much!
Your teeth are hurting me!
How is it? Is it tasty?
That dribbling tells me that you're mouth must really like it...
Then how about you show me that you love me so much by swallowing my semen?
We're not done, yet...
I bet sensei is feeling somewhat unfulfilled, too!
What are we doing now?
Never mind that...
No!
You've been itching to get a real one, haven't you?
You're dripping wet already.
No! Don't look!
Sensei, your lewd pussy is slobbering and wanting a real cock.
T-That's not true! Why would I-?!
That's a good voice. I guess your body is telling the truth.
Your dribbling pussy is inviting me.
N-No way!
Shut up with that ignorant talk!
Here I come.
I-It's entering me!
No!
It went all the way in. I guess you're quite used to it...
My cock fits well in your wet pussy!
No! Pull it out, pull it out!
You're my student!
You say that even though you're wearing those clothes?
Like I said, this isn't what you think-!
You shouldn't say such cold things
when you look like you're gonna cum with every thrust!
No way-! I'm not feeling aroused!
I think this'll be a good video;
a video of a masochistic teacher who gets aroused when being watched.
No, no!
Since we're doing this, let the camera get a better look at you.
No! No more! Please!
Pull it out, pull it out!
Who would have known that Misao's ex-boyfriend
would come in handy in situations like this...
C'mon sensei, look at the camera.
Please, don't record this!
I don't want it!
Sorry to keep you waiting...
Thanks, you sure are thoughtful.
Nanao... Finally my retribution will be complete.
So, we've got something to talk about?
Calling me out like this...
Um, well, since we're not exactly friends...
And we argue every time we meet...
I just wanted this to stop.
What are you saying, Kaoru? "We're not exactly friends?"
We've been childhood friends since we were little.
Umm...
I'll say this while we're at it. I do regret what I did.
I'm sorry.
Although it's not something you can forgive with just an apology...
There's something I want to ask. Can I?
W-What is it that you want to ask me?
If it's now, I'll reply honestly...
Hey, aren't you getting sleepy?
You've finally woken up.
Um, wha?
Untie me!
Sorry, but I can't do that.
It wouldn't be fun if you ran away before you hear me out.
What are you going to do?!
Didn't you promise that you wouldn't do anything to me?
That's-! That's why I...
That's why your prideful self gave me your ass in utter embarrassment?
What's with this?
This is Kaoru's room... I don't get it.
I broke the promise?
Or is that why I'm here?
For starters, I haven't broken our promise.
Who are you?
Because the one who promised you was the blackmailer.
I've got nothing to do with all of that, I just want to hurt you for myself.
A severe pain, one that'll last forever.
No way... Lies... You're kidding, right?
How can that criminal be you?
No, I've honestly been the one who's been tormenting you all along.
The reason? I bet you know.
But... I apologized before!
Everything... was too late.
No, stop!
I've always liked you, Kaoru!
Shut up!
If you're sorry about what happened, think of this as a way to redeem yourself!
What's with that look?! Your attitude really pisses me off.
You don't deserve any foreplay!
Huh? No, no!
No, no! Please, Kaoru!
It's too late now!
No!
It hurts!
This is the best.
I'm sure you're happy that you're redeeming yourself!
No, no-! No!
Oh?
What's this? You're going to help too?
Shaking your hips like that, you sure are a lewd girl!
No-!
That hurts-! Don't move! It hurts, it really hurts!
I hear that it hurts more for girls with thick hymens...
But I didn't know that you were so thick, Nanao...
This is great!
Look! My penis is entering your bloody pussy!
Forgive me-!
Humph! Forgive you?
You didn't listen when I said stop!
You don't deserve my forgiveness!
It hurts!!
I-I'll break!
How is it? Can you feel my penis reaching your uterus?
Stop it already...
You're starting to feel good? Unfortunately, this is revenge...
No, Kaoru, it's embarrassing...
What are you saying now?
How's this?
If I do it from behind, it reaches your deepest spots.
Don't... Don't thrust so deeply-!
No! No...
What a great voice.
My broken heart is finally healed by you, Nanao.
I'm gonna lose it!
Soon I'm gonna...
N-Not inside, please!
Please?! Don't keep being so selfish!
No! No, I'm not!
It's coming out...
It's filling me inside...
Nanao, I don't care how you really feel.
There's only one important thing...
And that is that the real fun starts now.