I'm starting a new life living in this place.
The weather here is fine,
and the chirping birds can be heard
from the spacious kitchen.
Okay, it's delicious.
Well then, I should wake her up soon.
But in this place...
E-Err... Milady?
W-What are you trying to do?
Oh... Good morning, Minato.
This feels heavenly...
Minato...
Is my pee spilling out?
Milady!
...improper ladies live.
Maiden Domain The Animation
After suddenly being left alone to fend for myself,
only Miss Kazari reached out to help
when I have nowhere else to go.
My grandma used to work
as a maid in a rich household.
[Chairman's Room]
I wonder why the lady from
there helped me this much?
Welcome to our academy, Asuka Minato-san.
Though I'm a student, I also serve
as the chairman of this school.
My name is Saionji Kazari.
P-Pleased to meet you. I'm Asuka Minato.
Well...
What is it?
Why am I wearing a girl's uniform?
Even if you ask...
[Shirasuzu Girl's Academy]
We're an all-girl's school.
Isn't that natural?
T-That's true but...
Is it a problem that we're an all-girl's school?
It is a big problem!
I am a man, after all!
Oh, are you?
I never realized since you
have a gender neutral name.
I'm sure that's a lie.
I think everything's fine though.
Nooo!
Oh, with these we don't have to worry
when the wind blows up your skirt.
It suits you well no one will
suspect anything about you.
And you also have a cute effeminate voice.
No, it's not about if anyone would find out.
The chairman says it's alright.
And you even willingly wore
the undergarments already.
You already gave up, right?
Welcome to Shirasuzu Girl's Academy.
I hope to get along with all of you.
She's cute.
There's a new face!
I am a girl...
[Asuka Minato]
I'm a girl...
Granma, from this moment onwards...
I don't think I can satisfy all of her whims.
Milady, it's morning already!
Good morning, Minato.
Good morning, Milady.
I already prepared you lunch.
Breakfast... By the way, I'm hungry.
It would be better to have
your hair fixed before the meal.
You can do it by yourself, right?
You...
What do you think I am?
Well then, I'm going to go greet the others.
Don't forget to wash your face.
In the second building of the Shirasuzu Academy, other ladies of equal standing also reside.
You'll need to be just a little mentally
prepared to meet one of them.
Alright.
Hinata-san?
Are you awake?
Welcome to the witch castle!
I am the Oriental General, Zarathustra!
From the demon king's army, left alone by the
heavenly kings, a warrior that transcended the gods!
Breakfast is ready.
Yay!
I'll be changing now!
Oops... breakfast... beakfast!
W-Wait... Hinata-san!
Don't suddenly get nude!
Eh? We're both girls so why?
That's...
Please forget about it...
You're weird, onee-sama.
I ended up looking all the way.
Now that the previous area
is done, only one left.
Wait, what's with this smell?
It stinks... It's repulsive!
Why is Yuzu-senpai...
This is bad! If this goes on...
What are you doing?!
What, you ask? I'm helping on cooking the meal.
How... How can this happen?
And I already made it earlier...
Making something like that is
way beyond understanding.
Kifune Yuzu... She's also known
as the Chef of Darkness!
Her main attribute is Poison-type!
Her power unleashes potent toxins...
What's with the commotion?
This stench...
Milady, take a refuge!
I see...
Kifune-san is preparing the meal...
She barfed!
What a baby...
And look who's talking!
Oh my! Why does this always happen?
As you see, I have to deal with
unfortunate events like this all the time.
I have seen something unsightly.
W-Why!
Why are you—
Why are you naked!
I stained my uniform a little.
I'm a boy!
[Locker Room]
I wonder if Miss Kazari doesn't see me as a man.
But with everyone being rowdy like this everyday is kind of fun.
Everyday is really fun, right?
Y-Yuzu-san! You don't have to
take your underwear off...
I always change to a sports bra on P.E. Class.
I-I see...
T-They're huge...
Hey... Minato-san...
It's a little embarrassing when
you stare at me that much.
D-Don't be!
I just feel a little envious when I see
the difference of our sizes since I'm flat.
T-Thank you...
But it's not really as big
of a difference as you think.
Here, try touching them as well.
E-Eh... that's... it's a chance... but...
That was a close one.
I-I can see it!
Calm down...
It's just panties.
It's nothing compared to what I see earlier...
Minato...
Shiki-Soku-Ze-Ku-Ku-Soku-Ze-Shiki...
Akuryou-Taisan-Mubyou-Sokusai-Shippuu-Jinrai...
Kenkou-Itteki-Meikyou-Shisui-Inka-Houou!
What happened, Asuka-san?
[Currently Under Cleaning]
I can't take it if things go on like this.
Girls can get that defenseless
when no men are around.
Pardon the intrusion!
W-Why are you two here?!
Yuzu-senpai insisted on taking a bath right now.
I sweated a lot today.
Oh! You're done cleaning here already?
Y-Yes I am...
I always take my bath after cleaning.
If that is so, why not join us together!
N-No! I'll be on my way!
W-Well then, I'll be on my way!
Onee-sama?
I wonder what's wrong...
Wait... Wait a minute!
When I see something like that, I'm gonna...
Minato?
You don't look good since earlier.
Is everything alright?
Miss Kazari's scent...
Do you feel sick?
I-I'm alright!
It's just hard to move around.
I don't understand.
What I meant was...
It... got... big...
I can't hear it.
My.. dick!
It got hard!
I'm sorry!
I said something weird.
So that's what it's all about.
Yes...
When you feel horny, you should release it.
Hey...
Show it to me!
Noo!
This is amazing...
Eh? Eh... Milady...
We shouldn't be doing this!
No... I'm gonna make you come.
If you're this hard, people
will know that you're a boy.
But this is...
If your cover gets blown up,
it would be inconvenient for me.
So let me handle this.
Milady's tongue is wrapping around my dick!
What should I do from here?
Please teach me.
W-Well...
You slide it in and out, and then suck it.
Too sudden...
Like this?
Your voice sounds cute.
It's twitching in my mouth.
Milady, Milady!
It feels good!
I'm gonna... I'm coming!
Shoot it out.
This is... Minato's sperm.
I ended up doing it...
Why do you look depressed?
Why did you do something like this?
For someone just like me?
Let's see...
Because it would be bad if you
end up assaulting other students?
...I won't do such a thing.
Maiden Domain
Am I that untrustworthy?
Onee-sama, you look down.
She only did that out of obligation
as this school's chairman, right?
Because it would be bad if you
end up assaulting other students?
I also feel that she is always
watching me from time to time.
Maybe I shouldn't be in here, after all.
Okay, I should properly talk to her about it.
That I'll be leaving to avoid
being a burden to everyone...
The smell of Minato's sweat...
E-Err...
P-Pervert!
Hey!
Give it back.
Oh, Milady... What on Earth were you doing?
Just as you saw,
I'm sniffing the smell of your sweat.
Did you become a full-fledged pervert?
Of course, I want to know the
smell of the person I love.
You mean...
Don't tell me...
You never noticed?
You really are...
Milady is...
But... huh?
That was... a kiss...
You are so dense.
You won't get it unless I do this.
Miss Kazari has.. feelings for me?
I am in love with you.
You mean... you never did it out of obligation?
What are you saying?
I've been seducing you all this time.
Milady...
But you never made a single move on me.
I won't just suck the dick of
a boy that I don't like.
You're just bad at expressing your love.
I also love you, milady.
Really?
Yes. I love you, ever since the day I met you
I'm glad.
You accept my feelings too...
Hey, what are you planning to do on me now?
I'm still not sure at the moment but...
I want to touch your tits.
It's quite embarrassing but...
You can do as you wish.
This isn't just touching.
You told me to do as I wish, right?
Y-You're right.
My head is spinning.
I want more...
My panties are drenched.
Me too, when I see milady's sexy body.
I can't hold back.
That thing... will go inside me, right?
It might be painful for you.
It's alright.
Come here.
Put your dick inside me.
I want you to take my first time.
Are you alright?
It hurts but...
I finally made you mine.
Let's mate a lot.
Minato, does it feel good?
Yes, very good!
Kazari-san...
You finally called me by my name.
You're voice is very cute.
It's twitching inside!
I'm going crazy.
I love you, Minato.
Kazari-san!
I'm... already....
Come. I want experience
sex up to the last thing.
I'm already...
I got so much inside.
Yeah. We got the sheets dirty.
Kazari-san?
It would be bad if everyone sees us like this.
I'm glad that I got to stay in here.
Minato... more.
Minato!
Not there!
Minato's dick feels so good!
Give me more.
My mind is going blank...
Oh no, I'm gonna come!
Oh no, I'm coming!
Minato...
That felt great.
Oh Minato, you're not waking up yet.
It can't be helped.
Delicious...
A butt?
What is this, feels good!
Wai— Kazari-san...
What are these?
H-Handcuffs?!
Kazari-san...
Stop that!
D-Did I do something wrong?
Yesterday was our first night together.
It was a very special day but
we ended up having sex only once.
So this is your punishment
for being inconsiderate.
I won't take any objection for now.
But that's...
So, make me feel good as well.
Kazari-san's pussy...
Minato...
You're also leaking a lewd dew.
Lick me too.
I'm also drinking all of her pussy juice!
Your dick is getting hard in my mouth.
Yours are oozing with syrup as well...
Minato, let's...
Let's come together!
Okay, I'm also coming soon.
I'm coming in Kazari-san's mouth!
I can feel Minato's semen in my belly.
I will be raping Minato for today.
Kazari-san, the handcuffs...
No!
I can't wait any longer.
I'm putting your dick in my pussy.
It's inside!
It's warm inside you!
Wait! You're suddenly getting rough!
I can feel it! So good!
I love your dick!
I'll get you more aroused too.
It's rubbing my womb, my pussy is trembling!
Kasari-san, this feels so good!
My mind is going blank!
Your dick is making me crazy!
Kasari-san!
Minato! Let's come together!
I want to come on your ejaculation!
Yes! I'm gonna shoot everything inside.
What's this?!
If you're gonna creampie me, I'm coming too!
If you'll come this much,
I might get pregnant.
I'm the one being raped though.
But my body is all yours.
And your dick is mine.
I won't let it go.
[Shirasuzu Girl's Academy Newspaper (Extra)]
[Beautiful Transferee]
[Passionate Love Discovery!!]
[Who's the partner?!]
What is the meaning of this?
Onee-sama, since when did this happen...
Hinata-san, just calm down. Did I do something?
It seems that you're with a special kind of
relationship that it created a public outrage.
They what?!
What are you talking about?
Who's the significant other?
Tell me who that person is!
Whooaaaaaah!
Oh my...
Minato...
I love you.
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project