Umm... Shindou-kun.
I love you.
Please go out with me.
Maiden Princess
~Satoru-kun~
It was supposed to be a simple study session
but instead I got my very first girlfriend...
B-But, you're cute, Okuno-san.
I'm, I'm just...
Jeez, how much of a pessimist are you, Satoru-kun?
Satoru-kun?
I'm always very conscious when you're around.
No, it may just be because I haven't really met any nice guys.
I can call him Satoru-kun, right?
Huh? Did I lose my pencil leads?
It's already classtime.
Okuno-san, use this.
T-Thank you very much.
Oh, so Yuuna-chan also can't go to the karaoke,
and they've just recently opened...
Umm, Okuno-san,
th-there's a new karaoke near the station.
Do you want to go together?
Huh?
Okay, Shindou-kun.
Even after that, whenever I didn't have time due to prep school,
you offered to take my place for after school cleaning.
You also introduced me to a good vet for my dog.
Is it really weird that I grew to like such a nice person like you?
I just said it!
Yeah, but I'm glad you're honest about it.
Wait, is this a confirmation?
It's true that I'm also too conscious about things.
In fact, I can somehow grasp the feelings of other people.
He's looking straight at me.
My breasts?
Is he looking at my breasts?
Hey, do you want my right breast?
My left breast?
Or both?
Oh no, why am I thinking about such embarrassing things?
Then, I'll take the left breast.
I-I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
He doesn't have to apologize like that.
I actually felt happy earlier...
Eh?
But it'd be embarrassing if I tell him to touch me more... right?
Umm, well...
Satoru-kun...
I want him to kiss me.
M-Megumi-chan!
It's really intense...
Our tongues are even intertwining...!
It's my first kiss and yet...
I'm a guy too,
So I felt like doing it when you told me
that you wanted to go out with me.
Can we?
Okay.
Not just a kiss, but I want to do more, lots more...
I, I don't...
I don't care about anything anymore!
I can't see him, but I know he's fondling my breasts.
Megumi-chan, your nipples are pretty.
I can feel his breath on my breasts.
He's really close!
His tongue feels too good.
I never knew being licked could feel this great...
Oh no, what should I do?
My nipples are starting to get a hard-on.
He'll think of me as a slut!
Wait... that's...!
His fingers are touching my most sensitive part.
Umm, Satoru-kun, it's my first time,
so please be gentle with me, okay?
Okay, I understand.
That's, that's my clitoris...
No, I'll really feel horny if he keeps on doing that.
From this point on, I won't be able to stop,
even if you tell me to, Megumi-chan.
No, please don't look too close.
So this is, the pussy of the class's cutest girl...
Satoru-kun is looking at it.
I-Is he going to lick it?
Is he?
His tongue would definitely feel good.
Hey, Megumi-chan.
I'm about to lick it.
W-Wait, it's dirty!
Please, lick it.
Make my pussy feel good with your tongue.
It's making really sloppy sounds...
My pussy is starting to overflow with love juices.
Megumi-chan, so you're really getting aroused with my tongue.
No, don't!
If you start sucking on it strongly like that, I'll really want more.
Insert it please...
I really want it now...
Megumi-chan, I can do it, right?
I'm going in.
It's Satoru-kun's dick, and it's gotten really big.
What should I do?
Are we really going to go all the way?
W-Wait, I fee scared...!
Dick, dick, dick, dick!
It's touching my pussy!
Oh no, now that I've seen it this big...
I really want It inside of me!
Relax.
But, I can't...!
I'm going to take Megumi-chan's virginity.
It's going in, it's really going in.
Satoru-kun's thing is penetrating me.
It's in.
It feels really hot.
My pussy feels all tingly.
Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm okay, just move.
It hurts a bit, but I have to bear with it.
It's my first time having sex,
so I want to fee good with Satoru-kun.
Megumi-chan!
Oh wow, my insides are being stirred!
Your insides are wrapping around me tightly, and it feels good!
Y-Yours too, it feels hot, and it's bulging...
So he's feeling it too...
He's feeling pleasure from this too...
I'm really happy.
What should I do?
I-It's my first time, yet I can feel it already!
I'm starting to become more lewd!
Megumi-chan, I'm about to...!
His dick is pulsating hard!
It's okay, just cum.
I'm going to cum too.
So let's cum together.
I want him to squirt all his cum on and inside my naked body!
After that, Satoru-kun and I officially started going out.
I wonder if he's going to think strangely of me,
if I say I want to study at his place again...
We've been having sex whenever we meet together lately...
I also feel like he's getting rougher and rougher each time.
Maybe today we'll...
Oh no, my pussy is vibrating with it!
I'll go crazy if this continues!
Because you're so slutty, I'm going to punish you.
S-Satoru-kun, forgive me!
No, I don't want this punishment!
Wait, I'm imagining weird things again.
Hey, Megumi-chan?
Sorry I'm late.
So, let's go to our place?
O-Okay.
Why is he blushing too?
Could he have... sensed what I was thinking?
I-I can't hold it in anymore.
No, don't, don't.
Don't be too rough!
Two fingers are inside me.
And they're roughly stirring my pussy.
If he keeps being this intense...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum!
Megumi-chan, did you cum again?
I came three times already.
It's overflowing with love juices,
this is embarrassing.
Today, I want to test something with you.
But why hasn't he fucked me already?
His dick is already hard and stiff.
I want to make him feel good.
Would he think it weird if I say I want to lick his dick?
Megumi-chan, suck it.
Suck... it?
Yeah, I want you to experience your first fellatio today.
Its intense scent,
its lewd stiffness,
these are the things that first come to mind.
So this is how she fellates?
I'm really happy!
So he's getting aroused with this.
I'm glad.
I'm going to lick all of it, okay?
She's fellating, but I can still hear her erotic voice.
Amazing, this is just amazing Megumi-chan!
It's twitching...
This looks interesting, I wonder which spots would feel better?
Maybe around its tip?
Megumi-chan, can you lick the bottom?
Is this alright?
Yeah, that's the spot.
Satoru-kun, I think I'm starting to like blowjobs.
Okay then, if you ever feel like cumming,
just cum inside my mouth.
Your face looks very erotic and cute,
just looking at it makes me feel...
I-I'm sorry for cumming a lot Megumi-chan!
Jeez, Satoru-kun, you came too much.
His cum is all over my face.
I'm sure my expression is quite lewd at the moment.
M-Megumi-chan!
Amazing, the looming scent of his cum...
Makes me not care about anything anymore.
Please make a complete mess of me with your dick!
Megumi-chan, I'm going to do it until I can't cum anymore!
Okay, do it.
Do it...
This position, my pussy is totally exposed,
it's difficult for me because it feels embarrassing.
I like being pushed like this.
Your thing feels even harder than normal, Satoru-kun.
It's because you're just so erotic.
I become very erotic whenever I'm with you.
Satoru-kun, just keep pushing hard.
Just keep on pushing, and pushing, and pushing!
I then fucked Megumi-chan many more times after that.
Oh yes, it feels good.
I don't know how many times I've cum already.
My pussy is getting really wet.
Oh no, my entire body will feel tightly if you lick me there.
P-Please, kiss me.
Kiss me!
Oh wow, this is really amazing.
He really knows what I want to feel.
It's okay, be rough with my breasts if you want to.
I feel really horny when you keep doing that.
Please, do it rougher, rougher!
What is this feeling?
His thing is hitting something deep inside.
Is it the entrance to my womb?
It's being penetrated already!
Feeling horny while doing it rough...
You're surprisingly lewd, Megumi-chan.
Oh no, please don't say that.
My body feels hot with embarrassment.
My pussy is starting to pulsate!
I'm about to cum.
Satoru-kun I'm about to, I'm about to cum...!
Just cum, Megumi-chan.
Just cum!
No... don't...
Don't push it too hard!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...!
Let's, let's cum together...!
We already did it four times,
but each session lasted a long time,
and it felt really good.
It's not going to get a hard-on for now even if you touch it.
It's okay, I kind of like it limp too.
Wait, don't!
I love you, Satoru-kun.
I love you.
I love you very much!
You know every single thing that would make me feel good.
Megumi-chan!
But I think I can't say it affectionately just yet,
though I'd like to be able to someday.
Oh, Satoru-kun, it's starting to get hard again.
I'm happy.
Megumi-chan...
Satoru-kun, look.
My pussy is wet again.
I'd be happy to let you play with it again if you want.
Well, it's true that your pussy is wet again, but...
No, no, not there...!
Your asshole is also twitching, and it looks erotic.
No stop, that hole is dirty!
Don't!
But if it's you, it's not dirty!
He's inserting his finger in my ass.
It feels very weird.
I think my love juices are about to flow even more.
Whenever I play with your ass,
your pussy gets even wetter.
Are you aroused?
N-No, I'm not feeling aroused!
Jeez, quit it already...!
Oh no, it feels good.
My ass feels really good.
Megumi-chan, I want to put it in this hole.
Can I?
Can you stick out your butt more?
O-Okay, like this?
So, we're going to do anal?
I'm a bit scared, though.
But I want to be connected with him there, too!
Okay then, here I go.
Please, do it gently, okay?
It's tight! It feels like it's squeezing me hard!
His dick is opening up my ass!
it feels like it's about to get ripped apart!
Megumi-chan, it's all the way inside.
My first time having anal sex is also with Satoru-kun...
W-What is this?
Don't stir my insides...!
This is just too much!
It's as if it's sucking me inside!
It feels very good!
H-He's feeling really aroused.
He's actually getting aroused with my ass.
Me too, my body is starting to feel hot.
It feels good for you too, right?
That's...
Oh no, this is embarrassing!
Don't read my mind so you know how I feel.
For me to feel so horny while being penetrated in the ass...
I've become a pervert now!
If you don't want it, shall I stop now?
Wait, please don't stop.
It feels good.
It feels very good when you penetrate me in the ass, too.
That's why...
That's why I want you to mess me up some more!
Oh crap, I'm about to cum!
His dick is starting bulge!
I'm sure I'll cum too if he cums inside my ass!
I'm going to cum anally!
Megumi-chan!
Satoru-kun!
Cum, cum, cum!
Cum lots...
Inside me!
Megumi-chan, you came while having anal sex.
That was very erotic.
He's pouring it all inside.
It's still pulsating.
Lots of his hot cum is flowing inside.
Can we stay like this for a while longer?
Yeah, it's okay.
I want to stay connected like this with you forever, Satoru-kun.