After Father died,
his secretary Shinohara-san took over
the hold of the Kamishiro Family.
No!
Your pussy is very lewd, Kotone-san.
See?
It sucks onto me.
If you... if you do it so roughly I'll...
Huh?
Why are you complaining? This is nothing.
Ne-Nee-san...
Nee-san!
Mamoru, please... don't look...
I don't want to be seen like this!
Oh! Your pussy is squeezing tightly!
Are you excited from being watched by your brother?
That's not true! It's not..
It's only because of the Bikou!
Mamoru's penis... it's become that big...
He wants to ejaculate but he can't... it must be painful...
Ne...Nee-san...
He wants to ejaculate but he can't... it must be painful..
The fume that is filling this room is called Bikou...
After smelling it, anyone's body would
start to heat up uncontrollably.
Nee-san, I'm sorry. I... this...
It's fine... It's fine, Mamoru.
It's all my fault
Even though such horrible things are being done
to me I'm feeling it ... Even though I shouldn't...
Kotone-san, the tip of my penis is
hitting the entrance of a womb.
Do think that you'd start moving your hips on your own...
My body... wants it...
It wants my Master's sperm so much,
my womb is... lowering down...
Oh? So you want my seed that much...
I beg you, my Master! Hurry, hurry and let it out!
If this goes on, I'm going to ovulate!
No! You can't, Nee-san!
I'm sorry, Mamoru, I can't hold back anymore.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming from Master's dick!
There! Here we go!
Kotone!
No!
My pussy...
is being messed up...
No!
Hot stuff is... going deep inside my womb...
Oyako Rankan The Animation
Ne-Nee-san...
I'll pour much more and more inside you.
It's just started!
Master... please let me go...
No!
If you don't hurry to satisfy our visitor and
release Mamoru, he'll really go crazy.
Please!
Master, please use Kotone's pussy... more! More!
Please use it lots!
It's flowing in...
Mamoru...
Yukino, how's madam-how's Saya-sama doing?
Yes. She's going to a p-party with the villagers tonight.
I see...
Well I guess that can't be helped.
She couldn't give birth to a man
who could be heir of this family.
Please, everyone...
Stop this...
Stop... please... stop...
This is horrible... I'm just here to participate
in a get-together with everyone.
That's why we're all having fun together like this, right?
No, no!
Don't suck my boobs!
Not there...
Ah, such disgraceful boobs you have.
The nipples are hard from being touch
by someone other than your husband.
I'm not that kind of...
Let me taste you more, Madam.
No... No...
Madam, Madam, why not have a drink.
Um, I'm sorry... I can't drink very much.
Huh?
Something... in the wine?
The so-called aphrodisiac.
Don't worry.
No!
Madam, great! Your pussy is squeezing tightly!
Please! At least put protection... put on a condom please!
It's a dangerous day for me, so...
Isn't that perfect?
If you get a child, you can make him the heir.
It's too late now.
So cruel... forcing me to do it... and making
me go through such embarrassing things.
Showing it to everyone like this...
What are you talking about?
You'll get along... with all of us, right?
Madam?
Amazing... It's going all the way inside...
So much deeper than my...
Not this... Take it out! Please take it...
No!
That guy's dick isn't even half a bit incompetent.
She'll go crazy right away.
Bear it You have to bear it, Saya.
If this goes on, I'll really go crazy.
I'll be violated by everyone in the village!
No more... stop going in deeper...
It's hitting the entrance of my womb...
the tip of your penis... it's hitting!
It's been my dream to be in love
with each other with Madam!
Don't say "be in love with each other", this is all wrong!
It's wrong but...
Wait, hey...
No!
No! I'll break!
Honey, please save Mamoru!
I, I can't hold back anymore!
It's coming! Something amazing
is going deep inside my womb!
I'll cum... Nol
This must be punishment.
To punish me for not giving birth to a heir.
I'm sorry, Honey...
And Mamory, Kotone, Ririko..
Mamoru, you poor child...
You were forced to hold back from
ejaculating because of me...
I have to do something for you.
It was hard for you wasn't it, Mamoru?
It was painful, right? Don't worry. I'll set you free now.
It's fine, cum as much as you want I'll take it all.
My body's been stained, but I've learned
to do a lot of lewd things.
If someone like me can be the slightest help to Mamoru...
Nee-san, I can't hold back anymore!
You can't!
I want to become one with Nee-san!
If I connect with Mamoru...
I don't know what I'll become...
Nee-san's insides...
Nee-san's insides are drenched...
You've been holding back as well!
Stop!
Don't say that...
It's not... This isn't!
I'm sorry, Nee-san, I can't stop anymore!
I didn't think that Mamoru's would feel this good inside!
Not just the womb... if you keep hitting there... No!
This is bad. I can tell that my womb is happy...
It wants more of Mamoru's sperm ... the
entrance of my womb is opening!
Nee-san! I'm going to cum!
No! I'll cum! Cumming!
Nee-san's insides are sucking on me... it's hot!
Mamoru...
You've done quite the outrageous...
Oyako Rankan
Miss Kotone's body is very important
for the sake of the banquets.
I'm sure you're clear of it.
The visitors to the banquet are very interested in you.
E-Everything one... starting now
Kotone will be using her body...
to teach everyone how to make babies
Everyone's watching it...
My most important place... is being
violated by so many eyes!
Hey, spread it more.
Yes. This is Kotone's pussy.
You put a penis in here, and make babies.
Amazing.
It's wet.
As if it's inviting a dick...
It's embarrassing, but I have to bear it.
I have to save Mamoru!
No, no!
Put a penis inside!
Ri-Ririko, why!?
I heard from Shinohara-san, that poison
has accumulated in Nii-san down here...
From Shinohara-san?
Instead of Nee-san, Ririko will
take out the poison for you.
Wait... huh?
Ririko... likes... Nii-sama. I've always,
always... wanted to do this.
Hey, um, Ririko...
Nii-sama's looks so big and tasty!
Yukino, you can come in!
Mamoru-san.
Ririko-sama... me too...
Yukino and I will do it together.
Nii-sama... in fact, Yukino has wanted to
become close with Nii-sama as well.
That's... no!
Amazing! So much is coming out!
Nii-sama, do you feel good?
Is Ririko doing this correctly?
If... if you suck on it that much...
Ririko will detoxify Nii-sama's naughty penis every day...
and return you to the usual great Nii-sama!
This slippery sensation of the tip...
The hardness of it standing erect...
Mamoru-san, please excuse me.
Yukino-san!
Compared to Ririko-sama, my breasts are
small, but I don't mind doing anything.
Nii-sama! It's twitching and getting hot!
I'm going to cum...
I can tell... it's twitching because it's about to cum right?
I love you, I love you!
I love you, Onii-sama!
So this is Nii-sama's...
Amazing! You let out so much and
yet your penis is still so large...
Ririko... but still, you shouldn't do this!
If this goes on you'll end up like Nee-san, too!
Don't worry about it.
I'm obtained permission from Shihohara-san.
Huh?
All's going according to plan.
If I use that man well, then from Miss Kotone to
Yukino... I can bring all of them to the banquets.
Mamoru...
I didn't know that you were this perverted...
So soft...
As expected from Miss, your use of tongue
is amazing. This feels too good!
If it's just me, I don't care what you
say; I don't care what you do to me.
For Mamory... If it's for saving Mamoru...
Woah, gonna cum again!
Please, hurry and cum!
You can use anywhere you want,
just hurry up and end this!
Everyone's is flowing inside!
It's hot!
My womb is so full from sperm!
This is...
Nii-sama's is so hot... it's pulsing...
Ririko can't hold back anymore, either.
Ririko...
I think I'll... I'll go crazy...
Nii-sama's penis is really good! It's good!
Mamoru-san... please, lick me down here...
Yukino-san, I'm...
That's right, please lick my soaked pussy.
Please feel more excited from this!
It feels good! No... No!
It feels so good I'll go crazy!
Nii-sans sperm! Please give it to where a baby is created!
Give me lots and lots!
Nii-sama!
Hasn't it ended yet? Please give it a break...
It has just begun.
You haven't used this place yet, right?
That's... not there!
Woah, this is bad...
No! Stop it! Don't move!
My butt... my butt will break!
But, you're squeezing quite tightly. Are you feeling it?
No way! That's not..
Why? My body is getting hot from these things...
Am I really feeling it?
Hey, aren't you about to cum?
No! Amazing!
They'll make me cuml
Even though I don't want to, my body
won't stop! My womb is ovulating!
No good!
What's this? It's rubbing...
Nii-sama s and Yukino's are... rubbing
so much against me!
Both of you are drenched down there. If feels good!
Ririko-sama.
Yukino! Not there!
Don't suck my boobs!
Ririko-sama, your boobs are very lovely.
They slippery and soft, and the nipples are so hard...
That... Don't say that! This is the first
time I've... my pussy is so hot!
Nii-sama!
Sorry, I'm about to be at my limit!
My too... I'm going to cum!
Everyone... Everyone's cumming together!
Nii-sama... please don't forget.
It's Ririko and Yukino that helped Nii-sama out.
From today we'll be the replacement for Nee-sama.
Sorry, Nee-san...
Amazing, she's covered and filled with cum!
If she get's creampied this much, there's
no way she wont get pregnant.
Mamoru..
Please, please God, if I'm impregnated
please let it be Mamoru's sperm...
Please let it be Mamoru's baby...
I beg you!