I started to spend more time with my
little sister since our parents divorced.
I remember Yui's face looking
just like a baby's back then.
Onii-chan...
What's wrong?
I have to take over my father's role.
I have to protect Yui.
Onii-chan, look!
Do I look good in my uniform?
Well, even a foal will look good in a dress.
Foal?
I might have already been feeling this anxiety at that time.
I'm not a foal, I'm a little sister~!
It's alright.
I convinced myself that Yui will stay
as the same innocent girl she is.
I turned a blind eye on the fact that she's growing up...
...until that day.
I'm aware of it myself.
Something is wrong with me.
Doing such a thing on my sleeping
little sister night after night...
I have to gradually loosen it up.
Yui's love juice...
I can barely fit two fingers now.
I can't put this inside her yet...
I want to do it... with my little sister already!
I want to have sex with Yui!
I want to be Yui's first, both in her heart and body!
I want her everything!
My mind got muddled with both
pleasure and depravity from Yui's scent.
Our relationship as siblings won't be
the same again if Yui finds this out.
Something went wrong inside me since that day.
a week ago
You got a love confession?!
Yeah...
He said "let's go out together".
I'm wondering what to do about it.
You're too young for such things like dating, Yui.
That's not true.
Everyone else already has a boyfriend.
What are you even saying?
Don't tell me that...
...you're thinking about dating him?
I felt as if my heart is being torn apart ruthlessly.
I took it for granted that we'll always be together.
I thoughtlessly believed that Yui
will be my baby girl forever.
Even so...
If she'll end up being taken by someone...
Yui, don't wake up just for this one night.
It was a mere whimsical thought at first.
I read a particular scene in a web novel.
The heroine made up about getting a love confession
to find out about how the man he loves truly feels for her.
They ended up becoming lovers because of it.
If I'll say that someone confessed to me,
I wonder how onii-chan will respond?
He usually faces me with that same carefree smile,
but now he's making such a face just from what I said...
I'm happy.
I'm happy. I'm happy. I'm happy.
...you're thinking about dating him?
I haven't given him an answer yet...
I was filled with joy that I missed
the chance to tell him it was a lie.
It's onii-chan's thing that's
touching me down there, right?
I never would have thought
that things will end up this way.
What kind of face is he making right now?
I feel uneasy...
...and scared...
Any more than this and I'll wake her up...
I could only pretend to be asleep.
Since then, onii-chan went to
do the same thing every night.
I pretended to be asleep each time he does.
He touches my own parts that
I've never even seen myself.
I feel uneasy, being unable to see what's happening.
Even so, I can't find the courage to open my eyes.
That's because I'm so embarrassed.
Even if I'm being exposed so much
and I'm feeling good from being touched...
Onii-chan came all over me again tonight.
I'm glad.
Alcohol? Mom isn't even drinking...
That's weird...
I'll make us dinner so drink this juice while waiting.
'kay.
Huh, isn't this...
I'm feeling light-headed.
I see... I fell asleep...
And onii-chan is doing lewd things to me
just like he always do...
He's going at it more intensely than usual.
I wonder if he's planning to have sex with me this time.
She might be in a deep sleep now, but she's still a virgin.
She'll feel the pain if I put it inside her...
Is she trembling? Don't tell me...
Yui, wake up if you don't like this!
I'm sleeping.
So will you... do it?
Is she not gonna wake up?
I want to put it in!
Put it in!
Onii-chan's thing went inside me!
No, I have to keep my eyes shut!
I'll make sure to stay asleep,
so keep doing it!
My part inside where his fingers couldn't reach
is getting stretched wider by his thing!
It's rubbing in a place where it feels good.
He's going at it relentlessly!
But I'm happy.
I'm making onii-chan feel good, am I not?
My insides...
They feel hot all over!
I can't hold my voice in now!
I came inside here but she's not waking up.
It's onii-chan's semen...
He released it inside me!
We're siblings, but I don't mind him getting me pregnant.
My head feels so light.
I can't hear anything else but slushing lewd sounds.
I can't think of anything else besides the pleasure.
Onii-chan, keep doing it more!
I want to make you
feel good inside me.
Onii-chan... Onii-chan...
Onii-chan...
Yui... I'm about to come...
So you can wake up now!
Onii-chan!
Yui...
Onii-chan...
That was a lie...
That thing about getting a
love confession was just a lie.
Really?
Onii-chan...
My head feels fuzzy...
What's wrong?!
If that wass just a lie, then what
was everything I did to Yui for?
They both had their first sexual experience
together without talking to each other.
Are you on your way home too, Yui?
Onii-chan.
Yes.
Shall we go home together?
Okay.
Onii-chan?
Onii-chan!
I want to have omelet rice for dinner!
Huh?
I want to eat some omelet rice!
Okay.
Got it.
I was unable to ask Yui if she remembers
what happened on that night.
But I won't be able to forget about it.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization