It's already been two weeks since
I raped my little sister in her sleep.
I never went to Yui's room ever since.
It seemed like she realized
what happened that night.
Yui... I'm about to come...
So you can wake up now!
Onii-chan...
That was a lie...
That thing about getting a
love confession was just a lie.
Really?
Her saying that the love confession was just a lie
might just be a confusion from her being drunk.
Good morning, Onii-chan!
Yui...
I have day duties so I'll be going first.
I'll be on my way!
She doesn't seem to remember
what happened that night.
We should just stay as normal siblings again.
Onii-chan...
What's the matter?
Are you not feeling well?
N-No...
This is just a sleep-inducing medication.
Huh?
I've been having sleep difficulties lately.
And it says that taking this
will give me a good sleep.
Why is she telling me about that?
That's why I'll be drinking this
before going to sleep tonight.
Yui, what is on your mind?
Yui?
She's not waking up.
Is the medicine really working right now?
I always regretted it since then...
About the fact that I raped Yui
due to my selfishness...
I decided to end it right after that.
I decided to be the good
older brother that I used to be.
I wanted to shoot it inside her all this time.
I can, right?
It's okay, isn't it?
She even drank that medicine just for me.
So, no matter what I do to her...
Damn...
Damn, it feels so good...
While looking at Yui as I keep thrusting a lot like this,
the feeling of depravity surges
as much as the pleasure does.
The one who made this opportunity for me
is nobody else but Yui herself.
That fact overwhelms my mind.
Coming inside her would be bad.
But I know that Yui will take it all in,
so there's no stopping myself!
Yui?
Onii-chan!
Good morning.
Let's go to school together.
O-Okay.
Did she figure out what happened last night?
What's wrong, onii-chan?
Hmm?
Yui wants us to be normal siblings.
She was only accepting my lust and nothing else.
Then, it's like this relationship is merely physical...
And later again that night, Yui...
...drank the medicine in my sight.
This isn't what I wished for.
However, I could never forget
about Yui's soft sensation
so I raped my sleeping little sister.
For every night...
That medicine became a cue
for me to go to her room.
I used my defenseless little sister
like a tool for self-pleasure.
Over and over...
I poured it all deep inside her.
When the morning comes, we're back
to acting like normal siblings.
Unless I drink this, onii-chan won't be doing that.
I'm sleeping.
So will you... do it?
Is she not gonna wake up?
I want to put it in!
Put it in!
Onii-chan's thing went inside me!
After the first time that we had sex,
onii-chan never came back to my room again.
Even though he used to come here every night...
I don't know how to face him anymore...
Onii-chan...
Why?
Aside from pretending like I knew nothing,
I don't know how else to act...
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, why won't you come here again?
I'm already like this...
Onii-chan... Onii-chan...
Onii-chan...
I can't stop it...
Maybe the reason that he stopped coming here
is because I woke up at that time.
Onii-chan...
My head feels fuzzy...
If I won't be waking up, I'm sure
that he will be coming back again.
As long as I keep drinking this...
Yui?
Yui...
I was having trouble sleeping...
I'll be going to bed now.
Good night.
Okay...
Onii-chan, forgive me.
Onii-chan came here...
He's more assertive than last time.
Stop looking down there, It's too stimulating!
This is embarrassing!
Onii-chan's finger feels amazing!
It feels good!
So good! It feels good!
Being licked like that tickles me...
What should I do? I came!
What should I do if he notices that I'm awake?
No, I just came and yet...
I'm coming right now, but he won't stop!
Is he not stopping because I'm fast asleep?
It's messing up with my head.
This pleasure is too much!
Onii-chan is about to come...
I'm asleep as you can see...
So come! Shoot it inside me!
Oh...
Yui...
Onii-chan.
Having trouble sleeping again tonight?
Yeah, but I already took the medicine.
I'll be going to bed now.
Good night.
Good night, onii-chan.
Huh? Isn't this...
Did Yui forget...
Huh?
Huh?!
Don't tell me that...
Yui...
You're awake, aren't you?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization