Umm... Haruna-san.
Yes?
A-Actually, I really am...
I really am crazy over woman's butts.
I always think of touching them, fondling them,
pushing my face into them,
even sniffing and licking them.
I've always loved them ever since I was a kid.
I'm a pervert.
Me too...
I'm a pervert like you, Morisawa-kun.
I also want to push my face into a man's butt,
to pleasure him with my mouth on it.
I'm a woman who always fantasizes about doing such things.
Haruna-san!
Can we start over?
Starting from this pleasurable moment.
Morisawa-san...
I know that I can't take back what I said anymore.
And I understand that I will be discriminated for it.
Even so, I don't want to give up when it's just begun.
Please, with all my heart, let me be a match for you.
Yes, with pleasure!
Haruna-san...
Yuuji-san, Yuuji-san?
Yuuji-san!
Huh? Haruna?
Thank goodness.
You just started sleeping while we were in the bathroom.
You were about to drown earlier.
You seem to be really tired from work.
Are you alright?
S-Sorry.
I'm okay.
I was having a dream.
A dream?
Yeah.
A dream of the day when we first met
after a matchmaking session.
Your clit feels really stiff now.
Please don't just play with my clit.
I know, you want me to touch this too, right?
My butt...
Yuuji, my ass feels good.
You sure are used to my ass licking already.
Even now I feel embarrassed about it,
but being kissed in the ass feels really good.
It's the inside that feels good right,
with all my tongue wriggling in.
Y-Yes...
In my asshole...
There, that feels good.
My embarrassing hole,
my slutty ass.
Please keep on licking it!
You just took a bath, and yet both holes
are already drenched in love juices.
Yuuji-san, I have a request to make.
C-Can we have anal sex?
I've been practicing alone lately.
Will you be alright?
It seemed very painful for you before, so I stopped doing it.
That's why I kept pushing myself.
Though I'm still not sure...
I'll do my best! So please...
Don't overdo it, okay?
Does it feel okay inside?
I'm alright, please move.
Make yourself feel good.
And I'll want to make myself feel good too.
Okay, here I go!
Haruna, can you feel it?
Your anus is now becoming my dick hole.
I can feel it... my anus becoming your hole.
Your asshole feels very hot and tender.
It feels really good for my dick!
It's your dick hole now.
I'm happy.
You were playing with your ass the entire time just for me.
You were pushing yourself for anal sex because of me.
Yes, I did.
Every day, every single day.
I kept playing with my asshole to let it get used to this,
because it just wants to have your dick badly.
So please, release all of your dick's secretions inside my hole!
Here I go!
Me too, I'm cumming!
Yuuji-san, I'm sorry, I knew you were already tired and yet...
Now we have to take a bath again.
No need to worry about it.
It felt good anyway.
I work hard, so I can freely have sex with you.
If you hold yourself back because I'm tired,
it'd be like taking away my reward.
Th-Then I'll do my best too!
I'll study more and more about sex.
Also, after working that hard, could I also...
Could I also ask for a good reward?
Alright, all done!
It's his day off, so I must let him eat
however and whatever he wants.
Now then, time to wake Yuuji-san up.
Yuuji-san, it's morning!
Food's gonna go cold if you don't wake up.
There...
If you don't wake up...
I'm going to kiss you.
Yuuji-san...
I'm awake, I'm awake already!
Hey, I said I'm awake alre-
Yummy balls.
I'll be taking these balls too.
She's not listening!
No, not there...!
Really good...
It's about to cum!
Then cum, cum!
And it's about to get all over my face!
Tanks for the meal.
Sorry, it looked really tasty so I just...
Well, don't worry about it.
I was quite surprised, though.
Huh? You're not eating?
I just drank your cum, so I want to savor it a little more.
Besides, just seeing you eat heartily
like that already makes me happy.
And the warmth of your dick also warms my heart.
Well, I am very busy every day.
So you never really had the time to lick my dick and ass.
I'm also happy that you made me cum very early in the morning.
Yuuji-san...
I'm not only doing chores when I'm at home, you know?
I see, so you're masturbating too.
Yes.
Would you like to do it with me today?
Of course, I'll be glad to.
But, after washing the dishes.
Oh you...
Can you see it?
Look at it, look at it!
So you're always doing it while sniffing my undies...
Y-Yes, before I do the laundry,
I get a real good whiff of your dick and ass.
Amazing, your perverted way of masturbating is really erotic.
I've already got myself a hard-on.
I'm glad.
I'm happy it's gotten stiff.
Please say more lewd things to me.
Say lewd things while I do this perverted masturbation.
It's really erotic, really beautiful, Haruna.
No, not those, no...
Not those sweet words, please...
Please no.
I only want those words to come from you.
It'd be too sad and embarrassing to hear It from others.
My heart would hurt so much that
I'd feel like dying if that happens,
Please say it more.
Oh, sorry, Haruna.
You're actually hurt by these ordinary words, right?
Sorry for not noticing it immediately.
I'll say it properly now.
Your shitty hole sure stinks.
It's not just your asshole.
Your pussy that's filled with a man's fluids,
and your slutty boobs,
even your dirty tongue that loves to suck on my dick.
Your entire body is like a toilet bowl that reeks of my cum!
So you're getting aroused by being told
you reek of the smell of my dick.
I smell like a dick.
Are you cumming?
Are you about to cum with my words?
Okay then.
Because you're a pervert, whose heart
is already soaked in my ball's fluids.
Oh no, I'm cumming.
Oh no!
Sorry, was that too harsh?
N-No, I'm okay.
It's just that it's a lot rougher than the words I usually think of.
Also, your words touched my heart, so I was surprised.
So please don't take back what you said, okay?
It's true that I was surprised,
but I felt happy.
I'm going to treasure your honest words.
Thank you, Yuuji-san.
This time, not just through words.
I really want you to dump your cum into me.
I want it, this swine wants it inside her.
No.
Because swines and humans don't normally have sex together.
What? No way...
So, you'll have to treat me like a swine too.
Does that sound weird?
If we're both swines, I think we can have sex just fine.
W-Well...
We're taking things to the next level from this point, alright?
This is my first time doing that, though.
Don't laugh if I can't do it properly, okay?
Read The
word below
Female Swine
Then, interpret these for me.
One, two, game!
It has to be insulting, right?
Y-You swine, Yuuji-san!
No "-san",
please.
No "-san", please.
Y-You swine, Y-Yu-Yuuji...
W-Well?
That was really cute.
Sorry, I can't hold back anymore.
How rude! You just laughed at me!
Sorry, I'm really sorry.
How about we do it a bit already?
Yuuji-san...
Wrong.
It's "Yuuji, you swine, insert your filthy
swine dick inside me already."
Your tension already eased with what we did earlier, right?
Y-Yes...
Yuuji, you swine, insert your filthy swine dick...
...inside my swine pussy already.
Maybe my tension really eased,
it feels a lot different from normal.
The swine's perverted and stiff dick...
Do it quickly...
He said a lot of harsh words to me already earlier,
but something inside me is making me feel happy.
Jeez, you already want to do it!
So please don't hold back anymore.
Yuuji, I want your dirty stiff thing to cum inside my womb already.
Okay, my wife.
This... your stinky and dirty dick...
Ha-Haruna?
You don't call me that.
You missed the 'dear' before 'wife'.
I-I did!
So, what should I order you to say next, Yuuji?
You fleshmonger, Yuuji...
Oh, it just got bigger.
So you get aroused when I say these things.
I love it.
This masochist dick.
Yuuji, you're such a dirty perverted masochist!
It feels pleasure from copulating and being raped
by this dick-stinky swine pussy.
My dear wife... Haruna-sama...
It feels very good.
Copulating with the dick-stinky you is the best!
I'm glad.
Then I'll violate your mouth as well.
Some of your dick fluids from early morning are still left, see?
Does my kiss taste good?
It tastes good, right?
Kissing my dear wife's dick-stinky tongue tastes great.
Oh Yuuji, how cute of you.
Yuuji, I love you.
Me too, it feels great and it's the best.
I love you, I love you!
I'm cumming, my balls are at their limit already!
Cum, release it all.
I want all of your masochist swine cum to fill my womb.
Yuuji-san, your cum...
Yuuji-san, so you can be quite the masochist.
Actually, I didn't know till now.
I'm a bit shocked.
But I'm glad.
It's a side of you that I found and only I know.
Yeah, and I think we'll find more new
sides of ourselves from now on.
It feels as if I'm about to become a sex
slave though, so it's a bit scary.
Today is the day of our trip to the hot spring inn.
It's directly managed by Hinazuki Tours,
so I've already been here many times as a child.
It's my favorite inn.
It s been a long time!
But that's not the only reason I'm excited.
Hey, Morisawa-kun!
It's also because I now get to meet my
long time idol, Ichikawa Youko!
They're about to do a shoot of their traveling gourmet show here.
Yuuji-san is also included in the shooting staff.
So it's already decided that we're going
to stay for a night here after work.
N-Nice to meet you!
I'm Morisawa Haruna.
Thank you for always taking care of my mas-
I mean my husband.
How cute!
It's just as I heard from Yuuji-kun!
Umm... I'm sorry to hear that it's going to be the last episode.
No, don't worry about it.
It's not your fault at all.
Even in these times of economic turmoil,
Hinata Tours has continued sponsoring us and
allowed us to use the place as a main spot.
That's why I have no qualms if ever they finally decide to stop.
Actually, I really feel like I have to do my part till the end,
to help this place gather more and more customers.
After that, maybe there's a chance that
the show might be revived again.
So positive, cheerful, kind, and strong.
My admiration for her is getting even stronger.
It s really delicious.
TL note: shungiku = edible chrysanthemum
The shungiku's scent and form doesn't even...
She even looks gorgeous while eating.
My father taught me lots of table courtesy and etiquette,
but I wasn't really able to learn it all.
Her overall sense is really good...
And the food really looks good too.
Just looking at it is making me hungry.
Cut!
Hey, this pork just let out a cry!
It's too fresh!
Ha-Haruna...
I'm sorry!
Youko-san laughed at me...
How cute.
Here.
Well, shooting's finally over.
Why don't we take a dip for a bit?
It's my turn to service you today.
Service?
Mixed Outdoor Bath
It feels great!
It's been a really long time since I entered a real hot spring.
You're in quite the good mood now, I see.
It's only us here, anyway.
There are supposedly no customers here tonight.
It's off-season, and we've rented the entire place for the shooting.
Even Youko-san?
That's right.
She finished her hot springs report after that,
and then went home with the other staff members.
Aw, I really wanted to see that.
You've got a gorgeous body that's on
equal terms with hers, you know.
Tonight, I shall clean this body of yours.
You're always the one cleaning me.
At least let me do the cleaning for tonight.
I'm going to rub this all over your body to make you nice and clean.
Amazing, it feels more intense than before,
and yet it feels very tender.
I can really feel his love for me with it.
The way he lovingly caresses me with his dick,
it feels like I'm surrounded by countless dicks.
Please...
What?
Let me suck your dick.
Nope.
That's what we always do.
Why?
I want your dick.
I want it!
My service has yet to end.
No sucking and touching until then.
No, no, Yuuji-san, you meanie!
He's really teasing me!
This time I'm going to wash your entire body.
O-Oh wow...
Please do it more, do it more, Yuuji-san!
Amazing, the smell of his dick is all over me.
How wonderful.
His dick's scent is starting to seep through my skin.
I'm glad that you love it.
Let's do it with more gusto then.
If you moan loudly like that, the inn staff is going to hear it.
But it just feels so good.
They'll find out that the princess of Hinazuki
is actually a pervert who loves having her ass
and body rubbed by my dick and balls.
So, shall we end this now?
No, don't stop!
I don't care if I'm heard.
I don't even care if I'm seen!
Then cum from this as much as you can, my perverted princess.
I love this.
I love this dick pussy.
I love it on my ass!
I love your balls!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
You're beautiful, Haruna.
There's lots of cum.
It feels warn, and it really stinks.
It feels very good...
Yuuji-san, I want to wash some more too.
This time, can I service you here?
Looks like you've gotten a lot more daring than usual.
Youko-san would definitely be surprised if she found out.
No...
Anyone but her!
This position is so extreme.
It's as if I'm really some human toilet.
I can't ever show this to Youko san.
This perverted side of mine...
A-Actually, I've been watching from the very start, though...
I tried to sneak in to take a bath,
but now I'm witnessing something really outrageous.
I never thought Haruna-chan was this lewd.
It looks like she's acting as some sort of lowly toilet.
It's even nastier since she's so cute.
Really, really horny stuff.
Oh no, I'm starting to feel tingly myself.
Amazing, I wonder how she can enjoy
that kind of perverted sex play?
Yuuji-san, your butt feels nice.
They 're caressing each other's most embarrassing,
dirtiest, and tender parts
They look really beautiful.
Both of them...
Give me more of your balls and ass.
I want to do it, too.
I want to plant my face in a nice butt, too.
I want to feel a cock and a good asshole!
Even under my foot...
I can feel it at the tip of my feet.
Oh Wow, I can also feel it in my lower back.
Me too, it also feels nice behind you.
I think I'm about to cum soon...
No, you can't cum just yet.
This is too good.
No, not yet!
She hasn't received service at her most precious part yet.
A girl must have her most important part
pleasured, give it Into her pussy!
Cum it all inside her womb!
Yuuji-san do it, please.
Please.
Let's have sex.
My entire body is aroused already.
It's itching for it already...
You want to cum inside me, right?
Right? Right?
Of course.
Because your pussy is the best.
I'm happy.
Insert it inside me now, hurry.
Let your dick service me from deep inside.
Oh no, it's slipping.
Hurry, hurry...
His dick is now inside.
Haruna, this is amazing.
It's all slippery inside with your love juices.
I-It's because you teased it till the end.
This dick, and my pussy...
I'm happy!
My ass!
You want to do it here too, right?
Okay.
Do my ass.
Stir my ass!
You're really cute, Haruna.
I want to show this self of yours to Youko-san and brag about it.
No, please don't!
I'm sure she's into anal sex too.
She's not!
I don't think she's the type to get aroused in the ass.
But I am!
I've already done anal sex quite a number of times.
Even now, I'm playing with both my
holes as I watch you two have sex.
I feel horny with it!
Your fingers... in my ass...
Yuuji-san, let's cum together.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Me too, I'm cumming!
In the end,
you were the one who pleasured me the most.
I wanted to try a bit harder to give you pleasure, though.
I'm the one who'll get dizzy here if you
plan on keeping it up much longer.
I'm very happy.
Back home, I'd never be able to request
this of you because you're so busy.
You giving pleasure to me, will be one of my precious memories.
That's right.
This is what it means to have memories
of something you'll never feel at home.
This inn is filled with lots of my own memories.
Things to see, the food, and the meet-ups.
And of course sex...
All of these small happy things,
will eventually be added to my memory album.
I'll remember them each time I think of this place,
until I get the urge to come back.
Maybe that's the purpose of staying at inns during travels.
This piace, is like my own memory album.
You... ko-san?
Why?
Didn't you go home already...?
I thought I'd enjoy this place privately this one time.
Might I ask,
did you see everything?
Without a doubt until the end.