My heart was racing the entire time though.
My eyes were hooked on what I saw,
and I started pleasuring myself.
It was really wonderful.
I feel like wanting to marry now.
Actually, I have a favor to ask you two.
This is something I can only request of both of you.
I want my ass to be violated as well.
V-Violate?
That's right.
I want you to make me cum with this slutty ass of mine.
It seems that upon seeing you two have sex,
my repressed memories of when I was
sexually disciplined resurfaced.
Se-Sexually disciplined!?!
Yes, when I was still a young idol,
the studio I worked with was engaged
in some shady business as usual.
It's clearly carved into my mind.
I've transferred studios since then,
and was since released after working hard for my freedom.
But the memories of such perverted sexual
acts will simply not disappear.
But,
my boyfriend right now is too beta
and isn't even up for normal sex.
Let alone up to the task of doing wild things with me.
Wait? So you do have a boyfriend?
What kind of man is he?
My manager, who's a really creepy fatass.
Wait, that's the guy that Youko-san always harasses.
Yeah, he's probably the only guy she doesn't hold back against.
I've even gone out of my way to pester
him, but he just won't budge.
He's been pushed around all his life,
so he never really believed me when I said I love him.
On the contrary, he's pretty happy when I'm the one abusing him.
Kind of like the reverse of how things should be.
Well, at least their feelings are mutual.
But you see,
I still feel uneasy with him not making love to me.
My body may now be the product of BDSM sex,
but I'm still insecure as to whether he
really finds me attractive or not.
That's why, after watching you two closely,
I've decided to retrieve my pride as a woman.
What I saw in you two earlier was something
I've been dreaming about.
I want you two to tell me how I can
make him love me like you two do.
I really, really want to help you out with this,
but then it will... right?
You're worried that I might steal his dick from you, is that correct?
W-Well...
No worries!
Amazing.
I always carry these with me, so that I can
vent out sexual frustrations anytime.
You'll use these to violate my body as much as you want, okay?
Th-Then, I'll be using one now.
Are you alright?
Amazing.
I've already experienced a vibrator inside my ass...
Yes, it feels really good.
Yet it feels completely different when you're the one putting it in.
Yuuji-kun, put one inside me, too.
Youko-san, your love fluids are overflowing like crazy.
Do it more.
The scent of her butt and pussy is getting stronger.
How wonderful.
Haruna-chan!
Why doesn't she want a dick inside this very wonderful ass?
My ass...
There, that's the spot!
Haruna, look.
Her pussy is starting to make bubbles.
Amazing.
She really is a masochist.
That's right.
I'm a masochistic woman!
Look.
Take a good look at this pervert's shitty hole.
Please, violate me more!
Oh no, now I really want to violate her.
If only I had a dick...
If only I had a dick, I could then violate
her ass to her heart's content.
Here, Haruna.
Huh!? This is...?
I can tell what you're thinking by looking at your face.
Th-That is...
Something that one of my producer's used when training me.
But I think it's okay if it's with her.
No, I want to be one with her!
Haruna-chan, come inside me.
Violate me.
Slowly.
Yes, keep it up.
It's been a long time since I felt this.
It's Youko-san's dick...!
Can you feel it?
Both of your "dicks" are having anal sex with each other.
I can feel it, yes, I can!
My ass feels good!
Youko-san, it's so big...
Our butts, are really connected...
Our shit holes are really connected together!
It's transparent so you can see everything inside too.
It really looks like your asses are connected together.
Yuuji-san, look.
Look more closely.
I can hear you.
And I can hear all the sloppy perverted sounds it makes as well.
No, those sounds are just...
Sorry, but those sounds just turn me on even more.
I'm really sorry for being such a dirty swine.
Yuuji-san...
A dick, a raw dick...
So good.
My apologies, but it's been a long time since I've tasted a dick.
This dick stinks.
You just took a bath, but the smell is already this strong.
You too, Youko-san.
I love dicks.
I just love them!
Your dick, please make it...
Make it cum, let me drink its cum,
squirt all of its cum on me!
Youko-san, your tongue is deep inside me.
This is it.
This is what I've wanted to do.
I'm putting this in your ass, okay, Youko-san?
Put it in deeper!
This is your ass... your ass...!
I can really feel your ass getting aroused from all this.
Drive it into my stinkin' ass some more!
Getting my ass violated, and licking the ass of another man...
If this was his ass...
If this was his dick...
It must be bigger, thicker and even smell a lot stronger.
I'm now making love at this level...
I'm being used as a masochist cumhole,
and thanks to this, my confidence as a woman has finally returned.
But, even after all this I'm still craving for it.
I don't understand.
Why doesn't he want to fuck me?
It tastes like Yuuji-san.
Why doesn't he let me lick his ass?
I really don't want to play rough,
but I really want to show off to everyone.
How we embrace, how we kiss, and how I take his dick in.
I want my pussy and ass to be violated
while being watched by everyone.
Everyone look.
Everyone, watch us have sex!
Look at how I get cummed inside by a creepy pig!
I don't care, even if I turn into a cum dumpster.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Got your confidence back?
Yes.
But...
More than that, I realized how much I really love him.
That's why, I want to convey these feelings to him no matter what.
Umm...
I don't think you should over do it too much.
I used to be an unpopular guy,
who lost hope in ever being worthy enough for a woman.
At the time, I eventually gave up trying to change things,
and just accepted the bitter fact, as I lived through mundane days.
You weren't interested in romance?
No, it's not that.
"I like you," "I love you," "Let me cherish you."
I doubt there's a single person who
doesn't wish to hear those words.
But, more than that,
those who are already used to their own hopelessness,
cling to this belief,
and grieve a lot as they learn to accept other people's feelings.
Especially in your case,
if someone who is beautiful right down
to her own asshole were to confess,
it would lead to even more pressure for other party.
I understand now.
It's not that he doesn't want sex.
He just doesn't want others to come off as desperate.
It was his pure and honest love that drew me to him though.
So he'll try to move away if I confess my feelings for him?
I wonder what I should do.
About that...
What if you just treat him like a real-life sex toy?
I see, treat him like an object, huh?
He might not be the dismissive type,
but he's also not the type to be hurt by it.
Because I'm the one who will willingly make him into my thing.
I think it won't be easy for the one who
exchanges such feelings as well.
Guess it's really difficult to be in a relationship where
mutual understanding is hard to achieve.
I guess you're right.
But I think a change is bound to happen
somewhere down the road.
Until both of you are unable to resist each other.
So it might simply fail and hell drift away from me, huh?
But if it helps set things in motion, then I accept this challenge.
Okay, I'm going back to my room then.
Oh, but these...
Those are yours now.
I've decided that he's going to be my sex toy.
Yeah, it's me.
Sorry for calling this late.
You're somewhere close by, right?
Come here as soon as you can.
Just come already.
I want to talk to you about that project for tomorrow.
This dream again, huh?
My first sexual experience, masturbation, orgies,
rape, shady sex activities,
lesbian sex, anal play, BDSM, and even slave play...
All of it felt great.
I'm not even kidding.
Even back then I was the type of person that
could perfectly control her own body.
No, it's just my instinct.
This isn't just some act, as it is part of my nature.
See, that's why even in the face of such great pain and pleasure,
even as the climax approaches,
I don't fear anything.
Are you ready then?
Three.
Two.
One.
See? That felt good.
I'm fine with this.
Everything's going to be okay.
Because no matter how large the wave is, it will soon cede.
Youko-san,
Youko-san!
Filthy.
I-I'm sorry.
I got flustered after you passed out.
So... we are going to talk about that project for tomorrow, right?
Yes, I'm about to explain it to you now.
Also, there's one more thing I'd like to talk to you about.
Something else you need to talk to me about?
Yes, in fact, that's actually the reason I called you here.
A-A sex toy?!
That's right. My personal human sex toy.
Got any complaints about that?
I won't listen even if there are any though.
Th-There isn't any!
I'm really honored, but...
But what?
Are you going to say some bullshit about not being worthy again?
Anyway!
You're going to be with me for the entire night!
Whether it's going to work, eat, shop, sleep, bath or pee!
I'm going to use you whenever I like it.
I'm going to kiss you whenever I want to.
I'm going to have sex with you whenever I feel like it.
I'm even going to lick your asshole if I so desire to do so.
O-Okay.
In exchange,
I'll take responsibility for all of it.
I won't complain at all about being unfair or unjust.
I won't ever hate you.
That's why you don't need to worry
about a thing, and just be my toy.
This is my asshole, your butt pussy.
My stinky cumhole that's had filthy
cum poured inside countless times.
Now, tell me what you think.
It's lewd.
It's erotic.
Thanks.
I would have been mad if you'd said it was beautiful.
W-Well, it is beautiful.
I really think it is.
I can't express improperly,
but it really feels like a dream.
True, it's my first time seeing a woman's pussy and asshole,
but I can already tell that yours are the most beautiful.
I want to keep looking at them forever...
Oh, maybe I should take a pic-
S-Stop that already!
Oh crap, I never expected this.
He was serious about it.
He was really admiring my ass.
I'm happy.
This guy is amazing.
A huge flower, and those hot lips,
his tongue full of saliva, his greasy skin,
and his warm breath,
all of it is getting sucked into my ass.
I can really feel his dick!
His sheathed dick, his dirty dick!
It's quite small, so it just came without warning.
This smegma-filled virgin dick desired my
asshole, and came so much thick cum.
A dick that has yet to be tasted by anyone,
my one, and only dick.
I don't want to let this go.
I want to keep rubbing my ass onto his face forever!
Being sucked by those huge lips... is just...
It feels like my insides are going to be sucked out.
It's my first time experiencing such a wonderful kiss.
I never imagined it would be this intense, lewd, and sweet.
Not bad for your first time.
Now I'm going to use you thoroughly, Mr. Sex Toy.
Umm... is this really okay?
My experience sums up to what you're about to tell me.
It's okay.
You're a sex toy so you don't need to think.
You simply need to do everything that I tell you.
Besides, you're afraid aren't you?
Of making a mistake when you try to do something.
See, you don't have to think about pleasuring me well like this.
Because I'm the only one who knows how to pleasure myself.
I don't have to do anything...?
Yes, that's right.
In a sexual act riding on the wave of a man's ego,
resistance and endurance need to be balanced,
lest your heart and soul become crushed easily.
Despite that, I grew up upholding this belief,
and lived a life that revolved around getting used to this principle.
I was able to perfectly balance love,
friendship, and my career with it.
To act according to how others perceive me,
became my second nature.
Perhaps that’s exactly the reason,
why I was never able to throw away my sex toys, since
those things aren't capable of emotion or reaction.
You, who fear disappointing others,
and me, who can only act upon other's expectations.
Both of us are in a difficult spot.
Don't give me that sad expression, you sex toy!
I-I'm sorry!
But...
If you ever desire to have sex with me as a man,
then you can violate me however you want.
Just like sex dolls are supposed to be used.
I won't hate you, whatever you decide to do.
So, what will it be?
I'll do it.
I want to have sex.
Oh, r-really? Of course it's okay.
I never expected this development.
Have I hurt his pride?
Or maybe he took pity on me.
Well, I might never know,
Huh? He came? He came? No way!
Now I finally had sex with him, and took his virginity!
I'm sorry, I came.
No, it's okay, I'm actually happy about it.
Just cum until you feel completely satisfied.
Because I'll be your sex doll, okay?
He's so engrossed in the act.
Oh, he came again.
He's been cumming a lot.
Inexperienced, but he's giving it his all.
Drenched in cum and sweat.
Dirty and stinky.
This repulsive sexual act feels quite good.
You're still holding back, right?
You can touch, lick and squirt on me whenever you want.
Oh! Now he's going wild.
Wait, this is amazing...
It tastes nice,
even though it stinks.
I'm happy.
But it also makes me sad.
I don't know if this can really be called true love.
But, I want to let myself fall back on this warm feeling.
An endless flow of semen.
From cumming inside.
From tit fucks,
from face squirting.
from deep ass kissing.
Everything he does is so gentle.
I want to become enveloped in your odor, sweat, and cum.
Forever and ever.
What is this?
I'm suddenly falling.
Am I drowning?
I'm scared! No, please sav-
Youko-san, Youko-san!
Yo-Youko-san, are you alright?
Idiot, you idiot! I was really scared!
I-I'm sorry.
I fell asleep while having sex.
And I was actually cumming the entire time.
Youko-san, what really happened?
I just had a nightmare.
My entire body's creaking and cracking.
No, it's different.
I just realized that I was already broken to start with.
Trying to fool myself while running away,
I thought I understood everything.
Everything turned into ashes under the sea,
and with that, I now am of flesh and blood.
You're a failure as a sex toy,
just like I am a failure as a sex doll.
It's the first time I've felt like a real woman.
Hey, let's do it again.
This time, I want to drown with you.
There, I love being penetrated gently.
Squirt it on me.
More... your cum feels really good.
The smell of your ass and cum,
I already feel like cumming just by licking it.
Umm... Youko-san.
I want to have anal sex.
No, not anal sex, not now, please!
I can't hold back any longer!
Oh no...
I already said that you can't...
Now I'm cumming all over, and I'm starting to feel weak.
My ass is starting to become loose,
and I'm starting to shit, what should I do?!
Do...? May be we should take a pic-
What? You called your boyfriend over right after that and did it?
So, I guess he successfully became your sex toy.
No, he became a man after that.
And I've also become his woman.
That's how pleasurable, scary, and wonderful sex was.
Scary?
I drowned,
during sex.
I held onto him, in tears,
and just came and came.
But, I wasn't able to pull away, and ended up doing it till morning.
It's all thanks to you two.
Thank you.
If I hadn't seen the two of you having sex in the bathhouse,
I might never have become one with him,
nor would I have become a woman.
But... where is he now?
He's a nuisance so I just dumped him.
Eh?
If he keeps coming near me,
then I won't be able to film properly!
Eh~?!
What's the meaning of this, Yuuji-san?!
I don't know! Director, I thought you all went home already!
Don't tell me...
Yup, it's a live candid-camera show!
And I just got something really good!
L-Live candid-camera show?!
Wait, is this payback for the cancelled show...?
Of course not.
I got the idea after our threesome.
I never thought I'd hear such an erotic story from you guys.
Now, let's have a few words from our very erotic
lady over here for our audience out there.
Um... Umm...
I'm sorry, father!