It's getting hot.
It's getting stiff,
and it's making my nipples tingle.
Your salty love cowper juices are overflowing.
I'm at my limit!
I get it, can't do anything about it anyway.
Now, where do you want to cum?
You don't need to hold back.
Just go all out and cum wherever you want to.
Please let me cum all over!
I want you to cum in my mouth too.
Just let your dick cum.
You just came lots of this thick stuff...
Huh?
Why am I getting a tit fuck again?
Tit Fuck Cheerleading
VS
Milking boobs cheer squad
A sweaty special lesson
That Yuu-nee.
This isn't training anymore.
They're just teasing me.
1000!
Whew, I'm pooped.
Go, go, let's go!
Just keep on, fight!
Good work, cheer squad member.
Hey there.
That's amazing of you to practice in here at this time.
Huh? Did I say something weird?
But you're also hard at work, right?
Oh, so you knew I was training.
Yeah, because I was cheering.
For you.
Wait, is Chieri-chan...
It's better to actually have someone
to cheer on than just self training.
I'm really honored to be cheered on by you.
You know me...?
You're the ace of the Cheering Squad, right?
No, I'm not really...
The sun's about to set.
How about we call it a day?
You're right, and I also have supervision duties later.
I'm going home as well.
Watch out!
Ah! I'm sorry!
Ow...
Are you hurt?
Yes, my ankle feels...
That's what happened.
The bone isn't really injured,
but my right ankle was sprained.
What's with the gloomy atmosphere?
Is a funeral going on here?
Coach.
Shizukuishi.
So, how serious is your injury?
Well, the doctor told me that it would heal in about a month.
That means you won't be able to practice or
coordinate the girls for the tournament.
That can't be!
Well, it's true that I can't practice,
but I can at least supervise them!
What? You won't follow my orders?
No, that's not what I meant.
Then listen to what I tell you,
if you want to get on stage again.
I... understand.
So this is Takayama coach, the spartan trainer
that led the club to the nationals many times?
Kura.
You two are just alike.
Everyone listen.
Kura will be Shizukuishi's replacement for the nationals!
I'm going to let Shizukuishi rest shortly before the tournament.
Makoto-chan.
She'll completely recover just before the tournament.
So she will focus on recovery.
This is my order.
Are there any questions?
Umm... coach.
Oh, Shizukuishi.
Does her participation also include management?
That will be his job.
S-So, who will supervise the girl's dorm?
M-me?
Coach, but we can't just let boys...?!
Are you feeling shy?
There's just one month before the tournament.
Are you capable of cheering well within that time?
A cheerleader will expose her ass and
legs until the end of the game.
What will you do with that fidgety attitude?
Hey you!
Yes!
You can't say no here.
And you have even more things to do.
There's a reason why I chose you to manage the girl's dorm.
You are all going to tit fuck him for the
entire month before the tournament!
This way you'll develop the guts necessary to give your all!
What are you saying all of a sudden?
Everyone's definitely going to object to this!
I have a question.
Oh, what is it?
What's a tit fuck?
You don't know?
When you tit fuck, you fondle your breasts like this.
To rub the dick well and make it cum lots.
You first rub the bottom part slowly.
Tit fucks are not just about pushing the breast to the dick.
You move it as if you're trying to squeeze it.
Your cowper secretions are leaking out.
Cowper secretions?
When a guy feels good like this, it leaks out.
With this, and my saliva...
You can lubricate it well.
Now we're getting serious.
This is an advanced technique.
So you take it in and lick it like that.
Your dick is quite big.
My breasts are not enough to cover it.
I'm-I'm honored!
You also play with the tip of the dick with your tongue.
It's important to synchronize this with
your rubbing and squeezing.
Remember that.
Oh wow, I'm feeling hot somehow.
You all are about to experience doing it.
Continue to rub it, and...
Coach, I'm about to...!
Already?
It's okay, just cum.
No need to hold back.
Do you want to cum on my face?
Yes.
I can't hear you.
Do you want to cum?
Yes, I want to cum all over you Coach!
Well said.
Release it, spray it all over me.
I'm at my limit!
Oh wow...
I can't drink it all.
That's great!
That means you get to work at the
home base of the cheerers, right?
The time has come!
This is my once in a lifetime chance to break
those bitches and make them cry!
The time has finally come for my own Cheer Squad to see the light!
What is that?
It's a breast lactation medicine that I specially prepared.
What's a breast lactation medicine, Yuu-nee?
Call me captain.
Good question there.
Just one drop of this lactation medicine,
will make a girl's breast bulge, and she'll
start to helplessly crave for a man.
Also, the same amount can make a girl lactate like a wild animal.
Use this medicine, and make them do something
really shameful and scandalous.
Not only won't they be able to join the nationals,
but they would even be at risk of disbanding!
Now go, and use that to collect pictures of those cheerleaders.
Let the hammer of justice fall down on those shameless...
Yuu-nee. Yuu-nee.
What? I'm already at the good part.
Is this even real?
If I prove it to you that it's real,
then you're going to have to follow me.
Okay then, if this is real.
In that case...
I'm going to test it myself!
Yuu-nee, are you okay?
Shut up.
But...
Don't touch me.
Oh no, I can't hold it in anymore.
What are you doing?
I told you to see it for yourself.
Yuu-nee, it’s bulging, and it feels hot.
No...
I'm starting to moan.
That's cute of you, Yuu-nee.
You idiot!
You don't need to tell me that...
Your nipples are also getting a hard on.
Do it gently!
So that medicine was real after all.
Now you know.
You're fondling it too intensely.
It's coming out!
Not the nipples!
Just let it out.
It's going to keep coming out.
Yuu-nee, your boobs feel firm, and they taste great.
I see.
Oh yeah, Yuu-nee.
Can you do a tit fuck?
What is that?
Actually, I'm now included in the cheerleadirig
clubs activities, and...
They're really doing some rather outrageous training.
It feels good.
I bet it'd feel better if you try to rub your boobs up and down.
Like this?
It feels like it's getting bigger between my breasts.
How lewd.
Yuu-nee, your breasts feel tender.
Oh crap!
How dare you get big like this.
I'm going to cum!
Yuu-nee, I'm cumming!
What's this? It stinks and it feels sticky.
You said that you'd do anything if I prove
that the medicine was real... right?
Takayanagi-kun, good morning.
Yesterday was really something, wasn't it?
And you've now managed to do the
job lightly taught to you perfectly.
I'm surprised!
So, is your impression of me better now?
Yep, you look cool!
Oh yeah!
Chieri-chan's cheering for me, how cute.
If it's okay with you, you can just...
What?
You said this is a real emergency.
Coach!
Hmm... well there's no curing your love for cheerleading anyway.
As long as it doesn't put a load on us, you can do what you want.
Yes, thank you very much!
So, are you finished with your tit fuck training?
Th-that's...
Looks like you haven't done it yet.
Not yet really, I'm sorry.
You need to do it right here right now, got it?
Yes, I understand!
Eh?
Having experience is important, right?
It's embarrassing so don't look too much.
Please, I won't be able to do it without you stripping as well.
You're right.
Is something wrong?
Sorry, it's just that it's gotten really big.
I'll start then.
Please do.
It's hot.
Are you okay?
Do you have a fever?
No, it's just aroused.
Wow, it started to get even bigger.
I remember Coach doing it like this.
Well? Does it feel good?
It feels very good, just keep on doing it.
Okay then.
Coach said to move it harder.
Like this?
Can you tell me how it would feel better?
Well, why don't you lubricate it more.
Lubricate? Oh yes, using saliva.
This is embarrassing though.
It's just me here, so it's okay.
That's exactly why it's embarrassing!
Eh?
Nothing!
I'm lubricating it now, okay?
Is it like this?
It feels slippery.
Make yourself feel better with this.
The tip is going in and out of my breasts.
I'm starting to feel tingly.
Takayanagi-kun, it's twitching.
How cute.
It's also making sloppy sounds.
Make yourself feel better, okay?
Chieri-chan, I'm about to...
Takayanagi-kun, are you alright?
It's hot.
I'm sorry, Chieri-chan.
It's okay.
It just meant that it felt good, right?
Go! Go! Let's Go!
Get the victory, fight!
Make it louder!
Hey you, straighten up!
Stop slacking!
Go! Go! Let's Go!
Get the victory!
Go go! Get the victory!
Let's go!
Get the victory!
Letl's go!
Let's go!
Get the victory!
Chieri-chan, what are you doing, that's dangerous!
If you accidentally fall down while still injured...
I know.
But, but I just...
Go! Go! Let's go!
Get the victory! Fight!
Takayanagi-kun...
Takayanagi-kun, thank you.
No need to thank me.
I can do this a thousand times if it's just this.
Thank you, my Cheerleading Captain.
Now then...
Is this okay?
Yeah, I can easily wash it anyway just in case.
Up and down we go.
It feels a bit bigger and harder than before.
So it is aroused then?
Takayanagi-kun, does it feel good?
I want to see your ecstatic face more.
Yeah, but I think I'm at my limit already.
It's making lewd sounds.
Take it in, Chieri-chan!
That startled me.
I just drank it.
Sorry, I just felt like wanting to make you drink it...
No, it didn't taste all that bad.
And I'm happy.
She's an angel.
But, I think I'm a bit tired.
Why don't we take a break first?
Thank you.
I was already thirsty, and that tasted good.
What? My body suddenly feels hot...
I'm lactating?
No way, I'm not even pregnant!
What should I do?
I can't get out of the bath this way.
It looks like its swelling.
Shall I suck it all out for you.
Yes, please do.
Oh no...
Amazing, your breasts are starting to lactate more.
No, don't say it.
It's embarrassing.
It looks really cute and beautiful.
Takayanagi...
It feels hot, my nipples feel hot...
Wait, l'm going crazy.
Not my nipples!
I'm going to suck lots out.
I'm milked.
I'm being milked.
I can't take it anymore...
My mind's going blank...
Next day
Excuse me.
I'm going to clean here, is it okay?
Seems there's nothing to clean though.
I'll just come back again.
Don't overwork yourself, okay?
Wait.
Chieri-chan?
Sorry, are you okay?
Yeah.
Umm, can we continue our training here?
It's okay, right?
Yeah.
Does it feel good?
I don't know, but I feel embarrassed that I...
Look, your nipple is having a hard on.
That's because you're fondling it lewdly.
No, that's...
Wow, it's already wet.
No, don't say it.
Don't, I'm going to lose it again.
I'm slowly becoming a lewd girl.
No!
No need to hold back.
You can cum if you want to.
Don't, don't...!
Takayanagi-kun.
Do it please.
I'm scared, but this is the first time I've felt like this.
It feels hot!
We're finally one.
Yeah, I'm glad.
It's pushing inside.
Does it feel good?
It feels good, Chieri-chan.
I'm glad you feel good inside me.
I'm going to cum soon!
It's okay, just cum whenever you want to.
My insides are getting rubbed back and forth.
I'm about to cum!
I'm coming!
It's hot, my body feels hot.
Your cum is getting poured inside me.
It's still big.
Can we do it again?
What do you want to do?
I want it in.
You have to ask more erotically.
Please, insert your dick inside my pussy.
Okay, here I go.
My insides are going wild inside.
Do it, do it more.
Sorry if I'm lewd like this.
It's okay, I love lewd girls.
Me too, I love you too.
I'm happy, Chieri-chan.
Let's cum together then.
Let's, let's...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming again!
Cum, cum!
Let out lots of cum from your dick!
Please, I want it inside me.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Your cum is pouring directly inside my womb.
Ooh, this is Shizukuishi Chieri, their club leader!
If their dub gets disbanded because of this scandal,
they won't be able to escape their loss.
Let's go and wreck more of their club members, dear brother!
Finally, they too will...