Go, go Hatona! Fight, fight, Hatona!
If they can win this, they'll make nationals.
Strike!
It's okay. It'll be okay!
They all practiced so hard.
Sex Manager
I'm in charge of this prestigious baseball team's sexual desires starting today...
Sex Manager!
It was back in April...
This happened basically as soon as I became their manager.
Saki-chan, where'd our precious collection go?
Huh?!
You mean that wasn't trash?
Of course not, Saki-chan!
The upperclassmen passed it on to us when they graduated!
B-But it was nothing but dirty magazines and DVDs...
Ah, now we can't cool off from practices
with those dirty mags anymore...
What are we supposed to do with our raging boners now?
What should I do? They all seem really disappointed now.
Ah, I'm done. I can't wait any longer!
Huh?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Wh-Why... did you take out your dick all of a sudden?
I can't wait either!
Huh?!
Jacking off with Saki-chan watching might not be too bad.
That's...
Saki-chan don't cover your eyes. Watch us carefully.
Th-Their dicks are getting bright red. This is so dirty!
Saki-chan, I have a favor to ask...
I-I wanna see your boobs!
Huh?!
Please!
Just for a little bit.
Please, Saki-chan!
I-If it's just for a little bit...
Awesome!
I can't believe I get to fap while looking at your boobs!
I-Is this enough?
Saki-chan, I want to see your panties!
Huh?!
We'll be even. You're looking at our dicks after all.
Even? But...
Aren't you getting excited by seeing our dicks, Saki-chan?
I never knew that mature dicks looked like this.
Did I just pee myself?
Something's coming out.
This is so embarrassing!
H-He's right though!
My heart's beating so fast and my body's heating up!
Saki-chan, hurry up and show us your panties.
O-Okay...
I really showed them my panties!
Holy crap, her panties are so small!
It looks like Saki-chan wet herself.
Did you get turned on from seeing our dicks?
N-No, I...
But look how wet you are!
My dick's pretty wet right now from my pre-cum too.
Pre-cum...
His dick's dripping with some kind of clear liquid.
So that's called pre-cum and not cum, huh?
Saki-chan, get closer and get a real good look.
O-Okay.
Wow, they're getting all red and big.
Saki-chan's face is right in front of my dick...
Sh-Shit.
Saki-chan, I'm at my limit!
Huh?
Me too! I'm cumming!
Oh wow, something hot just came out.
I've never seen cum before.
I-I'm about to cum too.
Go ahead. Cum as much as you want.
Saki-chan, open your mouth.
Huh?!
I-I'm cumming!
You really came a lot, huh?
Do you feel better now?
I never thought you'd become our fap material, Saki-chan!
You're the best manager ever!
But all your dicks are still so hard.
You're just too dirty, Saki-chan. I
feel like I can keep going forever!
What do you need me to do?
I want to see you masturbate.
Huh?!
I can't believe I'm getting undressed
out in the open like this. I...
If we can burn this sight of you masturbating into
our memories, our next match will be a cinch!
Really?
In that case, I'll have to do my best as the manager.
Saki-chan, I can't see your panties!
You need to open your legs more.
Huh?
L-Like this?
No, I still can't see anything!
H-How about now?
Holy shit you're so wet that your panties
are becoming see-through!
B-But it's so embarrassing masturbating out in the open!
If you're getting that wet, that means that
you're masturbating for real for us, right?
For real? Y-Yeah, of course I'm doing this for real.
If this'll help you all win, then I have to give this my all!
S-Saki-chan, if you're really doing this for real, then
could you take off your bra and panties too?
I want to see your raw pussy too, Saki-chan!
Huh? R-Raw?
I-I don't know...
But if I'm being serious about this...
Oh, I knew it! Pink!
See? I was right!
What do you mean by that?
Wh-What about down there?
Don't play guessing games about my private parts!
But you're serious about this, right?
Of course I am...
I'm betting pink!
Red!
Red-brown!
Knock it off! This is too embarrassing!
B-But if I'm doing this for real, then...
Can I get a closer look?
G-Go ahead.
Holy shit! So this is what your pussy looks like, Saki-chan.
Who cares about the color anymore!
I-It's really embarrassing if you're this close to it.
It's soaking wet!
I'm gonna fap with it right in front of me!
I wanna fap close to her boobs!
Me too!
Close to them?
Huh?!
Let's all show Saki-chan how we really fap!
Th-They're so close to me.
Oh my god, it's almost touching me.
I-I'm getting so embarrassed, my body's starting to heat up!
His pre-cum is dripping onto my boobs!
My heart's pounding so fast and
my body feels like it's on fire!
Her nipples are getting so erect!
My nipple's touching his dick and it's getting really hot!
It feels so good!
Your clit is getting really red and
it's starting to touch my dick!
Holy shit!
It's hitting me in my most sensitive place... No!
His dick's rubbing against my clitoris!
Shit, my dick's super hard right now!
I-I'm about to cum!
I-I'm about to cum too!
Sh-Shit, I'm gonna cum!
L-Let's do it together!
I never thought I'd ever see your
dirty side like this, Saki-chan.
My dick just won't go down!
Me too! I can keep going!
What should I do? This is so embarrassing, but I can't stop!
My body just keeps getting hotter and hotter!
Your hair feels so good around my dick!
All of your dicks are hitting against my private parts!
It's making my head spin!
I can see all the way inside your pussy!
That's so embarrassing, don't say that!
Hey, tell me what's happening with your pussy.
I can't tell you...
Come on, tell me.
It's getting so wet and hot!
What's it like inside?
Inside's even wetter... It feels like it's about to melt!
I can't believe bow easily my finger's going inside!
I'm stirring up my insides by myself!
Saki-chan, you're too sexy!
Shit, I'm gonna cum!
Everyone's about to unload their cum on
me... they're going to cum so much!
How are we supposed to hold back
with you looking this hot?!
I'm really helping them out!
That makes me so happy!
I'm about to cum too!
I think I'm about to cum too!
I'm going to cum!
Let's all cum together!
Together!
Saki-chan!
I'm cumming!!
Wow, it's so hot and slimy.
You guys have too much stamina.
Are you all okay now?
Do your best at practice tomorrow too, okay?
She's already this close to the team members?
Saki-chan's a natural manager!
Saki-chan, are you and the team
members getting along alright?
Huh? Oh yes, Nozomi-senpai.
What's wrong, Nozomi-senpai?
I've gotten close with the pitcher and catcher...
But they're always fighting.
They even fought with each other during
a match and ended up losing.
Huh? Do those two not get along?
Yeah. It's really troubling.
It's that bad, huh? Is there anything I can help you with?
I think they just have a lot of pent-up stress.
I'm trying to help them relieve that stress, but...
Pent-up stress?
Those two boys just have way too much energy.
Nozomi-senpai, actually, I...
Hm?
I might be a little stressed out too.
F-From the boys... From their dicks?
T-The white... S-Sem...
Oh, their semen, right?
Wh-When I remember the smell of their semen, I...
I get so excited.
I...
Saki-chan, are you a virgin?
Huh?
Do you want to have sex?
Yeah. W-Well, um...
But...
Oh, you don't have to be embarrassed.
Alright then, I'll set it up so that you and
the three boys can relieve your stress.
Let's go to their room.
Just like this?
Ichijo
Nikai
Really? Are you two serious right now?
You two barge into our room just to give
us tit fucks? You guys are messed up!
I want the two of you to get along better.
You two should be nicer. I even brought
Saki-chan along with me.
I didn't expect Saki-chan to help out caring for us too.
I can help you guys out just like senpai can too.
No matter what you say though,
I can't get along with this guy.
Yeah, I don't want to get along with
a self-absorbed asshole like you.
Geez, stop fighting!
I'll take good care of you, okay?
We're not fighting, we just don't jell together.
Don't be like that, Ichijo-senpai.
Just shoot out all your frustrations onto me!
Ichijo-senpai, your dick is so hard
and it keeps getting bigger!
How about we have a little competition.
The winner is the last one standing.
Competition?
It's a battle of endurance, Nikai-kun.
Nozomi... That feels so good! Shit!
My mouth is as hot as if you just came inside it!
Please use my mouth as you like!
I have more stamina than Ichijo!
You really think I'd cum before you, Nikai?!
Your tip's already really wet.
Shoot everything out of your dick.
Your dick's twitching so much, senpai! It's telling
me that it's ready to shoot out cum!
C-Can you tell? My nipples are just as hard as your dick!
Go ahead. Cover my boobs with your cum!
I-If you keep doing that, I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
Shit... Me too!
Shit!
You two came at about the same time.
We'll call this a draw.
Damn it. I don't accept that!
You two are perfectly in sync.
You two really do jell well together.
Ah, this smell. It really does make me excited.
Then next, let's see who can make Saki-chan cum.
Huh?
You're okay with that right, Saki-chan?
U-Uh, yes.
That's fine with me.
Please make my body your plaything.
Ichijo-kun? Nikai-kun? Remember that you
are both aiming for the same goal.
Please take good care of me, you two.
Please let me take care of your stress.
Okay then. Do your best to make her cum.
Please do your best.
I didn't think you were this dirty, Saki-chan.
Me neither.
I'm not!
I'm just doing my job as manager and relieving your stress...
That's just what you tell yourself!
It's not...
He's right. Your pussy's already drenched.
That's...
Your insides are twitching pretty badly.
It's not what you think!
Hey, Saki-chan. Look at me, not him!
Okay.
Yeah, that's a good look! So sexy!
Stop with the verbal foreplay and
stick your dick in her virgin pussy!
Huh? For real? She's a virgin?!
Sorry, Saki-chan, I didn't mean to let that slip.
It's okay. I want to hurry up and become
a capable woman like you, senpai!
You're going to lose your virginity
to my dick... I'm putting it in!
This is amazing. It's inside me!
Your hot and hard dick is inside me!
Holy shit! Your virgin pussy is crushing my dick!
And your insides are moving around too!
I can feel you moving around inside me!
Hey, so who has the better dick? Me or Nikai?
Both of your dicks are so amazing!
It's hard to compare them!
Holy shit that's good sucking! You're gonna suck me dry!
Your pussy's too tight!
Are you really getting that turned
on by Ichijo's dick, Saki-chan?
But this is my first time and I have a
dick in my mouth at the same time!
They're going so deep and they're lighting my body on fire!
I can't get enough!
Give me more of your dicks in my pussy and mouth!
You're too dirty, Saki-chan.
Saki-chan, your pussy's starting to
get even tighter. How's this feel?
It's hitting! It's hitting it!
It's hitting my womb!
Thrust it more into me!
Mess me up!
Please mess me up like crazy with your dicks!
Ah, shit!
She's getting so fucking tight!
Oh my god this feels so amazing! I'm about to cum!
You two are in perfect sync.
It's like you're using Saki-chan's body for pitching
and catching practice. It's perfect!
Really? That's good to hear!
I'm really doing my job as a manager, aren't I?
I'm relieved. Even if I graduate, there'll be a manager
who can actually relieve everyone's stress.
I'm about to cum too!
Shit, I'm gonna cum!
Let's all cum together!
I'm cumming!
We all came together.
With this combination, I bet we can get out of regionals.
Yeah.
Let's go to nationals!
When the two of you disagree on something,
remember Saki-chan's body, okay?
Please do so, Ichijo-senpai, Nikai-senpai.
No boys allowed. This space is currently being used by the managers.
Senpai, we won today too!
One more win and we're in nationals...
It's exciting, isn't it?
It's thanks to you that Nikai-kun and
Ichijo-kun were so dominant.
I didn't do anything. That was all them.
Hey, Saki-chan, did you know?
People are saying that after they were taken care of by
the new team manager, their grades have gone up.
I haven't heard that.
There are other team members saying that they
haven't done it with you yet and they want to.
They want to?
It felt good for you when you took care
of Nikai-kun and Ichijo-kun, didn't it?
Hm? Y-Yes, it felt really good.
Just thinking about it even now makes me a little hot.
Everyone's got a lot of pent-up stress and if we do it
here, there's no need to worry about cleaning up.
Okay, come in.
Huh?!
Everyone's really full down there apparently, Saki-chan.
Cum lots into the goddess of fortune's pussy, okay?
G-Goddess?
But wow you all really have been
saving up a lot, haven't you?
I'll do my best!
So this is the goddess's pussy?
Can I really just put it in?
Please don't tease me, I can't wait any longer!
Wow, the dirty goddess's pussy's so incredibly wet!
It's gonna take me in all at once!
Your dick's so big, hard, and hot!
It feels really good!
Your mouth is really wet too!
My body's reacting to you sticking
your dick down my throat!
Get your fill of the goddess's pussy and
get us to nationals tomorrow, okay?
You too. Make sure you be a hero tomorrow
by hitting a home run, okay?
I get really nervous when I step into the batter's box.
Even now, I'm...
Don't worry. I'll loosen you up.
Just sit back and relax.
I'll make sure to get you ready for the goddess of fortune.
See? You're getting bigger.
Your dirty fluids are coming out of the tip.
My pussy's starting to get hot!
Nozomi-san, right there...
Does it feel good right here?
There's more and more liquid coming out.
Wow, Nozomi-senpai, you're so amazing. You're
making him get so wet just by licking him.
Saki-chan, I'm gonna go deeper!
Huh?
O-Okay, go ahea...
Oh shit, it got caught!
Holy shit!
This is making me go crazy!
She suddenly got a lot tighter down here!
Fuck!
They're so deep! This is so intense!
You're so wet!
I can feel something rubbing against me at the end!
I'm in!
Oh my god, it's inside my womb! No!!
Holy shit! It feels so good!
Me too! It feels like I'm in a vacuum...
I'm gonna be sucked dry!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Shit... She's getting so tight! I'm gonna cum too!
I'm gonna cum too!
No wonder she's a goddess. She made them cum so quickly.
Look, your dick reacted to Saki-chan cumming.
I'll suck you off now.
You're twitching so much inside my mouth.
I feel like your dick's getting even bigger!
I know that with a dick this big, you
have to have a lot of cum saved up.
Wai...
It's gotten so big, I can barely handle it.
Hey, goddess of fortune. He's ready for you now.
Manda-senpai, please relax, okay?
I'll get all of the cum out from you, okay?
You're so big, hard, and you're twitching so mu...
You already came?
Sorry, I know you wanted to do that inside, didn't you?
But you're still really hard.
You still have a lot left in the tank, don't you?
I'll let you cum inside me next, okay?
But is something this big really going to go inside me?
Your tip's inside me!
All their cum is like lube inside me!
Your dick is hitting...
Senpai, your dick is amazing!
Your cum is pumping out inside me!
Please cum more!
You're hitting my womb! Can you tell, senpai?
This is so good! I'm gonna cum!
It's like you're turning my stomach inside out!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
W-Wow the two of you are so amazing.
Seeing you two like that makes me want to do it too!
Us too!
We can keep going.
Then I'll take care of you both in your room, okay?
Yeah! Let's go back to our room!
Manda-senpai, did you hear what they said?
You can still keep going, can't you?
Please make me cum more.
It'll be fine. We're definitely going to nationals!
Look. Manda-kun's up to bat.
Manda-senpai!
Keep calm, senpai!
Remember what we did together!
translation: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч