Go, go, Hakohou High! Fight, fight, Hakohou High!
Today's the finals of the regional tournament.
If we win this game, we'll qualify
for the National Championships.
Strike!
It's alright. Everything's alright!
Everyone have trained so hard for this.
Pakomane
( Fuck Manager )
Starting today, I'll take charge on dealing with
sexual urges of our highly renowned baseball club...
Pakomane!
It was still April back then.
It happened when I just started as the club's manager.
Saki-chan, have you seen our treasured collection?
Were they not trash?
No, they aren't!
They were stuffs we inherited
from the seniors who graduated.
B-But they're all just dirty books and DVDs.
Ahh... I've been looking forward to relieve
myself with those after the practice.
How are we gonna release our excessive lust now?
What should I do? Everyone's become upset.
Damn, I can't take it anymore!
Eh? What?
W-What are you doing, suddenly
pulling out your penises...
Me too!
Fapping while being watched
by Saki-chan is kind of exciting!
That's...
Saki-chan, take your hands off and watch us.
Their penises have become so red, they look so lewd.
Saki-chan, I have a request.
I-I want to see your tits.
I'm begging you, just a little would be fine!
Please, Saki-chan.
I-I guess just a little will be fine...
Oh yeah! I'll be able to fap while
looking at Saki-chan's tits!
Is this good enough?
Saki-chan, I want to see your panties.
You already saw our dicks, so it's just fair.
Even if you say that...
Did you not feel any excitement after seeing our dicks?
I never knew that an adult penis looks like that.
Did I pee myself?
Something just came out...
This is embarrassing!
H-He was right...
My heart is thumping like crazy
and my body feels so hot!
Saki-chan, show us your panties already.
O-Okay...
I'm really stripping in front of everyone!
Wow, her panties are so small!
Did you pee, Saki-chan?
Could it be that you got horny after seeing our dicks?
N-No...
But you're already soaked.
Mine too, it's already wet with
my pre-cum at the tip.
Pre-cum?
Something transparent is dripping down.
So it wasn't semen, but something called pre-cum.
Saki-chan, come closer and watch us.
Wow, they're so red and swelling as they stroke it.
S-Saki-chan's face is right next to my dick...
T-This is bad!
Saki-chan... I can't hold it in anymore!
I'm coming too!
Something so hot came out!
I-It's my first time to see semen.
M-Me too... I'm close...
It's alright, shoot everything out.
Saki-chan, open your mouth!
I-I'm coming!
Y-You shot so much out.
Did everyone relieve themselves?
Yeah...
Who knew that you'll be able
to handle all of our demands.
You're the best manager!
But everyone's penises are all still swollen.
It's because you're so sexy that we're still good to go!
What should I do?
I-I want to see you masturbating.
I'm only in my underwear at such a place...
If we'll be able to remember about how
you look masturbating at the bench,
We'll do better at the games!
Is that so? Then I'll have to
do my best as your manager.
Saki-chan, I can't see your panties.
Spread your legs wider.
Like this?
Nah, I still can't fully see it.
Is this enough?
Wow! Saki-chan's pussy is so drenched
that you can see it through her panties.
That's because masturbating in
a place like this is embarrassing!
You're already that wet, Saki-chan.
You really are serious about
showing us how you rub one out.
Serious? Of course I am.
If it's for helping you win the tournament,
I'll seriously make this feel good for me!
S-Saki-chan...
If you're that serious about this, can you
take your panties and bra off as well?
M-Me too, I want to directly
see your pussy, Saki-chan.
D-Directly? T-That's...
B-But I want to do my job seriously, so...
Oh, I knew it! It's pink!
See, I got it right.
What do you mean you got it?
T-The bottom?
Please stop guessing about its color, It's embarrassing!
But, are you not serious on your job?
O-Of course.
I-I bet it's pink!
I'll go for red.
Reddish-brown!
Please stop, it's embarrassing!
But I'm serious about being your manager, so...
Can we look closer?
A-Alright...
Wow!
So this is how Saki-chan's pussy looks like.
Who cares about what color it is.
It's embarrassing when you look at me that closely!
It's dripping wet. I'll rub one out next to her pussy.
I-I want to rub one out close to your tits.
Me too!
Close to... Eh?
Hey everyone, let's show Saki-chan
how we seriously masturbate!
Everyone's so close!
Oh no, his thing's gonna touch mine!
This is so embarrassing.
It feels like my body is burning!
It's dripping... His pre-cum is dripping on my breast.
My heart is pounding so hard
and my body feels so hot.
Wow! Your nipples got so stiff!
My nipple is being touched by his penis
and it's getting hotter and hotter!
It's feels so good!
Here too, her clit turned so red,
and it's hitting my dick. This is terrific!
He's hitting my most sensitive place! No!
His dick and my clit are rubbing each another!
Wow! Her nipple got so stiff!
I-I'm gonna come soon!
Me too, I'm gonna come too!
M-Me too... This is bad, I'm coming!
Let's all come together!
After seeing Saki-chan being this sexy,
there's no way my boner will go away.
Me too, I still can come more.
What should I do? It's embarrassing,
but I can't stop myself anymore!
My body keeps getting hotter!
Rubbing your entangled hair
with my dick feels so good!
Me too. Everyone's dick is
touching my private parts!
I'll get crazy!
Your pussy is gaping open and close. I can see inside it.
Stop saying it!
Hey, how is your pussy now, Saki-chan?
What do yo mean how?
Describe how is it now.
It's squishy and hot!
How about inside it?
It's mushy and got stretched out inside!
My finger easily slid inside!
I'm stirring myself up inside!
Saki-chan, you're so erotic!
D-Damn, I'm gonna come already!
Everyone, give me your penises!
Spray all of your semen on me!
There's no way I can stop myself
after seeing such a lewd girl!
I am being useful for everyone.
I'm glad!
Same here, I'm on the brink of coming!
I-I'm close as well! I'm gonna come!
E-Everyone come... come with me... together...
Saki-chan!
I'm coming!
Wonderful! It's so hot and slimy!
Everyone's full of energy!
Did everyone settle down?
Give all your best on tomorrow's training, all right?
She already made such a good
relationship with the members.
Saki-chan has what it takes to be a club manager.
Saki-chan, are you getting along
with our club members?
Yes, Nozomi-senpai.
What's wrong, Nozomi-senpai?
The battery pair I'm assigned on
are not getting along well.
They're always having a quarrel.
They even had a fight in the last game and lost.
Eh? Are they that much on bad terms?
Yeah, I'm worried for them.
Nozomi-senpai is worried about it...
Is there any way that I can help?
I think the two of them are accumulating stress.
I help them whenever it becomes
too much to bear for them.
Accumulating stress?
Those two are just too energetic.
Nozomi-senpai, that truth is I...
I think I'm also stressed out.
That thing coming out of the boys' penises...
The white, s-se...
Ah... semen, right?
W-When I caught a whiff of their semen...
My heart was racing somehow, and I...
Are you a virgin, Saki-chan?
Saki-chan, do you want to have sex?
N-No... But...
Jeez, you don't have to be embarrassed about it.
Then, how about I relieve your stress
together with the two boys?
Let's go straight to the boys' room right after this.
Right after this?
[Ichijou]
[Nikai]
H-Hey... Are you two for real?
Suddenly barging in and giving a titfuck...
Are you some kind of perverts?
This is to make the two of you get along better.
I even brought Saki-chan with me,
and you talk to me like that?
You too, Saki-chan.
Who would've thought that
you'll go and join here with us.
Even I can help both of you.
No matter what you both say, I won't
be getting chummy with this guy!
So am I, no way I'll try to get along with you!
Jeez, stop arguing!
I'll give you a lot of my special service.
We're not fighting on purpose,
we're just incompatible!
Stop saying such things, Ichijou-senpai.
Shoot all of your stress out to me instead!
Ichijou-senpai, your penis is so rigid,
and it's gradually getting bigger.
If it's like this, we'll just settle things with a contest,
and let the winner decide for your team.
Contest?
It's about who can avoid getting an orgasm longer.
It's a contest of endurance, Nikai-kun!
Nozomi, that's too much!
Oh, you're making lewd sounds inside my mouth!
If you keep doing that, you'll mess my throat up!
I-If it's about physical prowess, I'm way above Ichijou!
W-Who the hell... would come before you, Nikai!
Hey, there's something slippery on the tip.
It's a sign! Shoot everything out of your dick!
Senpai, your dick is twitching!
You were holding it in yourself but
I'm sure you won't be able to stop now!
D-Did you notice it too?
My nipples are now as hard as your dick.
It's alright. Don't hold it back
and shoot everything on my tits!
If you say that, I'm gonna...
M-Me too, this is bad!
I can't... take it anymore!
Both of you came around the same time.
The contest ends in a draw.
Shit, I won't accept this!
Both of you came at the same time.
You really are a good match after all.
This smell really makes my heart race!
Well then, you'll have a contest on
who can make Saki-chan come first.
You're fine with it, right?
Yes.. I understand.
Both of you please team up and make me come.
Ichijou-kun, Nikai-kun...
Please remember about the fact
that you chase for the same dream.
Please take care of me, senpai.
Please let me take care of your stress for both of you.
Well then, do your best and make Saki-chan come.
Please give it to me.
I never thought that you're this lewd, Saki-chan.
You said it!
That's not true!
I'm just doing my job as a manager
and handle everyone's stress—
Isn't that just some excuse of yours?
That's not... True!
Yeah, right. Your pussy is dripping wet.
That's...
Your pussy is twitching inside.
I-It's just a natural response...
Saki-chan, stop looking at Nikai. Look at me instead!
Okay...
Yeah, that face! You look so erotic!
Stop talking about that.
Hurry up and use your dick and
screw Saki-chan's virgin pussy!
Huh? Really? Is she a virgin?
Sorry, Saki-chan! It just slipped out...
It's alright.
I want to be like you, Nozomi-senpai. I'm fine
with this If it's for becoming a good manager!
This is a virgin pussy.
And my dick is lubricated now
I'm putting it in!
I-It's feels incredible! It's inside me!
A hot and hard penis...
Amazing! My dick is penetrating a virgin pussy!
Her insides are moving and bouncy!
Wow! You're humping my back, it's amazing!
Hey! which dick is better, mine or Nikai's?
I won't be able to know yet when you've
only been doing it together this much!
I still have to take in all of your stress!
You're sucking me so much!
You're squeezing me tight!
Your pussy is clamping on me.
Saki-chan, is Ichijou's dick
making you horny that much?
That's because it's my first time yet I'm getting
fucked by both of you simultaneously.
My pussy is squeezing deep inside,
and my whole body is burning!
Oh! I can't hold myself back!
You're screwing both my mouth and pussy,
you're gonna tear both of them apart!
Saki-chan, your so lewd!
Saki-chan, your pussy is squeezing me.
But how about here?
It's hitting me! So deep, you're
hitting my deepest parts!
More, senpai! Screw me there!
Deep in there, senpai!
Do it like you're breaking me down!
Please fuck me hard with both of your penises!
Shoot! You're squeezing me so much!
You're both amazing! It's like you're
trying to wreck me with your penises!
I'm so close to coming!
Both of you are full of energy!
Saki-chan's body is now working
as a part of the battery!
Is that true? I need to I do this to
become a better manager, right?
With this, even if I graduate,
my mind would be in peace
knowing that there's a manager
who can relieve the members' stress.
I'm also coming soon!
I can't hold it, I'm coming too!
Me too, I want to come together with everyone!
I-I'm gonna shoot!
I'm coming!
I'm... coming!
Everyone came at the same time.
With their tandem, we'll do just
fine in the Regionals, right?
Yeah!
Let's go to the Nationals together!
Whenever you have any disagreements,
just remember about Saki-chan's body.
Ichijou-senpai, Nikai-senpai, please do so.
[No boys allowed at this moment]
[The female managers are currently using the bath]
Senpai, we won again today!
Just one more win and we'll be in the Nationals...
Isn't it exciting?
It's all thanks to your dedication that
both Ichijou-kun and Nikai-kun did better.
Eh? It's not really me, but their own skills.
Saki-chan, did you know?
There's a rumor that when a new manager
helps relieving the players' stress
they will end up outperforming themselves.
What's with that?
I mean, I want to ask you to take care of our
members who you haven't done with yet as well.
You're asking me to...
Didn't you feel good when you took
care of Ichijou-kun and Nikai-kun?
I-It felt so amazing.
I still feel hot whenever I recall it.
Everyone's getting backed up,
and they can release all they want in here...
So I called them over.
Everyone's already got stiff down there, Saki-chan.
Everyone fill up the pussy
of our goddess of fortune!
Calling me a goddess is a little...
But, everyone's amazing.
You all have built-up stress, right?
I'll do my best!
So this is the so-called goddess's pussy.
Can I really fuck you?
Please don't tease me like that.
I can hardly wait for it!
Wow, this sexy goddess pussy is so mushy and slimy!
Shit! I'm pushing it all the way!
Everyone's penises are so amazing, big and hot!
I feel so good being ravaged by them!
Her mouth is slippery as well!
I'm feeling worn out deep in my throat,
but my body feels pleasure from it!
Everyone get yourselves relieved using our
goddess's pussy, win tomorrow's game,
and bring our team to the Nationals, okay?
You too, Manda-kun. You'll be able to
do a pinch-hitting home run. Okay?
I-I'm always getting nervous in the batter box.
E-Even now, I am...
It's alright. I'll be taking good care of you.
Manda-kun... Just relax and take it easy.
I'll be preparing you so that you'll be able
to do it with the our goddess as well.
Look, you're starting to get an erection.
There's a lewd fluid dripping out of the tip.
My pussy is starting to throb as well!
Nozomi-san, right there... it's terrific!
Does it feel good here? Your juice is dripping out here.
Nozomi-senpai, your amazing!
You already made Manda-senpai's
penis that hard just by licking it!
Saki-chan... I want it deeper!
P-Please do...
I got stuck inside! Incredible!
It's rubbing down my throat!
It's too much, I'm coming!
Whoa! Her pussy suddenly
squeezed tight! This is bad!
I'm getting violated on both ends... I-I'm...
She's so slippery inside!
I'm hitting something fleshy inside!
I reached it!
You're too rough!
No... It's in my womb! No!
Amazing! I reached something that's clamping me tight!
It feels so good!
Same here... I'm getting sucked in!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Wow! It's squeezing me...
I can't take it! I'm coming too!
I'm coming as well!
As expected from our
goddess. They already came.
Manda-kun...
Your penis got this hard after
seeing Saki-chan's orgasm.
I'll be sucking you now.
Manda-kun, you're twitching inside my mouth!
It seems that your penis will get even bigger.
Your balls got this big as well.
You got a lot built up here, right?
Wait...
It got big like crazy!
Goddess of fortune! I'm done
with Manda-kun's preparations.
Manda-senpai, just relax down there please.
I'll be sucking you dry of all your semen!
Manda-senpai, it's so big and hard, and it's twitching...
Did you already come?
I'm sorry! You want to come inside me, right?
B-But you're still hard as steel.
Your semen tank still can shoot out so much.
I'll let you come inside me next, okay?
B-But can something this big go inside me?
The tip went inside!
The semen inside me is acting as a lubricant!
It's hitting my womb!
You're penis is amazing, senpai!
Your shooting semen is pushing me up inside!
More... More... Fill me up inside!
It's hitting my womb! Can you feel it too, senpai!
Oh no! I'm gonna come too already!
You penis keeps going in and out of my womb!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
I'm coming, coming... I'm coming!
Y-You're both amazing! Saki-chan and Manda-kun!
I-If you show me something so amazing!
I-I'll end up wanting it too!
W-We too...
We're still good to go!
T-Then, I'll be taking care
of you both in your room later.
Alright! Let's go back in our room!
Manda-senpai, have you heard them?
Senpai... You can still keep going, right?
Please make me come more!
It's alright. We're going in the Nationals for sure!
Manda-kun's next on the bat!
Manda-senpai!
Senpai, please don't be nervous!
Please remember me taking care of you!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project