Everything started...
when I opened that box.
When I opened the Pandra's box.
It's like I've gotten a baby!
The demon that has possessed me, Parasite,
used my magic powers,
Cumming... cumming, I'm cummingl
to capture the talented female students of our Academy,
A lolita's bust feels so good!
And tormented them one after another.
Onii-chan's penis is... knocking
inside me... again and again...
And finally it came to...
Take it out... No...
my best friend Rayleigh, Kuro-chan...
No!
and took her, too.
Parasite's true intention, was to search
for a body worthy of being its vessel.
Wonderful, what a truly wonderful body!
And after finding a true housing for itself,
the demon took over Kuro-chan's body,
and took my virginity with it.
This must be retribution.
It's retribution for what I've done bringing
disaster to such a peaceful academy.
Parasite continued to unleash its hidden powers.
It possessed the male students,
embarrassed all the girls in the academy,
robbed them of their magical powers,
Onii-chan's penis is great...
to increase its own strength more and more.
have lots and lots more sex with me!
I'm sorry.
It's all my...
All my fault...
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Pure Desires Dark Hope
The Last Hope remaining
U-Unico... get a grip... of yourself please!
Con-Concentrate!
No, there... don't, not this!
It shouldn't be...
Am I... going to lose again?
You've got a rough attitude,
but you're body's being quite honest.
Looks like these guys are at their limit here.
Let's get you to be their partner.
Penis... feels very good!
Let it out!
Let out lots of thick semen into Unico's small pussy!
Amazing...
There's so much of thick, sticky stuff...
Parasite will induce the realization of one's desires.
There isn't anything as straightforward
as the desires of a man.
Stop... no...
This...
Wait a moment! That's...
How is it?
Are you about ready to accept your fate as a cum dump?
Don't joke around...
I will fight until...
No, I'll break!
A huge penis thrusting into my pussy and my ass-pussy...
No, no... I'm going to... go crazy...
Well! Use every part of your lustful bodies,
and squeeze out the semen of all of them!
Yes! Creampie...
Please creampie me...
Please cover Unico's slutty nude body with semen!
Mess me... mess me up completely!
Cumming... cumming!
Once violated by a person possessed by Parasite,
no matter how powerful you magic is, you
will lose yourself in the lustful pleasure.
The half of a century we were sealed inside this box...
It sure was long...
You damned witch!
No!
Look, she wet herself!
Don't look...
Look at that!
This witch's got her mark at a place like this!
I, I beg you...
Please save at least my son!
Huh?
I... I'll do anything for that child!
Please...
If you suck all our dicks, I'll consider that.
That's...
You want to refuse? That brat's gonna get executed, too.
I... I understand.
It stinks...
It's because I haven't showered in days.
Neither have I cleaned this part.
C'mon, take care of mine, too.
I have to bear it.
If it's for that child, this is nothing...
Mother...
I can't stand waiting in line for so long!
Let me use this side instead!
No, that side is...
By the way, you're a widow, right?
Don't you have frustration from
not doing it in a long time?
No... that's not true!
Then how would you explain,
this soaking pussy that's sucking hard on my dick?
Huh?
That's not... No... too rough...
C'mon ma'am. Don't forget about
the dicks over here, either.
Wow, as expected from a wife!
She's real used to serving cock!
Looks like... I'm about cum.
No... not... not inside!
That was an amazing pussy.
I haven't felt this good in a while.
is this part of your powers as a witch?
Magic? Of course! This is far from enough!
Hey, bring the others, too!
We'll pass her around for everyone to enjoy!
St... Stop it...
You bastards...
Shut up!
I just can't wait!
I'll enjoy this hole.
Just a while, please! Let me rest!
Alright, here I go!
No, not that place!
What are you talking about? You think
we'd spare you only using your pussy?
No...
Oh, a penis!... Going deep inside...
It's rubbing hard...
Oh a penis she says!
I never thought a witch would look
like this drooling with an ahegao!
My asshole... feels good...
It's good!
She's starting to move her hips on her own.
She's really getting turned on from this.
Cock, cock! Thrust me more!
Witch or not, she's just a slut now.
Doesn't feel good, you perverted witch!?
Yes, my butt and my pussy being done
at the same time... It feels good!
This is the best!
Cumming!
Let it out!
Spray lots of stinky semen into me!
Cumming!
Amazing! So much is coming out...
Mo... mother...
The hate of the young man who was descendant
of a witch became a vortex,
and so us Parasites were born.
But, after humans stopped hunting witches
and joined forces with the magic users,
we were sealed into this damned box.
Now there is nothing to stop us!
Your body has a good compatibility with demons.
As special treatment, we'll use you as the mother
to give birth to new members of us!
We’ll take over your consciousness and increase
your body’s reproductive activity.
No... no...
It's inside...
A tentacle cock is thrusting inside me...
It's reaching my womb...
A tentacle cock is having baby-making sex with me!
How wonderful!
More! Give both your body and mind
to us and drown in the pleasure!
No!
Shut up!
Back down, you.
Such a dirty smell...
It's as if it’s violating my nose...
No way...
The squishy tentacle cocks...
They're so hot...
And there are so many...
It's coming out!
My dirty pussy is having a tentacle cock
creampie all its thick semen inside!
No! Wow... so hot...
Stain me!
Stain my body with the thick, sticky semen!
You look wonderful mind-broken!
Now, continue to be violated until you're pregnant!
Yes... please mess me up more and more...
Make me pregnant...
My butt is being pulled apart...
Stuff a tentacle-cock inside my ass-pussy...
My butt... I love it being fucked!
Amazing...
My pussy and my asshole... both have
tentacle-cock thrusting inside!
More...
Give me more of the thick semen
to my mouth and boobs!
The tentacle cocks are going in and out... in and out...
There's so much of the semen... it's making
such slutty sounds as they move!
Cumming!
I'm cumming from being surrounded by loads
of tentacle cock and stinky semen!
A-Again...
Sh-Shiro-chan...
Kuro-chan!?
Are you Kuro-chan?
Please get a hold of yourself!
Shlro-chan...
Shiro-chan, I...
Kuro-chan’s soul hasn't disappeared.
She’s still alive!
Kuro-chan was the first person to ever talk to me...
She's my only friend...
I have to save her.
I have to save Rayleigh, save Kuro-chan!
Huh, what is this?
Is this...
Kuro-chan!
Shi-shiro... chan...
This can’t be! What in the world happened?
I always thought that this pendant
was a curse to open the box...
But in fact it's not!
What!?
This pendant is for when in case the box was opened...
The last... the last hope!
Don't joke with me. I won't accept that. I won't approve!
Kuro-chan!
No... the slippery stuff...
No, not there...
Too thick...
I’ll destroy all the hope you can have.
And take away your bodies again.
My nipples... they're too sensitive...
If you rub... or pull...
I'll...
Shiro-chan...
My body is covered in slimy stuff...
Deep inside... deep inside my pussy and
butt tentacle cocks are going crazy!
I can't hold it...
This time I'll violate you two at once.
It's rubbing my pussy...
Shiro-chan...
Your nipples are getting... so hard...
Kuro-chan... no...
It feels so good!
Haha! Both of you look wonderful as sluts.
Now feel free to drown min pleasure!
I... I'm going to cum soon...
I'm gonna cum!
So hot...
It's so hot!
The tentacle cock... is twitching...
It's coming... it's coming!
Shi... Shiro... chan...
Kuro... chan...
What, what is this!?
This can’t...
What happened?
The demons... Parasite... disappeared?
Everyone who was possessed has all fainted, too.
You can't even feel the presence of demons anymore...
What's going on?
I wonder if this is what they call a miracle.
A month after that, our school
returned to its peaceful state.
It's great that it's calm again,
but why is there always more and more
work at the student council??
Geez...
Where did Shirley and Rayleigh go!?
They promised they'd help me with the work!
Nurses Office
I really don't think this is right...
We're both girls...
Don't worry, it's fine...
I also...
I like Shiro-chan, too...
Shiro... chan...
Kuro-chan...
No... not so rough...
I'm so jealous... Kuro-chan has such big boobs...
But Shiro-chan's are so cute!
No... my nipples are... sensitive...
Right there... it feels good...
Shiro-chan's pussy is really wet with love juices.
Kuro-chan...
My clitoris is... really hard...
When they rub together... it's so good!
No... Shiro... chan...
Shiro-chan... we've only been together for a short time...
but I'm really glad and happy to have met you!
Me, too. I’m glad I met Kuro-chan...
Shiro-chan... it feels good there...
More... rub there lots and lots!
Amazing...
We're covered in our juices...
Our nipples are hard...
It feels so good...
Kuro-chan...
I... I'm going to cum...
Me, too...
Let's cum together... together!
Shiro-chan!
And so I returned to my position as the library monitor.
Unico.
Huh?
Umm... did someone call me?
Was it just my imagination?
Unico... Unico!