Olympus Royal Academy of Magic
Student Council Room
What's going on...
with my body?
This...
Just having my nipples teased... is making me... so wet...
Student council President, Fumika Reichenbach.
Well then, release the magic hidden inside your body...
The transfer student... you said you were Shirley, right?
To think that... a monster like you...
made it into this school...
If you just be honest, you won't have to get hurt.
No...
That's... dirty...
Don't put it... so deep inside...
My first time... was taken...
By... by such a monster like this...
What?
This... my insides are... hot!
This is bad...
It feels... really good!
You pussy... is really good...
Cumming.
I...
I just... came... from being creampied...
How is it?
Your pussy is yearning, yearning for semen, isn't it?
Don't joke around...
There's no way... something like
this could... have felt good...
Then, I’ll be sure to trap you more...
within the vortex of lust.
No...
That’s...
This is... I can't...
Take it out!
No way... this is... too much...
They're attacking so much, my mind is going blank...
Am I really going to lose it?
It feels too good!
My womb is...
so full from cock, it's like I have a baby!
Don't! If you thrust so much, I’ll break!
I love this! I love it!
I love cock!
Mess up my pussy... more and more!
I can't take it... I'll cum! I'm cumming!
Womb sex feels so good!
It's coming out...
So much semen is spurting into my womb...
I'm sorry.
It's really my fault...
That box... if I hadn't opened that box...
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
That's right...
That day, I opened it...
Pandora's box...
What's wrong, Shirley-chan?
So, have you had lunch yet?
No... I was going to go buy lunch just now...
Great! I made some bento.
Let's eat together.
Why?
Huh?
Why do you do that to me?
Why? Well, Shirley-chan's always
eating the bread from the cafe,
I was a little worried, since we are friends.
Friends...
For some reason, my chest feels very warm.
Oh, you just laughed!
So that's what you look like when you smile!
Hey, can I call you Shiro-chan?
Shiro-chan?
Yeah! You have beautiful white hair like silk,
and you name is Shirley White, so Shiro-chan!
Okay...
I have black hair, and called Rayleigh
Black, so... Kuro-chan!
Okay?
Stop... not now...
I don't want Rayleigh to know...
You were destined to bring me to freedom.
You much gather magical powers for me.
Please... please spare just Rayleigh...
Hmph. I suppose it's alright. If you want
to save the girl with dark hair,
you've got to provide me with other magic.
The next target is,
The library committee leader, Unico Wingedhorse.
Shiro-chan... what on earth is happening?
If it's Onii-chan... I don't mind anything!
Onii-chan's penis! It's gotten so large, and it's twitching!
Unico-chan... if you're so... rough...
Unico-chan... lick my, too!
There's so many... of Onii-chan's penis...
The smell mixed with the smell of sweat is amazing!
Unico-chan is... my... my dick...
Amazing...
Onii-chan's penis... is going int and out my pussy...
I... I'm going to... cum!
Okay! Cum inside, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan.. give it to me in my butthole, too...
Really?
Amazing...Onii-chan's penis is thrusting
in and out of my butt and my pussy!
I see! It feels good when I rub your horn, doesn't it?
My pussy... my pussy feels good!
A man's penis... the smell of sweat...
and the thick, sticky semen...
I love it all!
I'm sorry...
I can't do anything...
Oh, right there, the tip...
It's great...
Two at once... you're so perverted, Unico-chan!
I... I get a titty fuck with these huge boobs of a loli...
Onii-chan's penis... is hot... and tasty...
These huge tits feel so good!
Cumming!
Unico's boobs are being ejaculated on like a pussy!
Ah... with such a small body...
Unico-chan's butt and pussy are being
attacked at once... she's so cute!
Thank you... I love you, my Onii-chans!
Unico-chan's pussy... is wrapping around my dick...
It's so good...
I'm cumming again! Stick out your tongue!
Amazing... there's so much semen!
Yes, yes!
Both my butt, and my pussy...
are so full from your penises!
I can't... think of anything but sex anymore!
Inside... inside my brain... it's so full
of... full of semen and penis...
Please let out lots!
So much semen inside!
Cumming, cumming!
Who is it?
Shi-Shiro-chan?
Rayleigh...
Shiro-chan...
It's Shiro-chan... right?
Why do you look like this? What are you doing?
She has seen us, it can't be helped.
Let's take the magic of that girl.
Don’t! You promised to spare Rayleigh!
Shiro-chan!
What?
Minotouros
Run...
Run away, Kuro-chan...
No...
Please, stop...
No!
Don't... don't tease my boobs... so...
No...
Embarassing...
If you... if you rub my clitoris so much...
No... don't...
What is this?
Such a monster...
My brain is... going blank... it's a strange feeling...
Kuro-chan... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
This... this is a... penis...
It's smelly... and hot... and huge...
It's like it'll dislocate my jaw...
No...
This... not with my boobs...
The penis is so hot, my boobs are going to get burned!
No!
Don't... to be so rough!
It's thick and sticky almost like jelly...
and it’s reeking all the way into my nose...
This is... semen...
Don't put in! Something that large... I can’t!
My pussy... will break!
It hurts...
You're... too... rough...
Your penis is... all the way... it's...
I... a monster took my... first time...
This is horrible...
Amazing... it's reaching all the way inside...
The smell of sweat, and this suffocating body odor...
is making my mind go crazy!
No... if this goes on, Kuro-chan will... really fall...
From... behind...
Shiro... chan...
No...
Even though I don't want this...
Even though Shiro-chan is looking... at me right now...
Perverted voices... are coming out of me!
It feels good!
So thick!
This... even though it's my first time!
My pussy is being messed up completely...
Cumming... I'm cumming from a monster's dick!
It's coming inside...
White and thick semen...
I'm being creampied...
What?
What is this incredible magic power...
expanding right now?
This is great. I really needed this!
Wonderful! A wonderful body!
Kuro-chan...
I noticed as I was mingling with this girl.
This body has incredible magic buried inside.
It is truly worthy as a vessel for me!
Vessel? Could it be that you are from Pandora's box?
That's right. Good job on all the
work you've done, Shirley.
But I have no more business with your body.
That's...
What about Kuro-chan?
What's going to happen to Kuro-chan?
Instead of others, why don't you worry about yourself?
Stop... no!
Stop it..
It must be mortifying for you,
having all that you done to others now happening on you.
What is... this sensation?
It's like electricity... flowing throughout my body...
No... don't... rub there...
How is it down here?
Oh, it's perfectly closed,
like a virgin still knowing none of
the dirty. What a cute pussy!
That’s... no!
Don't, not there...
Don't put your tongue inside!
You... are you turned on?
Pretending you're being licked by Rayleigh?
What a pervert.
Then again, when you're that into it, I've
got to answer those expectations.
C'mon, it's Rayleigh's dick!
You're glad, aren't you?
That's right, good job.
Focus on the glans, but rub the stalk, too.
Good job. Pay attention to the nooks and corners, too.
Right there. Mix in your saliva, too.
Lick it more...
Not yet. Take it in deeper!
White stains are covering your porcelain, doll-like skin.
It's even more beautiful now.
It's been a while...
Since I've had this feeling...
This is getting my spirits raised, too!
So you were a virgin!
So after you violated so many girls one after
another, you still kept your own chastity!?
How hilarious!
That's right... this is a punishment...
I'm being raped... for doing those things to everyone...
How is it? Deep inside, you were
yearning for me, were you not!?
Something that’s not me... is inside by body...
This is... this is real sex...
Yes, yes!
More! Cry, moan, and entertain me!
No... if this goes on, I'll fall, too!
Like the others... I'll fall into the hell of pleasure!
What a great meat hole!
I didn't think that you'd have
potential to be a cum-dump!
That's...
No...
Not my nipples... and my clitoris... at the same time...
I'm cumming!
I'll make a creampie with your virgin pussy!
Amazing! There's still so much more!
So much...
Great, my power has grown once more..
Please...
Give Rayleigh... give Kuro-chan back to me!
What are you talking about?
To attain my full power, much and much
more magical energy is needed.
This is...
The beginning of despair!
Amazing!
Cock... thrust my pussy more!
It feels good!
More...
Amazing... so much cock!
My dear Onii-chans!
More... have more sex with me!
Semen is so smelly!
The thick semen is so hot... I'll burn myself...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry...
Everyone... it’s my...
It's all my fault...