Kiss in the Dark
Episode 2
I'm not Kyosuke's son...
That I was adopted...
It can't be...
I beg you, Mira.
Please don't be down
with a face like that.
What?
Even if you don't have
a blood relation...
...Kyosuke-san is still your papa.
And I too...
Kazu?
Hey, what happened to you?
I love you.
If my lover was Kazu,
then would I have...
...not had to suffer like now?
Mira.
You are so cute.
But my body doesn't tremble
like the times with Kyosuke.
Is this because we are not related?
I thought our relation was something...
...that was born from
the deep and strong bond...
...as related family.
Was this just my own assumption?
Kyosuke!
It's frustrating but
they look great together.
When are those two going to get
married?
I want to become Mizuki Utsunomiya!
Okay, we are going to
start the main take!
So I was right about it.
What?
I was kind of aware of that...
...you and him were doing
a lot of stuff together.
Because you keep on getting
more attractive, and...
...when we were changing for gym class,
I saw some love marks on you.
But because you guys are family...
...I had underrated saying
nothing was going to happen.
Since today I found out you guys
were not related, I made my decision!
A-about what?
I nominate myself! To become your lover!
Wa...
Wait a second!
We are childhood friends
and close friends.
We aren't in a relationship to
do something like this, right?
So right now...
If you say not right now,
then when is it okay?
How long do I have to wait?
T-that's...
I know.
I waited this long...
I can wait a little longer.
I'm sorry.
Waiting is hard...
Kyosuke...
What should I do?
If you are sleeping in a place
like this, you will catch a cold.
It was okay if you were
in bed ahead of me.
You were pretty late today, huh?
Yeah.
After work, I was seeing someone.
Really...
I worried about this alone and
you're on a date with someone?
No...
I was with Kazu too...
But...
...I have to make things clear now!
U-um...
Huh?
It's about the family registry...
Yeah, about the copy, right?
About that, I submitted it the
day of the enrollment ceremony.
What? Is that so?
What the hell?
Then I can't talk and ask questions...
Normally, you would be worried
thinking who your real parent is.
But what concerns me the most is...
Kyosuke...
Hmm?
What am l...
...to Kyosuke?
Mira!
What's the matter?
Being left alone at home
made you lonely?
I wasn't...
Of course I wasn't lonely...
Then, why is this little boy crying?
I just came home and
you are so passionate...
Please...please...
What are you asking for?
Don't leave me...
I...I am not going to be okay
if you are not with me, Kyosuke.
It's okay.
So wasteful to abandon...
Kyosuke, Kyosuke...
I love you!
After all, this is
just a normal "love"...
Regardless of the fact if I'm related
or not related to him, I'm in...
...Love with Kyosuke.
It's hidden, right?
Man, my bad...
Thanks to Kyosuke, once again
I am this bright and lively this morning.
Okay!
Let's go!
Hey Mira...
Is it true that Papa-san is going to
get married with Mizuki Utsunomiya?
What?
Well, recently everyone is
talking about it, you know?
To tell you the truth,
I saw them at the TV station.
Those two had this out of
the ordinary ambience...
Their marriage is just a rumor...
Oh, is that true? I thought it was...
Shun!
You're right. It's most likely
my misunderstanding.
Well, I'll see you later!
Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
More than that, it's about
yesterday's answer...
If it's about that, you don't
have to tell me for a while.
Um, Kazu, l...
By the way, my mom has gone
totally crazy for Kyosuke-san.
Remember, at the parents get-together?
What?
I didn't know that the
parents get-together was true.
She said the scenery from
the hotel was beautiful...
What?
Why was your mom there with Kyosuke?
What are you getting angry for?
The hall for the parents get-together
was the hotel in bayside!
I-I'm sorry...
Or better yet, if our parents get
together, then we'll be brothers.
Huh?
Meaning...
...if your papa and
my mom get married...
...we can live together without
being bothered by anyone else.
Having nice parents and
a sibling who get along...
An ordinary family...
I just thought for a little that
I wish something like that happened.
I'm sorry, Kazu.
It's fine.
It's not your fault.
Good morning, Lost kitten.
Utsunomiya senpai!
Good morning!
Does it seem like you can
blend in with the new class?
Yes!
Luckily, I'm in the same class
as my childhood friend.
Kazu...
Oh, this is my
childhood friend Kazuki Hino.
Kazu, this is Utsunomiya senpai.
He's the student council president.
Nice to meet you.
Oh no!
Well, Mira, I'll see you later.
You can come visit the student
council room whenever you want.
Ah, Yes...
What's wrong? It's so not you...
Don't go near him anymore.
Why not?
He helped me at the enrollment
ceremony and he's a nice good person.
He's after you.
After what?
Are you an idiot?
Idiot? Idiot?
He looks at you like he wants to eat you
up.
Ha? I don't think so!
He's good at acting.
That's because he's...
...the son of the great
actress Mizuki Utsunomiya.
What?
The woman's son?
Just because he's the son of an
actress doesn't make him good at acting.
But the way he looked at you...
His ulterior motives were totally clear.
Who cares?
It's not like I'm a virgin.
Mira!
I'm sorry.
That looks delicious...
It's delicious! Because I made it.
Here.
Delicious! It's awesome!
Right?
You will seriously become a great wife!
Right, right? Good cook and good in bed!
Mira!
The teacher is calling you!
Huh?
Papa-san was...
Kyosuke-san was in an accident!
No way...
It's a lie!
No!
You said that you wouldn't
leave me alone!
Why...
No!
No, let go!
I'm going to die with Kyosuke too!
Hey, if you shake him that much...
No!
Mira...
Kyosuke...
It's okay, calm down.
Kyosuke!
Kyosuke is still alive.
Mira...
You have to be quieter in a hospital...
Kyosuke!
I'm happy you are
worried about me, but...
Right?
It's warm...
Be glad...
Thankfully it was only a light injury...
...so he will be able to
get out in 2 to 3 days.
Hojo-san...
Come on.
Let's let Kyosuke rest.
Yes.
I heard that he didn't use a stunt man
since it wasn't that dangerous.
But apparently there was
some kind of miscommunication...
Are you serious?
Kyosuke should take advantage
of this time and take a rest.
I told him until late last night
that he's been working too much.
Last night...
Then last night Kyosuke was late
because he was with...
...the president of the agency.
Mira?
Um... I totally thought
he was on a date...
Oh...
He pretends like he is
horsing around all the time...
Pretends?
If you are fooled by it, then no wonder
everyone else gets fooled.
Pretending to be a playboy.
He's been an honest man
since back in the day.
Are you serious?
Poor guy. Even his beloved Mira
has misunderstood him.
I tried to convince him
many times that it's impossible...
...to raise you alone.
But he said he would raise you
and wouldn't listen to me.
Man, I need to take my hat off for him.
You are really important to Kyosuke.
So I want you to take care of him too.
I'm glad you grew up
to be a very good boy.
He always talks about how
you are so cute and brags about you.
Brags about me?
How much does he know about us?
Do you know why Kyosuke took me in?
What?
What are you talking about?
No, it's nothing.
Excuse me!
How's Kyosuke?
Mizuki-san.
I'm sorry, if I didn't sprain
my ankle, he wouldn't have...
No, it's not your fault...
Kyosuke...
He never told me that him and Mizuki
Utsunomiya were costarring together.
And she's calling
Kyosuke with familiarity.
I hate...
...this person!
Are you by any chance Mira?
Yes...
So...you are...
I don't like...
...actress's tear...
Yesterday, Mr. Kyosuke Munakata
was released from the hospital.
There has been a rumor that he got hurt
in place of Ms. Mizuki Utsunomiya...
...so it's been said
that their marriage is near.
Man, all the channels are
talking about the same thing.
Who could it be?
Why is she here?
My father is not home right now.
O-okay...
I came to see you today.
You don't like me...
May I ask what business you have with
me?
I want you to become my son.
What the hell is with this person?
Is it not possible?
Of course that's not possible!
Meaning she wants to marry Kyosuke?
My father won't allow you to do that.
Well, he said if you are okay
with it, he doesn't mind...
Because I have the right to.
That is a lie!
Why does she say that
she has the right to...
...with that much confidence?
Kyosuke didn't really
agree to marry her, did he?
There's no way...
Papa, that cloud looks like a boat!
Papa likes that one next to it that
looks like a soft serve ice cream.
Don't you want to take a boat and...
...go to another county
far away together?
Papa wants to eat a plum
flavored soft serve ice cream.
Why can't we just be...
...happy?
I'm just...
...tired now.
Mira...
Kyosuke...
Why are you here?
It's telepathy.
The truth is... I looked around for you.
I went everywhere that you might go.
I didn't know what I was
going to do if you were gone...
I was about to cry
if it was a little longer...
Fool...
Even if I disappear, there are
many people who will love you.
You are the fool!
There isn't anybody
who will replace you, Mira!
The only reason for me
to live in this world is you.
Mine is too.
Today, that woman came to our home...
...Mizuki Utsunomiya.
Yeah.
I heard from her.
Are you really going to marry her?
Who is?
Kyosuke...
Why?
Because she came all the way
to our home and...
...asked if I wanted
to become her son...
...saying that she has the right to.
But I made her go away...
I understand...
I'm sorry...
If I think about your happiness,
I don't have the right to do such a thing.
I get it. I should have talked
to you about this a lot earlier.
What?
The secret of your birth...
It's okay.
I know already.
Hmm...
I thought something was
wrong from the other day.
Mizuki Utsunomiya is...
...your mother.
What?
Oh? You just said you knew...
What about how she is my older sister?
No...
Mizuki and l... We lost our parents
when we were young.
We lived just the two of us together.
We used our beauty in a useful way.
And even without parents,
we were living like pretty well off.
But when Mizuki was about to be
the star of the celebrity world...
...she became pregnant.
She made a decision to have
the child and raise him.
That was when an offer from Hollywood
for her to star in a film came in.
And because of that,
myself who was in High school...
...took you in to raise you.
So she grabbed the Hollywood dream.
And in exchange,
I raised an adorable baby and...
...ate him all up.
When you say it,
it doesn't become a joke!
But, if she is my mother, then
what about Utsunomiya senpai?
Is he my brother?
No.
Takayuki is the son of the movie
director that Mizuki married afterwards.
Even though the father has
passed away a couple of years ago.
So meaning...
...it's not that Kyosuke and I don't
have any kind of blood relation at all.
I'm happy and troubled...
It's a strange feeling.
But Kyosuke, you worked
really hard for me.
Good boy, good boy.
Of course I am going repay you for this.
When you become senile,
I'll change your diapers.
I'll even give you a
piggyback, and huggy...
Then can you to do it right now?
You're heavy! I'll be squashed!
So...
...am I allowed to stay
by you now on too, right?
Of course.
I'm going to get you to
repay what you owe me.
I love you, Papa.
Please cherish me for life.
Of course...
Even if it's right this second...
matatakisae wasurerukurai
瞬きさえ　忘れるくらい
As much for me to forget to blink...
anata dake de itsudemo
あなただけで　いつでも
...I'm occupied with
just you all the time.
Please stop the time forever.
toki wo tomete zutto
瞬間を止めてずっと
This room that no one's in...
dare mo inai kono heya
誰も居ないこの部屋
The TV is vacant.
terebi ga munashiku
TVが空しく
kimi no kakera sagashite
キミの欠片探して
I look for a part of you.
mata minai furi wo suru
また見ないフリをする
Then I pretend I wasn 't looking.
machigatteru kitto bokura wa
間違ってる？きっと僕らは
Am I wrong? We most likely...
...don 't need anything else.
hoka ni nanimo iranai
他に何もいらない
Because not even
one person knows the truth.
datte hontou no koto wa
だって本当のコトは
dare hitori wakaranai yo
誰ひとり　わからないよ
matatakisae wasurerukurai
瞬きさえ　忘れるくらい
As much for me to forget to blink...
anata dake de itsudemo
あなただけで　いつでも
...I'm occupied with
just you all the time.
kokoro no naka misukasareru
心の中　見透かされる
You look through my heart.
Stop my love.
Stop My Love
yasashii kisu futari dake no asa wo
優しいキス　ふたりだけの朝を
Gentle kiss with just the two of us.
We start the morning again today.
kyou mo mukaeru toki wo tomete zutto
今日も迎える　瞬間を止めてずっと
Stop the time, forever...