No way, no way, no way!
I just ended up doing it with that guy...
We just had sex.
He did his own daughter.
This pain...
So I really did it with him...
Why were you using my underwear to...?
That's...
Didn't you hate them?
This one time, I sat with you in the living room,
and you were sweaty, wet and creepy like always.
You sniff it because it's creepy?
No!
I just happened to see an erotic scene that time on the TV
and that got me aroused.
Since then I became addicted to your smell
and that part gets wet each time.
Smell...? Aren't the tissues in the trash already gone?
But you also lick those used tissues
while thinking of Mom, don't you?
I don't like that.
Why would I do that?!
I'm a normal person!
Although...
I'm not really that perfectly normal.
I'm still too dependent on sex at this age.
I have to find other ways to satiate my inner lust these days.
You creep.
That's still the same, you pervert.
But you don't have proof, right?
I said you don't have proof.
So show it to me!
Try having sex with me.
Can't you do it?
So that was just a lie?
Well, you are...
We're father and daughter.
I already told you that the mere smell of yours is enough
to make me horny enough to crave sex, didn't I?
But you never prohibited us having sex before, have you?
Of course I wouldn't have said something like that at all.
Stop quibbling!
You're the one who's nitpicking!
I just stopped because you objected at the last minute.
Take responsibility.
Do it until the very end.
Hey, come to your senses.
It may be small compared to Mom's,
but it's still fresh.
No one else has touched it yet.
Hey, won't you cut it out already?
Men like that, don't they?
You get it already, don't you?
Now that you know your daughter's dirty secret, I
doubt this can end without anything happening.
O-ouch...!
I-I'm sorry.
Are you Okay, Dad?
What?
A memory of someone apologizing
to me 10 years ago here had just...
What?
I can also apologize if I am wrong you know.
What's that, are you embarrassed?
You're really cute, Hyouka.
What are you saying
I've never been embarrassed!
Just do it quickly.
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to kiss me or something?
To get in the mood or something.
How insensitive of you.
Is that so? Okay then.
We can't kiss if it doesn't touch.
I know that!
Don't beat around the bush over something as trivial as a kiss!
Are you Okay?
Here, show it to me.
Eh? So this is a kiss?
Calm down.
You don't have to force it too much.
Shut up.
Just continue.
Is this good enough for you?
It's good enough I guess.
I'll give you plus points for taking the lead.
Don't misunderstand!
I just wanted to know what a male tastes like.
You really like my smell that much?
A male's smell!
Geez, let's just have sex already.
Well, even if you say sex...
Don't just stay dumbfounded there.
What's with this stiff thing then?
I'm this cute, so can't resist our cravings, huh?
Well, I'm a guy too.
Rather than being sex craved,
I would say it's a natural sexual reaction.
That's what's hitting me.
So, are you saying that the sensation of your daughter's pussy
is nothing but a sexual reaction?
Regardless of who plays with it
what feels good, will feel good.
You just want to insert it...
Hey, Hyouka! Are you Okay?
This is...
nothing...!
It hurts.
Ouch, ouch...
What's this?
Why is it this painful?
You're a virgin, so there's no helping it.
It would slowly feel good as it goes on, I think.
Is that true?
Probably.
I never thought it would be this painful...
Oh no... I can no longer bear with it.
No, don't move!
It hurts!
It will feel good soon.
It hurts.
I don't want this anymore.
Pull it out.
Don't say that, now that we've become one already.
Really? You're happy that we've become one?
You can move.
I'm Okay... with this little amount of pain...!
Dad...
Slow down, a bit...
This is...
Does it still hurt?
It still hurts!
It doesn't feel good at all.
No, stop this already.
I don't want this.
It hurts on my side,
yet you're the only one who is feeling good.
Tsk...
It's somewhat...
This, deep inside me...
I'm about to finish.
Dad...
Just a little more...
This feels, somewhat...
Hey, wait... just a bit.
This is...
It's coming out.
This is Dad's...
No way...
Dad's smell is coming inside me...
This stinky smell...
What should I do? I'm his daughter.
What's this? Some kind of H-game?
I can't believe I just made love with Papa!
Oh, but wait a sec, he's used to this right?
Well, he's been doing it with Mom,
so he's probably used to handling women.
But he didn't mind it too much even
when doing it with his daughter.
Dad, this feels really good!
Eh? So he's also doing it with Onee-chan?
I guess he tried to act cool precisely because its our first time.
What am I thinking?
Pervert Masked Girl, Hyouka~ The pigtailed one who loves Papa’s underwear
Under one roof with dad and the naughty erotic daughters
Original Animation
Hey, hey, Dad...
It's Okay.
I'll do it.
No it's fine, Okay?
Calm down, Ayame.
W-what's with him?
And here I was worried about facing him...
He's smiling happily while speaking with Onee-chan.
Hmph.
Good morning, Hyouka.
I'll be going.
What about breakfast?
It's Okay, I don't need to eat.
What?
Well, umm...
About yesterday...
Wh...
What's with that?
Don't say such weird things early in the morning!
Idiot.
You're really insensitive.
Insensitive...
Mom went away because of that.
You understand, right?
What?
So you didn't notice...
So Sae left me because of that?
I-I don't know.
I just thought maybe that was the reason.
Besides, the reason I heard from Mom was different.
What you knew something?
I said I don't know!
I'll be going ahead.
Geez, he just changes mood when it's about Mom.
Excuse me.
I want to talk about something.
I don't have club activities today. Do you have time?
Sorry, I still have something to do.
Sorry about that.
I see.
Geez, what is he doing?
Hey, Dad!
Come, let's go shopping!
Hey, I don't remember making any such promises...
I'm shopping for Mom.
You would get bonus points with her
for helping me with this errand!
For real?
Hyouka, are you coming too?
No. I have something to do.
So this will be a date?
I just can't do something that bothersome.
That's the usual Hyouka for you.
I just finished running so I'm hungry.
So that's what you really want?
Hey, Hyouka!
What's with you?
What are you doing?
You're feeling cold right?
You waited here for 3 hours, right?
Geez, what were you doing there?
Saying that you're a bit busy...
You should have just gone home straightaway.
I had some "physiological problems earlier...
I also had something to do earlier,
so it's not like I've waited for that long...
But, what about the shopping thing?
I'll do it next time.
Besides, I've made my precious daughter wait for so long.
Oh, guess you are a bit of a smooth talker, huh?
No, I mean...!
Anyway, was that thing you said yesterday a lie?
About what?
I told you already, didn't I?
About wanting to do it everyday...
Having sex...
well, that's...
I told you to show me some proof, right?
Was that a lie?
You're going straight home from here, right?
Then show me your proof.
Besides, it was just painful yesterday.
Show me some proof that it will feel better.
H-hey...!
Everyone already went home.
Come on, quickly!
Hey...
Stop complaining, come on...
Geez, putting on that sweaty jacket...
It's nothing short of stinky.
It's also wet...
I guess your rotten dick is also the same.
It's stinky, but it's the smell that I've been sniffing.
Oh no, now the smell is stuck on my hand.
Hey there,
as punishment, make me feel good too.
Your thing here is starting to get stiffer.
It's a really thick smell...
But...
I can't get enough of it.
This is...
amazing.
Better than when I do it myself.
No, if you do it that intensely,
It'd be wet with your drool.
My drool is not as sticky as this.
Dad sure likes to focus on weird things.
I'll suck it for you.
Wow.
My thing is getting sucked.
This stinky smell...
I want to stick it deep inside me.
It's coming in.
Something thick, deep inside me...
It hurts...
Hey, it still hurts.
It's Okay, it will feel good soon enough.
What's this?
My body feels numb...
Why did you pull it out?
I'll put it in immediately.
No...
What...
What's this?
What is this?
It feels good.
It doesn't hurt anymore, does it?
It feels great, more than the pain.
Your cock feels good.
Wow, Dad's cock is even bigger then yesterday.
I know how your cock looks like,
as it fits very snugly in my pussy.
What is this?
Having sex feels way better than just masturbating.
Is it because it's Dad's cock?
That's why it feels good, right?
Hyouka...
Dad's cock sure/feels good.
My pussy remembers your cock's shape it seems.
Hyouka, so you really think of me that way...?
I don't want it if it's not Dad's...
I will not think of having sex if it's not you!
You never showed me this side of yours before...
I can't say it because I'm embarrassed you know!
I don't want to be seen through.
Dad's cock is going in further.
Like this...
It's Okay, Dad.
Release it inside me.
It'd be bad if it gets stuck in my uniform.
That's not Okay.
What if you become pregnant?
What?
Just release it in me!
Release it quickly!
Here, do it!
It feels good.
Let the cock cum like this!
I'm also going to cum, with this cock...
I'm cumming!
Dad's stinky smell, is inside me...
I'm about to cum again because of this smell...
So this is how good sex feels...
Dad's smell also feels good.
What, you haven't taken your bath yet?
Yeah, I'm already about to.
What do you mean that you're already about to.
About to...?
You're not going to drink the last bathwater
or suck the hairs in there would you?
Why would I?!
Are you telling the truth?
Just how do you see me...wait.
No way are you...?
What?
Nothing.
Anyway I'll take a bath now.
Hmph.
Are you searching for my underwear?
Ouch! It hurts!
What in the world are you doing?
Shut up.
It's my habit so it can't be helped.
A habit...?
I just plan on taking my bath in the morning instead.
Eh? I didn't hear anything about that.
Well I didn't need to report it.
Geez, you're going to sleep that way?
I can't believe it.
And you're sweaty.
Do you plan on sleeping with your sweaty body
just so that your smell would seep into the bed to mark it?
Hey, your way of thinking is going haywire!
I bet you're feeling great that I'm now left with you.
Geez, there's a limit to how much you can misunderstand.
I'm not aroused with your smell.
I'm just aroused with the smell of a male.
See, men always have their thing down there.
My body just naturally reacts to that smell.
I'm not thinking about anything else but your smell, got it?
Hey, wait...
It's because you're emanating that sweaty smell,
that I'm starting to feel weird.
Getting me to smell this stinky smell...
Try thinking about the one who would
clean those stinky sheets for once.
Hyouka, this is...
Shut up.
What you only need to do is to shut up now, pervert.
Dad's butt stinks and I'm all over it.
Oh, wow...!
I won't lose.
Release it already!
I want lots of Dad's smell...
It's about to come out, right?
Cum lots of it quickly!
There's lots of stinky stuff...
You even made a mark on me.
You plan on making me yours, right?
This thick thing is entering so deep. I can't get enough of it!
It feels good.
You can thrust it in me more.
My pussy feels good, right?
Do it more.
Cover me with your smell.
Push it in more, along with that stinky smell.
Make me go wild with your cock.
Wow!
It's reaching up to my womb.
It's Okay
Stir up...
my insides with your cock!
It's deep inside!
My womb will break.
Keep this up and release it in me.
Cover me in semen.
Impregnate me!
Cum in me.
Release your stinky semen inside.
Make my insides full!
It's going in!
Lots of it is getting in.
This stinky thing feels good!
My, really now Dad...
Mom's bothered about that, right?
Well...
What's with him?
So he really does it with Onee-chan...?
You're really insensitive.
Well, he did it with me last night.
Good morning.
Good morning, Hyouka.
I was just talking about something with Dad.
What is it?
See, we're about to switch with Sena
and the others next week, right?
Oh yeah.
But I was thinking that the present status quo was fine as it is.
What do you think Hyouka?
I don't really care about that.
There, Dad! Hyouka also said that its Okay!
But, she didn't say...
Hey, you'll be late if you don't hurry up.
Oh no...!
Sorry for making you wait...
What are you doing?!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
What? It's just a goodbye kiss you know.
You've also been doing it, right?
That's different!
That wasn't just some goodbye kiss, was it?
Then I'll also...
What are you saying?
We'll be late if we don't hurry up.
Geez!
Hey, what's wrong?
It's lunchtime.
Sorry, I still have work to do.
I see.
That's what I thought,
but I'm already feeling hungry.
Want to eat together?
Yes!
Geez, getting suddenly cute like that isn't fair Hyouka.
Ouch, ouch...
Oh this is bad...
Eh?
Dad?
Are you a dog or something?
What's wrong?
I injured my leg a bit during club practice.
Show it to me.
H-hey, what are you doing?
Hey!
This is embarrassing!
Don't be a fool.
You don't need to hold back as my daughter.
That's not it.
I did not mean...
It's because we're at school... Hey...!
No, go a bit higher.
Here?
Higher.
Hyouka, you're...!
It's because...
when I smell you, Dad,
I'm unable to hold back.
I want to be more engulfed
in your smell.
I want to do it here.
Dad's cock is amazing!
It's also big today!
It feels good.
I want to do it more with your cock.
Lower down your voice.
Even if you say that, I just can't do it!
To feel this good!
I can't get enough...!
I'll thrust it in deeper,
so try to bear with it.
I understand.
I'm going to hold it in.
So go in as deep as you can!
This feels good!
If you go that deep inside me...!
Idiot! Don't raise it, lower it!
I can't do it.
I can't hold back this great feeling!
You're gripping me very tightly.
Huh? I wonder where Dad went?
Oh, Sena and Kanami.
What's wrong Onee-chan?
I thought of going home with Dad, but...
He's not here?
We're supposed to switch the day after tomorrow, right?
And was planning on talking about it along the way...
I see.
So, where's Hyouka?
Yes!
Your stiff cock is filling me deeply all the way in!
Dad this feels good.
This intensity is too much.
I'm about to cum!
Let's cum together.
Together, with Dad...
With Dad...
Dad...!
I love you!