www.SubDESU-H.net
Just a minute.
This seems totally unfeasible.
You have a daughter and yet you obviously masturbate.
What are you thinking?
Are you an idiot?
Your wife's barely left, and now this?
Freaking gross.
No wonder she left you.
I may be a father, but I’m also a man.
It’s a physiological phenomenon.
Physiological phenomenon?!
My ass!
Are you saying you’re masturbating against your will?
If you hold back your sexual desire, you might die.
Then die right here and now!
Quit masturbating and quit life all in one blow!
You semen hose!
Sorry I got home late.
What’s wrong?
Onee-chan!
This guy was jerking off in the room yesterday.
Jerking off!
Freaking gross!
Um... wait, well, um...
Is this true?
Yep. And here’s the aftermath of it.
Don’t you think we should turn him in to the cops?
So that’s what it is. I’ve never seen that before – I’m surprised you knew what it was, Hyoka.
It’s obvious from this trash can what’s in it.
She’s right. It’s true.
Well, dad is still a man.
You can’t argue with a physiological phenomenon.
That crap again?
What’s up with you two?
I’m telling you, jerking off is not a physiological phenomenon.
Please, Hyoka, don’t yell so loudly about it...
W
Papa-Love
Sexy Girls Wanna Fuck Their Daddy At Home
Original Animation
Huge Breasted Mishiri and Ayame ~ Innocent Natural Curiosity ~
When I was young, no one told me a father is supposed to be insensitive, ignorant, a smoker
and someone who neglects his family while sleeping downstairs.
How horrible!
Oh, but he’s a man. He’s allowed to have an occasional slipup.
Mom sure was mad.
I was worried about her so I sent Sena and the other girls after her, but..
Dad, why don’t you go to bed?
Sae... did you come back?
W-Wait, Dad!
No!
Don’t do this, Dad...
Are you sleepwalking? I’m not Mom.
I’m Ayame! I’m Ayame!
Ayame wouldn’t be this developed.
But I... I am this developed!
Oh no.
That’s not the point...
You seem extra sensitive.
Don’t, Dad!
Please, I can’t have this...
Dad...
I’m sorry!
I was sleepwalking and you looked like Sae...
And you were, um, so big and soft and they felt as good as Sae's...
He was just sleepwalking, but... am I really the same size as Mom?
Dad must really miss her.
I'm pathetic.
She’s known for not crying... and I made her cry.
Wh-What’s wrong?
Um... so, Dad...
It’s about what just happened.
And I’m okay with it.
I’m sorry!
I know I was sleepwalking, but that’s no ex-
It's fine!
That's okay...
Dad... you were about to pleasure yourself just now, right?
It’s okay. You don’t need to hide it.
But I can’t just...
What’s wrong?
I’m kind of in the middle of something here...
Does a man really have to do it that much?
Does it hurt if you don’t do it every day?
Well, it’s not exactly...
I mean, Hyoka and I both don’t have a mom now...
I was wondering if that was the reason...
Guess so.
So I was going to do today’s session...
So you need to go back to your room.
Can’t I help you with that?
Wh-What’re you saying?
You’re trying to take Sena’s place?
Well, I’m very flattered, but-
It must hurt.
But if it’s for your sake, I’d do anything.
Don't you want it from me?
Because I’m inexperienced? And not as good as Mom?
Th-That’s right.
Yes, you’d never be as good as Sae.
So you’d better l-
Then, teach me?
So I can be better than Mom.
So I can do it the way you like.
No, you don’t have to...
Don’t worry.
I know I’ll be good at it.
So please, Dad.
Let me be Mom’s replacement?
Please, Ayame, stop it...
It must hurt you.
If I can bring you relief, I want to take mom’s place.
Don’t you want to have sex with me?
Can I even answer that?
You’re my daughter.
You’re in a different position from Sae.
No... I don’t care what you think about me.
I love you and I want to have sex with you!
Wow. It’s throbbing and so hard...
I can see the lines...
Did that hurt?
N-No, no, it’s dirty, so stop it.
Why? I don’t think it’s dirty.
After all, it’s my dad’s d-dick.
But this sort of thing isn’t normal.
I don’t care if I’m not normal.
If I get to be joined with the one I love.
But I’m your father. We’re related.
And you’re underage and you have a boyfriend... okay?
That doesn't matter!
See? I’m fine with this sort of thing.
I wanted to squeeze your dick like this, Dad. Does it feel good?
Yes...
We’re a family, so we know how to help each other best.
Mom was good at it so I know I am too.
See? I’m okay with this too.
How salty.
Hey, Ayame, you’re not a child anymore...
Because I’m not a child anymore, I want to have sex with the one I love.
So why can’t you accept that?
It’s wrong. Hands off...
Your father doesn't remember teaching you that sort of thing...
Wow, your dick... it’s getting bigger... and thicker...
Wow... your sperm... so much.
So this is your sexy flavor.
But... what do I do after this?
This isn’t this end, right?
Well, um, you know...
I shouldn’t teach you that, as a father...
Oh please, you’re covered in sticky cum and you still talk like that?
Face your fate, will you?
Mom’s not here anymore.
S-So I’ll... t-take her... place...
Please, calm down.
I’m a woman too!
This is embarrassing for me!
Being forced to beg for it from the man I love...
Oh... I see.
You’re right.
Ayame, I’m sorry.
As a man, I’m a disgrace.
Really? You really are sorry?
Yes.
Oh? Then, if you kiss me I’ll forgive you.
Sure.
Yay! Then, smooch...
Wait, you just had me in your mouth.
Ohh, just when things were getting good!
Jeez. Jeez, jeez!
I titty fucked you and you won’t even kiss me?
I’ll get my revenge on you tonight!
You can’t get up now, right?
Ayame, what are you doing?
I’ll do you this way now.
So pretend I’m Mom.
Ayame... I’m your father!
Seriously...
If you won’t love me, then think of me as Mom.
I’m fine with that.
I don’t understand you!
Anyway, this is wrong!
Wait for me, Dad.
We’ll finally become one now.
Ow...
That’s your hymen... wait, Ayame, don’t!
It hurts...
I guess we’re no longer father-daughter.
At last... we’re one person, Dad.
Ayame... this is your first time.
Come, let me see.
Okay.
It must hurt.
You should probably stay like that for a bit.
Sure... I’ll be okay.
I can hang in there.
But are you okay?
What do you mean?
Well... It seems like you’ve finally resigned yourself to it.
Your mood changed suddenly.
That’s not true.
I’m just overjoyed to be joined with my sweet daughter.
Really?
I’ve been wanting to give you my virginity, so I’m glad you’re happy.
I’m gonna move a little.
Is this... okay?
Okay, Dad, you don’t need to hold back.
Dad...
So rough...
Move slower...
It’s better faster.
I’ll withstand the pain, so please, give me your dick!
Does it feel good for you?
Dad, does it feel good?
Yeah.
Me too.
It feels... I want more...
I want all of your dick, Dad.
I feel... funny.
My bellybutton is squeezing into me.
Will you get off me?
We can’t finish like this.
Don’t!
I want your sperm.
In me... in my uterus, please.
Stupid... you can’t get pregnant...
I want it!
I want it in my uterus!
Oh, I feel something coming.
Dad... Dad!
Wow... What is this?
I’m flying... Dad...
Oh no...
Ayame... it was your first time, but you’re cumming?
Is this... what cumming is?
I’m not sure... I’m not sure...
Huh? I can’t move...
Oh, was that on purpose?
You found me out. I love you, Dad.
I see. I love you too, Ayame.
I want to ask you if you love me or Mom better, but...
For now I’m just happy you said you love me.
Good morning!
Dad, have a seat.
Hyouka, Hyouka.
Do you want seconds?
No, I don’t...
I mean, I don’t even want “firsts” if it’s this much.
Y-You’re sure in a good mood today.
Well, well, well, you know why.
Oh, you silly darling.
That’s right, Hyouka, I’ll be taking Mom’s place now, so you can call me “Mom” if you want.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Hey!
Ayame, I came to watch your studies.
You can’t do that. Calm down, okay?
Freaking gross, really.
You did something again, didn't you?
Making Onee-chan like that? It must have been you.
I hope you’re not spoiling her too much.
Dad, are you finished with work yet?
Let’s go home.
I’ll be done in a minute.
Okay, then I’ll wait for you.
I told you I’d take Mom’s place for you.
You must be upset that you can’t have sex.
And even though you tell me it’s wrong, your dick is still getting hard.
Hey... use my stockings to do the same thing as the video.
It’s okay with me.
You really want to have sex, but can’t, right?
So that’s why...
Come on, Dad, do whatever you want.
Dad...
You ripped my stockings.
Dad... Now they're all torn.
Can you see it?
Hey...
I actually want to have sex but we don’t have to, Dad.
You see how wet my panties are, right?
Thinking about you makes juice flow out.
Yeah... you’re so wet.
That’s because I want your dick so much I can’t stand it.
Ayame.
Dad! That’s what I wanted!
It’s here! It’s here!
Dad... your dick...
This... yes...
Oh yes, it’s so deep!
It’s embarrassing, but I can’t hold back!
Fill me up, Dad!
Yes, more, more, deeper!
To my uterus... I like it in there.
Dad, you’re... making me so full...
More, I want more.
Your dick... it’s coming all the way inside...
Twirling around...
It’s stuck deep inside!
This feels too good!
Dad... I’m cumming!
I’m cumming!
Dad... Keep going and cum in me!
Cum inside me!
Hey, that’s not a good idea.
But I won’t let you go!
Just cum like this.
Dad... your dick... let it out inside...
I’m cumming too!
I’m cumming... cumming!
Dad... Your sperm... so much went in...
I’m so happy.
There’s still some left.
Dad... Your sperm is on my uniform.
Book: History
Dad, hurry, let’s go.
Lunch?
I ate it early because I was looking forward to our time together at lunch.
I’d rather free up more time for sex.
Ohh, pests!
I’m gonna go tell them to leave so I can have sex with Dad...
Wait, stop joking!
But I want your dick soon, Dad.
I can’t hold back.
Hey, people will notice.
Lucky us, the school nurse is out today.
I’m not sure if that’s exactly “lucky”...
There’s plenty of beds we can use.
Dad, will you listen to my request?
Request?
A friend told me...
That she does it with her butthole too.
Butthole... anal sex?
Anal sex sounds dirty and sexy.
Dad, you pervert.
You're the pervert! You haven’t even done it much the normal way yet!
She also told me she only does anal with a guy she truly loves.
That it hurts, but it’s a special treat for him.
Did you and Mom do lots of anal?
Well, we weren’t like that...
Then you’ve never done anal?
I’d be your first?
But I haven’t agreed to do it yet...
What a relief! If you had said no I would have brought this here for nothing.
Ayame...
I’m really nervous.
Staring at me like that is embarrassing.
Your asshole is pulsating...
Oh, Dad, you meanie.
Please, hurry.
Spreading it so suddenly...
No...
So cold!
It’s spreading... with your finger...
Spread it slowly.
Okay, I need to be gentle.
Oh! It’s inside... oh no, oh no!
I feel like I’m gonna poop! Oh no, oh no!
Move slowly, Dad.
Slowly!
It feels so strange.
This... does it feel good? Do I like it?
Please! Give me your first time, Dad!
All in good time. Be patient.
It’s starting to feel good.
I like my butthole.
Please, hurry.
I want your dick, Dad!
Very well.
It’s coming!
Dad’s first anal sex.
I’m so honored.
That your first is me.
I dreamt of this.
Your first... I wanted it.
I’ve given both.
Both my front and rear holes are yours.
I’m so happy.
It’s okay, Dad, move.
Fill me up. Make me feel good.
Wow.
What is it? It feels very strange.
It’s good...
I think... I’m starting to feel good.
Dad... That hole too? It’s feeling too good now.
Yes... having my pussy twiddled and my butthole fucked... I’m losing my mind...!
Let it out!
I can’t get pregnant from it, so cum lots into my butthole!
Into my butthole!
Wow... Dad.
Cum!
It’s throbbing... so much hot stuff... coming in...
Dad’s sperm... is making my body hot!
Wow. I can’t stop throbbing!
So much is pouring in!
Your semen is spilling from my butt... it’s spilling out!
I wish your semen wouldn’t spill out of me...
Oh dear, lunch is over.
Dad, should I ditch class while we fuck in here?
Hey, that’s no way to talk to a teacher, Ayame.
Jeez, you dare talk that way after what we just did?
Hyouka, don’t say strange things.
The way Dad is now, it’s okay.
After all, he has me.
Right.
I have my ace in the hole... what?
What do you mean?
Hey, don’t jump to conclusions.
Ah, I didn’t mean sexually.
I meant that he wouldn’t be lonely because I’m here for him.
What a problem...
It’s only a matter of time before she finds out.
What’s that?
What is that? Exercising in the middle of the might?
It doesn’t sound right anyway...
Oh, Dad...
What did she say?
Dad’s smell... yes...
The flavor... is so salty, I can’t resist it!
The smell of his dirty underpants.
It’s so smelly and I can’t breathe.
I want more... let me lick it more...
She’s smelling my underpants while...
Don’t watch. You shouldn’t watch that...
I’ll make them clean for you.
I’m dirty too, and I’m telling you I’ll lick your pants clean with my dirty tongue.
You really are a horrible Dad.
But you’re getting bigger, aren’t you?
You’re gonna cum in my mouth again, aren’t you?
Sensational...
Dad's underpants...
www.SubDESU-H.net