Kiss in the Dark
Episode 1
Man, is it already this time?
I'm late! I'm definitely late!
Kyosuke!
I was right. You're still a sleep!
Didn't you promise me that you would
wake up at 6:30 AM and be ready?
Today is my big day for the
start of my academy years!
Who's the bad boy that's
interrupting my sleep?
Who is there other than me?
If we don't hurry up, we'll be
late for the enrollment ceremony!
Hey, Kyosuke!
Kyosuke!
You come in here too.
Let's go back to sleep together.
Stop joking!
I beg you, please don't
go to bed naked. Naked!
I'm wearing...
What?
...Channel's Egoiste.
Faint!
Good morning, my cute Mira.
We are family, aren't we? Family!
I'm late! I'm definitely late!
This is bad.
I'm late from the first day
at the academy.
I worked so hard and got in
the academy of first choice.
Damn it. This happened
because of Kyosuke!
If he didn't start such a thing...
That perverted actor.
It's not like he's a porn actor, but...
Emergency Life Saving ERO
He's been in Hollywood movies.
Eros x Gal Killer
If you do it like this...
Stop.
A lot more...
Not that...
I need to get inside somehow.
Yeah! I found an entrance!
Kyosuke?
No, I'm sure he's still sleeping.
No, it won't open.
Not here either.
Failure
Man, why is it like this?
Where is the building
for first-year students?
Huh?
What are you doing in a place like this?
Aren't you a new student?
Upperclassman?
No, um... Well, I got lost...
So you are a first-year student.
Y-yes!
On top of being lost, I couldn't
get into the building from anywhere.
Also, I couldn't remember
what class I am suppose to be in...
I made it up...
I see. But everything is
going to be just fine now.
Your name is?
I...
I mean...
My name is Munakata!
Munakata...
My name is Mira Munakata!
What?
With the kanji for fruit and
kanji for goodness, it's Mira!
Really? That's a cute name.
This guy... He's really tall...
...and his face is really good looking.
He didn't make a weird face
when I said my name.
Student Council
Student council president?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm Takayuki Utsunomiya, third-year.
Nice to meet you, Mira.
I was right.
Mira, you are in the 3rd class.
Oh, is that so?
I'm glad.
By the way...
...where is first-year
3rd classroom located?
All the teachers are in the
teacher's lounge, so you should be...
...able to get into
the classroom easily!
Hooray!
Ah...
Mira, thanks to you, my academy life
might become more enjoyable!
What?
On the enrollment ceremony list,
I'll mark it as you were present.
Thank you very much!
Yes! The teacher and the
parents aren't here yet!
During this time...
Mira!
Over here, over here!
Huh?
Kazu?
I saved you a seat.
Oh yeah...
I forgot that my childhood friend Kazu
got into Hakuou with me.
Come on. Come over here.
You're in the same class too?
Yeah.
But why did you know?
That's 'cause I checked on
the class assignment chart.
As expected, he's
always a thoughtful guy.
Where were you during
the enrollment ceremony?
Y-yeah, well...
Suspicious...
I was worried about you.
W-what?
What happened?
What?
Well, something...
Were you guys fighting on the
morning of the enrollment ceremony?
Mira...
No...
Shun?
The one that moved away
during elementary school?
Never thought I'd see you
in a place like this.
Y-you...
Weren't you on TV the other day?
I heard you are going from
lndies to major debut...
You were watching?
So it was you.
Your dream from
when you were little came true!
When I grow up, I'm going
to become a musician!
I'll become a soccer player!
I'll...
Um, um...
Mira!
Ah, Papa!
I'm going to become Papa's bride!
I'm in the soccer team and he's
still in mutual love with Papa-san.
Dangerous
Does Kazu know about Kyosuke and l?
No, there's no way!
But wait a second...
Papa, I love you!
I didn't know when I was a little kid...
Splash, splash, splash.
...that it wasn't normal to do
those things as a family.
By any chance, did I tell them
something really bad?
Hey Shun!
Well, I'll see you later.
Okay.
I'm always watching your shows!
Munakata-san, you are so
wonderful on TV also, but...
You are more wonderful in person.
Thank you very much.
Hey, it's Papa-san.
Huh?
He is here?
Then the car before was definitely...
While I was doing everything
I could to make it to school...
...he came with a car.
Even so, Kyosuke-san hasn't changed.
My mom using the fact that he knows
her by face and she's clinging to him.
Papa-san is definitely young...
How old is he?
He's 33.
But it's definitely a lie.
Because with my age, he can't
be that young and be my father!
Certainly.
I hate him.
I hate Kyosuke.
Who did you say you hate?
Kyosuke...
You are already an academy student,
huh?
What is it all of a sudden?
That was pretty fast.
Well...
I took off to be present at
your enrollment ceremony...
...we have some time so why not continue
from where we left off this morning?
I only had milk since this morning.
Papa is hungry.
Mira, you're not satisfied
with just milk too, right?
Milk?
T-then, why don't we
go get something to eat?
No.
Let's do that!
I'm sorry, but I am in
the mood to eat at home.
Look. Right here is my favorite...
No, don't. What are you saying...
Yes.
Ah, thank you for everything before.
What? Right now?
Yes, that's okay.
Kyosuke?
I'm off today, so...
In front of Kawagishi Park Station?
That's fine.
At 7 o'clock?
What? The promise for a date
with someone else?
Yes.
Then I will come
pick you up with my car.
Hooray!
Serves you right!
Ah, no, it's nothing.
Then I will see you later.
Well, let's see...
I'm thinking of taking a
shower before I leave, but...
...I need to punish a bad boy.
From right now,
I'll make you understand...
...what it's like to be a woman.
No...
Academy students are all male!
H-hey, Mira?
Morning, Kazu...
The sun is yellow.
You be a good boy and stay home.
What do you mean by class meeting?
Who are you meeting up with?
Damn it!
What the hell is he doing sex surfing?
H-hey, Mira!
Huh?
Ouch...
Idiot.
You've been out of it
even though it's still morning.
Arg!
I don't care anymore!
I'm making a new start from this year!
Right, Kazu?
Y-yeah...
Good morning, Lost kitten.
Good morning, Utsunomiya senpai.
Ah?
Thank you for the other day.
Thanks to you, I was able
to become your underclassman.
It's okay. You can talk to me
however you like.
You are really cute.
Hmm?
Bye.
See you at school.
You should watch out.
You think so?
I wonder if that perverted old man
is cheating on me as we speak.
I heard this time it's definite for marriage.
When is your wedding planned for?
Mizuki-san! What is your son in law
think about Kyosuke Munakata?
Mizuki-san! Please say something!
He promised me he'd be home early
today!
Hey, Kyosuke.
You're always so beautiful.
That makes me happy.
By the way, is Mira-kun doing well?
He became an academy student, right?
Yeah, he did.
Tell me...
...in detail later...
What's up with this air?
What the hell...
I made dinner and he doesn't even call.
Don't tell me he's
with someone else again!
I can't!
My jealousy is totally obvious!
Why is someone like him my father...
Why is he my lover?
He went to bed already?
Mira?
Mira...
I'm going to move out!
I'm going to move out like mom
who left us so long ago!
Mira!
You are the only one.
To me...
...you are the only one.
Kyosuke.
My only reason to live
in this world is you.
There is no replacement
for you anywhere, Mira.
Oh no, I forgot to give this
to Kyosuke yesterday.
Do I have to submit this
within this week?
Crap, it's till tomorrow.
I remember you can only get...
...a copy of the family register
in your permanent domicile.
Hey Shun! Are you
going to the studio now?
Y-yeah.
Our permanent domicile
is the next county over.
Well, I'm off.
Yeah, good luck.
Kazu, come with me for a little!
I'm going to join the soccer team...
Can you do that tomorrow?
Mine is an emergency!
Munakata
I can't believe we need a seal...
...to get the copy of the original.
I wasted 300 yen.
There, there.
Hey, remember how
they use to have secrets...
...about your birth in
old dramas and mangas?
What?
I remember Kyosuke being in
something like that before too.
Oh, I know!
Kyosuke-san was the brother of
the girl with the main roll, but...
...they weren't actually
related by blood.
And he got really confused, but...
...somewhere along the line
they loved each other.
It's unbelievable, right?
I thought it was so lame.
But I was watching with my mom
and I actually cried during it.
Are you serious?
Hey, what would you do if you
weren't really Kyosuke-san's son?
Of course I'm going to be glad.
And you guys will love each other...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Ah, no...nothing.
My father and l?
You got to be kidding me...
But being gay, having a Shotaro
complex, and committing incest...
Then am I going to have one less issue?
Y-you...
Don't say it yourself!
It hurts. Stop!
Ward Residents lntegration Window
Munakata-san.
This can't be true...
What's wrong?
Are you serious?
Mira...
Kazu...
I'm not...
...Kyosuke's real son?
It's a lie, right?
As much for me to forget to blink...
matatakisae wasurerukurai
瞬きさえ　忘れるくらい
...I'm occupied with
just you all the time.
anata dake de itsudemo
あなただけで　いつでも
Please stop the time forever.
toki wo tomete zutto
瞬間を止めてずっと
This room that no one's in...
dare mo inai kono heya
誰も居ないこの部屋
The TV is vacant.
terebi ga munashiku
TVが空しく
I look for a part of you.
kimi no kakera sagashite
キミの欠片探して
Then I pretend I wasn 't looking.
mata minai furi wo suru
また見ないフリをする
Am I wrong? We most likely...
machigatteru kitto bokura wa
間違ってる？きっと僕らは
...don't need anything else.
hoka ni nanimo iranai
他に何もいらない
Because not even
one person knows the truth.
datte hontou no koto wa
だって本当のコトは
dare hitori wakaranai yo
誰ひとり　わからないよ
As much for me to forget to blink...
matatakisae wasurerukurai
瞬きさえ　忘れるくらい
...I'm occupied with
just you all the time.
anata dake de itsudemo
あなただけで　いつでも
You look through my heart.
Stop my love.
kokoro no naka misukasareru
心の中　見透かされる
Stop My Love
Gentle kiss with just the two of us.
We start the morning again today.
yasashii kisu futari dake no asa wo
優しいキス　ふたりだけの朝を
kyou mo mukaeru toki wo tomete zutto
今日も迎える　瞬間を止めてずっと
Stop the time, forever...
I wasn't Kyosuke's son...
Then what about our relationship?
On top of that, getting
married to that person?
What?
Kyosuke was in an accident?
Kyosuke!
You reactions are extreme...
Did it turn you on that much?