Unforgivable, Tamao Tsukamu.
Since it has come to this,
I'll use the power of Sasugake clan and bury you six feet under!
You there,
help me up.
My body is still...
Young Master.
I am the Sasugake clan's personal secretary.
The only reason why the Sasugake clan turned a blind
eye to your aggressively egocentric behavior
was because you were supremely unrivaled.
You truly were the perfect heir to carry
on the legacy of this Sasugake clan.
What a miserable defeat.
You have lost all rights to be the next
successor of the Sasugake clan.
Further selfish actions will not be tolerated by the clan master.
Wait! Stop!
My grandfather, who was revered for being
the best swordsman in the country,
started to avoid dueling me when I was but seven years of age.
The blade was already a part of me the moment I held onto it,
and I knew how to wield my deadly ki early on.
TL Note: ki  is the circulating life energy that is balanced in
positive and negative forms and is inherent in all beings.
Even long before, ki was an inseparable element for a
swordsman putting their lives on the line during a battle.
When ki invigorates your body,
it becomes a radar of sorts that senses your
enemy's movements beforehand.
Not only that, a simple bamboo sword becomes
hard as a steel rod in your hands.
Your fight earlier was splendid.
You really are amazing...
I wonder if it's the fact that you are peerless
because your ki  is amazing or,
your ki  is outstanding because you
have been unrivaled to begin with.
So, I took advantage of your potential
and dragged you into this mess.
However, I never thought that you'd become this manly.
Allow me to give my utmost gratitude.
Thanks to you,
the graduating students don't have to
become prostitutes and have sex against their will.
You also protected the upcoming graduating students.
To tell you the truth,
I'm overwhelmed with my feelings of
affection and gratitude towards you.
If you so desire,
I would even gladly offer my own body
and spread my own legs for you.
But.
If I choose that...
Then I won't actually be getting the real  you. Right, senpai?
That is correct.
They're serious?
Someone will die if we don't stop them!
They're really serious.
Konome's really going for it!
Gamble Duel
Last Fight
Kiritani Konome
vs.
Tamao Tsukamu
Going for it... ?
Fighting with weapons without the
possibility of stopping midway?
If Konome's using a real sword in battle,
then she can no longer be stopped.
She has a "shell" around herself.
A shell?
Born into a household that specializes in kendo,
she was trained with extreme discipline at a very young age.
Without faltering or loosing,
she just continued to train herself as a swordsman.
Hence she wears the shell of a swordsman.
That's why for her, any agreement
made in a contest is absolute.
Even when she was forced to be Kunitake's fiancée
because her father bet her and lost to Sasugaki's father,
she simply viewed it as the result of the contest
and solemnly accepted it.
In order to break her shell as a swordsman
and obtain the real her,
the only option is to win this fight!
I can feel it.
Her overflowing killing intent...
The premonition of death!
Konome senpai's mind is completely calm.
There is an extremely high probability
that I will die here.
However...
I won't let that happen!
I won't allow her to shoulder the guilt of killing me.
If there is one thing that could let me win,
then this would be it!
I accept my defeat.
For you to have used a double strike in that attack...
The first blade was used to absorb my attack
while the second "lower blade"...
... was stealthily used to strike my abdomen.
My womb feels numb from the direct
hit of your overwhelming ki.
And with that unexpected attack,
my unbreakable form is finally broken.
Konome senpai!
I love you!
I love you so much!
Konome senpai!
With Konome-senpai, I...
Konome-senpai...
Konome-senpai!
I
My mouth is now filled with Konome senpai's fluids!
I want to gulp it down, but...
My breasts are getting sticky and wet...
Konome-senpai!
These are your... breasts!
So soft...
Softer than any that I've ever touched...
It's like they are melting!
Fluffy pair of boobs!
I see...
The reason why these big boobs don't
get in the way of her kendo training
is because of their inherent elasticity!
Wait...
No...
Konome-senpai!
I'm sorry.
My body feels weak. It's defenseless and
has become somewhat sensitive.
Senpai!
Tamao-kun... No, not that part...
Don't...
It's dirty...
Wow, amazing...
No, don't...
Tamao-kun, where are you looking at?
Tamao-kun!
Konome-senpai!
We are the executive members of the graduation album!
I think we have an obligation to have
sex and leave memories of it here!
Y-Yes, you're right.
After all, we're members of the Yearbook
Album Committee, right?
Is this pose Okay?
It's great!
It's beyond great, senpai!
You're gorgeous!
Show me your butt!
Face this way!
Yes!
Yeeeeees!!~
Konome-senpai, please.
Slowly unveil yourself to me in that pose!
Show me that!
That place!
I-I get it. Just wait...
That's right. Open it wide and do a peace sign!
Now put your tongue out and smile!
Senpai!
You're cute!
You're absolutely cute!
Really cute!
Super duper cute!
Now, senpai...
Come inside me..
Senpai... Senpai...
Konome-senpai...
This sensation, this feeling...
Now that it's inside, I can actually feel
the mammoth size of your member.
Earlier during the match,
those thugs tried to penetrate me,
but it felt like they were trying to poke
me with a soft jelly like thing instead.
Thanks to my angry killer aura, they
couldn't even get past my entrance.
I am so glad.
I'm able to give you my innermost spot.
Senpai...!~
I came right at the entrance of your womb...
Senpai!
Konome-senpai!
Senpai and I are connected to each other.
Like this... Deep inside her..
Wow, I just realized how overwhelming your penis is
as it pierces deeply inside me.
Senpai... Senpai!
Tamao-kun...
Please, please keep screwing me like this.
Yes!
Like this?
Yes, just like that!
Konome-senpai?
I'm sorry. It seems I just came on my own!
Her body is perfectly sculpted for sex!
Here, just like this...
Senpai, how's this?
It’s good.
It feels great.
Tamao-kun,
I'm going to cum again.
Tamao-kun...
Konome-senpai!
Senpai...
I totally love your big butt!!
It's big, round, soft and shiny.
It’s slimy wet.
Be it your naked ass.
Or your ass in panties.
Or your ass in a skirt.
TL Note: Hakama are Japanese clothing that are worn by women
for sports such as kendo and in other traditional ceremonies.
Even your ass in a hakama.
I love em' all!
I... I love it!
I love this butt!
I adore it!
I love both senpai and her butt!
My big butt, my body and my feelings...
They're all yours, Tamao-kun.
So please take everything that is me.
Please.
Y-Yes!
Konome-senpai, please marry me.
Yes...
Tamao Tsukamu-san.
I might be imperfect,
so please take care of me.
Oh no, please! Even I got carried away in the moment...
But me, also. Please take care of me as well.
Now then, my dear.
Your job is waiting for you.
They are ready for you to fulfill that promise you made.
Pardon me, but after what just happened,
are you Okay with that?
Of course.
After all, I have become the wife of the one
who owns this out of the world thing.
We haven't taken pictures of us having sex, so...
Can we do it once more?
Yes! It will be my pleasure!
I-I'm going to become a Yearbook Album Committee member?
That's right.
You may not know this but...
Our school has a tradition of making
two separate graduation albums.
Eh? T-This is...?!
It's a Hamedori  Graduation Album.
Um, but I'm still a virgin...
This is impossible for me.
That's not true.
I was able to do it,
so I'm sure you can, too.