Cheerleading Club Leader
Honjoumiya Tsubomi
3rd Year Tea Ceremony Club Leader
Mogami       Haru
Not only did you defeat Honjoumiya Tsubomi...
you also challenged the daughter of a yakuza boss,
Mogami Haru, to a gamble fight.
This is news to me.
Now then...
For what reason have you come here for?
It's about time you...
are told everything.
This is...
Last year's sex photo graduation album!
I wanted to investigate a lead
involving shady people misusing the graduation
album and for that reason,
I invited you on board, as an album committee member.
The student council president, my fiancé, Sasugaki Kunitake
uses the sex photo graduation album of our school...
...as a prostitution catalog for political and business circles.
Wha-?
Most probably he does it...
to secure his shady connections
when he enters the financial world sometime in the future.
And of course...
He plans to let the students do it this year too.
No way!
No way in hell!
What then?
Fight...
Fight... with me!
If I win, please end this prostitution
business of yours, immediately!
Also...
The albums that you have distributed
till now... will have to be retrieved.
If you don't comply...
I will not hand over the photos that I have collected this year.
Also...
You would have to break off your engagement
with Kiritani Konome-senpai.
Tamao-kun?
Gamble my woman you say?
The feeble puppy's getting cocky
And even challenges me to a fight...
Very well then.
Interesting!
I'll take that challenge of yours!
The fight starts 3 days from now, after school.
I'll create a special ring just for the event.
It's a head-to-head match.
A fight between two men.
You best prepare your outfit.
Sub
Desu
-H
Pisu
Hame
!
Here, in Shousen Academy's specially setup ring,
lots of students are wildly participating
a fiery match today!
It's a gamble battle!
Student council president,
Sasugake Kunitake.
Graduation album committee member,
and a kendo club member second year student,
Tamao Tsukamu-kun.
The announcer will be me,
Broadcasting Club's vice president,
Jibu Rose.
Commentary will be held by,
Juuri "King" Rora!
This will surely be a wild fight, JR!
The rules aren't just limited to standard fighting.
Unfair tricks are permitted no matter what it is.
It's a hardcore match!
Hardcore match... Look!
The ring is filled with dangerous stuff!
Objective is to incapacitate the opponent,
and snag the graduation album that hangs
above the ring for the ultimate win.
What a monstrous size!
What an overwhelming pressure!
But I can't lose.
I must not lose.
Class 3-D Michisato Madoka
Go-home Club
For the seniors who entrusted their sex photos...
Class 3-A Matsuto Iori
Swimming Club
Class 3-A
Oda Kaede
Class 3-C
Hoshizake Misaki
Class 3-B
Swimming Club Chief
Shimada Ryou
Class 3-D
Suenaga Moe
Class 3-B
Makabe Mai
Class 3-D
Go-home club
Miyanagi Sena
... my seniors who created sex photos with me...
Class 3-D Gravure Idol
Girls Circle
Kizaki Caldina
Cheerleading Club Leader
Honjoumiya Tsubomi
Tea Ceremony Club Leader
Mogami Haru
And...
for Konome-senpai's sake!
President Sasugaki is asking for the microphone.
Tamao-kun.
And all viewers present.
It isn't interesting if we just go with a standard fight.
Let's... have another rule that would elevate
the fight to an interesting level...
The stage's curtain's opened.
This is-!
President Sasugaki has already launched
his first attack with the mic,
without even waiting for the bell!
Tamao-kun!
Everyone already knows that,
Kiritani Konome over there is my fiancé.
But I have currently set her as a gamble for this fight.
Winning will only make this a normal fight.
I will originally gain nothing from such victory.
So at least for me and for you the viewers,
I have added something to make this more enjoyable.
Don't fool arou-!
Konome...
...senpai!
What's the meaning of this?!
The lower body part of the girls brought
by President Sasugaki are!
Look at this JR!
They're completely exposed!
Kunitake-san!
I'm supposed to be the only prize here!
Stop this!
Release all those girls!
I can't accept that demand you see...
Embarrassing these girls is something,
that needs to be done to set an example to those who oppose
Stop fucking around... bastard!
Tamao-kun hits with a counterattack!
He burst with a drop kick from below!
Make them stop!
Right now!
That was lightning fast!
That was an Olympic-level suplex!
He drove through the table head first!
Let me go, you...!
Stop...
Who the fuck are you?
Don't fuck with me...
What should I do?
At worst, if it was only me,
I was prepared to be raped.
At this rate, the other girls will also...
Tamao-kun...
Notice... it quickly!
Tamao-kun!
Don't be fooled by the president's size!
Concentrate on...
... your gut...
Believe in... your true self.
I'll defeat him quickly and save you all
He's up high!
This placement is... bad!
There is a set of ladder below!
Choke Slam!
It's a fury laden direct choke slam!
From that height...
His face has now turned blue!
That's some heavy damage.
Could Tamao-kun still get up?
Stop that.
Don't just use somebody's breasts.
It feels gross.
Tamao!
Toughen up you jerk!
Blow him off quickly!
Caldina-senpai...
One hit from a clothesline!
Tamao-kun's body flew over,
and out of the ring!
Dammit!
President Sasugaki is,
laying the knocked out Tamao-kun...
in front of the... announcer's desk?
Let me tell you why I am doing this form of public execution.
Primarily, it is to render you incapable of facing
Konome anymore, who trusts you deeply.
This will effectively destroy her resistant nature all together.
Along with all of your friends,
I will attack both their mind and body,
to crack open the minds that won't submit
in order to make her the perfect wife!
Will the president really go jumping from
there with that gargantuan body?
D-Don't...
Don't move like that
Oh no...
Someone else other than Tamao-san's is entering me...
N-No way...
I...
... won't lose!
For Konome-senpai's sake...
I just cant lose!
Stop!
Pull it out!
Pull it out!!
Pull it out!!!
Pull it out!!!!
It's no good...
I-I can't win.
Our difference in physical abilities is too great.
It's a tazzmission!
Give up already, Tamao!
You'll die!
Look well...
Tamao-kun.
Senpai...
Konome-senpai...
I'm sorry.
I'm just...
too weak.
I can't save you.
Miyanagi Sena-senpai...
Kizaki Caldina-senpai...
Honjoumiya Tsubomi-senpai...
Mogami Haru-senpai...
Ever since he entered the kendo club,
I have always admired Konome-senpai.
That's why... when she asked me to help
as an album committee member,
I was really happy.
I knew that she had a fiancé...
That's why at the very least
if I am able to do something for her...
I thought that if I am able to be of some use to her...
Even if I am not able to reach out to her with these hands...
I want to release her from her bondage!
Senpai!
Konome-senpai!
I can't take it anymore!
Stop already!
I'm going to cum with my butt!
So please stop!
You won't do with just that!
You want to be of some use to me?
Don't just think about my happiness only!
Yourself!
What do you want to do yourself?!
I want to...
So... witnessing these girls being forced to have sex...
What do you want to do?
What do you want to do with me?
Claim it with your very own hands!
Tamao Tsukamu!
This is the final blow, Tamao-kun.
Die.
This is...
a pedigree?
No!
It's a gachiguri...
I want to...
Konome-senpai...
Kiritani Konome...
Even if she has a boyfriend...
Even if she is betrothed...
I want to...
Alright, let's finish this.
This is!
Tamao-kun revived?
Hey, that's...
His thing is...
Kiritani Konome is my girl!
Don't you touch my girl!
JR...
I thinkl just saw his stiff thing brighten up earlier.
I think I saw it too.
It's not his erection...
It's his gut!
Gut?
Tamao's gut... just fired up.
That's why we see it shining like that.
President Sasugaki.
You are not suitable for Konome-senpai at all!
I will make Konome-senpai happy!
Is this some sort of illusion?
The broken wooden sword isn't even
making any physical contact,
yet is dealing some heavy damage to President Sasugaki.
It's his spirit.
Tamao-kun's overflowing spirit from his gut,
is taking the form of a wooden sword.
He's hitting inside the muscle... right into the soft tissues directly
What?
Down?
He's down!
After that volley of explosive hits,
it's the first time he's gone down!
Is he going to jump like that from the corner post?
Five Star:
Tamao Splash!
Tamao Tsukamu,
has climbed the ladder
and has taken the graduation album!
As expected of a hardcore match thanks
to the performance of Tamao Tsukamu!
It's his victory!
Give me the mic.
Ah, Okay!
Kiritani Konome-senpai...
I...
challenge you to a gamble match!
Okay.
I accept!