PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO PERO
Now then, Milky-chan, please take care
of my good-for-nothing son, okay?
I will!
I'm the only one that really knows him, anyway!
Thank you, Milky-chan.
I'll be off then.
Take care!
Onii-chan, it's noon already!
Food's gonna go cold if you don't wake up already!
Onii-chan, wake up already!
Jeez, my good-for-nothing Onii-chan's really
on the verge of becoming a NEET.
But that's exactly what's so good about him!
And I'm the only one in the whole world that understands that.
...Or so I thought!
You like big breasts, right?
You can fondle these bouncy breasts however you want.
You being a good-for-nothing person
really turns my maternal instincts on!
If this goes on, that bouncy thief will
take my Onii-chan away from me!
I'm never gonna let that happen!
Onii-chan, I’m coming in!
As messy as it's always been.
Don't just barge into my room!
Oh, but I did!
I'm in charge of your lunch,
because your mom asked me to!
I can't just do nothing.
I get it, now please leave.
Are you perhaps... in the middle of enjoying this?
W-what are you saying?
That's not true!
Then are you... maybe... having sex with that woman?
I don’t see how that is any of your business.
But if you're dating...
...you wouldn't be all alone.
I already told you that we aren't like that.
No matter how I look at it, you were
definitely playing with yourself.
Well, this is...
This is my chance!
I can use this opportunity to win him over!
Hey, Onii-chan,
if you’re really that interested in a girl's body...
I can show you mine, if you want.
What?! What's gotten into you?
Or are my breasts too small for you?
Well, size isn't all that important...
Then, why don't we put it to the test?
Oh, so all your knowledge about sex comes from this book!,huh?
Okay then, I shall teach you the real thing!
Hey! Are you seriously...?
I You don't want to have sex with a real girl, Onii-chan?
Of course, but...
Which one is it?
Jeez, you're so indecisive!
Woah! At least one of you doesn't know how to lie.
Look, this is the panties you've always wanted to see.
They sure are cute
You mean like a child's?
No, I think they suit you.
Cute things, you know.
R-Really?
I'm happy, then!
This is actually my favorite pair!
Can I take a closer look?
Um... Okay...
But only because it's you, okay?
They smell kinda good.
Th-they do?
I can't really tell.
Your breath is tickling me.
Hey, can I touch them?
Huh?!
Touching them is a bit...
Off-limits, huh?
I can't be doing this.
My chance would be gone if I turn him down.
Well, you can, but just a little.
Really, Milky?
You just said
the thing all guys want to hear.
You're living in a fantasy world.
This paragraph says something like, "Explore the
undiscovered flower garden in front of you."
That tickles.
Why?
Why does it feel so good?
Is it because it's Onii-chan?
My insides feel somehow weird.
It also says "...and make her climax at least once."
No, don't stare so much.
Does it look weird?
I've never seen one before, so...
But it’s still beautiful!
Really?
No, you're making my hips move too!
I can't see anything. You need to spread your legs.
L-like this?
This is really embarrassing.
Just by having him stare, it already feels...
Onii-chan, you have to make me feel it all the way inside.
It explicitly says so here.
You really just want to cum, don't you?
That's not true!
Just show me how it's done, as the book says.
What?
This position is embarrassing.
Your thing is totally exposed.
No, don't look!
Don't... lick it...!
That s where I pee.
I want to see more of you...
No, don't spread it!
On all fours now?
Your asshole...
It looks cute.
This is embarrassing.
If you keep fondling it like that...
Please...
Don't be so rough...
No, not there!
It feels too good.
My nipples feel good!
I'm starting to become really sensitive.
Don't!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum, Onii-chan!
So, what are we going to do next?
Onii-chan, I just came, you know.
Aren't you supposed to be teaching me?
Jeez, you're such a meanie.
It says here, "Have the woman you just
pleasured perform a blowjob on you."
I see...
Okay then, please do.
Jeez, you’re so helpless.
I'll have to make you cum then!
Does this feel good?
Yeah... Keep it up...
Does it feel good here, too?
I want you to put it
in your mouth.
Like this?
Your thing is twitching.
I can tell you're aroused.
It's moving all over in my mouth.
It feels like it's going to burst!
Onii-chan!
It tastes really weird.
But I love your scent and cum.
We're not done yet, right?
What does it say next?
Well...
"Next, do whatever pleases you.
A swimsuit, a school uniform, or a PE
uniform are all acceptable choices.”
What does that mean, Onii-chan?
Just as it says.
You're gonna have to change...
Eh? But I didn't bring a swimsuit nor a PE uniform.
I have lots here.
Why do you have school swimsuits and PE uniforms?
Here's my chance!
If he's yet to have sex with his girlfriend,
then I can win him over by being tolerant of his hobbies!
So, Onii-chan,
what should I wear?
The fact you have this is very suspicious,
but I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
In many ways, you are really good-for-nothing.
According to the book, the only way to
gain the advantage over big boobs
is to be sexually aggressive, exploiting his fetish.
Onii-chan, what are you suddenly...
If you play with my nipples like that...
They will get hard!
No, don't play with my nipples!
Hey, Onii-chan, your hot thing is...
It's rubbing against the swimsuit and my skin.
The tip is also rubbing against my nipples.
It keeps on twitching while my chest is being played with!
Your thing is getting even bigger.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Lots of your hot cum is pouring on my nipples.
It feels really embarrassing,
but it's written in the book, right? The 69 position?
What?
Why? My body is starting to feel all tingly.
I'm also going to do yours.
I'm really sensitive now, so...
It feels good when I lick the tip, right?
It's getting big again.
Amazing...
D-don't. If you lick there...
We both are about to...
Your tongue is all the way inside.
It's getting bigger inside my mouth...
It's already at its limit, right?
It dripped a bit.
You came all over my face.
It tastes weird.
Onii-chan, it's still big.
It's really vigorous.
Does this mean you're ready for round two?