A stifling crowd.
A man and a woman get their bodies close to each other...
and feel each other's lively touches.
A strange atmosphere in our daily lives.
In that atmosphere, even a sigh becomes intertwined...
and awakens indecent desires within a woman's supple body.
He seems enchanting and guides them sexually.
A magician with his fingers.
People call them...
perverts.
Could this possibly be...
a pervert?
Hey, what are you...
W-Why you...
Stop...
No way!
C-Cut that out...
No...
Not here...
N-No...
You're really wet.
No...
Next stop is Ukuro. Ukuro.
The doors will open on the left.
I'm going to come...
No...
I can't belleve the hands of a pervert are going to make me come...
My nipples and clitoris...
You're not good at all.
It seems you imposed on many women in their morning commutes...
but it might be better if I scream and have you arrested.
I want you to improve your skills.
And these hands...
Make me come.
Hey...
S-Stop.
N-No way... No...
No...
Don't do that!
N-Not there...
I have a favor to ask.
I'm heading back to Shizuoka right now.
Can you be my bodyguard?
I kind of stand out, and I don't know when a pervert might strike.
To tell you the truth, I'm lonely.
I was invited to my friend's wedding today.
Hey, do you normally leave in this kind of situation?
If you do, then I have a plan.
Everyone...
Does it feel good?
It's mortifying to be on the receiving end all the time.
Amazing... So strong...
I can't control myself anymore.
No! It's too much!
I'm coming...
I'm coming! Yes!
He seems enchanting and guides them sexually.
A magician with his fingers.
People call them...
perverts.