Jinguuji Miko medium detective office
I'm Kanda Rokuro.
I'm my own manager, a smart assistant
and I do odd job duty in this office.
She... Jinguji Miko is a genius medium, also
a beautiful venus with a nice figure.
We met through destiny and have fallen in love...
...at the same time I became an assistant.
Since I'm deeply in love, I'm also going
to follow her my whole time.
Although I have many things to learn about her.
What will I find? Everyday is so exciting!
My son's under the critical point because of my desire.
The seal has appeared?!
PROFILE 1
KANROKU'S DOPPELGENGER
Hello, this is Jinguuji Miko medium detective office.
I feel horny like you.
Your cock is honest, isn't it?
Make love to me.
Coming extasy?! But she's not occupied.
Help... me!
Stupid... you'll regret if you stop fucking me.
Before it's too late!
Chance! Miko-san!
She's my secretary I sacked!
Still you who has any hatred, you
dead ghosts shouldn't be here.
Rapidly rise into heaven!
Good job, Miko-san.
Yes, such a powerful ghost... thank
you for your support, Kanroku.
What?! You did my daughter?!
No way..the situation just involved us.
Mao's first lover... I'm occupied by ghosts easily.
Please help me out from now on...
instead of working at your office.
That's anannoyance... Don't you think, Miko-san?
I don't mind, I've wanted another assistant.
Miko-san!
Mao, keep away. Man, wear trousers.
Just like that we welcomed a 2nd assistant.
I think she's a little entusiastic... but she's so cute!
Great Izumo co. President... he rewards as he likes.
Nearby he can build a castle in Maldives.
No consideration of their status, they're
the same in terms of annoying.
O... Ok.
Your idea is good, and pay better
attention to your clothes...
...always shabby...
Hello!
Hello, I bought some apples... there was so many
at a low price, want to eat them now?
Good.
Me too.
Alright.
Mao-chan... you've been occupied again?
- Stab...! 52 times...!!
- SO MANY?!
Staaaaaaaaaaaaaab!!!
I will soon be finished preparation.
Please, place that note on her head forever.
Miko?
Azusa!
Long time no see.
No need for friendliness, today I claim you...
...because you request such cheap rewards...
That robs work from me.
Ask for a higher reward.
Our policy is a reasonable price and reliable job.
Stop false charging.
Who are you?
Assistant with my manager, and odd...
Looks so so...
Don't touch! He's my steady.
Steady? Hmm... looks too young.
I won't change the price.
Huh... have you any greed?
By the way, who are you?
Ryougetsuin Azusa. My senior.
Ok, then Miko, instead of lowering
your working price, support me.
What do you say?
You can't support your senior's request?
In this job genre senior is the same as parents...
...so I believe you can take some
time for me occasionally.
Anyway I need you, come with me.
Miko-san, shall I follow you?
Eat the apples.
Here.
Thank you for your consideration.
I've never seen inside a motel...
Quickly let's finish. Will you make a shield?
Y... Yes!
Kanroku-san.
How about teatime?
No, thank you.
Miko-san has been away, so there's
no work. You can go ho...
You wanna let me go home?
I had no such thought.
Then I will stay, ok?
Ah... well, ok.
Really? I'm so happy!
It's only us...
Treat me as you like.
Mao...
Rapidly go rise into heaven!
I've decided to marry you, Kanroku.
I'm in love with Miko-san...
Then forcefully...
N... No...
Mao-chan...
No, stop.
Mao...!!
No... please...
Stop...
Freeze!
You overdid.
Clench your teeth!! Now rise!!
Sin, cosine, tangent, vector, equation
of higher degree, 3.141421356...
Mao-chan, it's not allowed in this office...
this is a holy workspace... so please...
Damn.
Thank you Miko, for your job as a decoy,
I was able to finish smoothly.
I don't have that kind of will.
That was a nice scene.
I dunno!
By the way, Miko. One of our employers resigned.
Therefore I'm frustrated, would you satisfy me?
No, I can't, Azusa, let me off!
Kanro... ku... san...
That was great, Miko. It's just you were frustrated.
For us medium, vigor equals medium power.
For additional performance you
need a partner, don't you?
That assistant... how about him?
Kanroku-san is just an assistant, I
don't have such emotion for him.
Another girl... cute and aggressive.
Kanroku and that girl will be nearby...
Again I say, I don't like him!
Ok, I sleep now... Goodnight.
Bye now.
Renumeration.
I have many hand glasses...
It's a magical glass... fullfills your wishes.
Good, breaktime.
I made us some green tea and cookies.
Tasty green tea...
Thanks, and this is a present for you, Kanroku.
For me? Really?
It's a little early for a happy-birthday present...
A present... from Miko!! Can I open it now?
Ok... this is my first choice for a guy's present.
I hope you like it...
Huh... a tie...!
For your looks. You need to take care of your fashion.
Thank you very much Miko-san!
Please don't misunderstand... as a office staff I pre...
I'm really happy, thanks a lot Miko-san.
Kanroku-san.
Miko-san.
Good morning!
Good morning, Mao!
Already at the office, Kanroku? Great!
Thanks.
Miko-san, I'll work hard again today.
Do your best.
Kanroku-san, let's clean the office together.
- No, wait a moment, please.
- Follow me.
A birthday.
Looks good, but I feel slightly lonely...
Found it out.
Ok, good!
I'm back, Mao.
Welcome back!
Such hard work...
You said "it's easy" when you go out.
That means I worked very hard.
I worked too.
I know.
Pay for this month is slightly higher.
Oooh... great, Miko-san.
Kanroku-san, I wanna go to a movie theater.
How about tomorrow?
Sorry, tomorrow is...
Already scheduled?
Ah... well...
Then, next week reserve time for me, please.
I'll go home now.
Ok, bye.
Bye bye.
Kanroku, can I invite you to a bar?
This is saturday-evening...
Ok, but just for one hour.
I'm so lucky!
Hello, this is Jinguuji Miko medium detective office.
Miko-san... this is Kanroku.
What is it?
In fact... ah well...
Eh...
Yes.
Yes, 9:00 AM. Ok, good night.
I'm finished being tempted for tomorrow's
birthday... only with Kanroku...
I didn't guess her answer...
I hope god's in his heaven, and all is right
with the world. Then next night I can...
Sorry, please wait for a while.
No problem, I will wait any time.
When was this glass mirror put here...? Oops, I
should adjust the tie Miko-san bought for me.
It's the biggest event in my life,
absolutely successfull...
Whatever I get Miko...
No, no...
I must play it cool..
Then i will seduce Miko with my charm.
Then she will want to fuck...
I own that.
Who?!
Eh? Myself?
Yes.
Yes, Kanroku-san.
Sorry, I'm late, Kanroku-san.
Miko-san, you're beautiful.
Thank you.
Shall we go?
Yes!
You'll be a stolen heart tonight.
Cold...
It's time to check-in. Let's go to the hotel.
Yes.
Kanda Rokurou
Izumo Mao
Damn, nobody comes on Sunday!
Miko will be...!!
Hey, Miko?
What're u doin'?
Happy birthday!
Thanks, Miko-san.
Wasn't it expensive?
It's the best day of my life, no problem.
Let's toast in honor...
of your beauty.
Your just a little drunk.
Azusa-san, do you know who he was?
I say again, your doppelgenger.
As in a clone... amplificated desire.
Desire?
That glass gives substance.
Deeper desire makes the doppel clear.
So who knows what it will do to Miko-san.
But since he is a ghost, she must notice that!
About that I can say one...
Before medium,
she's a women...
having desire, any passion makes coolness lack.
So her desire may cloud her judgement.
That is...
You can be proud of that, and that doppel
will be absorbed into that glass.
Therefore no serious problem I feel.
Problem!! My most important day
and I can't stay with her?!
I'll protect her from my clone!
Then follow me!
Bahhh! Don't kill me!!
Ah... Kanroku-san...
Don't hold out, Miko-san, you're
an excellent present for me.
Miko-san!!
Damn crappy clone!! What did you do?!
You see.
Both... Kanroku?
Miko-san, this is a phantom!
Cruel phrase.
Original was your emotion, that
means I'm essential and truth.
Shut up!! Don't put together love and avarice!
Get back from here!
That glass is for counseling. Desire yields
delusion and mistaking PolterGeist.
I didn't know that.
Miko, really you couldn't notice?
The doppel was a mirror image...his
hair style indicated him false.
No way. Since I was invited, I couldn't see him openly.
...Miko-san...
Anyway, stay here tonight. I'll go home.
Azusa, the mirror!!
W-w-w-what's... happening?
There pouring out.
Desire had began a self-reproduction.
Why?
Triggered by your doppel on this position is bad.
Damn residual spirits... also departed soul gathering!
Perhaps impossible to put them back into the mirror...
Then?!
No confidence... but I'll try!
Kanroku! Azusa!
Gah... can't self-secade away...
Miko-san... escape...
Kanroku-san... I depend on you.
Miko...
Gods in heaven and earth, lend me power!
Good job.
All cleaned up... nice work, Miko-san.
Miko-san!
She's not sick!
It's a side effect of her performance.
Instead of god's power, sexual
capacity is out of control.
Reckless sexual vigor?
Let her relax.
Did you hear the words...
"I depend on you"?
K... Kanroku-san...
Have... sex... with me...
Not as an assistant, as a guy... you have to do it.
Really it's ok?
Kanroku-san... yes, I ask of you.
Miko-san.
Miko-san...
If you allow me to... I will stay with you forever.
Kanroku-san...
Huh... we could return regularly.
Yeah, sure.
Kanroku-san...
M... Mao-chan!
Good morning...
You had a confidencial travel... and didn't
come home until the morning.
Ahh... we had a deeper reason... right Mi... Miko-san??
So cruel... was I ostracized... I wanna travel with you!!
Yatte mitai koto ippai
Mao!! Don't remove that pendant...!
Mayocchau hodo afureteru noni
Gah... stab...!! 108 times staaaaaaaaaaaaaaaab!!
Mainichi no hima mo ippai
Futari no escalator hissi de nobotteru kibunn
Wow... it's very sunny today!
Kyoumi iro ni ippai jibunn no karada utsushite mitemo
Korega watashi no shoutai
Hayari no fashion ha emotion janai imitation
Atsuzoko jyussenchi takai sekai
Kokokara mieru monoga hontou tte omottenai kedo
NEXT EPISODE
Nakyanai nakanai nakyanai sagasanakya mitsukaranai
Sappari kotae ga denakute soredemo asa ha kuru kara
Pink no fuku de dekakeyou
Anytime anywhere anyway tamesa nakya hajimara nai
Taiyou ga utatane suru mae ni kakedase so what can I do?
PROFILE 2
A PENDANT DELIVERS FASCINATION AND TERROR