I'm back.
Hello.
Oh this? Sorry, I borrowed it,
instead of wearing pajamas.
Outrageous!
You require of tired me, another job?
Please stop, Kanroku...
I ask you to have some willpower.
Dinner will get cold!
Before dinner, I will taste you!
Dinner menu is...
boild beans, adzuki-bean soup with rice cake,
baked abalone and clam, pickles, miso soup...
Only abalone and clam?
As a dessert, gelatin cubes and
boiled beans with molasses.
How about fresh milk?
Don't cum inside me... I'm not on the pilll!
Jeez...
Despite my age I still had a wet dream.
Kanda Rokurou
Izumo Mao
PHANTOM HUNTER MIKO
PROFILE 2
A PENDANT DELIVERS FASCINATION
AND TERROR
Mao-chan.
Being late is not rare, for Kanroku.
Don't worry, he'll come soon.
Well, Miko-san...
Yes?
Good morning!
You're one hour late, Kanroku-san.
Sorry.
Don't worry, are scheduled work is for tonight.
Please rest a little till it's time. Mao-chan, you too.
Okay.
St. Marianne Nurse's School
A dormitory in a nurse's school...
That is a student nurse harem.
Though at midnight additional ghosts appear...
only dead people will be here.
That's not true.
Thank you for your hard work.
We'll relieve your fatigue.
Let's carry him to another place.
We can study him there.
I feel no indication of ghosts, nothing will
be happening today... shall we go back?
Miko-san...
Well... I have a bad feeling.
Welcome to St. Marianne Nurse's School
Emergemcy lifesaving room.
Poor guinea pig.
W-w-what does that mean?!
We're residents, you will help our practice as nurse's.
The concept of "elucidation of male sexual function".
J-j-just stop.
Hmm... in normal condition... Harumi, record.
- Okay.
- What's ok?!
- Just raise it.
- Okay.
- What?! Don't do that...
Complete.
Okay, next I'll...
I see...
My dad is worrying...
So you finally have to decide.
Kanroku will feel lonely.
Really?
No reaction.
All right.
How about this?
It reacts!
Additional...
Stop right now!
Althought I feel lucky!
Rapid reaction observed, standing upright!
Something great...
Gradually becoming bigger.
Weird...
How about now.
N-now?
Full reaction, popping veins... great!
I can't bare it, I'm going mad.
Fuck me...
Me too!
I can't control myself!
Lick!
Last experiment at last!
You horny?
No, stop right now!
Sayuri, how's it feel?
Slightly tight... but nice.
It's going in all the way!
Change with me please, I wanna study.
Ah... don't grind! I'm cumming...
Shinjuku Koma theater, Geronpa,
no praises, danger: no mixing...
Damn, was almost there...
Get off Sayuri, I'll try!
No reaction...
You can't treat me readily.
No way, use this.
That...
Central nervous system of ejaculation is in the asshole.
Here insert this...
Sayuri, Harumi, hold legs!
No... fuck!! That's not for insertion!!
Sachiko, this is...
Maximum power
Follow me.
Kanroku-san!
Electroshock sucks...
My last request was fabrication... produced by
those nurse students. It was a cruel incident.
Ah... Miko-san, how about coffee?
I've gotten some already, thanks.
True.
By the way, Mao is late? That's odd...
She has a meeting with a view to marriage.
Marriage?
Perhaps she couldn't tell you,
Kanroku. Do you mind that?
No, just seems unexpected...
I wish her success.
Mao, I'll never allow you to get married to that guy.
This meeting is over.
Don't follow me, I'm taking shower.
Kanroku-san...
Only once...
Please...
Kanroku-san!
Izumo family
Ise family
Well, what cooking are you good at, Mao-chan?
Chilled tofu.
Then favorite movie?
"Friday, 13th".
Mao, put your heart into it.
Being a horror film freak is bad?
Then, what's your hobby?
Being occupied by ghosts.
Mao!
Haha, so fun, I like you.
Like? Even after this?
What's happening?!
Mao... are you occupied again?
Fucking dad!!
A living body is good. Don't you think so too?
Let's enjoy having lively sex...
You again?!
Don't bring disaster into this world you
no name ghost... raise into heaven!
Miko-san, cast a sealing spell!
Lend me power... for sealing this evil ghost!
Damn!!
As we thought, Mao brought a pot.
Perhaps to break up this meeting...
But why?
That is...
Kanroku-san...? Kanroku-san!
Mao.
Be quiet now.
But...
Please pay attention to her. She has to set things right.
Ok, I didn't consider her feelings.
Sorry, Mr. Ise, will you cancel this meeting?
Miko-san?
Take care of Mao.
Why did you do such stupid thing?
Stupid? Falling in love with you is stupid, Kanroku?
I'll go to USA tomorrow.
USA?
To study.
Provided this meeting fails... long
before being determined.
I couldn't say the truth..
Mao-chan.
My last request... only for tonight, stay with me.
I felt her heart was...
...into Kanroku.
Please satisfy me too...
Ah ok...
Finish inside me... please... Kanroku!
Kanroku-san!!
What time is your flight?
Your flight...
It was...
...just a joke!
I will go to the office tomorrow, as usual.
Whaaaaaaaat?!
Haha, you've been tricked.
Damn it...
Wanna do it once more?
Noooo.
Please.
Come on...
Alright... only this once.
Kanroku... thank you, I'm so happy.
Jinguuji Miko medium detective office
Miko-san, good morning.
Kanroku-san, aren't you going to see Mao off?
Haha, you've been taken in?
Dear Miko-san, thanks for your kindness
in this short time, bye! From Mao.
That was her joke...
She told me studying abroad was a lie...
It's hard for her to be seen off by you.
I was told the same.
I'm really sorry, Mao-chan.
If only I can make someone happy.
I'll choose...
I'll choose Miko-san.
For her...
...happiness.
Michinoku Kokeshi-lunch, rice with beef in Maezawa, Sanriku, Makunouchi Kamogawa-lunch, add order.
Stop master, or you'll have a stomach ache again.
Shut up, I wanna enjoy myself since
I'm not in the mountain's.
I admit we live in a deep mountain...
But when will you supress yourself?
Ah... Call Azusa and Miko
No! Master, you must make a visit.
What do you say? I already had a reservation
for a gorgeous Condominium.
You still think we shouldn't call them?
Jinguuji Miko medium detective office
Hello, this is Jinguuji Miko. Oh
Kayano? Long time no see.
Oh really? Yes I'll go of course, thanks. Bye now.
Kanroku-san.
Yes?
Shall we go to the beach?
Excellent!!
Kanroku-san.
You have a long time to look at me in a swimsuit.
Miko-san, you look very good.
Thanks.
Miko!
Azusa... beautiful!!
Yay.
Azusa, you too were called by master?
Exactly.
Ah, this is spare clothes, hang on to it.
Where's the master and Kayano?
Hot girl hunting!! Curving hips, waving
breasts... soooooo exciting!!
Punishment from Heaven!
Sorry for bothering, really sorry.
This is judgement, you perverted master.
Azusa-san, Miko-san, thanks for the help.
Sorry, I was away changing my clothes.
Chamberlain is hard work I guess.
- Sorry for trouble.
- Miko-san, Azusa-san... don't leave me!
Gimme your paw, to this nice-body beauty.
Once he was a watchdog, now he always sleeps.
Azusa, let's drink.
Okay.
This is Kanda Rokuro.
Our master, Hyakkendou Keijin
and his follower, Kayano.
Nice to meet you, I'm Miko's assistant.
Ah, so you are her assistant.
Yes. We work hard together.
Already you have good partnership.
What?! That is are you having sex everyday´?
I beg you not to speak of that loudly.
Not everyday yet, only once...
For us medium, sexual desire is routes
of spirits. Devote yourself.
Okay, I'll do my best!
By the way, Kanda.
Yes.
Kanda. I've never heard of that name before.
Just remember! It's similar to Kandagawa Toshirou!
Kandagawa Toshirou: actor's name.
Sorry for you to see him like this.
Everytime you watch him instead of us, Kayano.
I prepared a special item to release you from Master.
What's this?
Eagle-nail pendant?
Magic item for indian's.
Take a hair from him and...
insert it into the pendant.
Do the same for another pendant, and it's complete.
Hang it on his head.
Breasts!!
Master?
Okay, it succeeded.
Be quiet for a while, Master.
You said "Master", that means...
Yes, these're trading body pendants.
Then the dog body = master spirit,
and master body = dog spirit?
It's easy to fix.
Okay, let's go to the beach!
Really ok?
I'm afraid of what he will do when he awakes.
It's bad bothering others, so supressing him is a good idea.
Ready!
Kanroku-san, nosebleed...
Are you ok?
I'm okay...
Don't worry, just put a bandage on.
After this long, I feel like relaxing.
You can take a rest, sure.
That pendant works very well, where did you get it?
From an individual import, but I bought alot of unit's.
So there are many?
You try with these.
Yeah, good idea.
Azusa, Kayano-san, food's ready!
I'll take dinner first!
Ughh... I ate too much!
I enjoyed it!
Then...
- Ouch.
- What's up?
You took my hair... what are you doing?
Kidding!
Good suggestion.
Huh? Me?
Am I Kayano?
Oops, this is Azusa's body.
Not a strange consideration.
What did you do that for?
I'll use this chance for feeling happy a little more.
Like this.
Just stop!
I'll act as you. For the performance.
This body is too sensitive.
Stop Azusa!!
Make them stop, Kanroku!
Kanroku!!
- Hey, don't play with my body selfishly.
- How's the lower half...?
What is this?
Who did this prank.
Azusa, don't touch!
Feels so good...
Kayano... you too acted with Azusa? Stop right now!!
Can I continue, Miko?
Yes, please do.
I AM MIKO!
First time I felt such extasy.
This pendant is evil... so if remove it!
You have to remove both at the
same time, or it's dangerous.
Electric discharge is a safety option.
Ah she unlocked the safety herself.
Please fuck me.
Put it inside me...
Ok, exchange marriage vows.
No, please stop!
Your noisy...
We can hardly enjoy ourselves.
Damn, they treat me as a dog!
- Master!
- Eh?
- Ahh... cumming...
- At last there's the perverts.
Punishments!
Principal offender! I'll kill you!
- No! Not me!
You parasites
Tan-ren-ha!
Once more!
Azusa-san, don't run with an erection!
Shut up!! Then don't expose my breasts!
I feel blue...
Remove all pendants, now!!
Ah I've returned to my body!
But master hasn't changed yet! He's still a dog!
Ah... master, please don't... or I'll be horny too!
Lucky dog.
Looks like he's cuming... that might be good.
I don't get you, Kayano!
Ah! Please, don't stop!
Whaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaat's this?!
Japanese cake freak
All lined up for you.
Fuck!! Who can eat this much!!
You need punishment!
You naughty girl!
Your tits feel so nice.
Excellent!
Sooo goooood!!
Hello!
Welcome back.
Hi, Miko!
Kanroku-san!
Surprised?
Eh...?
It's summer vacation in America.
So I came back temporarily.
I see.
Kanroku, you feel any regrets
pushing me out of your life?
That's not true.
I feel quite happy.
Really?
Of course.
I'm so happy.
Don't touch... I'm sunburnt!
Oh you went to the beach?
How about going again this weekend?
Sounds good!
I bought a new pretty swimsuit.
Look forward to it please, Kanroku.
Summer season has come... I
prefer it myself to be honest.
Yatte mitai koto ippai
Mayocchau hodo afureteru noni
Mainichi no hima mo ippai
Futari no escalator hissi de nobotteru kibunn
Kyoumi iro ni ippai jibunn no karada utsushite mitemo
Korega watashi no shoutai
Hayari no fashion ha emotion janai imitation
Atsuzoko jyussenchi takai sekai
Kokokara mieru monoga hontou tte omottenai kedo
Nakyanai nakanai nakyanai sagasanakya mitsukaranai
Sappari kotae ga denakute soredemo asa ha kuru kara
Pink no fuku de dekakeyou
Anytime anywhere anyway tamesa nakya hajimara nai
Taiyou ga utatane suru mae ni kakedase so what can I do?