Mom. Where's Mom?
She's with Dad. Far, far away.
Mina, don't cry.
Such a crybaby.
Sis, what's wrong?
No, nothing.
Hey, Mina, are you tired?
Can I carry you?
Yes.
WELCOME TO PIA CARROT 2
Today's Special #3:
Would You Like Me to Choose Your Dinner?
Hot!
I'm late.
She'll be mad. Ouch.
Oh, it's you, Mina.
What're you doing here?
Mr. Maeda.
I came to visit Sis, and I got lost.
Lost in the Dorm?
It's their day off today.
Her room, I think, was downstairs.
I'll take you there. Come on.
Thank you.
My legs feel funny.
My legs are asleep!
That's Mina.
That's my sister. What're you doing?
Today's Special #3:
Would You Like Me to Choose Your Dinner?
Why do I have to do the dishes?
Don't complain.
You were late at our busy lunchtime.
With a face like that,
how can you wait on customers?
- Yes.
- Afterwards, clean the bathrooms.
What have I done to deserve this?
Shit. It's Azusa Hinomori's fault.
He's cursing at Azusa again.
Shit, shit, bitch.
His tardiness is nothing new,
but that hand print...
Something happened between them.
Something?
It's Azusa's day off today.
Must've been in his room.
My back hurts.
Lunch should be served on just one plate.
Bathroom is clean now.
Mina. That was my job.
Hey, it's your day off, isn't it?
Yes, but I work the late shift.
I'm sorry about this morning.
No, it wasn't your fault.
It was just your sister.
She just hates me all the time.
Sis worries about me more than necessary.
Since Mom and Dad died
when we were young...
...she's been like a mother to me.
Well, Mr. Maeda.
Mina, no more Mr. Maeda. I don't like it.
Can I call you Brother?
I've wanted to ever since I met you.
Could you take me to the pool
on your next day off?
Yeah, sure.
Brother.
What to do? Is he angry?
I could apologize.
But it's his fault.
He's earned it with his usual behavior.
Why do I have to get depressed over him?
But...
They're slave drivers.
I should go to an arcade
to relieve the stress.
Oops. It's full.
You guys. No other entertainment?
This is pathetic.
Young people go to Karaoke
and arcades to relieve stress.
The End is near.
Hinomori.
"Like a mother to me."
And I thought she was just tough.
Yusuke the Owner?
Okay. I get it.
Hey, hey, what's going on?
Yeah, why isn't Koji late?
Something must have happened.
And Azusa is not here yet.
Good morning. Sorry I'm late.
Good morning.
- Hey. About yesterday...
- Good morning.
Hello! We're open for business!
Okay.
Hinomori can go out
with whoever she wants.
I don't give a damn.
What're you mumbling about?
Brother, what's wrong?
You're here at the pool with me,
and you're not having fun.
No, no, I'm having a great time.
I'm taking a dip, too!
Brother, wait!
May I help you?
So listen.
To relieve your stress,
dive into the cold water...
...wash away the pent-up
frustration, that's the best.
And you've been drinking and drinking.
For letting go of your anger,
nothing beats getting drunk.
What could be pent up inside her?
Dunno. Excuses for getting drunk, maybe?
How rude.
I'm suffering because Azusa is depressed.
What? Because of me?
She's right. You're kinda down these days.
No, I'm doing fine.
Don't lie to us.
You just can't fool grownups.
A girl in love, is a girl who lies.
No, no.
Azusa is in love.
With who?
Must be Ryoko's ex-flame.
No!
Yes! And Jun's conqueror.
That beast.
No way.
Ryoko's broken down a barrier
and now she's free.
What barrier?
He may be a beast, but now you're in love.
Azusa, be honest with yourself.
Yo, man. One more large beer.
Hey, there goes the Beast.
Yeah, that's Mina and Koji.
Really. He's got Mina.
Ouch.
Why did you do that?
I see. I get it.
Hey, that's mine.
No! I'm late, late again!
What're you doing, pervert?
I'm sorry.
Don't touch it.
She lost her parents when she was young.
She's very needy and a crybaby.
- What?
- Be nice to Mina.
Yusuke the boss gave this to me
because I gave him a wedding gift.
Here.
Take Mina with you.
She doesn't like extreme scream rides.
The boss's wedding gift,
and he gave it to her?
BBQ Party
He should've brought his bride.
Then I'd have checked her out.
Maybe he was too scared of you
to bring her.
What do you mean? Huh?
Don't worry. Drink, drink.
Aoi was in love with Yusuke the boss?
Looks that way.
How cute!
Maybe he's hungry.
He might like some BBQ.
No. He needs his mother's milk.
Wow. He looks delicious.
Mina, emergency evacuation.
What're you doing? Let me go.
- We need to find his mother.
- Sure. I'll help.
Hey, Puppy Mom!
Puppy Mom. Where's she gone to?
Poor puppy. Is he gonna be like us?
Mina.
She can't be far.
I'll go look. Wait here.
Koji.
Mom. Where's Mom?
She's with Dad. Far, far away.
Sis?
Koji will stay my big brother, won't he?
What do you mean?
A big brother.
I always wanted a nice big brother.
I made him take me to the pool
the other day.
It was fun.
Oh, yeah,
he was worried about your pendant.
I told him it was important because...
...Dad gave it to Mom on their first date.
That made him sad.
Sis, what do you think about him?
What?
He gets around,
he's a kid and wishy-washy.
I knew it. You're so clumsy.
He has no sense of time
and he's always late.
He's kind to everybody.
He's helplessly dumb.
He feels the same way about you.
That's the puppy's mom.
- Koji.
- Brother.
- What's wrong?
- He can't.
I'm drowning. I don't know how to swim.
Sis.
Yusuke's stupid.
So nice we found the mom.
Me, too, I'm hungry.
Azusa and Koji, where are they?
Leave them alone.
They finally became honest
with each other.
Fireworks.
- Pretty.
- Really.
Sorry about your pendant.
Forget about it. Are you all right?
Yeah. That was stupid.
I can't even swim.
No, no, you were great.
I was impressed.
No.
Then, let's stop.
Don't stop. Idiot.
Koji, no more.
Give it to me.
I'm embarrassed.
Hinomori, you're beautiful.
Ready?
Koji.
I love you, Koji.
Hello.
Welcome to Pia Carrot!