What a beautiful morning.
Well, time to work.
Good morning, Jun.
Good morning, Azusa. See you later.
What a shy boy.
He's cute when he's asleep.
WELCOME TO PIA CARROT 2
Today's Special #2:
Would You Like a Dessert First?
Hot.
Who shut the door to the cool hallway?
I'm late.
Time for the uniform.
Occupied.
Jun Kagurazaka, isn't it?
It's not a bathroom. Don't lock it.
Sorry. It's yours.
Why bother to lock to change clothes?
Man to man, nothing to be embarrassed about.
I'm not embarrassed.
See you later.
He's just like a girl.
Koji's not here yet? Late again?
Oops! Ms. Manager will explode again.
I'm here!
Today's Special #2:
Would You Like a Dessert First?
Closed
He's late again. He'll go like this.
Yeah, possible.
Ryoko is tough on tardiness.
He'll be fired.
Really?
He should be fired. Fired.
Just thinking about it makes me sick. Fire the bastard.
Anything happened, Azusa?
- He's always so horrible, but--
- What? What happened?
I need to know. Tell us.
He was not even dressed.
And he kept his door open.
He's a pervert. A pervert.
She dares to call me a pervert?
Wait, my door was open?
You're the one who closed my door?
Stay away, pervert!
I'm not a pervert.
I was sound asleep and why did you dare to close the door?
That room is a sauna when you close the door. A sauna!
That's your problem.
And that woke you up and now you're not late.
You should thank me for that.
Thank you?
You ruined my beautiful morning and I owe you thanks?
You ruined my morning.
You showed me a nasty thing first thing in the morning.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
What did I show you? Tell me.
We have customers.
Smile. Smile.
Smile all the time.
Welcome to Pia Carrot.
It's so hot, isn't it?
Ms. Hinomori, would you show these two to their table, please?
Of course. Welcome to Pia Carrot.
How about this window table?
Mr. Maeda, ice water, please.
Right away.
They might make a good pair.
Backing up. Backing up.
Field Trip: Hot Springs Hotel Resort
Tropical Room:
Jun Kagurazaka & Koji Maeda
Two in one room.
It's so hot and we're going to hot springs?
Yo, Koji.
- If I don't go, will they fire me?
- Yeah.
Hey, guys. I was looking for you.
- It's the owner.
- More work.
We got a shipment.
Sorry to bother you during your break, but...
...please put this all in the storage room.
All of it?
Yes. Thank you.
- What a slave driver.
- Yeah.
We're totally exploited.
Jun.
You really are fragile.
No. I'm not.
Don't push yourself. I'll do the rest.
Don't worry. I can do it.
See?
You'll hurt yourself.
Take a break over there.
Koji. You're so kind.
Your skin's so creamy. And you're skinny.
I'm sorry. You okay?
I feel like I was struck hard twice...
- I'm fine.
- That's good.
Let's get this done.
But I feel like I felt something soft.
Back to work. Work.
It's the Summer Festival at Kitaura Shrine.
Summer Festival.
- Here.
- Thanks. You're a good man.
Koji, you want to go?
- The Summer Festival.
- Yeah, why not?
Let's go pick up some girls.
What a crowd.
Why the hell does Jun want to meet me here?
We could've left the dorm together.
Koji will be shocked to see the real me.
Hey, don't cry.
Cute!
This crowd would be a good excuse for not being able to find Jun.
Good.
Hey.
Isn't that Koji?
It sure is.
What're you doing here?
What am I doing?
It's the Festival and I'm meeting Jun.
He's late.
I see. Two men alone.
Jun's here, too? Where?
Not here yet.
Mr. Kagurazaka, Mr. Jun Kagurazaka, where are you?
Mr. Jun Kagurazaka, Mr. Kagurazaka, your friends are waiting for you.
- Please come to the gate--
- Aoi, you're embarrassing us.
I'm late again.
Time card. Uniform.
- Jun.
- Good morning.
Sorry we missed each other last night.
Yeah. Too many people, I guess.
Well, it was good you didn't run into us.
I ended up with Aoi and others and it was horrible.
They ate and ate and forced me to eat, too.
Fried noodles, ice candies, bean candies, okonomiyaki, octopus-balls...
...chocolate banana, and rice cake in mitarashi sauce...
...nerian flavor, tsubuan flavor, seafood cakes, corn--
Where is Koji? Late again?
Oh, no. Koji Maeda is here. I'm changing now.
I'll be right there.
Welcome Pia Carrot Staff
- This is better than I thought.
- Yes, isn't it?
It's so cool here in this summer heat.
That steam must be the hot springs.
Hey, Jun, let's go to the hot springs and sweat it out.
I'll wait till tonight. Watch the stars and soak, you know.
Watch the stars. That's good.
Then, let's go to the lake.
Good, let's go.
There are two girls on a boat. Can't leave them alone.
We'll pick up girls. Revenge for the Summer Festival.
It's lucky there's a tree. Hey, Jun, let's go.
Koji, why there?
Come on.
We don't want Azusa and the gang to find us.
They'll probably stop us.
- Stop us?
- Come on, Jun.
Yeah.
So nice to be away from work.
Hey, Aoi, this is a study trip.
But what do we study?
- Oh. Koji and Jun.
- Yeah.
The way they are, boys will always be boys.
Kinda cute.
Men are animals.
Boys are boys, they'll always be children.
Children? They might not like you calling them children.
Why? Why, why, why?
Haven't run like this in a while.
Neither have I.
But what happened to the girls I saw from the hotel?
Maybe they're on the other side. Let's take a boat.
Yeah.
- Here we go.
- You can't.
It's swinging.
Stop it, Koji.
Be a man and take it, Jun.
That was so fun.
But we didn't find any girls.
What's up?
The first star.
What're you saying? Like a girl.
What if I was a girl?
What?
You don't mean....?
Just kidding, kidding. I'm famished.
Shit, I'd rape you!
He did get my heart pounding.
Could I be gay?
No! I'm straight!
What should I have?
- Not that much.
- But you said you were hungry.
-Still... Switch plates.
- No way.
Two guys flirting with each other....
- You're so mean, Koji.
- You scared me earlier.
They're such good chums.
Jun used to be so quiet before.
Maybe they're like brothers to each other.
More than that. Maybe.
Gay?
I late too much.
Stars are beautiful.
They really are.
What a beautiful night sky.
Koji, thank you for today.
It was so much fun.
I've never relaxed so much.
I have a dream of my own...
...and I've been fighting for it in my own way.
But it never worked out. I think something was missing.
I think, today, you showed me what it is.
There's something I want to tell you.
It's... I haven't told anybody.
I'm...
How innocent.
Yeah. I should go to the baths now.
Jun? Hey.
He's gone to the baths.
Public Bath - Men - Women
Why didn't he tell me? I'd have joined him.
This is so nice.
Hot and good.
Lucky, it's connected.
Men and women together.
Someone's in the women's side.
Oh, no. It's Jun.
I'm getting cooked. I should get out.
Hey, Jun.
You pervert, having fun all by yourself.
Koji, this is the women's side?
Women's side? Come on, you know about it.
It's connected in the deep end. Any girls so far?
No, just me.
It's not my lucky day.
I'm so drunk.
Sounds like a girl.
Koji.
Let me see.
Too much steam, though. Good, good. Oh, no.
- Let's go to the deep end.
- Yes.
Trouble. Aoi and Sanae are coming.
I heard voices. Is someone here?
Get drunk and soak under the stars. Nothing beats it.
This is heaven.
You'll drink some more later, right?
Of course.
Get cooked and get drunk. Nothing beats it.
Cold beer will taste oh so good.
Then why not just go out?
Why let this chance go?
Okay, Jun, we'll dive and peek.
- You'd better not.
- Don't be so rational.
- Dizzy.
- You okay?
You got overheated?
Okay. Time to get drunk again.
Oh, well. I'll join you.
Talk about boozers.
Hey, look, Jun. What a view.
I've had it.
You should take--
Hey. Jun?
Are you all right?
Not there. Then he's...
...a she!
I'm sorry.
I meant to tell you the truth, but...
Don't worry about it.
That girl.
I'm embarrassed. You saw everything.
Nothing to be embarrassed about. You're very beautiful.
I'm an aspiring stage actress.
I've been through many auditions.
Nothing's worked out. But I'm determined this time.
It's the part of a girl who pretends to be a boy...
...to get close to a boy she loves.
So I wanted to use the restaurant to practice and give it a try.
You brilliantly tricked us.
I don't think anyone saw through it.
Thank you. Tomorrow is the audition.
Today was my last day here.
But before that, just with you...
...I wanted to meet you as a girl.
At first I thought you were manly.
I wanted to get close to study you.
But somewhere along the line...
I love you.
No.
I want to know more about men.
It's incredible.
I can't think anymore.
I'm shocked Jun was a girl.
Me, too.
I just want her to pass this audition...
...and become a successful actress.
He knew about it and shared the room?
It's so dirty!
That reminds me, Koji's late again?
Good morning.
Morning's almost over. You're late.
Shut up. Don't scream at me.
You're the one who has no business screaming at me.
- Shut up, if you don't want to get it!
- Say that again?
Good morning. Is everybody here?
We're all here.
Very good.
Let me introduce you to Jun's replacement.
Come on in.
She's joining us starting today.
Azusa's sister, Mina Hinomori.
Pleased to meet you.
I smell trouble.
Can I call you Brother?
I've always wanted to, ever since I met you.
Why am I thinking about him?
Oh, I see.
I don't care if Azusa is dating someone, though.
What are you mumbling about? Aren't you having fun with me?
Our next episode:
Would You Like Me to Choose Your Dinner?
See you!