Wait for me!
It's gone.
Okay. Then I'll run!
WELCOME TO PIA CARROT 2
Today's Special #1:
Would You Like a Four-Course Dinner?
Ouch.
Is this my lucky day?
Animal! Pervert! Rapist!
- I didn't mean to...
- Die!
Pervert! Rapist!
Did she drop this?
What's inside?
Wanted
What is this?
You laughed!
What did you do that for?
That's for me to ask.
What's wrong with laughing
at a cheap, old pendant?
Hey, wait a second.
What's with her?
Today's Special #1:
Would You Like a Four-Course Dinner?
What? The interview's over?
Yes. If you come late for the interview...
...we don't need you here.
We're getting busy with the lunch crowd.
Excuse me.
I'm late for various reasons.
Excuses?
We have policies and procedures...
Ryoko, why not interview him?
Aoi.
We just lost a part-time guy.
Jun's not strong enough for heavy lifting.
Heavy lifting is my specialty!
But punctuality is our policy.
Give him a chance, Ms. Futaba.
Mr. Yusuke.
He looks gutsy, too.
Gutsy?
Are you the owner? I'll work hard.
Hire me, I'll work two days a week.
Two days a week? Spoiled brat!
We need manpower! Six days a week!
Live in the dorm!
What?
Yeah. I'll just need to wake him up.
Then you're hired, start today.
- Name?
- Maeda. Koji Maeda.
Ms. Minase, get him a uniform.
Yes, Mr. Yusuke.
Ms. Futaba, will you take him
to the dorm after work?
The interview is over.
Welcome to Pia Carrot 2.
Thus began my summer job.
This is really hard.
- Need a hand?
- Thanks.
I'm Jun Kagurazaka. Nice to meet you.
I'm Koji Maeda.
Ryoko's nice in person, but a bitch at work.
You'll get used to it. Keep it up.
Okay. I will.
I'm Sanae Enishi. Pleased to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Here it is.
Okay.
I'm dead.
Koji Maeda
Sleep.
What is this?
What the hell is this heat?
No air conditioning! It's hot!
And filthy beyond imagination.
What's that smell? Smelly. And hot.
Smelly. Dirty. Hot.
Hot, hot! No air conditioning, no fan!
What is it?
So cool.
Of course it is.
The entire building is air conditioned.
What?
What did you say, Ms. Futaba?
I don't like, "Ms. Futaba."
Call me Ryoko when we're not at work.
Sure. May I? So, Ryoko.
- Show some respect, though.
- Sure.
- And what was it again?
- Air conditioned?
Yes, the whole dorm is air conditioned.
Air conditioned? No way.
What about my room?
Not even a fan. It's hot as hell.
That's a bad room.
The previous resident said it was too clean.
He remodeled
so that it felt like his own home.
That's the only room available.
You'll have to put up with it.
No way.
Hey, you two.
I'm throwing a Welcome Newbie party.
Come on up.
Aoi's room!
I'll be right there.
It's cool in your room, isn't it?
Don't be so overjoyed.
Take a bath first, though.
Do I smell bad?
Yes.
Unlucky or what? Why that room?
I am smelly. I smell like my room.
What if Ryoko hates me for this?
Ryoko.
She's cute. Tough at work, though.
Someone's already here.
Oh, Maeda. I'm just leaving.
You smell.
Do I smell that bad?
I'll wash myself! I'm washing myself!
Wash, wash, clean, clean, more and more!
Jun's skin was creamy
and his body was supple like a girl's.
Oh, not me.
I'm turned on by a guy!
Go down, go down.
Oh, no!
Welcome Newbies
What's wrong?
Too tired after so much work?
I know I work everybody a lot.
- Am I too tough on a newbie?
- No, it's not that.
Is it because we called you smelly?
Don't worry about that.
You're not smelly at all.
You smell good from the soap.
You smell good, too, Ryoko.
Open up, Ryoko!
I'll get it.
Everybody says they're busy.
Even Sanae and Jun begged off.
Young people have no energy these days.
Let me introduce you.
Azusa Hinomori,
who was not late for her interview.
Koji Maeda, who was very late.
I'm Azusa Hinomori. Nice to meet you.
I'm Koji Maeda...
You!
You two know each other.
No! We don't!
Excuse me.
Just looking at this man makes me sick.
You looked so innocent, Ladies' Man!
- Let's get drunk, anyway.
- Here's your glass.
Let's forget everything. Party, party, party.
That's why I love young,
healthy men and boys.
How about you, Koji?
So, Ryoko, fall in love.
I work and work. Maybe I'm a workaholic.
I'm always envious of Aoi.
She's so carefree. She never holds back.
So what, Ms. Futaba? No, Ryoko.
You're you.
You're wonderful, Ryoko.
You're nice, Mr. Maeda.
Call me Koji, Ryoko.
You have a boyfriend?
How about you?
There is someone.
That girl?
Please, no.
I just met her this morning.
Good.
The girl I like is right in front of me.
Then kiss me.
Ryoko.
So listen.
As I've been saying, men...
What're you doing? Hey.
No, nothing.
Bottom's up!
As I've been saying...
...there are only men and women.
Welcome to Pia Carrot.
Watch out!
What're you daydreaming about?
Nothing. You'd better watch your step.
I've had enough. How dare you say that?
Hey, both of you.
We have customers. Smile, smile, smile.
Smile all the time.
Welcome to Pia Carrot.
Oh, well, Mr. Maeda.
Please be brisk at work,
so you won't cause trouble.
Ms. Hinomori, please be calm.
Don't rush and be careful.
Thank you oh so much.
You'll pay for this, thank you.
Watch your back, please, thank you.
Something is going on there.
Welcome Newbies - Beach Party
Wow! Women!
Yeah, yeah.
Koji, don't go crazy.
Never seen girls in swimwear before?
No, no. Aren't you swimming?
I'm a little sick.
Too much of a crowd.
Can't you swim on your own?
Beat it. I'm not asking you to join me.
Ask me, and I'll turn you down.
Don't get lost.
Talk about getting lost...
...Ryoko's not back from the snack bar yet.
She's so geographically challenged.
I'll go look for her.
Please, don't.
She says no.
Then why do you wander
into a deserted area?
You were expecting us, weren't you?
I just got lost.
We're trying to be nice, you bitch!
How could you get lost
between the water and beach?
- I will rape you.
- No!
No, no. Stop. No. Let me go.
- Do as we say!
- Help, somebody!
Nobody will hear you scream.
No.
I will rape you.
Nice body.
Let's get drunk and have a party.
No. Stop, please.
You don't quit, do you?
No. Please.
No!
I will rape you.
She's too much.
No!
Stop!
Over there.
Koji.
Who are you?
The man of justice and truth.
My real identity is...
...a temp!
How did she get over there?
- You!
- I will rape you.
You're doing the full monty!
Don't look at me!
Voila!
- Give them back to me.
- I will rape you.
- Wait for me.
- I'm coming.
I'm coming with you.
Our undies.
You'll pay for this.
I will rape you.
Thank you. I was scared.
Me, too.
But I wasn't late this time, was I?
If you had been, you'd be in trouble.
Can we have a real interview now...
...just the two of us?
A romance born out of a shocking incident
usually doesn't last long.
Okay with that?
It feels good.
I'm embarrassed.
Ryoko. You're beautiful.
Liar. Liar.
Koji. It feels so good.
Wow, not there!
No.
Ryoko. You're so wet.
No. I'm so embarrassed.
Ryoko. Are you ready?
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
- Ryoko.
- I'm scared.
Don't worry.
It feels good.
It feels so good.
Ryoko, did I pass the interview?
You passed, Koji.
Koji!
Wow, Ryoko, you look so happy,
you know that?
I decided to be positive about everything.
Wonder what happened to Ryoko
on the beach...
That reminds me.
Koji was bruised all over and exhausted.
Poor kid.
Maybe he's too tired to make it on time.
He'll do fine.
He's got my alarm clock.
Azusa
Ouch!
That tramp, Hinomori Azusa!
- I love you, Koji.
- What?
Jun, no way!
We're both men,
and there's only friendship between us.
But you make my heart pound.
Wait a minute! Am I gay?
No! I am normal!
Our next episode is:
Would You Like a Dessert First?
See you!