Satomi. How about this one?
Voilà!
That looks good on you. Cute.
I knew this would be good.
I'm getting this one for Okinawa.
Yusuke will like this one.
Yeah...
Thanks for waiting.
Did you find something, Shoko?
Perfecto. She chose something for you.
Who did you choose yours for?
Me? None of your business.
Hey, Shoko,
Rumi wants you to come spend the night.
Rumi said that? I'll be there!
Haven't shared bath with you in a while.
Right.
Hey, Shoko.
Yes?
You're looking beautiful these days.
Am I?
Ding ding!
I've got it.
Hey!
What're you doing?
Confess. Who is it?
Tell me, tell me. Is it someone I know?
I can't.
Which means...
Can't be Dad...
What?
My brother?
I've got it.
Shoko, don't worry about it.
I'm here for you.
Your love shall blossom!
Yusuke, don't give me a cold
before we go to Okinawa.
You mean?
You're coming, too, Kiyomi?
As a payment for tutoring you.
Something wonderful is going to happen
in Okinawa this summer.
Yusuke, do you like staring
at your cousin's underwear?
I do...
No. I don't.
Employee Okinawa Tour
I'm so happy.
We're all going to Okinawa together.
He's taking the entire Pia Carrot staff.
It's a big expense for the boss.
I want to show off my swimsuit to Yusuke.
Yeah. That'll be fun.
Satomi, of course you'll help me,
won't you?
Yes. Of course.
Let's get to work.
Boss. Good morning.
Good morning.
Oops!
Boss!
Hey, you two. Happy with your work?
Excuse me.
Yes.
About the shift change during the trip...
What?
Shiho, is everything all right?
Right. The shift change.
You're going to Okinawa, too, Yusuke?
Didn't I tell you?
Are you all right?
Right, right.
I'll be here. Bring back a souvenir.
I wonder how Shiho is doing.
Satomi's acting weird, too.
Me? None of your business.
Bro, stop your daydreaming.
Shut up, I'm thinking about
something serious.
You're thinking about girls again.
Kiyomi, Please.
Yusuke, what's wrong?
No, no. It's nothing.
Shoko, stay away from dumb people.
Satomi, what are you saying?
Don't worry.
Just because you're dumb,
doesn't mean I'm going to dump you.
Bro, look. Look. Okinawa!
You are all free to do as you please
until dinner at 7:00. Have fun.
Yusuke, I need to talk to you.
- What is it?
- Yusuke? What did you do this time?
- Yusuke, we'll be on the beach.
- I'll be right there.
Well, that's a surprise.
I didn't mean to hide it.
Are you happy for me?
I'm getting remarried.
Whoever she is.
It's for you to decide.
We'll talk more when we get back.
Later, then.
A stepmother.
Isn't Yusuke coming?
He's always slow.
There he is.
Yusuke, we're here! This way!
Hey.
Yusuke. What's wrong?
Guess it was a shock to him. He's young.
Don't worry. It's good for him, too.
Thanks for waiting.
Yusuke. You're here.
Yusuke, we got ourselves a boat.
Let's go to the island over there.
Let's go, Bro.
Yeah, why not?
- It's cold.
- What're you doing?
- Wait.
- Wait for me.
They're both kids, after all.
Really, I thought you liked kids.
- What do you mean?
- Nothing.
What's up?
Nothing. It's just...
You're kinda pretty.
Yusuke!
This road is rough, Shoko.
You're not saying
you're bored with Shoko, are you?
Calm down, Satomi.
No excuses now. You took her to a hotel.
To a hotel?
It's not like that. It was...
I will never forgive you
if you break Shoko's heart.
Hold on a second.
Bro.
What is this?
What did you do to Shoko?
Explain it to me.
Shoko.
Yusuke.
- I'm outta here.
- Satomi.
Satomi.
- Do as you please.
- Not you, Bro.
Satomi, it wasn't like that.
Don't worry. Stay with Yusuke.
But...
Yo, Bro.
- I don't care.
- Bro, you're idiot.
- Satomi!
- Bro! Bro!
Screw them.
Satomi.
Bro, Bro. Satomi's gone under.
What?
Satomi!
Satomi.
Satomi, wake up.
Hey, Satomi.
- She's awake.
- Satomi.
- Yusuke.
- Good. You're fine.
Satomi.
Yusuke.
Yusuke. Satomi.
Satomi?
Shoko? It's open.
Shoko.
I'm sorry, Satomi. I was...
I was just so happy and...
What, anything wrong with Yusuke?
You know I went to a hotel with Yusuke.
Yeah, but...
You're mistaken.
I took him to the hotel. It wasn't his fault.
But you and Yusuke...
Nothing happened. Nothing.
It's just I adored Yusuke.
But now I know who he loves.
What?
I'm saying he loves someone else.
We have a problem. It's Satomi.
Satomi?
I told her about us.
And she ran away.
Satomi!
Satomi?
What? You thought I'd jump again?
Well, no.
I hate myself. Shoko told me everything.
- Everything?
- She was like, "He's yours!"
- And I was so happy.
- Satomi.
I'm sorry, Shoko.
About Bro.
Don't worry.
I just had a crush on him, that's all.
Serves him right.
He was, like, totally panicked.
Was he?
Hey, Shoko, we're in Okinawa, after all.
Let's go find some men!
Yes. Let's.
So that's our plan tomorrow.
Bro is like so boring.
Wow! It'll be fun.
Satomi.
I'm sorry.
Thank you, Yusuke, for caring about me.
Satomi. I...
Satomi. I want to look at you.
Sorry. Are you upset?
Turn away.
Okay, Satomi.
Yusuke. Okay now.
Don't stare.
Don't be silly. You're beautiful, Satomi.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Satomi. Are you sure?
- Don't ask.
- I love you, Satomi.
Thank you.
What? Too rough?
- I don't know.
- Maybe you liked it.
- Don't be crude.
- Relax, and let me.
- Hey. Yusuke, not there.
- I told you to let me.
Don't worry.
No, Yusuke. I'm embarrassed.
No, not that.
Satomi, you're cute.
I'm sorry. I don't know much.
It's my first time, too.
- I'll bear it. Okay?
- Satomi.
- All right?
- Yes. Fine. Go on.
- I'm inside you, Satomi.
- So this is you. I'm happy.
- Does it hurt?
- No, just a little.
Let me move.
Satomi. I can't hold...
It's all right. Come inside me.
Satomi.
Yusuke.
It was wonderful, Satomi.
I'm so happy.
Move, Bro, move.
It's about your turn.
No, remember the coin flip?
I'm going ahead.
Bastards.
I'm tired. Come help me.
Welcome home, Yusuke.
Shiho?
We need a new introduction, Yusuke.
This is your new mother, Shiho.
Pleased to meet you, Son.
My mom?
No! All our souvenirs!
Why this?