One month and three weeks
until Lita is shipped out.
I still have headaches.
But I've stopped grieving
over my lost memory.
At least during training sessions.
Lita reinforced that.
I's in.
Spread it wider.
Does it feel good?
What are you going to do?
If an enema is about takes,
you've got a long way to go.
It's coming out.
What's going out?
Please, I heave to shit.
I haven't given permission yet.
If you leak just a bit,
you'll be punished!
Master, please...
What are you pleading?
Plug my asshole.
I can't hold it.
How vulgar.
She wants to be plugged.
You don't need the anal plug.
Let it out.
You have your permission.
Hurry up and cry out,
you pig!
Pigeon blood
2st Training
How unusual to see you working.
I'm busy.
Don't bother me.
Lady Regina is going out?
This is a critical moment for
The Malte Company.
She goes back and forth
between the top financiers.
And invites them to the
competition event.
I won't be free until that happens.
I'm tired.
Work and earn your pay.
By the way,
they say the death of the journalist
investigating the Mayer incident
was accidental,
but the police...
Why bring that up?
I don't care.
What? You don't feel anything
when you hear the name, "Mayer"?
I'm not interested in the least.
Unbelievable.
What is it?
It's oil.
How's your health?
Master, your visit
is an honor.
No stomach ache?
No. Not at all.
Your shipping date is far off,
but the competition is soon.
Should it impinge your training,
immediately notify Vanessa or...
Master.
You suffer from headaches?
Who told you that?
Vanessa?
No. You sometimes hold your head
during training.
It happens all the time
It's nothing.
More than that,
why won't you play
your ocarina?
I like the song.
Master, you know it?
I've heard it somewhere.
I remember it.
That's all.
I like the melody.
You play it well.
No, I'm awful at it.
Will you play for me?
No?
I will do whatever you desire.
But...
Kaoruko is taking a nap.
Elza.
We're far away.
You can be at ease.
Play all you want.
Thank you, Master.
But It's alright.
It's not worthy
of this beautiful place.
I learned to do this
to everyone in the mansion.
Yes, Master?
Do you remember your past?
Lita was orphaned.
Father... mother... scary...
scolded... beat me... hit me...
make... stick me... penetrated...
all the time... bands... tied...
pain... It hurts!
But I had my friend.
What?
Friend?
The son of the family
that moved in next door.
They moved again night away.
It was only a year.
It's because of him that I am alive.
He gave you the ocarina?
No. I made this...
...myself.
I was moved.
What is this feelings?
Master.
I have a request.
Please tell me about you.
- Please.
- Chris.
That is all I know.
What's the matter?
Why do you cry?
I didn't mean to.
Master, it's nothihg.
Really.
Where and what
were you doing?
You can't talk
even if you wanted to.
You must be puniched
before work.
Turn around!
With less than a week from the competition,
I decided on a prescription
in the name if Kaoruko.
Master, what did you say?
You decide on the torture menu.
Master.
I'm sure it's not satisfying
to do just foreplay.
Thank you very much.
Master.
Go slow. Go slow!
Stubborn!
Master, Mistress,
Please do as you wish
and hurt my precious body.
Yes.
Those eyes.
That voice.
That's enough.
Why, Master?
I have to give this pig
much more pain!
That's enough for now.
The competition event is tomorrow.
The cat o' nine tails
leaves more than bruises.
Do you want to show
damaged goods to the buyers?
As you say.
Your are always magnificent
at the whip.
Someday, I'd like to seriously
be at the receiving end.
You endured well.
How luck you are
to receive the Master's tongue.
I will not allow you
to defeat Lita.
That is absolute.
Vanessa.
Clean up this pig.
I dreamed of Elza In the morning.
I don't want to.
Put you slothes on.
She was here.
Traditionally, the trainer doesn't appear
at the competitive event.
The assistant Mistress is in charge
of the demonstration.
- Lita is missing?
- Yes.
I looked all over the mansion.
She's nowhere to be found.
Elza is also missing.
They may be together.
What does Kaoruko say?
She says she hasn't seen them
since morning.
Get me know when you find them.
That's when...
my part starts.
You two seem to get along.
How does the pig feel
about Elza?
She is always kind to me.
You like her?
- Yes.
- And Elza?
Really? That's wonderful!
Well, then play together.
Come, come.
You shouldn't wear clothes.
Show the pig
your beautiful body!
Elza.
She is not in the mansion.
The slaves are searching the grounds.
I'm cumming.
I'm jealous.
Two women...
without needing...
a dildo or vibe.
Elza.
The competition was utterly boring.
That's understandable.
Everyone was waiting
for the main course.
Lita, where are you?
Master, we found her.
Lita by herself
in an upstairs hallway.
She is very weak.
And we found semen in he pussy.
We don't know whose it is.
She doesn't want to talk.
Can she penform
in that condition?
She can probably manage.
But...
now we can't find Kaoruko.
Did you think I didn't know?
Conspiring with that pig.
Trying to deceive the Master.
Whit a gutsy maid.
What?
I can't hear you.
What did you say?
Goodness
You can't talk like this.
Not with this disgusting mouth.
The pig must be...
A change?
Lita by herself?
The customers shouldn't wait
any longer.
Customers.
Please try whatever pleases you
to my filthy body.
Is there anybody?
I will do anything.
Become a dog!
The image of a man
seeking a deadly meal arose.
Show more spirit, you dog.
Show your face.
Wtat am ugly face.
This is not a dog.
It's a pig.
A female pig!
Let's go for a walk.
Walk.
I said walk!
It was dangerous.
That man has no love.
More than anything.
he doesn't have Lita's trust.
A gunshot?
So your asshole itches?
Let me scratch it.
This is nice and smelly.
You have a tail now.
What an impressive dog.
You can't lay down yet!
Pee like a dog!
You can't?
Not enough fluids?
Very well.
Drink all you want.
It's time for your meal.
Here's your favorite sausage.
Eat it.
Why are my jizz slaves onstage?
It's not possible.
They lack the intelligence
to escape from their cells.
Super repetitive cum loads with
extreme premature ejaculation.
We administered the maximum amount of
super aphrodisiac for the final bukkake.
They'll keep going until death.
Lita will die before the slaves.
Shall we stop them?
No. Look.
Magnificent.
Master, Lita is...
She is probably out of her senses.
Nonetheless...
You have exceeded.
Lita.
An indulgence called shame.
And a trance called agony.
Learn from this.
Lita, this is the real you.
What a bunch of miserable men.
All for a sickly pig.
You still want to swallow cum?
Here's white hot jizz.
This is fresh semen.
Drink it all up.
Now, now.
If you don't swallow it all,
you won't breath.
Master, we must stop it.
She'll suffocate.
Master?
Master...
please take my filthy pussy...
and enjoy it.
Snap out of it.
You are not to serve me.
You are to serve these customers.
Don't forget it.
Elza didn't come to the time and
place as she'd asked in her memo.
Instead, there was somebody else.
Master.
What are you doing here?
Are you waiting for Elza?
She is not coming.
I let her go.
For what reason?
That must have been quite a sight.
Yes.
He is the first example
of success
for the project.
Do you think not?
Yes, undoubtedly.
You are bothered by Kaoruko,
correct?
No.
She was always a problem child.
When she loses interest,
she tears of the limbs and head.
Whether it's dolls,
or whatever.
Master.
This is the first time.
First time?
That's right.
It's our first time.
That's not
what I'm talking about.
You're a virgin.
Hurry!
Strange memories
filled my empty brain.
They were memories of Kaoruko.
I was kept by her.
I betrayed her and ran to my friend.
Her past boyfriend
that looked like me...
Her face...
So beautiful.
More more.
Stick it in deeper.
More, more...
I knew with certainty.
Elza had no home
to go back to.
Elza will not return.
She no longer lives.