I remember now.
I remember everything.
It was different back then.
In the six months I've lived
in this mansion,
my mind was...
...corrupted by emptiness.
I AM A DIRTY
PROMISCUOUS WOMAN
They're getting used to it.
Yes, and the slave as well.
The pedestrians are no longer bashful
and are now enjoying her.
She looked this way.
She knows.
I'm sorry, Master.
- Let's go home.
- What?
She's getting confident.
She's knows we're watching.
She's acting.
False fears and bashfulness
fails to move emotions.
As you say.
We will leave her.
Let's go.
Pass in front of her.
Oh, well...
Master!
Pigeon blood
1st Training
The slave has returned.
You're not shining.
Your pride is gone.
Oh, you like confinement?
You weren't watching.
No I didn't.
I was with tne car.
I left for a minute to buy a newspaper.
That's all!
Other than that...
Oh, it happened then...
Master!
Please wait!
What?
Please keep me here!
You?
Is this girl insane?
Or is she a bona fide
pervert?
Please keep me here.
I'll do anything.
I'don't need pay.
I will absolutely do anything.
Absolutely anything?
Elza looks worried.
She's afraid of being replaced.
I beg you.
I have no place to go.
I won't trouble you.
I'll sleep in the garden.
All I need a day is
a piece of bread and water.
I beg out!
No. Go back to town.
We'll give you a ride.
Now get up.
Don't hide them.
Endure it.
Now slowly exhale.
Good.
Starting tomorrow, I will train her.
Master!
Vanessa, doll her up.
As you say.
Your name?
It's Lita.
Lita, from now on,
you are my slave.
Yes.
I couldn't remember anything from before.
But when I awakened one morning,
I was the Master of this mansion
and the trainer of slaves.
Both Mistress Kaoruko
and Secretary Vanessa,
without hesitation...
Master.
...would call me that.
The owner of this house and Lady of the Region,
Regina looked at me and said,
"I'm counting on you".
And then said,
"Don't disappoint me".
But I didn't know anything.
There wasn't anything I could do.
Why?
Where did I learn to do this?
Who am I?
- Master, have you retired to bed?
- No.
I brought your medicine.
That was sudden this afternoon.
It's never hurt like that.
From now on...
Vanessa is an expert of pharmacology
and biology.
I never sked her,
but somehow, I know.
Shall I prescribe something?
I'm alright.
The medicine is working.
It can't be that quick.
It's too strong.
Calm it down.
Yes.
Would you like to fuck my pussy?
There's no need for that.
As you say.
What of that girl, Lita?
She has signed a contract.
She requested it.
Apparently, she has been
prowling the area for the past week.
Sleeping in the park during the night.
How strange.
Let me suck you.
Contract.
What about me?
Do I also have a contract?
Master, what will you do?
Tomorrow, I will bring her records.
But to make her a commodity
in the remaining two month's...
...is too mush.
Even for Master.
We must ask the Lady
for a change in curriculum.
Continue.
Forgive me.
There will be no change
In the training cheduie.
Two months is enough
to make something of her.
Your pussy is all wet.
- Forgive me. I didn't mean for that.
- What?
Don't.
What's this?
- This exaggerated thing?
- Master...
Isn't it too big for a swollen clit?
To think you had this thing on you.
Where did you get this?
Master, please stop.
- You're cruel.
- Were you born a hermaphrodite?
I know you weren't born like this.
Lady Regina gave it to me.
Why are you altering your body?
Could you take care of me?
Don't be the only one having fun.
Yes, I know.
Your cock too...
You better not cum before me.
Oh, yes.
- I'm going to shoot cum.
- Me too.
Master, forgive me.
In two weeks, I'm going to
enter Lita in the competition.
Master...
It was clearly a gamble that
nobody thought would win.
It's morning?
You slept well.
You're quite a pig.
Kaoruko,
younger sister of Lady Regina,
is quite a princess.
She assists me as a trainer.
At times, she brandishes
a whip herself in my place.
What are you hiding?
Show me.
I said show me!
You just don't get it!
Master.
Forgive me.
This pig is hiding something.
She had Elza sneak it out.
Show it to the Master!
You are a stubborn pig.
Please...
...spare me this.
It may become broken.
I'll keep it.
I'm not taking it from you.
It will be put back in your room.
Elza.
Don't just stand there.
Hurry up and say
what you have to say!
Master, please enjoy my body...
"my dirty body!"
Please enjoy...
...my dirty body.
Let me enjoy it.
Hang her up.
How do you like your
hymen broken by a horse speculum?
- It's beautiful.
- Yes.
And it corrupts into a dark color.
I look forward to it.
How is the tightness?
Not yet
She's stiff from resisting.
Pig! Unless you loosen up,
it's always going to hurt.
She's getting used to it.
She's getting steamy and wet.
Her clit is hard.
What's the matter, Lita.
Not enough?
What a greedy pig.
Good. Let's crucify her.
It felt very good.
Thank you very much, Master.
What do you want to have
done to you?
I would like it if you...
would please play
with my dirty smelly pussy.
I will do that.
Would you like to use
a topical anesthetic?
This is her first time.
No gels.
It hurts.
What a cute thin dick...
...for a female.
What's the matter?
What are you fidgeting about?
I have to pee.
You shouldn't hold it in.
Let it out.
Show your vulgar self.
But I'm ashamed.
What?
I can't hear you!
You pissed on the floor!
What are you going to do?
I
Pee all you want into this.
Don't miss.
If it spills over,
you will be punished.
I can't anymore.
I'll help you.
I'll make you squirt!
She needs stimulation.
I can't tell whether
she's peeing or squirting.
You don't like it?
Do you want me to stop?
No, Master...
Which is it?
I won't miss.
Here, drink it!
What shall we to her next?
Enough with the hardware.
Master.
You don't intend to use your cock?
That's the one thing you mustn't do!
I know.
The unwritten law that Master and Slave
shall not intertwine.
Because she's product?
What the real reason
for this detestable taboo?
That's it!
Yes, that's it!
After shame, inflict pain.
That's it, right?
Master, please loan me
this female pig!
No.
Calm down.
Your state of mind
will defeat the slave.
Master, forgive me.
I was just...
Useless.
We must demote her to a meat slave.
Do as you please.
May I defeat her?
It's kind of a waste
after all that work.
Make her a freebie with a purchase.
Free furniture?
The customers will like that.
We're going out.
Have the car ready.
Keep the catheter as it is.
Even after I finish training her,
a hired hand like me don't go out.
I can't believe Regina
would have somebody watch me
while in this cage.
It's clear who's behind this.
She thinks she's shadowing me.
It's a wonder
she manages her job as a maid.
She's the only one.
I thought there were
more maids when I came to.
Kahn, the driver,
is unfathomably mysterious.
Any good news?
No. More missing persons.
A young woman and a vagrant.
None have surfaced.
And a journalist died in a car accident.
The one investigating the Mayer case.
The family of an investigator disappeared.
Only the husband and wife's body turned up
That was five years ago.
You remember.
Why?
The police report was a fabrication.
They kept lying,
but the truth came out.
When that happened,
there was an uproar.
What do you think?
You're saying somebody
put a lid on it?
What was in the police report?
He got involved in
a drug syndicate turf war.
He was hired by one,
and the other found out.
Something like that.
If that's what the police says,
it must be true.
Drive carefully.
Oh, the Ledy Regina's firm,
Malte Company, is going global.
Malte is one of the top five
food companies in this country.
Uh, stop.
Hey.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I just got dizzy.
I've heard this song before.
It wasn't a headache.
A strange itching in my brain.
It beckons me.
I know what's going on.
You act in vain, Kaoruko.
To make me seek a slave.
It's not fair.
Where were those taken?
Who did?
Is that...
I won't give you up.
It's my part.
No.
It's not me.
The color of my hair an eyes...
Nonetheless...
Stick it in.
No...
No.
How destitute.
Still a long way to go.
Lita.
Are you periodically medicating him?
Yes.
Recently, almost everyday.
He thinks it's for his headaches.
There is no fear
that his memory will return.
So long as his memory doesn't return.
Is he superior?
Yes.
All the data points in that direction.
No wonder Kaoruko
asked to spare his life.
Or is the curriculum
making him grow?
Worship.
Yes.
Worship him, Vanessa.
As you desire, Lady Regina.
Lita endured well.
But her skill as a slave
didn't improve.
It never did.
Lita
was the same
as when she first arrived.
Nothing changed.
Neither Lita, the mansion,
nor I.