Yes? Who is it...
They told me that Papa took moneys
from the company and disappeared.
Oh, I see. So, your name is Hotaru-chan?
I was abandoned?
U-Um, I will do everything I can
to pay off what my papa stole.
Papa... Why?
You're such a good daughter,
paying off the money he stole with your body.
Huh?
From now on, you're going to be our new plaything.
N-No, this isn't what we agreed on!
No!
Please! Don't look!
I'm sure this will be the last time you act so timid.
What's going on? My body's getting so hot!
I bet you'll be satisfied real soon!
I'm not an easy girl!
I'm feeling so sensitive, though!
I like that. You're really turning me on.
Let's see how long you can hold out, Hotaru-chan.
His finger is... No!
I'll play with you for as long as you need me to.
What's this? You're getting so wet.
Can't you hear the erotic sounds
coming out from back here?
I'm so scared! Save me, Papa!
You're trying really hard.
You're not cumming at all, Hotaru-chan.
I guess that means this just isn't enough for you.
No, that's not true. I've been holding
my orgasm back for a while now,
but I don't know how much more I can take!
My head's starting to feel weird!
It's being pretty honest to what it wants,
twitching as if it wants something.
No!
I'll give your pussy a little kiss.
Don't!
His tongue is stirring me up inside!
Oh, no. It feels too good.
So good!
My body's rejoicing over the pleasure!
You wanna cum, don't you?
I want to cum!
Did you really think I'd let you cum?
Wh-Why not?
Something like this shouldn't faze you at all, Hotanu-chan.
Th-That's so mean. Just a little more
and I would've... I was so close!
I'm getting pretty turned on,
maybe I should just do this myself?
No, don't do that! Use that cock on me!
What's the matter? Why are you kissing my cock?
So this is what a man smells tike?
Amazing! It just keeps getting harder!
Look, she's sucking it by herself.
Oh, my. Isn't it dirty, though?
No, my body wants these cocks
to mess up its insides really badly!
Be fair! Help me out too.
Don't bother. She's not even listening.
Look, she's completely focused on sucking right now.
Cock! Cock!
It's so cute how much effort
you're putting into sucking my dick.
It feels pretty damn good.
Maybe I'll tease her a little.
I can put it in me, right?
Wait, stop for a second.
Huh?
A call just came in saying we've
figured out where your dad is hiding.
We'll be getting our money back,
so you can go home now, Hotaru-chan.
We'll take care of the rest by ourselves.
Huh?
N-No, you can't just stop
after coming this far. That's not...
Um, I don't want you to go!
I'll be your toy. I'll repay my father's debt,
so um, please, use my pussy!
Hm? Is it really okay for you to be making
a life-changing decision like that?
Y-Yes, it is, so please, hurry!
That so? Then, here I go!
So good!
You actually don't care about his debt at all, do you?
You just wanted an excuse
to have a cock inside your pussy.
This is amazing! I've never felt this good before!
Y-Yes, I just wanted a cock!
Take this! Does it feel good?
Your cock feels so good!
What was I hesitating about?
If this keeps up, I'm going to cum so many times!
Harder! Do me harder! Drown me in your cum!
Hotaru-chan, one cock isn't enough for you, right?
It won't fit!
Do it! Give me your seed!
It's coming!
Here I go!
Get pregnant!
There's so much of his seed flowing into me!
This feels too good. Now that I know
how good it feels, I won't be able to...!
Does this feel good, Master?
I'll make you feel even better, okay?
You look so cute when you feel good, Master!
I'm so happy, being surrounded by all these cocks!
Please, hurry and push your cock into my dirty slut hole.
Mess it up with your big cock!
I can't get enough of the smell of dicks!
I love having them in both of my holes, it feels so good!
I don't want to be apart from cocks ever again!
I hate you, Papa. I don't care about you anymore.
I wanted you to spoil me.
You just left me alone, by myself.
Oh, you did pretty well.
It's a shame you were still caught.
Ah yes, I have something I want to show you.
More! Give me more of that dirty cock juice!
Wh-What?!
What do you think?
What's going on? What are you guys doing?!
You can't do anything now, finding out this late.
Your beloved daughter is now our toy.
Now, she's paying off what
you stole from us, with her body.
My daughter?!
Give it to me!
Give me your cock juices! I'll bear everyone's child!
Um, I'm sorry, but I've been single for
quite some time, so... I have no daughter.
Th-then, who's this girl?!
Happy Halloween!
Uh, Hotaru-chan, you really should be going to schoo...
I don't wanna hear that from the guys
that kidnapped the wrong girl and collared her!
Ah, well, we never thought we'd get
the apartment number wrong like that...
That aside, Papa won't be back for a while,
so you guys will take care of me, right?
Here's a quick summary.
Yuzuhara Hikari, late for her usual bus,
ends up on one with a bizarre erotic twist!
Mahoroba Turns Into A Square Window
What's going on? I need to get off this bus somehow.
Where's the stop button? Oh, there it is...
You're pretty young, aren't you?
You're making this old man really hard.
What should I do?
You have quite a nice body.
My body's shaking.
Moan for me.
I need to say something!
Excuse me!
You're inviting me to do this, right?
U-Um, no, I'm not. I...
Everyone says that.
I need to set him straight!
Here.
Huh?
U-Um, I really don't want to do this!
You're such a bad girl, making my cock hard like this.
No, please... Somebody help!
What are you talking for? Hurry up and suck it!
No, I really don't want to...
No!
Come on, suck it!
I shouldn't be doing this!
Suck it good!
Yeah, that's good!
It reeks of sweat and it tastes weird.
Just for today, I didn't wash my cock.
Lick it clean for me, okay?
No way... I can't believe I'm sucking a cock right now!
Okay, looks like you know how to
use your mouth. Next up is your throat!
Yeah, that's good. I need to reward you, huh.
Huh?
I'm going to pour the reward
down your throat. Drink every last drop.
I don't want it, I don't want it!
It's gonna blow! It's gonna explode!
That was the first time in my life I did anything dirty...
I did something dirty with a man I don't even know...
Um, could I go next?
Me as well.
Sure, sure!
Come on, take them off!
You have a beautiful pussy!
Yeah, it's already soaking wet!
Come on. Come on!
Sto...
What a great reaction.
You have a really nice ass, don't you?
I love the smell of girls.
I love the way your tongue moves!
Hikari-chan, it's time for your milk.
Does your body want to have sex
so much that it's starting to throb?
For a girl wearing such a straight face,
you have a really dirty body.
I wonder if all students are that stressed out.
Maybe we should help her out with that?
Well, she got on by herself,
so we'll have to turn her into a cum dump.
That's right. Actually, there's some good scenery coming up.
Maybe it's time to show little Hikari-chan off to the world?
Don't be shy.
No! No!
Put me down! People are going to see me!
They took pictures.
They could see every part of my body...
They saw me.
Oh, god, your asshole is amazing!
I'm gonna cum!
People are watching me!
No!
I can't believe people can see me doing this!
Hello, Mama? I'm staying over at Yui-chan's today...
I'll call you again later, okay? Talk to you soon.
Sorry I kept you all waiting.
Please take good care of my dirty pussy tonight too!
Sorry I lied to you, Mama.
I fell in love with cocks!
It's going so deep inside me!
I'm so happy, I can't stop anymore!
I want to be their pet forever!
Your cocks are so thick!
Rub them against my pussy and asshole, please!
Your cock is amazing! Fill up my body...
my insides with your cock juices!
Here I go, Hikari-chan!
Yes! Give it to me!
Give me enough cum to break my body apart!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
In the end, we couldn't get a wink of sleep.
Hikari-chan, I got some good footage.
I'll send you the DVD later.
Looking forward to seeing you again.
Hikari, you've been pretty happy recently.
Oh? Did you get a boyfriend or something?
Nope, Syrup just got back together.
Whew, what a relief. I thought there was
a scandal or something between the members.
Aren't you focusing on the wrong thing here?
I'm not sharing this secret with anyone!
– We've arrived at Enka Center. If you would like to get off here, please press the stop button.
– Hey, look. Isn't that girl cute?
I think I've seen her somewhere.
She seems like the quiet type.
She's totally in my strike zone.
She's the kind of girl who turns red instantly
when you say something dirty.
Maaan...
Huh? What're they doing?
What?!
This is so embarrassing, mister.
What's wrong? You haven't been coming
to see us at all, so we've been lonely.
I've been really busy with tests!
You're saying tests are more important
than having sex with us?
You're so mean.
Hey, won't you use your mouth to get me hard?
Of course!
Have you been cleaning your cock, mister?
It's better when you don't.
You're a complete slut now, aren't you?
It's hard to imagine you ever being
embarrassed about doing these things.
You're a complete mess down here.
It's so delicious. Your cock tastes so good!
Well then, I'll put it in your pussy for you!
Your cock feels so good! So good!
It's going so deep inside me!
Since you haven't had a cock in a while, how does it feel?
Great! Your cock feels great in my pussy,
and this cock in my mouth tastes so good!
You're just going to make me harder
if you spell it out like that!
I"m gonna cum! Spread my pussy wide,
so everyone can see me cum!
Hikari-chan, do you know?
Yes?
Today's bus is just a normal bus.
Then, I want everyone to see me,
just like they didiback then.
I want everyone to look at me with scorn,
having sex in this embarrassing position!
I'm cumming!
Everyone, please, watch as these horny
cocks pump my pussy full of cum!
Cum is so good...!
How about you kids over there have a turn?
Huh?
I'll make you two feel really good, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч