Uh, as you all know, you shold be
leading, healthy, rule-abiding lives.
Hey, you hear?
Another one got suspended.
Please make sure that you do from now on
and don't fall under any bad influences.
Because of her, right?
Inukai Kyouko.
She's gotten herself a nickname – "the teachers's watchdog".
What about her even looks like a watchdog?
I'm gonna get her and break her.
Don't do it, man!
She's just gonna beat you at your own game.
No, she's a human being just like us.
She definitely has a weakness.
I know that it's gonna work... probably.
This is strange.
Hidaka-sensei hasn't replied yet.
He said that he had something
important to speak with me about.
Something important, huh?
Hey, Kyouko-kun. Morning.
Kyouko-kun, I'll be honest,
I've loved you from the start...
thump-thump
Yeah, there's no way that's it, right?
B-But, just maybe...
What's the watchdog doing in a place like this?
Don't tell me, you're meeting someone here?
I'm just conducting my patrol.
What are you all doing here? You look ridiculous.
Want me to send you to a hospital?!
Calm down, calm down.
Are you sure you wanna take that attitude towards us?
We have some good information for you.
What's that supposed to mean?
I just thought that you'd like to know.
You know, about where your precious Hidaka-sensei is.
– I'm gonna make it so that you never get to see the light
of day ever again! Ever again! Ever again! Ever again!
– We didn't do anything!
– I'm gonna make it so that you never get to see the light
of day ever again! Ever again! Ever again! Ever again!
Here's not a good place. Follow us.
See? He's here, sleeping safe and sound.
Sensei?! Hidaka-sensei, please get a hold of yourself!
A mannequin?
Sorry to disappoint you.
What are you trying to pull?!
Hidaka-sensei's not here.
This is your fault for letting your guard down.
But whatever,
that doesn't matter because
you're gonna become our slave now.
Th-This was your plan all along?
Y-You cowards!
Yeah, keep it up.
You...
Quit squirming!
Stop! Don't touch me with your filthy hands!
My body's still numb! I can't fight back!
Are you trying to make me submit
to you scum by doing this?
Let me just tell you that if you go any further...
What are you gonna do?
They're fucking huge!
It's all over.
You always had your way with us, right?
I know that you've been doing
that to try to get with Hidaka.
That's why you're the watchdog
of the disciplinary committee.
Wait, this...
Don't bother with that guy, he's bad news.
You don't need to worry about a thing,
we'll break you in real good.
Don't... Stop!
It's dinner time. Eat up.
No!
Look at the face the infamous watchdog is making!
I'm doing this with these lowlifes...
Hey, back here.
Hurry up and use your tongue already!
Yeah, good girl.
This is so humiliating.
I'm doing it with these thugs instead of with sensei...
I can't believe I'm pleasuring these scumbags.
Not too bad.
Never thought you'd knew how to do this right, Inukai.
I bet she learned how to do it for Hidaka.
That makes me jealous!
Have some of my hot cum!
Yeah, mine too.
Hey, drink all of it.
So this is semen?
I'm so stupid. Why am I obeying them?
Isn't that enough?
I have someplace to be. Let me go already.
Didn't we tell you? We're making you into our slave.
Who said we were done yet?
Wha...
I obeyed your orders though!
What... are you doing?
Nothing much. Just a massage.
Feels good, doesn't it?
I found some of these weak ones
just lying around at my place.
No, stop it!
This is pretty fun.
Isn't it?
No! Don't touch there...
Stop getting turned on.
I'll stretch this out for you too.
N-No, stop!
What are you holding back for? Just cum already.
No, don't look! Don't look!
Oh shit, look at her go!
How old are you?
We're gonna have to discipline you now.
I just peed in front of people. How could I do that?!
Oh, I got hard again.
I'm gonna take your pussy for a whirl first.
Huh?
Wait, no condom?
No! Anything but that!
Wait, don't! Please!
Clean relationship or not, if we tell everyone about your
relationship with Hidaka-sensei, I doubt it'd end well for him.
Wouldn't matter to us either way.
So now tell me, what do you want me to do?
I can't hurt sensei like that!
Fine, I got it, but... anywhere but there, okay?
You can do it anywhere else.
What's "there"?! I don't know where you mean!
No, this can't be happening, it's inside me!
Oh, so you really were a virgin?
I was supposed to give my first time to sensei...
Aren't you happy that your
first time having sex is with me?!
You can start using my last name starting today.
I just came and now I can't even
put a single thought together.
Where's your usual spunk?
Try barking for me!
Why don't you just cum? You like my cock, don't you?
No, that's not gonna happen.
There's no way that you'll be able to satisfy
me with something as worthless as that.
That really hunts my feelings.
No!
Just by flicking a switch, you start to feel like a toy!
Stop!
Looks like you came already.
I'm cumming!
We're not done yet.
Okay then, I'll take this hole.
The ass? That's weird man.
Shut up, I like it here.
No! Whatever they do to me just feels so good!
Damn, it's so tight!
Suck this too.
I'm gonna cum inside you!
No! I don't want this, but I... I...
My hips are moving!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming from your cum!
Damn, I feel good.
My womb is... this can't be!
I'm done. Give me a little break.
What do we do with her?
Should we just leave her here, tied up?
That's just mean.
N-No, I need to stop it.
I-I'm really going to break!
What are you doing? Looks like fun.
We were just called over all of a sudden,
but we're still suspended, you know?
Sorry 'bout that, but she just insisted
that she wasn't satisfied yet.
Wait, that's Inukai!
No!
Is this real?!
We can do whatever we want to her?
No!
I'm cumming!
I told you not to cum without permission!
Don't you want to satisfy Hidaka?
Stop! Stop!
I don't want to cum! I don't want to!
I'm surprised she's such a masochist.
We should change her name into the
"Teacher's bitch in heat."
Disciplinary Committee
After a while, I realized something.
My mind began to be tainted and changed by these fools.
Inukai-senpai?
Your speech today was so moving!
Th-Thanks.
I want to one day become a person who can
uphold the rules as well as you can, senpai!
You're wrong, I'm not...
Um, senpai, behind you!
Yo, Kyouko-chan.
Need to talk to you about something, got the time?
Y-You guys? Keep it short.
What do you mean, "keep it short"?
Class is starting soon.
About half a month ago, they took advantage
of my affection for Hidaka-sensei and humiliated me.
No one's coming here. Take it all off.
After that, I've been forced to take care of these
idiots' sexual desires almost every day.
They've tormented me to no end.
Then they humiliated me by trying to train me.
I have no plans of submitting to them
because I already have a man I love!
Hurry it up before someone comes.
Do the usual.
Please let me lick your dick, Master.
Even right now, I'm just following their orders. That's it.
Who would actually do this because they liked it?
Not yet. Don't take it out yet.
Who would...
Not yet! Heel! Heel!
All right.
Looks like you're already ready to go.
I thought you wanted a break from all of this.
How's your first dick in three days taste?
It tastes so good!
Here! Please shove it into my ass!
Class started.
We can just be late!
No! It's spreading!
You're so tight as always!
It feels so good in my ass! Do it more!
Sensei! Hidaka-sensei!
Oh, so you're fantasizing about Hidaka?!
Shut up. I'm cumming!
Your semen's coming!
You came this much. Are you satisfied now?
Yeah, I'll be good for a while.
What? You don't look too satisfied though.
Don't worry, I called a guy who
said he wants to do it with you.
With me?
Am I going to be raped again like last time?
This is great. I've always wanted to try this.
I'm actually walking around school naked!
If someone saw me, I'd... Wait, what am I hoping for?!
It's good timing 'cuz I hear that
the boys are in self-study right now.
Huh? Does that mean...
Keep it up until you get satisfied, got it?
I-Inukai-san?!
You're kidding!
Why's she naked?
Her tits are huge.
Is this my class?!
Come on, Inukai. Let's get everyone
from your class in on the fun.
Show them that you're a perverted masochistic pig.
No! I'm in front of my classmates like this!
You can see everything!
Oh my god let me see.
They're looking!
You can just fuck her as much as you want, okay?
You serious? This is like a porno!
Um, I really don't think this is a good idea.
Everyone's getting so hard.
You're getting cold feet now?!
Just suck them off like you did for us.
Inukai-san? Is this really happening?!
Hidaka-sensei, I'm sorry!
Please let me clean your dirty cock.
I'm so excited, I'm starting to forget
about Hidaka-sensei completely!
My body can't live without dicks anymore!
I-Inukai-san is really sucking my dick!
Suck mine too!
I can't concentrate because of you!
S-Sorry.
You're just saying words. Are you really sorry?
Your mouth feels good.
Cum whenever you want.
You really had us all fooled, you fucking whore.
This is awesome. I never expected
to have my cock sucked in a classroom.
More! I want to be treated worse!
Do it already! Don't tease me!
You want it that bad?
Beg for it!
Yes! Please, I'm your cum dumpster!
Please use my dirty, perverted,
whore pussy to make yourself feel good!
Is that right?
Okay, eat up then!
Your dick! Your dick feels so good!
This is good. I thought your pussy'd
be loose, but it's actually really tight.
The watchdog's pussy's really something else.
Play with my pussy more! Fuck it hard!
I'm cumming!
Gotta make it so that we can all see.
Everyone's gonna see me cum.
Look at me cum from being raped
while I'm completely naked in the classroom!
Don't space out, do me next! Now!
Me too!
Look at the face she's making.
It feels so good.
You're squeezing so tight!
I always kinda liked you because you were so serious
but now you're nothing but a dirty, sex-craved animal!
You really couldn't care less whose dick's inside you, right?!
Yes! I'm a dirty girl who loves dicks!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna dye you white!
This feels so strange.
They've always avoided me at all costs, but now...
They're trying to connect with me.
Even if they're treating me like some kind of livestock,
I never thought it'd feel this nice.
No! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming and being cummed on!
Maybe I've been strange for a while now.
It feels so good to show my true self to my entire class.
I need to pee.
You're really gonna do that?
Use me until you're done!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much.
Sensei, what should I do?
What are you doing, Hidaka-sensei?!
You have me!
I'm pregnant! Please take responsibility!
No, uh, this isn't...
This is the end! We're getting divorced!
I love you sensei!
Wait, you've got it all wrong.
What do I have wrong?!
Told you, didn't I? He's bad news.
Well I guess I'm not really one to talk...
Hey!
I don't need this anymore.
Inukai...
Just leave her be. She's gotta be shocked.
What are you guys waiting for?
You're gonna take responsibility
and domesticate me, right?
Huh? We said that?
Give us a break.
Hurry up, let's go!
I'm gonna go home and play some video games.
I have club.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч