Huh?! "Night visit?!"
You're being too loud!
Nobody told me about that!
Of course not, because I just decided it right now.
Yukimura-kun said that he's interested in you anyway.
Y-Yeah, but...
I don't think you have to...
It'll be fine. We have guys coming to our rooms too.
No, that's not the problem here.
Don't worry, he'll lead you all the way.
We'll never be a couple
I don't even really like him that way.
I just can't ever seem to flat out reject him.
Was he in this room, the Wakaba room?
Excuse me.
Wow, there's really no one here.
Huh, Yukimura-kun's not even here.
He must've been confused just like me.
But now what should I do? I can't just turn tail back to our room.
Fine! I'll just have this entire room to myself.
I'm not even interested in sex.
God I drank too much.
Yeah, when nighttime hits, I just go crazy.
Wakaba Room
I know! You've already said that like a hundred times!
Yeah, I couldn't even look Inuka-sensei in the eyes.
Yeah, she's too uptight.
Nah, that kind of woman could unexpectedly be a masochist.
Let's sleep already!
We have to be up for the field trip tomorrow.
Did Yukimura-kun come back?
Oh, hey I found a girl!
R-Really?!
What's going on?
This was the teachers' room?
Gotcha.
He reeks of alcohol.
They're all drunk.
Hey, Makino.
Did you come to sleep with us?
What? Let me go! Let go of me!
There there.
Here, move more.
Something's touching my butt!
Wow your boobs are so soft.
Your skin's so smooth, I can't stop myself.
No, stop!
This... This is a dick, isn't it?
It's touching me down there!
Don't rub it!
Oh man this is so nice!
I never thought the day would come when
I could have sex with a student.
Huh? You came already?
How unseemly of you,
They saw...
They saw me cum!
Huh? What are you guys doing?
Huh? That's weird, I can see a girl's butt.
Well, whatever.
Don't really know what's going on, but count me in!
Huh? My clothes are stuck. Did they get caught on something?
No! No!!
Oh, there we go.
Alright open wide. Here comes the airplane.
I'm dreaming right? I have to be!
Huh? It's not going in.
There's no way a teacher would do this!
There we go!
This is great.
This isn't a dream.
His dick is in my mouth for real!
It's been so long. I'm gonna unload lots on you.
I don't want that dirty stuff!
This is so good.
I'm cumming!
No! Don't!
No! No!!
Huh?
It's so slimy. It feels disgusting.
Kurosawa-sensei, are you half asleep or something?
Huh? Fujimoto-sensei?
This is where the real fun is.
No!
Okay, open wide.
N-No!
It's such a pretty pink color.
I can't believe Makino came to our room
for sex. I don't get kids today.
I didn't come here for that!
Look at how wet it's getting. What a shameless pussy.
My heart is pounding so hard!
I think it's time to start this party.
Here, drink up.
I'll make you a woman.
Hey, it's gonna overflow. What a waste!
Alright, who's up first?
Okay, I'll go first.
Huh? I'm starting to feel lightheaded.
Don't look so displeased.
Makes it more fun to play with her.
No, I don't have any more strength.
Hey, can you see, Makino?
My dick is gonna go inside your innocent pussy.
His dick is going to go inside me!
His dick is inside me!
Your pussy just ate me whole!
It's tingling down there!
Take it out! Take it out!!
Your hole is just so wet and perverted, I can't get enough of it!
Your pussy juices just keep pouring out!
I'm really having sex right now.
For someone who was against having sex,
you're getting really tight, Makino!
Do you not want to let go of my dick that badly?!
No! That's not... That's not true!
No! What's going on?
Why am I moaning every time his dick moves inside me?!
You're putting me in a tough position.
I'm not trying to cum inside you,
but if you don't let go of me, I might just have to.
No! Don't! Don't!!
Hey, calm down. It was a joke.
What are you saying?
Hey, Makino, my dick is better, right?
Not again!
I wanna go! I wanna leave!
Sorry, but you're not going anywhere.
No more.
If this goes on any longer...
I'm gonna break!
It's coming again! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!!
Did it feel so good that you fainted?
If there's an open spot, I want in!
Let me go into this cute asshole right here.
And I'll just shove it in there!
Hey, Okiura!
Wow her asshole is the best!
I feel like my dick's gonna melt.
I... can't...
Looks like she's starting to like it.
It feels so good!
N-No! I-I'm gonna cum! I-I...
I'm at my limit! I'm gonna cum inside!
Don't!
Huh? That's not good.
Don't worry. It'll just be once.
Don't! I'm gonna get pregnant!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
I'm cumming inside!
Stop it! Don't come inside me! Stop your cum!
Hey, it's not fair that you're the only one who
gets to cum inside her, Mishina-sensei.
I'm...
Hey, Makino, come back tomorrow night too, okay?
I drank the cum.
Man, tomorrow's the end of the field trip, huh?
All I got to do was sexually harass Inuka-sensei.
Do it!
Well, come on, isn't that okay though?
We have a new pet now.
Isn't that right, Makino?
Yes, I'm your cum dumpster.
Nurse's Office
That was a good nap.
The nurse is... in a meeting I think?
Well, whatever.
I need to get home and get to writing.
Oh man, I can smell Erika-senpai's sweat!
What?
My karma!
I need to calm down!
Captivating Sabotage
Those are my stockings aren't they?!
It's your fault for skipping class all the time to sleep!
Aren't you skipping too?!
No, I'm sick.
What part of you? Your head?
Look there's some kind of lump here.
It's a real life dick.
Where? I don't see anything...
Oh, whoops, my hands slipped!
That was close. What are you doing clinging to me?
You're not a dog, for god's sake.
Knock it off!
Wait, what? No way, his dick is in my mouth!
No!!
But seriously, your mouth-pussy is amazing, Erika-senpai!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Hey, I thought the plan was for tomorrow.
Sorry, couldn't help myself.
So with that being said, sorry, senpai.
No!
I'll need you to help these other two guys out too.
Wait, let go of me!
Do any of you even know what you're doing right now...
I'm sorry. I can't help you two out...
Do you know anyone who'd come this far and just stop half way?
Don't you feel sorry for those two?
Yeah, exactly. Also, it looks like you want this to happen.
Don't be stupid! Of course I don't!
Alright.
No!
Hold her legs.
Take good care of us, Erika-chan.
I never thought I'd see you like this, senpai.
No! What are you doing?
L-Let go of me!
You really don't feel anything? I guess that's
to be expected from you, senpai.
S-Stop!
So that means you won't cum, right?
If you can survive until sunset, we'll delete the pictures.
Oh, so you'll behave now?
Erika-chan, your tits are huge!
I'm gonna have you suck on it.
Geez, you guys.
Her pussy looks so lonely, it's crying.
Until the sun sets? But I have to endure this!
Right, Erika-chan?
I'm more of an ass guy, myself!
Damn, this is good!
N-No, I'm gonna lose it!
No!
Hey, hold her down!
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Senpai, you were just about to cum, weren't you?
I don't think that's right at all.
As punishment we're gonna double penetrate you.
No!
She's so tight!
Stop thrusting it inside me!
I'm cumming!
My womb! I'm cumming!
Oh man, she came really hard.
No!
She's even peeing now! Look!
Oh come on, give me a break.
Huh? What's that?
I didn't cum...
Huh? You didn't cum from that, so you want it even harder now?
You're too dirty, Erika-chan.
Look at 'em go.
I like it.
I can't believe that the Erika-san is sucking my dick!
Come on, senpai, you want us to delete the pictures, right?
Why don't you try begging us?
I think I've lost it.
After being played with these guys like I'm their toy, I...
Please take your huge cocks and shove
it into my steaming hot pussy!
But I think somewhere in my heart I wanted this...
I wanted to be ravaged like a frail animal by a beast.
Wow, this is kinda shocking.
Uh, could you give me a tit fuck?
So fucking soft!
Senpai, I'm cumming inside!
Get pregnant!
Senpai, I just came...
Give me every last drop. Don't hold back on me.
I'll clean your asshole for you, senpai.
Thank you very much.
Maybe I'll start coming to the nurse's
office more frequently now.
Erika-chan, you alive?
Oh, looks like you're still good to go.
Here!
Gonna thrust this all the way to your stomach!
Erika-chan, did you just wet yourself again?
So dirty.
Come on, you can't be flaking out now!
Your dick feels so good!
Your dick feels so, so amazing!
If you suck it that hard, I...
Senpai, I'm gonna cum down your throat!
Please take your cock and pump my dirty pussy full of your cum!
Oh man, I feel so much better.
That was my first time.
Uh, so the pictures...
Pictures? Oh, right.
Like hell I'd ever delete them.
See you here tomorrow.
Wow that was cold. Let's go home.
I could go for some ramen.
I'm starving.
Same here.
Me too! I wanna go!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч