It's so pretty.
Look, down there.
Everyone looks like ants from up here.
Up until recently, I never thought I'd be able
to go on a date with Komachi-sensei.
– I don't think I can see your house from here.
– But this is reality. I don't even want to think about sharing her smile with anyone else.
I love the red and white look of the Tokyo Tree.
What about you?
Yeah, I love yo... it, too...
Oh, so you like that color scheme too?
No, I meant that I love you, Komachi-sensei.
You might think I'm not dependable since I'm a student,
but I really love you more than anyone else.
No, you're really dependable.
Whether it's at school or surrounded by this
beautiful scenery, you've always been there for me.
I became interested,
then began developing feelings for you.
Then... I fell for you.
Sensei... Would you really be okay with a guy like me?
That's what I should be saying.
Are you sure you're okay dating an older woman like me?
You won't regret it?
O-Of course not! I wouldn't!
I'm so happy I found you.
Um... Please take good care of me!
On this day, in this place, we went up the tower
as teacher and student, but left as lovers.
—An eternal sweetheart's every day—
First love and the various distances
Holding hands like this really
makes it feel like we're dating.
Yes... It's kind of embarrassing, isn't it?
You're right.
Hey, do you have time after this?
There's somewhere I want to take you before our date ends.
We have tomorrow off anyway, so I can stay out late.
Really? Then, let's go in my car!
Wow. It's beautiful.
Your mouth is even hanging open in awe.
I'm so happy that I was able
to come here with you today.
Komachi-sensei...
In a situation like this,
the older one should take the lead, right?
Would it be okay if I stayed at your place tonight?
This is where you live, huh...
You keep it really clean.
I'll make us some tea,
so please make yourself at home.
Thank you!
Komachi-sensei?
Sorry that took so... long.
D-Don't overthink what I was just doing...
I was just... taking in your scent...
Sorry.
That's... so cute...
Komachi-sensei...
You know what?
Yeah?
I love you.
They're so big and soft.
This is embarrassing...
It's the first time anyone's ever touched them.
What should I do? It feels so good!
My nipples are tingling.
I need to... take the lead, somehow...
Your eyes, and your dick, are telling me something.
I think I know what you want.
You're a guy, after all.
Let me take care of you next.
Sit over here.
Here we go.
This is my first time doing it... Does it feel right?
It's getting even harder.
Does that mean it feels good?
Yeah, it does. Does it feel good for you?
Yes. I'm getting so turned on
watching the one I love feeling good.
I want to make sure that you feel good too.
I'll feel good too.
If you say so, then...
I'm glad you're so obedient.
It's getting even harder!
Just cum whenever you want, okay?
I never liked how people kept looking at
my chest during class or in the hallways, but...
It makes me really happy when you look at them.
I'm sucking my student's dick right now.
I think I've become a really perverted teacher.
Komachi-sensei, I'm at my limit!
Are you about to cum? That's fine.
Cum all over my breasts. Cover them with cum!
Sensei!
You let out so much of your hot stuff.
It's also my first time doing this.
I've already prepared myself to take
the person I love inside me, don't worry.
I want you to have it...
something I never gave to anyone.
My first time.
Komachi-sensei, I'm putting it in.
It's so tight.
Komachi-sensei, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. It still kind of hurts,
but it hurts a lot less than I thought it would.
Don't worry about it,
and let's just focus on feeling good together.
Komachi-sensei, that really turns me on.
Amazing... Your hot thing is moving inside me!
I never thought sex would feel so good!
Even though it's my first time,
I can tell my pussy is a complete mess right now.
No! When you rub my boobs,
I get even more turned on!
We're going to feel good together, right?
You're more of a meanie than I thought you were.
My student is making me feel so good!
He's turning me into a woman!
The way you're moving your dick is amazing!
I'm going to lose it!
My student is imprinting my pussy
with the shape of his dick!
Komachi-sensei, I love you!
I love you so much!
I love you too!
Do it harder!
Fill my mind and my pussy with nothing but you!
Use your dick to make me feel your love!
You're getting even bigger.
Are you going to cum? Are you going to fill
your girlfriend's pussy up with your hot cum?
Cum! Use my pussy to cum!
I'm going to cum too!
Make me your woman!
Wow...
Your cum is overflowing...
We did it.
I did it with the one I love.
Hey...
If we were closer in age and met as students at school,
what do you think would have happened?
No matter how I met you, I definitely still would've
fallen in love with you, Komachi-sensei.
G-Geez!
I'm so glad we're dating.
Pretty Cation. I'm Yakuouji Komachi.
Maybe it's about time you just called me Komachi?
4 April
I-I like you!
I came to Japan, and met you.
We like the same things.
When we hang out, it's never boring.
And so, I...
fell in love with you.
I want to talk to you more.
I want to go on more dates with you.
P-Please! G-Go... Go ou...
Rachel?
Yes!
I feel the same.
Sorry that you had to be the one to confess first.
I didn't want to lose you, so I was too scared to ask.
I like you. Please go out with me.
Yes, of course!
Угу, Рэйчел старинное русское имя. Ладно хоть не Миша Ивачкова...
On this day, I became lovers with the
student that came over from Russia.
Pretty Cation. I'm Electrichika Sapsan.
Please call me Rachel.
Summer break
It's already been three months
since we started dating, huh?
She dressed up as a maid for me...
Master!
Role played as a ninja for me...
Older brother!
You're harder than anything I've ever felt!
We're both into cosplay...
I wonder what I'll have her wear next.
You shouldn't be slacking off.
We need to finish cleaning
so we can go be lovey-dovey!
Got it.
2 hours later
I'll be going in first!
She's so pretty when she swims.
Why did you get so big?
Does seeing me in a swimsuit turn you on?
Sorry! Just looking at you in a swimsuit made me...
You're so hard. What am I going to do about you?
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it does, but...
Ever since we started dating,
you've taught me so many dirty things.
Your dick is getting so big.
I know exactly what you want me to do.
Rachel...
It feels good...
You're moaning.
I'll put it in my mouth, now.
You look like you're feeling really good.
That makes me so happy!
You're going to cum soon, aren't you?
That's fine. Cum a lot into your girlfriend's mouth!
I'm cumming!
I swallowed your cum out of habit.
Did it feel good?
Yeah, that was hotter than usual.
I want to... feel good too.
Let's go somewhere without people.
Nurse's office
I can't...
Your penis is rubbing against my vagina.
I can't resist anymore!
Put your dick in me, and let's feel good together.
It's so hot... I feel like it could burn me!
Rachel, you're so wet. It feels so good!
You can't just say stuff like that!
When my lover's penis goes inside me,
I just automatically get this wet.
I was thinking lewd thoughts
before we even started cleaning.
Please, give me lots of your cum
as a reward for holding back so long!
Showing such restraint, you're a good girl.
I'll cum lots and lots inside you, until you're satisfied.
I feel like I can cum,
just thinking of you giving me a creampie!
I'm going to cum soon, so hold on for a bit, Rachel.
I can't! I'm gonna cum!
Please shoot your semen into my vagina!
Rachel, I'm gonna...
Let out a lot, please!
Shoot out lots of cum into me!
Your semen is flowing into my stomach!
W-Wait! I just came! It's too sensitive!
I'll do it just a little while longer,
until you're satisfied.
P-Please, wait! I'll go crazy!
This is the first time you've done me so hard!
I'm gonna cum again! It's going to be so good!
Rachel, let's cum together.
Yes! I want to cum from your semen again!
Please cum all the way inside my womb!
You made me cum so many times at school today.
I can't think of anyone else
I would want to see me like this.
I'm really glad I came to Japan by myself, and met you.
Fireworks! They're so bright!
Wow, they're so pretty!
Let's come see them next year too.
Yes, of course!
Next year, the year after that... forever.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hdr
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч