It's finally lunch time!
Having an empty seat next to you is really lonely, isn't it?
Nozomi, you must be lonely without your boyfriend today.
Is it that obvious?
Um, go on ahead,
I'll meet you guys in the cafeteria in a minute.
Okay. Take your time.
So like, when I got on the train...
He should be better by now, right?
Okay.
I'll go see you after school.
An eternal sweetheart's every day
First love of the two sister
Huh? I smell something good.
Oh, you're awake! Good morning.
Nozomi-chan? Why are you here?
Isn't it obvious? I really missed you
and wanted to see you so...
So I came over.
Oh, really? Thanks.
How are you feeling?
I feel a lot better now, my fever's basically gone.
That's good to hear. Oh right!
I made you some rice porridge,
so why don't you have some?
Okay, open wide.
Thanks for the food, it was delicious.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
Now that I think about it...
Huh?
When we first started dating your cooking was awful,
though you've gotten pretty good at it recently.
Thanks for making me food all the time, Nozomi-chan.
Yep, I'm happy to hear you feel that way.
Oh, right. Do you wanna... take a bath together?
Okay, stand still. You sweat a lot, didn't you?
This big thing is always coming inside me, isn't it?
Yeah, I want to put it inside you if possible.
What I'm doing right now is servicing you, right?
It got bigger. So it feels good even when I use my hands, huh?
Well then...
If I do this, it'll feel even better, right?
It feels really good!
I'm already imagining this dick messing me up.
I'm starting to really want it.
If you cum, I might get even more turned on!
Nozomi-chan...
Cum! Make me sticky with your cum!
So much came out.
It's so hot!
More, give me more, please.
Wait, Nozomi-chan...
More... I want more of your dick.
I want it to fill the emptiness inside me.
But if you keep doing that, I'm just gonna cum again...
Then cum! Cum inside your girlfriend's mouth!
Let me drink all of it!
I'm cumming!
There's so much cum.
Thanks for the meal.
Pretty Cation. I'm Asagiri Nozomi.
Would it be okay if we spent today together?
Whew, I bought a lot of stuff.
I haven't shopped in a while so I ended up buying a lot.
Oh, I know! Let's install that game we got
from the guy in front of the station.
Good idea.
I wonder what kind of game it is.
I think he saidi it was a romance simulator.
Sounds fun, right?
You're always so excited when
it comes to games, Nozomi-chan.
Is it that obvious?
You're right. I'm pretty into games.
You might even call me a closet otaku.
That's just another part I love about you.
Geez. That's embarrassing.
Instllation Complete
Run
No!
Armaya
Nooooooooooooooooooooooo..!!
Don't!
This is bad. This is really bad.
Is it really okay for me to be showing this to Nozomi-chan?
I'm ready to go now,
so why don't you take that hard dick of yours and...
put it in my pussy.
Wow that sounded like something straight out of a game.
Look at how wet you're getting. You're such a dirty girl.
But I can't stop my fingers.
I just keep getting wetter and wetter
and it's starting to feel really good too.
I guess your fingers will be good enough then.
No!
I want you to put your dick inside me!
Okay? Please?
Nozomi-chan...
It's coming insid...
My pussy...
My pussy is being spread apart...
N-No! It's just too much stimulation for me!
I'll go slowly, okay?
You're only moving a little bit, but...
I can't control my hips!
Your dick is going crazy inside me.
It's reaching everywhere inside me!
If the person I love keeps fucking me this intensely,
I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Nozomi-chan!
No! You're going to make me lose my mind!
You're going to break my boobs if you rub them so strongly.
I think I'm gonna cum!
You're gonna cum? Your clicks gonna cum?
Yeah. I'm gonna cum with your pussy, Nozomi-chan!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum too! Cum a lot inside me!
Let it out!
It's filling me up inside.
I don't think all of it can fit inside me!
You came a lot, huh?
Your pussy just felt too good.
Wh-What are you doing?
You're not satisfied yet, right?
How about I take the lead this time?
Let's switch it up.
It went inside.
It's twitching inside my pussy.
Your face tells me you're feeling good too.
Look who's talking. Your face looks really lewd right now.
Yeah, that's because it feels good.
If I keep moving like this, I wonder who will cum first.
Maybe if I keep moving like this, you'll cum first.
That's rich coming from someone
who looks like she's about to cum.
Yeah, but I want to make you cum first.
Cum with my pussy again!
Wait, you're being too rough...
I can tell just how hard your dick is!
Your dick is making my head throb!
I'm not gonna lose!
Oh my god!
Your dick is going crazy inside my pussy!
I-I'm at my limit.
Cum! Give me your baby juice!
It's so hot.
Your semen is flowing inside me.
We sure did do it a lot.
Yeah, I didn't know you had that side to you.
To be honest, I didn't realize until we were doing it either.
Huh? Why didn't you say anything?
I thought it'd be refreshing to try something new.
You never fail to surprise me, Nozomi-chan.
Let's do it again later, okay?
Two hours already?
No matter how much time passes or how much
I convince myself, I'll never be ready.
Sorry I'm late!
Onee-chan caught me as I was leaving and
I had to take care of some chores before I left.
It's fine, just calm down, okay?
Okay, thanks.
So what did you want to talk about?
Wow, I never knew about this!
I remember now. That's the smile that I...
I wish I knew that these lit up earlier.
Onee-chan should've told me about this.
Sakura-chan, I like you.
Huh?
Will you go out with me?
Ah, s-sorry. I know this is out of the blue.
No, no, that's not it.
These are... I'm just so happy!
I like you to, senpai.
I look forward to dating you.
Pretty Cation. Hey there, I'm Asagiri Sakura.
Let's stay together forever, okay?
This is crazy. So we're finally boyfriend and girlfriend, right?
Yep, exactly.
From the bottom of my heart,
I'm glad that you're my first boyfriend, senpai.
Sakura-chan...
We've always shared the same hobbies and hung out
with each other. I'm glad we can take the next step.
Okay. Let's go to your place and
watch a romantic movie or something.
No, wait. It's pretty late, so I'll walk you home.
I already told onee-chan that I might
be coming home late tonight!
It's always been my dream to watch a movie with
my boyfriend while he eats the food I made for him.
So... please make my dream come true.
My dear little sister
Oh man, movies are really great, aren't they?
The little sister started calling her brother, "onii-chan",
half way through the movie. That was so touching.
Yeah, just by changing the way you call someone,
the distance between them shrinks.
The distance... Okay!
Onii-chan?
Huh?
I want to close the distance too,
so is it okay if I call you onii-chan?
Is this because of the movie we just watched?
Um, but if you do that it feels like
we're doing something really wrong...
Is that a no?
It's okay.
Then...
I took your first time.
Sakura-chan...
Do you want to... continue where the
kissing scene in the movie left off?
Huh?
Wow, it's bursting out!
What are you doing?
I've always had an interest in this.
I'll make you feel good.
I've only seen this stuff in manga, but is this how I do it?
Does it feel good?
I-It feels amazing.
Then I'll take this to the next step, okay?
Sakura-chan, you don't have to push yourself this hard.
What's happening?
Just by licking it I'm starting to feel weird.
Does that mean you're getting turned on?
No, not at all! I just want to make you feel good, onii-chan.
So big!
That's against the rules!
He looks like he's feeling really good.
I'm the only one who's seen his face like this.
I'm so happy... I think my pussy's getting really hot!
Sakura-chan, I'm gonna...
I can't stop!
That really surprised me!
So this is what it tastes like.
Onii-chan, please take my first time to mark
the day we started going out together.
You're touching my boobs!
You're so perverted.
Well, yeah, we're doing perverted things together.
I don't even recognize the voice that I'm making right now!
But I really love the perverted side of you, onii-chan.
Sakura-chan...
Are you going to touch me somewhere else?
Yeah.
You don't want me to?
You can do anything you want to me, onii-chan.
Then I'm going to touch you here.
What is this?!
Something more intense than I've ever felt before is coming!
My body feels like it's melting!
What should I do? I can't hold back my dirty moans!
Just let yourself feel good. I'll be sure to watch you.
This is so embarrassing, but I can't get enough of it!
Something's coming! I'm gonna cum!
Just let it out.
It's not stopping! I can't stop cumming!
That much? That's so embarrassing!
It's so embarrassing, but...
I think it's your turn to feel good with my body.
I'm gonna put it in.
All of it went in.
Yeah, but doesn't it hurt?
It does, but I'm fine.
What's important is that I'm really happy
to be connected with the person I love!
So see this through to the end.
Make me your woman, onii-chan.
I'm really happy too.
Okay, I'm going to move.
What's going on?! It hurts but it feels good too!
It's so tight!
You're rubbing me so much!
It's like it's scrubbing inside of me!
I think I'm going to lose my mind!
Please, can you call me by just my name?
Yeah, sure, Sakura!
That makes me so happy.
It's getting even bigger inside me!
I love you! I really love you! I love you so much, onii-chan!
It's starting to twitch inside me!
It's getting hotter! I think I'm going to melt!
I don't think I can hang on if this keeps up.
I can't stop moving my hips! It's like electricity's running
through my body, I can't even form a single thought!
I'm making so many erotic noises!
If I get too used to this,
I'm going to become addicted to it!
Does being inside me feel good? Am I making you feel good?
It almost feels too good!
Onii-chan, make yourself feel even better with me!
I'll give you my everything, onii-chan!
I want to show you everything about me!
If you say stuff like that, you're gonna make me cum!
You're going to cum? You're going to let it out?
You're going to shoot your feelings inside of me?
Sakura, I love you!
Stay with me forever, onii-chan!
Give me your semen!
Sakura!
I'm cumming!
My pussy's soaked.
I've got you all to myself.
I wish time would stop for everyone but the two of us.
I've never looked at anyone but you, Sakura-chan.
I thought I asked you to just call me Sakura.
Well, I'm in a good mood now, so I will forgive you.
Keep taking good care of me from here on out, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч