Spread your legs.
Ah, no, no, I can't spread them any further!
Fool! You think you can win the next contest with this?
Aww...
If you don't win the next contest, you know what's going to happen to our club?
Terminated...
That's right.
ln this club, you're the only member, Mai.
Yes, I have to have good scores or else.
That's right. Everything is up to you.
Professor, I really want to win the next contest.
That's why we're practicing day and night.
Ah, it hurts professor.
Come on.
Right, we can't win the next contest with this.
Good, I won't stop practicing even if you couldn't stand up anymore.
Professor, I will follow you.
Thank you, Mai. You're our club's hope.
Yes professor.
No, ouch...Recently the pranks have been cruel. I don't know who's behind this.
Thumbtacks spread all over, and weird bugs in my leotard.
Very cruel things, but I can't tell professor.
Professor has been working hard on my contest.
I don't want him to be distracted.
Professor, no matter what happens, I hope to win and be praised by you.
I won't lose. No, never. I won't lose.
But professor, when I win, please give me my reward.
With professor's... I want it bad.
Oh no, I'm thinking dirty thoughts towards professor when he's already married.
I also have Takashi.
No, no. Practice, practice.
There, lean back more, Mai.
I, I can't go any further, professor.
Here, try to focus on your thighs.
Ah, professor, professor, more, professor.
Put your entire body in line with your thighs, and lean back like a bow.
Lean back like a bow?
Great, all right, balance, use your fulcrum.
Aah, Professor, it's going to go in!
Good, apply more pressure.
Ah, I mean your fingers, professor.
Don't worry. I will hang on tight. Focus to your fullest.
Aah, Aah...
Good, that's the way. You're starting to sweat.
Aah, that's not sweat, professor. Ah...
Huh? What is this if it's not sweat?
Never mind. No, don't move it around that much!
Move around. Yeah, move it around and become the bow!
Aah, I'm cumming, cumming!
Yes, the two of us will enter the contest, Mai.
Yes.
Stretch your legs more, and raise the ball higher.
Like this?
Not enough, embellish your performance so the judges go crazy.
No!
Your legs like this, under your chin.
Aah, you're moving it around again.
All joints will be softer by moving it around, so you can perform freely.
Ha, it's hitting my spot. Professor, it's hitting!
Of course, don't doubt to my words.
No, I mean... Ah, no, it's going in, going in...
The performance needs to get you the points. This trick is of c-class difficulty.
Aah, no, no! Don't stimulate it any more...
That's the spirit, Mai. You're getting better.
Aah, good, professor.
Good, good. Yes, that's the way, Mai.
No, professor. No!
What are you denying yourself?
No, professor, no, not there, professor.
Stretch your legs out more, Mai.
Ah, professor, Your face is very close to... No, no--!
Hey, both my hand's busy. What am I supposed to do?
No, no, no!
Hey, this position looks easy but it isn't so.
Which means the judges will like it!
Ah, ah... Professor, I...
Yes, your body relaxed, so your legs are stretched.
Really professor? Really?
Ha ha ha, good job, Mai.
Ye, yes, professor.
You two are so foolish.
Good job, Mai.
Professor...
I always believed in you, Mai.
No, it's all because of your help, professor.
He he, you...
Can't be helped. You volleyball nut. I shouldn't have taken you as a son-in-law.
You have no strength, and your always busy with kids.
I hope you didn't forget that I'm the daughter of the director.
When your young sense accepts my technique, you will perform really artistically.
Professor... you're really thinking about me...
Mai, you're my hope, no it's my dream.
Professor, you're my dream, too.
I want to perform like you, and...
And what?
Together with you...
With me?
Ah...I'm going to win at the competition.
Y... yea... that's right, Mai. We're going to win together.
Yes.
Hopeless! Okay. I'm going to destroy both.
I'm going to show my power.
Mai, ah, sorry, still practicing...
No, we have just finished.
Takashi...
Sorry. Well, it's almost time for curfew, so...
You're very close. You just came here to tell so...
No... I just met a dorm worker.
Oh, okay.
Takashi, I'm going home soon. Go home first.
Are you sure?
You don't need to spend time with him until curfew?
We're not like that, professor.
Ha, ha...it's nice to be young.
Professor!
Now, it's okay for today.
We have early morning training tomorrow again. Be ready!
Okay, professor.
He, he, damn, I didn't know the professor was still there.
It seems that you were almost telling him that we would go to the girl's dorm together.
Sorry, sorry.
You're so careless.
Did you see his crotch was bigger?
What? What are you saying?
I'm sure. It's obvious because of his leotard.
I don't think so.
If he is a straight man, he'd get horny for body like yours, Mai.
Hey, I'll get mad.
I wonder if you would get wet...
I'm going to kill you if you say anything more.
Sorry, I'm just kidding with you.
Dumb you, Takashi.
But you look so good in that leotard.
I'm going to take a shower.
No, no. You're sweat is sexy. Don't waste it.
No, you're strange.
I'm not.
It's so great to taste girl student's leotard with sweat.
You, pervert.
I can image your pussy is wet too...
Don't make me embarrassed.
I love the leotard going into your ass.
No...
But, you don't wear a supporter usually? I can see yours so clearly.
It's better not to wear anything. Because I can move allot easier without it.
I really need good scores at the next competition. So...
Ummm.
Anyway, hurry up, Takashi.
Okay.
Hey, your pants.
Okay, ah... see...
Yours is big already... wow...
Of course! You're always training, Mai. You don't care about me.
I don't think so. We did it three days ago.
That's too long. I could empty my nuts twice a day.
You always have a dirty mind.
Not dirty mind, you're in my mind.
You're thinking of sex with me, right?
I can't hold it. No more... Let me in...
You're not romantic at all.
I want to be inside of you.
I can't believe it.
Ah... cumming... can't... hurry...
Ah... I want to fuck you. Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you, fuck you...
Damn!
Ah... easy... easy...
See? Your pussy is already wet. You want it any time.
No, I don't.
Look! You are twitching.
Ah... dripping... your love juice... dripping...
No--
Just sucking makes you wet.
I'm not convinced.
Okay now. Ready?
Ah... ah...
See... going... going...
Ah-- no...
Oh, great. Good...
Ah... no... ah...
Okay, turn around.
What?
Like a doggie.
No--
Hurry up.
Okay, Takashi. No--
No-- ah...
You're squirting bubbles out of your pussy, Mai.
No-- ah-- no--
Look. Your ass hole is also twitching.
No, don't look.
Do you really wipe your ass after you shit? I can see a paper attached.
No, no way! Stop it!
I can see a little shit. I can see something brown.
You liar... no... stop it.
He, he, he. I'm kidding. Nothing is attached.
I can't believe it.
Ah-- No--
Your mouth refuses it, but your other mouth wants more and more.
Ah, no. No. Don't do it too hard. Ah...
Your other mouth says more and more.
I don't think so.
How about this? Look, high speed fucking.
Come on, come on.
Ah... it's going to break. Don't do it too hard.
I won't cum yet.
How do you like it?
Come on, come on. You like it?
Mai is good looking but the professor's wife. I love her big ass. I saw it yesterday.
Oh, professor and his wife.
Honey, you're always working hard.
What? Why are you here?
Mai's lesson is not your business.
Oh, yes, it is.
Because you're too busy teaching her, I'm not getting satisfied.
Stop it. We're in a school.
That's okay. You and Mai are almost naked all the time.
Don't say it like that.
I don't think you can stand life without a girl's body.
I guess you and Mai are already...
Don't say that... stupid.
You want to try?
Try what?
Right here.
What are you saying? Are you crazy?
No, I'm really sane. See?
Ah... she...
I'll admit you're being faithful if you get hard on.
Damn, what are you doing?
Oh, you're not hard at all.
I can't get excited here.
Think about here, this place.
Damn you.
Okay? Please--
Shit, stop it.
Why? We have more than 30 minutes before the club.
Fuck!
Or you're going to wait 'til Mai helps you to cum.
Stop it! You, bitch!
Okay, I'm going to help you to get hard.
Oh, wow...
Look, my pussy is already wet because of its lack of sex.
Unbelievable nasty bitch!
Look! I'm squirting a lot. Nasty juice... like a flood.
You're a daughter of the chief director.
What are you going to do if someone is watching?
Because of my father, I can do anything.
He can fire anyone...
I can't believe we're both educators.
Educator?
You mean the educator who can touch Mai's body?
Shut up! Shut your mouth!
Ah, ah... ah... I'm getting so horny...
Bitch.
Please fuck me... your fat...
Shit! Do it...
Ah... I can't stop it...
Wow! This is an adult woman.
She has a nasty body.
Please someone, fuck me...
Yea, but... she is the professor's wife...
Shit... oh, man...
Compared to her, Mai is still a child.
An--no... not this position...
What are you saying? Don't you feel good?
No...
Don't say only "No".
Because I don't like it.
Why can't you say, ''Please give me your big cock in my pussy'' sometimes?
You, pervert!
Hey, I'm going cum inside of you if you stop using a sweet voice.
No, no...
Your other mouth is yelling to get more. Making noise...
I don't think so.
Look, look. Here... Ah...
Ah... there...
Shit, I'm going to fuck your ass, too. Come on.
No, no... No--
Ah... ah... ah...
Oh, shit.
Ah... ah... professor...
Okay. Raise your legs up.
Ah... Stop please.
Who are you talking to? Are you ordering me?
Ah... but... this... ah... ouch...
You're already lubricated enough.
Ah... is this a part of practice?
Of course!
Your favorite professor is busy today,
so I, his wife are here to train you especially.
Ah... ouch... that's painful. No, please, stop.
Hey, come on!
No, I won't.
You're not good at Ribbon, are you? You need to practice it harder.
No, I don't want to go out like this.
What are you saying? At the competition, you have to show yourself in front of everyone.
But not naked...
You do something like opening your legs. Unlikely normal position...
No, oh, no... What should I do, If someone sees me...
For new gymnastics you have to show yourself.
No. Don't pull me out!
Hey, you look like a pig. Don't be oinking!
No...
Walk to the building.
No, no way!
Say ''Oink''.
Look! There is a boy over there.
Mai's naked dance. Here is a naked pervert walking.
Don't... no...
Ha, ha, ha...
Come on!
Ouch, ummmm.
Look, Mai. This is twitching.
Great! I didn't know a girl's pussy was like this.
No, stop it... please...
It's funny. Very funny.
Turn around. Look.
Ha ha ha.
What's the matter, Mai? You look down.
Ah, professor.
Listen.
Don't give up even though you're facing to adverse circumstances.
Professor!
I know.
You're in a pain.
I know who did it to you.
But I can't do anything.
Professor!
I'm adopted as the husband.
I don't have any powers in the family unfortunately.
And also depends on the result of the next competition, I'm not sure if I can stay in this school.
What! Is that serious, professor?
Yea, but, don't worry, Mai.
You need to focus on only the competition.
Yes, professor.
Okay. Good.
But, professor...
Hey, no tears.
But...
Mai...
Ah, professor...
Ah... soft...
You're brawny, professor.
I can't hold anymore.
Me, either. I love you, professor.
Mai.
You're warm, professor.
I can't control anymore...
Me either.
Mai, your clothes.
Yes, professor.
Ah, how beautiful! Mai.
Professor, your hand... my....
Mai, I have been waiting to be like this.
Professor, me too. I have been thinking... everyday....
Mai, I didn't know you have such beautiful tits.
No, proferssor, embarrassed...
Mai, I'm going to touch you.
Very soft.
I was right. I have been thinking.
Ah, professor.
You feel so easily, Mai.
I want everything of you, Mai.
Ah, professor... I'm glad.
Are you sure, Mai?
Yes, professor. I'll give you everything of me.
Mai.
Ah, professor... great... your...
More than Takashi's?
Yes. It's very different.
You're honest, Mai.
Ah... Very big... My jaw is going to be...
You don't like big one, Mai?
Ah... I love it so much. I was just surprised.
But your pussy is too small. It might not be fit.
Oh, no. I really want yours.
You want my dick in side of your pussy?
Yes, professor.
Okay. I need to lubricate here enough, so...
Ah... ah...
Ah... professor... inside of me... ah...
So tight, your pussy, Mai.
Ah... professor, it's full.
No, not yet.
What?
Come on.
Oh... I feel something is twined.
Professor...
Mai...
Ah... ah...
Ah... good... oh...
Ah, professor, great... inside of me... ah...
I really feel something is twined around my dick.
Ah... ah...
Mai...
Mai, how do you like it? Do this, so I can put my dick far in.
Wow... woof...
Can you feel it?
Ah... professor... I can feel it... woof...
Yea, Mia... You're good... Ah... Mai...
Oh, my...
Do you feel good?
Ah... it's very different.
With who are you comparing?
Takshi. It's different from him.
Who do you like the most?
Professor's... yours... good...
Shit! Dumb Mai!
Ah... more, more... give me more...
Shit! I can't stand.
Wait!
Ah... Madam...
Here.
But...
It's okay.
Oh, my...
Let's enjoy together.
What?
It's okay. Come on.
So cute... ah... great... you're very young.
Oh... no, Madam. Ah...
You're so excited with my skill...
Of course... ah... don't... ah... cumming...
Ah... so cute... but, you can't cum yet.
If I lick back like this, you feel more...
Ah... oh, Madam.
I want you inside of me now.
I wanted it for long time...
Okay, I'm going to ride on you.
Yes. Great... powerful...
Look. I'm going to put in.
Yes. Wow. It gets drenched already.
Ah... see... a little bit...
No, not yet.
I know, but...
Okay?
Oh, it's all in.
How do you like this?
Ah... it's very tight...
Great. It's very different from Mai. Ah...
Look! You're all in side of me.
Wow! Great! lnside of you. Madam.
Can you see it? Your... all of your dick...
In and out...
Ah... on, Madam... I can't hold...
No... not yet...
Yes. You can hold it once you have done. And repeat it.
Ah... I feel good.
Yes, as long as you hold it, you can feel better.
Ah... you're an adult... This is the adult sex...
Yes. The girl shouldn't be only laying down like a tuna.
Yes. You're right.
See? Do slowly next.
No, so good...
Hey, Mai... a little bit more...
Um?
What to say... but you don't put your feeling...
What? What are you saying?
So... for example. You ride on me without telling you...
What?
Don't make that voice.
Because I don't know what you're saying.
Hey. What a sigh!
Because of you, Mai.
You too, Takashi.
What?
You're just doing...
Just doing?
I don't feel love from you.
What? What? What? What?
You don't have love, either, Mai. If you love me, you can ride of me.
What are you saying? Stupid.
What the fuck!
If you really love me, you can try all different kinds of position.
Please stop it. So nasty!
You're always thinking about only sex.
Because I love you.
That's not love.
I'm not your sex doll.
Okay, tell me what kind of loving sex are you expecting?
Think by yourself.
You have to tell me.
I don't know what kind of position you like, Mai.
I'm not talking about that.
Don't yell at me.
But I feel your pussy tight if you do so.
Stupid.
Terrible!
I don't know why he doesn't have a delicacy.
He has always dirty mind. It's terrible.
I want to see my professor.
He must understand my feeling.
Ah-- professor. I have only you, professor...
Professor--
Um... ah... Mai...
Professor, please fuck me. I want you.
What happened, Mai?
We have just had it awhile ago.
Please don't talk. Ah... ah... professor...
Mai... okay, okay...
Ah... professor... there... ah...
Mai, don't say anything... I know what's going on, just touching you.
No, no, professor. It's different.
I know, Mai. You love me seriously.
Ah... professor...
I'm going to clean up for you.
Ah... nice... I love you...
Your pussy is getting very clean, Mai.
Ah... you're making me cleaner...
Your pussy is only for me.
Yes, professor. I'm all for you.
That's right.
Ah, professor, please give me. Give me your cock.
I want to make love with you.
Ah... it's very different. Position is not the matter...
Um? What?
No, never mind. Hurry, professor.
Oh... Mai.
Professor, ah... ah...
Ah... Mai... Mai... oh...
Ah... professor, great... ah...
Oh... so tight... Mai...
I don't care about a ballet any more.
I want you... only you...
Mai, what are you saying?
I don't care about Takashi or anything...
Mai...
Ah... professor...
No, Mai. Pluck up!
We're trying hard 'til now for what?
Together... together with my professor...
Yea.
Ballet is our common goal, isn't it?
Common goal...
Yea, our dream.
Professor... I...
I'll try my best.
Okay, Mai. Let's move onto our dream together.
Yes.
Oh... Mai... tight...
Ah... professor... good... cum in side of me...
Shit! Fuck!
Why don't you leave them alone?
But, Madam.
I have a good idea.
Idea?
There is a means to destroy them.
Destroy?
I lost my husband by a little girl. I need to do something, of course.
Oh, Madam.
It's better wait for now.
You're right.
Leave everything to me.
Okay. If you say so...
Um... good kid.
Wow! Is this costume for me?
Yea, it's from me and Madam.
Takashi...
Try hard on the competition, Mai.
Yea, you need to save the club.
Yes.
Good. You can do it, Mai. You're going to save the club.
Yup. You're going to do it, Mai?
Yes.
This costume is a special made. It's very vivid then the others.
You need to show yourself off at the competition.
She and I were looking for this very seriously.
Ummmm, Takashi, I'm happy.
I was harsh with you but it's everything for the competition. Hope you can understand me.
Yes, I know.
Okay, try hard then.
Yea, Takashi. Thank you.
Yup!
Okay.
Thank you very much, Madam.
Ah... How nice Takashi and she are!
I was taking them wrong.
I need to try hard.
Professor, I'll try my best performance surrounding wonderful friends.
I'm going to win.
That's the best I can do for them.
La, la, la...
Yea, good, keep going...
Yes, professor.
Violently here with full of emotion...
Yes.
Good. Great. You're so beautiful, Mai.
Professor.
Keep concentrate.
Yes. Sha, sha, la, la...
Yea, like a stream.
Yes, like a stream.
Good. Good job. I'm sure you're going to captivate judges.
Yes, professor.
Um, have lots of fun.
Can't wait to see...
Tomorrow is the day.
Um, she raises her leg so high, Mai... he, he, he...
You asked for it. My husband, too.
You're bad, Madam.
Oh, so are you.
National Student New Gymnastics Competition.
This is the competition of new gymnastics for students.
Mai has been falling into raptures.
But Mai has needed to win the competition in order to keep the club.
Wow! Great performance! It's like a ball is alive.
Wonderful! I can't believe this was done by a student.
Wow, I'm doing great. It's my best performance so far.
It's my first time I can feel so free.
Ah... I feel good.
Everyone is looking at me.
Gazing my performance.
I can move so naturally like the ball is a part of me.
Oh, that movement.
Ah... a little unbalanced... but...
it's not a big deduction point.
Ah... what? what? what?
Ah... this is a big deduction.
What's this. I can't stand up.
Ah... no, oh, no... What? What vibration is this?
What? Ah... My whole body is shaking. Oh, no. I'm sitting down.
Ah... I'm going to get a deduction. What happened?
Ah... woo... no...
What? Mai's thighs is shaking. What's the matter?
Oh, no... something is vibrating.
Shit, it's was okay before. It's going to be a big deduction.
Ah... Ah... Ah...
It must be something attached on her leotard.
Ah... oh, no... no... it's over...
See? The vibrator is the specially strong one.
No one can perform naturally with it.
Mai. Are you okay, Mai? ''I fucked her.''
Ah, professor. Ah...
What?
Ah, professor, I... I...
What happened? Ah...
I'm sorry, professor. I... I...
Mai, you have something on your leotard?
So wet...
Professor...
I can talk to judges now, so we can still make it...
No, Professor. I... I'm going to dance.
Ah, Mai.
Hey, ass hole! Step back!
Professor... Professor, I'm okay.
Mai...
I... I'm going to keep dancing even I'm alone.
I need to try hard... ah... I'm trying harder...
You fuck your lovely student... You fucker!
Shit!
Ah... something hitting me.
Mai...
Ah... no...
Shit! Today is a nightmare.
Ah... ah... oh, no... I'm feeling too much.
Ah... my tits... I can feel it too...
I know people watching me, but I can't hold it...
Mai, what are you doing?
Ah... it's okay... I don't care... ah...
Fuck!
Ah... good... good... ah... look... look...
Umm, Mai...
Look, Mai's... Mai's pussy... look, see...
Professor...
Are you serious?
Professor, fuck me, please!
What?
Here in my pussy... with your fat cock...
Ah-- see? My pussy is already so wet.
What the heck!
Shit! We were completely taken in.
Ah... more and more... there... there... Professor, hurry... like yesterday...
Oh, no... my life is over... ummmmm.
Ah... professor... cumming... ah...
Shut up!
Ah... cumming...
Shit!
Ah... look, look... ah... ah...
Ah... here... look at me... ah...
Um, highly successful.
You're genius, Madam.
Don't call me Madam. I'm no longer his wife.
Ah, I'm also end up with Mai.
And then what are you going to do?
I want to be your dog.
Ha, ha, ha... you're cute.
Ah, Madam.
Ah... cumming...
Ah... I'm going to cum... cumming...