Leticia Apple (Age: 18)
Silfie Cloud (Age: 18)
Eleanor Fortworse
Lapisu Melucurius Freya
Rachel Havest
Cliff Cloud
Cloud...
Yes, your honour?
Thanks for coming...
Such negativity, please be strong.
Don't worry about me...
Take this as the proof of his identity...
I shall hold onto it, your honour.
Cloud...
Yes your honour?
Cliff...
Take care of my prince...
I understand, your honour.
Now go...
Take care...
Of Cliff...
My king!
What's wrong?
Brother!
What? You don't have any money?
Can't you take this instead?
T-This is-!
Sure thing missy!
Hold it right there-!
You scamming bastard!
W-What the hell are you doing?! Who are you?
Shut up! I bet you thought that you could scam her for a year's profit by taking that ring?
Let me go!
There she is! Over there!
Huh?
I'm sorry!
H-Hey!
Don't let her escape!
H-Hey! You're not going to buy it?
Over there!
Surround her!
W-What should I do?
Hey!
This way!
Just follow me!
Don't you lose her!
Someone cut them off from in front!
Miya?
Let's go!
Yes!
There they are!
Wait!
But, Eleanor-sama-!
I've got an idea...
Huh?
That man, I've seen him before...
Rei-nee!
Cliff?
Is that you Cliff?
I'm home, Rei-nee!
Cliff...
Welcome home Cliff!
Everyone! Cliff has come back!
Cliff's back?
Cliff?
Cliff did you say?
Cliff, welcome back.
Master!
Who's Cliff?
I don't know.
We'll talk later, come on in, come on in.
Sure!
So, when did you get back?
Uh, just now.
Do you know her Fie-sensei?
Onii-chan?
SubDESU-H
Onii-chan...
Fie...
Is that you Fie?!
Onii-chan, welcome back!
Fie...
I was surprised that you came back so suddenly!
Are you well Fie?
Yes!
But the working at the church and taking care of the children was hard work...
Since I'm back, it'll be fine...
Who is this person?
Um, it's...
D-Don't tell me that it's your...
No, she isn't!
So, after protecting her from the imperial guard, you brought her here?
Well, pretty much.
So then onii-chan, what is this person's name?
Oh, actually, I haven't asked you yet, have I?
Geez, onii-chan...
That's just like the Cliff I know!
Um, I'm Leticia...
I'm Leticia Apple! Please call me Leti!
Is my name strange?
No, that's fine.
And, you don't have any money, do you?
You can stay here, but we can't do it for free...
I'll help out in this place!
I'll serve customers or clean the place! I'll do anything!
That'll be fine.
Then, we'll be counting on you.
Thank you very much!
Well, we're so busy that we'd ask the cat if we could!
Lapisu? How long have you been there?
We haven't opened yet...
I've been here all along.
I wanted to hear Cliff's stories, since he's a wandering bard right?
Y-Yeah...
I didn't know you were a wandering bard!
Who's that girl?
She's the witch of the lakes, one of our regular customers.
I see...
Leti, what are you playing around for?
I-I'm sorry! What should I start with?
Well then...
Can you start by peeling the onions?
Welcome!
She sure is cute!
Umm...
Oh, over here!
Yes! Right away!
She sure is a hard worker!
I guess.
This is the third time...
I guess...
Geez...
I-I'm sorry!
I'll clean up here...
But-!
There must be other things you can do, aren't there?
Leti.
Yes?
Can you sing?
Huh?
How about singing along with my Lute playing?
Yes! I'll sing! I want to sing!
Is that okay?
That's fine, however... If your songs aren't good, you're going back into the kitchen.
Yes! I'll try my best!
In the countless times we've met
Your kindness has always been flowing throughout
You haven't lost a single charm
Everything is within the heart
Open your arm and bath in the sunlight
All throughout your body
Release your feelings to the endless sky above
Beyond those wavy clouds
there shines a rainbow
Keep on running, towards the gleaming rainbow in the distance
What's wrong Silfie?
Rei-onee-chan...
You look like you're feeling down...
Are you and Cliff already having sibling fights?
That's not it...
If it's okay with you, you can consult me anytime! So c'mon, cheer up!
I think I'll leave soon.
Oh Lapisu, why don't you have a bath here?
Then maybe I will.
Cliff, don't be thinking about doing anything perverted...
Is that true?!
Ele, not in here please.
Ele-!
This isn't good!
Excuse me, I got a little carried away Rei-nee.
Never mind that.
Ele? Are you really Ele?
Do you guys known each other?
That's right, we've known each other since we were little.
Oh, really?
Leti, could you please do the finishing up?
I'm gonna go heat the bath.
Sure!
Ele, you seem well.
Yes Master! It's been a while hasn't it?
Princess...
Princess?
Ele, she's a princess?
Where from?
Cliff! Don't be so rude to her!
Milady here, Leticiara Lamew Synphonia-sama, is the first princess of the Kingdom of Synphonia!
Really?
Yes, I am... And Ele is my bodyguard.
Oh! Isn't that amazing Ele?
This isn't the time to be praising me!
You're the one who got in the way when I finally found her in the market this morning!
Even if you say so, who wouldn't help someone in a situation like that?
A-Anyway! If you get one thing wrong, you could be sentenced to death!
I got it! I got it!
Ele, Cliff-san only tried to save me.
But princess...
Moreover Ele, I've decided to live and work in this place!
What?!
You'll become unrefined working in such a place!
Ele, "Working in such place"? That's a bit rude...
I'm sorry! I didn't mean it like that...
It'll be fine! Cliff-san is here, too!
M-Me?
How about you live here too, Ele?
Princess!
Well, Rei will be delighted if you say you'd stay around, Ele.
Since you're like a sister to her.
However, Princess Leticia, you probably shouldn't tell Rei about your royalty.
Princess, Rei-neesan dislikes people of royal blood...
I think it's best if you hide your true identity while staying here.
Understood!
And everyone, please call me Leti instead of Princess Leticia.
Also, there's no need to be so polite!
Understood.
Master!
Oho, no, I'm terribly sorry!
Geez Master! What are you saying! Be sensible!
Silfie...
Why... Why is it?
Rei-onee-chan...
Talking with God?
U-Um I...
Am I an acceptable confidant?
Actually, not long after onii-chan arrived,
the Cleric came to visit...
Silfie Cloud.
Y-Yes?
You've been working hard to care for orphans, whilst following the will of God.
Therefore, I permit your entrance into the Seishinkan academy!
Thank you very much, father!
If you enter the academy,
you will be forbidden to interact with the outside for three years.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
I wish to study hard so I can become a better person for the people.
That's a good intention.
Now you should get ready to go.
Understood, Father.
Hmm... So that's why you were worried...
I can't tell onii-chan...
And when I think about how I can't see onii-chan for three years, I...
Well, I know I'll miss you, and Cliff will too.
But I can't turn down the father now...
I guess you're at the age now where you should seriously think about your future...
I thought you were still a kid, but I guess you've grown up.
I know how you feel Silfie.
Huh?
Fie-sensei?
What's wrong? You seem down...
I-I-I'm fine! It's nothing.
Really?
Yes, really! Now go and play.
Yeah, let's go!
Wait!
If I really feel this way, I shouldn't have promised the father I'd go...
What should I do?
Fie~!
O-Onii-chan!
What's wrong?
Ele and Rei-nee were worried about you...
Are you sick?
That's not it...
Lemme see if you've got a fever.
I'm not a kid anymore! Don't worry about me.
Really?
I guess I should fix the roof...
Um, onii-chan...
Cliff-san! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Yo!
We're off to the market.
Have a nice trip...
Onii-chan...
Welcome!
Yes, yes, sorry!
Thanks for dinner.
Cheers!
Thank you very much!
Good night!
Rei-onee-chan...
Can you come to my room?
You're still troubled about it?
Yes...
Since this is a good opportunity, I'll tell you...
What is it?
What's this?
It's the diary that your parent's left our grandfather, when they left for their pilgrimage.
Huh?
You should read where the bookmark is.
W-What's written in it?
Well, put simply...
You and Cliff aren't really siblings.
What?!
When our former king was about to pass away,
Cliff who was still a baby was given to a relative,
so that he wouldn't be killed in the war.
At the time, Father Cloud was the King's Cleric,
that is, your father.
Before he was given to him, Cliff was given a bracelet to show that he was the prince,
for when he eventually took the throne.
No way... I can't believe it...
The bracelet that he constantly wears is the only proof of who he is.
Only a small number of his relatives know this.
The truth of Cliff's heritage as the king's successor is written on that torn page of the diary,
I guess it was sensitive information.
Onii-chan is the king's successor...?
So, you and Cliff aren't related by blood.
I can't believe that onii-chan isn't actually my real onii-chan...
It's the truth.
Lapisu?
Why do you know that?
Since it's my job to protect the truth.
What do you mean?
I'll tell you one day.
Rei-onee-chan, does onii-chan know about this?
He should know.
Can I keep this diary?
Sure, so Silfie, you should be honest with your feelings now.
You should confess your feelings.
Silfie...
I can't go to the Seishinkan academy like this!
Can I sit next to you?
Lapisu-chan...
Isn't this lake beautiful?
In this lake, sunk deep below lies someone's feelings.
Feelings?
This kind, pure and crystal clear water that surrounds the feelings is like your soul.
My soul?
Your soul shall protect and preserve the peace of this village.
That's your objective.
N-No way, that's too much for me...
You have nothing to worry about!
Huh?
All you have to do is keep being yourself.
Yeah...
Rei-nee?
Don't be so loud, it's nighttime.
D-Don't tell me that you're sneakily visiting me to have...
Don't be silly.
Or were you expecting something?
W-What do you want so late?
Cliff, you should pay more attention to Silfie.
I-I wasn't trying to neglect her...
Silfie is really troubled right now.
Really?
Apparently, she's received the permission to enter the Seishinkan academy.
And she was troubled over telling you Cliff.
Seishinkan academy?!
She never said anything about that-!
If she joins, she won't be able to interact with the outside world for three years.
Three years...
That's not all, she's always had feelings for you. Feelings of love.
Rei-nee!
Fie and I are siblings!
Well, actually you're not.
You and Silfie aren't related by blood.
N-No way...
You're the only one who can save her from these feelings.
Onii-chan...!
Fie...
I-I'm sorry!
Wait-!
Fie...
Onii-chan...
I was so stupid to not notice your feelings!
Onii-chan!
Don't go to Seishinkan academy!
I have to, I promised the Cleric.
Just decline!
I can't!
I heard from Rei-nee, about everything...
Huh?
And I read that old diary in your room.
Then...
You know that you're not really my onii-chan...
I'm the same as I've always been.
And the fact that you're my cute little sister doesn't change.
You really are my onii-chan!
Yes I am, so please don't leave my side.
I'm so happy, but I have to go.
It's always been my dream to study at Seishinkan academy so that I can become a better person for the people.
Fie!
I don't want to leave you onii-chan, but-!
Fie...
I've always been thinking of you onii-chan...
Not as your little sister...
That's why I've been suffering... It hurts more though.
Fie... I thought you were still a kid but...
I'm not a kid anymore! That's why...!
That's why...?
That's why my chest is about to burst!
Your chest...
Please!
I know it's wrong, but I can't leave your side without doing anything!
Fie...
Kiss me...
Please give me courage.
I can't go to Seishinkan academy like this...
Fie...
Suck me... Suck me more...
No-! Finally my feelings have...!
It's so hot!
Something is happening...
O-Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, that's-!
Onii-chan, keep doing that!
I'll make you feel better, okay?
Yes...
Onii-chan, not there-!
Onii-chan! It's so good!
It feels so good there!
Onii-chan!
Please...!
Onii-chan, please...
Fie-!
I can't hold back...
Amazing, it's amazing!
It's so amazing onii-chan!
It's amazing!
You're doing it so rough!
Fie! I love you!
Onii-chan! I love you too onii-chan!
Fie-!
Onii-chan...
Thanks for your courage...
Rei-onee-chan?
Mister?
Isn't anyone here?
Goodbye onii-chan.
Goodbye Rei-onee-chan.
Goodbye everyone.
Yumi-chan?
Silfie!
Fie-onee-chan!
Fie!
Fie.
Silfie!
Fie!
Fie-sensei!
Fie...
Do your best Silfie-san!
Fie, take care.
Leti... Onii-chan...
You were all waiting for me here?
Fie-sensei!
What is it Yumi-chan?
Here!
Thanks!
I will be back in three years time.
If I become a Cleric, I might be able to help you when you're the king onii-chan.
Then Onii-chan, I'll be off.
Yeah!
I'm off!
Onii-chan, thank you.
Now then, Cliff has to do something about this place.
And about Leticia too.