No, stop!
No!!
You'll rip me apart!
I beg you, stop!
Guignol-sama. The preparations are ready.
Good.
Well then. Let the games begin.
Princess Knight Catue
Fall of The Dragon Princess
If you re here, Dragundaala must not be far, right.
Father was strict, but he praised my strength.
Mother was gentle, no matter what.
Jin, I'm finally catching up to you.
That sound came from the castle just now.
And I smell smoke. I have a bad feeling about this.
My God, what... what happened here?
Anna, is that you?
Your Highness, run! Hurry!
Why?
A dragon! How...?
Anna! Anna, what happened?
Well, well. Dragundaala's Imperial Princess returns.
That armband... the hallmark of a Dragon Knight.
It all makes sense now.
Identify yourself!
Of course.
Monster Battalion 7th Platoon Captain Guignol, at your service.
The pleasure's all mine, Princess Catue.
Monster Battalion?
Shouldn't you freaks be underground? Why are you here?
We bring a declaration from our King, who calls
for the establishment of a world government.
W-World government? That's a laugh.
You attacked my kingdom, you killed my subjects...
This aggression will not stand!
I think you've misunderstood. We haven't killed any of your subjects.
Your subjects killed each other.
What? Nonsense!
It's true, I'm afraid. I merely prompted them.
Prompted?
Yes. Eons ago, the humans of this world
were different beings. Did you know?
What's that got to do with anything?
Humankind's ancestry comprised many species.
There were dog people, bird people...
But the Dragundaala bloodline originated from dragons.
Wh-What!?
Long ago, the Monster Clan used magic to give
surface dwellers their human appearance.
As such, we can easily do the reverse.
Impossible!
We changed the strongest of the Dragon Clan back into
dragons, and they preyed upon the weak among them.
Damn you to hell!
What happened?
It's no use, even for a so-called "Dragon Knight".
What?
Huh?
Impossible!
That was my family's ancestral sword.
You've won.
Kill me.
What giving up already? Don't you want to save your parents?
You mean, they're alive?
What if they are?
The kingdom needs their King and Queen.
Take me in their stead.
Really?
I don't think that decision would please them very much.
What then?
All right
I challenge you to follow my every command for the next seven days.
"Challenge" me!?
If you succeed, I'll return the King and Queen,
turn the dragons back to human form, and withdraw my minions.
This is suspicious. What's your angle?
You give up too easily. No fun at all.
I like a strong opponent, that's all.
Fool! That's no reason to forfeit a victory!
So my chivalry surprises you.
We monsters are connoisseurs of a good time,
which makes us look bad to those who don't know better.
I should take advantage of this "chivalry"
and kill him... but it might be a trap.
Well, what do you say?
Do you swear you'll keep your word?
Of course.
On the honor of the great Kruul, King of Monsters,
I swear to release your parents if you do as I say.
Very well.
And I swear on the honor of my ancestors
and of our great King Lawrence,
I will meet your challenge.
Then we have a contract We begin tomorrow.
Day 1
Gentlemen, introducing the heir to the
Dragundaala Kingdom, Princess Catue.
Catue-sama?
She's alive? Thank God!
Princess Catue?
What are you wearing?
What humiliation.
The Princess has something important to tell you all.
The Kingdom thanks you for your military service.
In return for your devotion...
Go on, unless you don't care about freeing your parents.
I would like to express my gratitude to you all.
What arc you doing, Your Highness?
Don't move!
Be still.
So now I know what a man's penis looks like...
Did that hurt?
No, not at all.
Come on, start expressing your gratitude, Princess.
Lick it with your tongue.
Some kind of juice is coming out the end...
I'm supposed to lick this?
Well, Princess?
Giving up before you've even started?
I'll do it I have to!
Is that good?
Yes. It's very nice. Wh-Whoa!
Wrap your mouth around the whole thing
and give it a good suck, please.
Your Highness! That's~!
Forgive me, Highness! I'm cumming!
This is a man's semen...
It smells bad.
Your Highness... you're too kind to offer us such treatment.
Catue-sama...
Forgive me, I'm going to cum!
Me too! I'm sorry!
Forgive us, Princess.
Forgive us... it feels so good!
My cock feels so good in your throat.
Forgive me, Catue-sama...
Forgive me.
Here comes more...
and more... and more!
Splendid.
You really are a benevolent ruler.
Are we finished for today?
Yes. Tomorrow will be even more of a treat.
You'll love it.
Dammit. I can't give up now.
Oh, my. Why the long face?
My daughter... is Catue all right?
Yes. She's been bathing in the semen of her own soldiers.
What in the world...? Poor Catue.
Perhaps you'd like to trade places with her, Queen Nina?
Do as I say, and I'll relieve Princess Catue.
Do we have a deal?
Can I trust you? To help Catue?
I promise.
All right. So you'll let me take her place, then.
You truly are a loving mother. Now, then...
What's this? Are you enjoying this, Queen Nina?
No absolutely not.
What about this?
No...
No!
Is this the voice you use in bed with your King?
What? Never!
So you're responding honestly to my lovemaking prowess.
No! Don't be ridiculous.
Its not nice to lie.
Stop that!
Don't..
Nina-sama, you like it, do you not?
I... do not.
Even with your nipples getting this hard?
My breasts are...
No, stop this!
Oh, what's this? Something's leaking out of your teats.
Stop!
You'll hurt my nipples!
No... I'm cumming!
Remarkable. Even a vulgar creature
such as myself can make you cum.
You're a filthy one, Queen Nina.
You're wrong. I'm... I'm...
You gushed quite a bit of milk.
But this is hardly fair. Now it's my turn to have some fun.
But...
Remember, its for Princess Catue.
All right. I'll do it.
Are all monsters this big?
Compared to who? No matter.
Pleasure me with your queen-sized breasts.
Good, just like that, but harder.
Like this?
Yes. Now suck it, too.
Just like that.
You're good at using those tits, Nina-sama.
I imagine your king must be very content.
I'm so ashamed, I could die.
Wh-What?
What happened? My body... it's hot!
Oh, dear. Aren't you feeling all right?
No, it's nothing.
Oh? What's this I smell?
Are you in heat? Let's see...
Well, isn't this a surprise.
You've been enjoying my little visit more than you let on.
No, I didn't, I just..
No need to be embarrassed, Your Majesty.
If you like, you may pleasure yourself to your hearts content.
Is that an order?
It's not an order. You're free to do as you please.
Yes...
So good...
Yes... Oh, yes!
Oh, God...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Good heavens, you really marked your territory, didn't you?
I hope you enjoyed yourself.
Listen, about our agreement. It seems we forgot to swear on it.
So I guess I'll be having my way with Catue tomorrow, too.
My apologies.
Day 2
Princess Catue, we have a most distinguished guest visiting today.
Jin!
Catue? I'm sorry. They got me.
Jin, you're alive. Thank God.
Please, leave Jin out of this.
What's this, a demand?
Please.
You're willing to throw away your mother, your father
and your whole kingdom, just to save your pride?
At the very least, don't let him see me humiliated.
Do dragon knights always ask for special
concessions from their opponents like this?
Dammit!
Catue, don't worry. No matter what my heart is true.
I love you.
Jin...
Thank you.
All right I'll do it I can last seven days.
Glad to hear it.
Because today you'll be fornicating with this thing.
Fornicating?
From the Pig Clan?
Correct.
Traditionally, the Dragundaala used
members of the Pig Clan as slaves,
as I'm sure you're aware.
You bastard! What hardship must I endure this time?
Your temper only serves to make this game
more fun for me, Your Highness.
"Game"?
In this game, you may not use human words until further notice.
Instead, talk like a member of the Pig Clan. As in, "Oink, oink".
What?
Furthermore, every time you utter speech, Jin will suffer.
It stinks!
This smells much worse than the ones from yesterday. Disgusting.
All right, Princess Catue.
Pig Clan men like to have their balls licked.
Show this fellow a good time.
That won't do.
Take them all the way into your mouth.
Catue...
Ugh... smells like rotten garbage.
How do you like those pig balls? Tasty?
There's no way it could taste good. This horrid smell!
Whats wrong? If you don't answer, your friend's in trouble.
Oink, oink, oink.
See that? He's enjoying it now.
Suck a little harder.
Oink!
What the... ?
Oink... Oink, oink!
N-No!
Oh, God...
That's too deep!
Oh? Princess Catue, are you enjoying yourself?
Oink, oink.
Enjoying myself? I'm not enjoying myself.
I'm not... enjoying myself!
Having a fat slab of pork tongue shoved between my legs?
I'm not enjoying it at all!
It would appear there's a lot of love juice spilling out of you, Princess.
What? My body's getting hot!
That's...!
What's this sensation? I'm so hot! My body is...
No, stop!
Your pussy is absolutely sopping. How perfectly filthy.
Jin, please don't listen to him!
Oink... Oink... Oink...
Oink!
Oh no. That thing will never fit.
Please, stay away!
Stop... you're too big!
Please, not that!
What's that? Was that human language I heard just now?
Jin!
Be careful. Any more words like that will
have a dire impact on your friend.
It hurts! He's going to split me in half!
God, somebody, please help me!
I'm going to burst!
It hurts... is this what sex is like?
Please, stop it!
It's getting bigger inside me. Oh, no!
Stop! Don't shoot inside me!
I lost my virginity...
In front of Jin...
Wonderful!
I've witnessed a historic reconciliation
between the dragons and the pigs.
Beautiful.
But it's a shame that your fiancé doesn't see it the same way.
J-Jin...
Jin, please!
Well then...
Tomorrow's going to be even more fun. Wait and see, Princess Catue.
My humiliation... isn't over?