If she can withstand seven days of sexual assault, she'll cause the Demon Tribe army to withdraw, and will be able to rescue the King and Queen.
This is the proposal that Princess Catue, Dragondaala Kingdom's First Imperial Princess, has taken from Demon Tribe Commander Ginyol.
The soldiers of the Demon Tribe army will open up the flower of pleasure to the embarrassing free lusts of sexual desire.
Catue, taking on the restoration by herself, was trembling with fear.
Meanwhile, Ginyol, who has taken away the power of Cateu's mother Niina,
has locked Niina's soul into the depths of both pleasure and lust with a powerful magical charm.
Moreover, Niina whose spirit has been broken,
abandoning her restless holy kingdom, in taking up the position of saving her daughter's life,
has made an unfortunate serious mistake on her own.
What is the goal of Ginyol, who has assaulted not only Catue, but also Niina?
What will happen to those taken: her father Ampiya, to Catue and Jin?
And finally, will Catue, in the remaining three days of sexual assault, be able to take back her kingdom?
W
The One Family Lunatic Feast
Fifth Day
Today is the day it will be carried out, princess Catue.
Foolish.
How much do you think embarrassment matters to me now
What was that? That voice, just now?
It can't be Mother?
Mother!
Y-yes!
More, more, violate my pussy more!
More!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Mother, like this I can't believe it.
You bastard! What have you done to Mother?
We unleashed the lust that was asleep deep within her body. That is what I presume.
You bastard! I will never forgive you!
That voice...
Is it Catue?
Mommy will take little Catue to heaven with her together.
Mother! You should not be saying things like that!
Please, take those strange bugs off you quickly!
But, I have gathered these little ones to lick away my naughty juices.
It feels so good as they prickle me.
Now, Princess Catue, this very day would you kindly play with Niina-sama?
You bastard! Asking a mother and child to do something indecent like that!
Catue, I'm so happy.
To be doing something that feels as good as this with my daughter!
Just thinking of it turns me on!
My clitoris!
My clitoris is rustling!
My clitoris is extending!
What... is that?
No, no, this is not my mother!
With my newly formed monster penis I will take good care of you my darling, all right?
No... Mother!
Stop! Let me go!
Why do you want to run?
This is the long-awaited reunion of mother and child.
Mother, return to your true self!
Catue, it makes me so happy that you've developed such a nasty body like this!
No, I ask you to please stop, Mother!
My, my, it's already this wet.
You are, indeed, my child.
Naughtiness is hereditary, it seems.
Stop saying such nasty things...
Please, return to your true self!
Why are you being so prudent, Catue?
It's all right to be more honest with yourself.
You want it to feel better.
I don't believe you.
Mother... enjoying nasty things like this!
It's going to be fine. You can leave everything to Mother, Catue.
NOOOO!
Mother, you must not do this... between a mother and daughter...
Just as I would have thought, your nipples are quite sensitive, are they not?
Just as mine are.
I'm not... feeling... anything...
Liars are bad little children who must be punished.
Your clitoris should also be very sensitive.
Mine is like that.
No! Not like that... not... feeling anything...
You really are my daughter!
Then, surely you must feel this easily.
Mother, not that...
There is no need to worry, Catue.
Don't! Not that! Mother!
I never thought the day would come when I could enter my daughter's pussy!
It's coming! Mother's penis is coming inside me!
The penis is rubbing against me!
My pussy is being opened up!
I'm inside! The monster penis is inside my daughter!
No! Mother!
Good! the pussy that I nurtured feels so good!
My uterus is being stirred into squishiness!
Penis! There's so much penis inside me!
Don't move! That's enough! I don't need any more penis!
Ah, Catue's pussy is becoming soft and squishy...
Inside of my child, to be together like this... I can hardly believe it!
So good! Pussy is so good!
Penis inside my daughter's nasty pussy is so good! I’m fucking my daughter!
No, don't!
Mother, you're thrusting too hard!
Don't, Mother, I'm being turned on!
I'm being turned on by the thrusts of your monster penis!
It's good to be turned on, Catue!
Feel it more, feel it more!
Mother's...
Catue, I'm going to cum, a lot is going to come out,
I'm going to shoot into you hard!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, mother!
I have to cum!
That's good, go on and cum, Catue!
Cum!
Mother! I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Catue!
Make my daughter pregnant!
I'm cumming!
My mother’s seed…I’ve gotten pregnant!
Wonderful.
I could truly feel the love between parent and child.
Wh-what?
You bastard, what are you planning?
As I was watching you two, I became envious.
Stop! Let me go! Let me go!
That won't go in! A cock as big as that won't fit!
It's a penis for the sake of Catue-sama.
Please, take a good taste of it.
No! What's this? The penis is beating my pussy up!
I'm being slowly but steadily violated by his cock!
My pussy is going on its own!
All these bumps are going into my pussy!
It hurts! Being fucked by a cock like this!
Stop, stop, please, don't go that far in!
What is this? Hot, my insides are hot!
It's because of what is coming from my penis.
My bodily fluids act as an aphrodisiac.
That bumpy dick juice is coming inside me...
I can feel it, my pussy is getting aroused...
It's raising me up...
No! The juice is overflowing!
Why is it overflowing like this?
It seems you're thoroughly aroused.
Very well, then, shall we allow the rear hole to have a taste of this as well?
Stop, stop, that at least is... truly... really... impossible...
It can't be! It went into my anus!
That bumpy penis fit inside!?
No! My ass, my asshole is being fucked...
How is it? Does it not feel good?
The feeling is coming... waves are stirring up inside...
I can feel it...
My ass, my asshole is melting... I'm going to melt...
What's this? You're taking good care of her anus?
Mother, help me!
Very well, Mother will take good care of Catue's mouth.
Stop that, Mother!
This can’t be true!
You can't do that, Catue-sama. You cannot go against your mother's words.
W-what?
Catue!
Your mouth is very good!
Then I shall be good enough to take care of this end.
Catue! Is it delicious? Is my penis delicious?
If it were not delicious, would she be raising her voice as much as she is?
I take the fact that her hole is thick with juice as evidence.
Oh, Catue, take more! There's no reason for you to hold back!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum! Ginyol!
Then, Niina-sama, shall we do it together?
I'm cumming!
I, too, am cumming!
The semen is still coming, it's still coming out!
I am also ejaculating!
Oh, my, I came...
W-what's this...
I'm dizzy...
D-don't...
It's...
not stopping...
It stopped...
It's raining semen...
Catue, you're so pretty.
Catue-sama, do you surrender?
Or, perhaps, do you wish to resume?
I, myself, do not have any objections.
Then, let us continue in this way tomorrow.
Sixth day
Today I think we will have a little trial.
J-Jin!
C-Catue?
On this fine day I will have your bodies meld together.
You bastard! What are you scheming this time?
I simply wanted to see the two of you in your loving forms.
You bastard! How grotesque do you plan to make us go?
Jin. There are no other options.
Catue...
Would you... do it with me?
Would you... love me?
Catue...
Jin... I've already been dirtied...
You don't have to say anything.
I feel the same for you as I always have.
Jin! Your palms are hot!
That's right. Catue! Catue!
I'm so happy! Jin... Jin is licking me!
Catue, it's so pretty.
Really? But... that area has been roughed around a lot.
You poor thing. In that case, I'll be very gentle.
Yes!  Jin's tongue licking that dirty place on me!
Jin! Purify me! Lick me more!
More, move more, do anything and lick everything clean!
I'm cumming!
Catue, is it okay?
Jin, I want you... to be inside me...
Jin, Jin is here!
Inside me, Jin is finally inside me!
Jin, Jin, we're together!
Jin is violent inside me!
Please, harder, more, erase everything!
Jin, I love you, I love you... let’s be like this forever...
Yes, I'm going to cum...
Jin, together, please, let's...
Let's cum together!
My body is... hot!
Jin... what's wrong?
Catue... I always... loved you...
Jin!
Oh, my, do accept my most sincere apologies.
I must have forgotten to inform you.
I cast a curse on Jin-dono that would revive a latent image as soon as he ejaculated.
The monster... the monster is te-tearing me apart!
I'm cumming!
I’ll die! I’ll die!
Jin, please, please, return to normal!
Jin, return...
My holes... are tearing apart!
No... no...
Seventh Day
It suits you quite well, does it not, Catue-sama?
As you wish.
I have nothing left to lose.
And you went to the trouble of wearing such an appropriate outfit on this final day.
That voice...
Jin!
Jin, don’t you recognize me?
Now, Catue-sama, let us proceed to the final wager.
Please kill this dragon.
What did you say?
There is nothing to be concerned about. It is a mere beast.
It's not a beast!
This is Jin! There’s no way I can kill him!
Then do you give up on the resurrection of the kingdom?
After six days of being raped to this extent, you would make it all meaningless?
How will you choose? I care not either way.
Jin. I'm so sorry!
I can't... Jin is someone I love. I can't possibly kill him!
Those are such nice words.
Haven’t you already killed your beloved by your actions, in a manner of speaking?
What did you say?
The dragon you had in your hands the day you came back to this castle…
Who do you think that was?
It couldn't be... that dragon was...
As you have realized, that dragon is your father.
King Lawrence.
As to be expected from one of the dragon family.
That was superb!
Something... something like that...
No. NOOOOO!
I have been waiting for this moment, Princess Catue!
A body wallowing in pleasure, a heart fallen into despair,
this moment right now when you have fallen between the two!
This is the one who should take Mazoku Country, the one with the strongest genes,
of the Dragondaala family, you, the strongest Dragon Knight, who were about to be king!
Coming, coming, turning, instantly, the sleeping power,
the sleeping power of our great king of our great clan!
I ask, I ask, this daughter here,
transfer from her the ancient powers!
Why did that happen?
It can't be... this is...
What can be happening?
Can this be... recessive genes?
Such a laughable tale.
Born into the main family and taken over by the dragon genes,
and at the end, finally, it was all recessives!
Well, whatever.
My goals have be thwarted, but over these past seven days you have allowed me to pleasure myself with you.
As a thank-you for that, the arm of the law will give to you a lifestyle that is most befitting.
Princess Catue.
No! Please stop!
There's no need to worry. Leave everything to me.
I beg you, please, Niina-sama, Niina-sama!
It's tight! Anna, you're a virgin, aren't you?
Please let me go, if you do that...
Very well, then I shall let this body fill you completely.
This fat dick will pleasure you.
It hurts, it hurts, Niina-sama!
Such a tight fit, you’re a virgin all right, it feels so good!
It's going to tear me! Tear me apart!
Catue-sama, I beg you!
Please help!
What? Done already? Penis, penis, where's the next penis?
Penis, please give me a penis!
Someone, come to Catue’s dirty pussy,
And squirt it full with semen, please!
Penis, I'm so happy with penis!
Anywhere on this slut Catue, please allow me to suck you dry!
I'm cumming!
Catue-sama!
Oh, dear, Anna, this is a problem.
If you cannot even take this amount of penis...
You've been forgiven.
No! Please fuck Catue's dirty asshole!
Oh, yes! It's the best!
Go all the way into my rectum!
Mother, look at me!
My asshole has opened up to take his cock!
Look at how far it goes!
That won't do, Catue, being Jin's only bitch.
Jin-dono ... please fuck me, too!
Oh, Jin-dono, hurry up, put a cock into my asshole and pussy!
My asshole! Break it apart with your thick hard cock!
The Dragondaala family, despite such high and mighty origins, has come to such an interesting conclusion.
You make such a fine sight, you two.
Enjoy your eternity with Jin-dono.
My uterus is being violated! My entire insides are being violated!
More, more, the more you put your penis in the more I expand!
It's coming out of my breasts!
I'm contracting!
Mother!
Catue!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming
I'm cumming!
Together!
mitome taku nakute kagami ni utsuru hitomi ni kizu wo tsuketa
I don’t want to recognize the eyes reflected in the mirror,
kudake chitta akai kakera
wounded, smashed up red pieces
kiduka nai mama de i takatta noni tsuyoku naru kontorasuto
Even though left unnoticed, contrast getting stronger
ukabiagaru riaru ni mata nai te yowai mama de nigeru no?
Reality rising to the surface, I cry out again, running when already so weak?
kurikaesu ayamachi ni nan do kuyan datte
Over and over again making a mistake, how many times to say I’m sorry
itami ni nare te shimattara susume nai
Can’t go on now that I’m used to this pain.
kokoro no mama koe o agete kono uta ni nose te
To your heart’s content, raise your voice, extend in this song,
shinji teru negai ni ima hikari ga sasu
The light now stabs the wish I believe.
kowaku nai wa kotae nante koko ni ha naku te mo
I’m not afraid, whatever the answer, it is not here.
hitori ja nai tte koto mou shitteru
Saying I’m not alone, I already know that
koko de owaranai wa
It won’t end here.