The demonic army planning to conquer the world
invaded the kingdom of Dragundara,
land of the descendants of the sacred dragons.
General Ginel, the leader of the demon army,
promptly decided for the country's annihilation
and captured the king and queen using forbidden magic.
Princess Catue, Dragundara's imperial princess,
in order to force the demon army to withdraw
and to retrieve the king and queen, accepts Ginel's offer:
she must endure his sexual desires for several days.
Not only was she forced on the first day to shower in an immense amount of semen from the soldiers,
but she also had to go through the tragedy of losing her virginity in front of her fiancée, Jin.
Not only her body, Ginel schemes to crush even her mind.
So, will Princess Catue be able to endure the multiple days of assault and reclaim her kingdom?
SubDESU-H
PRESENTS
Day 3
Hey, do it better!
Amazing! You suck so well, Hime-sama!
I-I'm cumming!
Now, drink it properly, got it?
That's no good; I'm sure I told you to drink it to the last drop.
Y-You scum, what are you planning this time?
Oh no, what a scary face.
This is a game. I'd like you to enjoy this more.
B-Bastard! Don't mess with me!
Wh-What are you doing?
N-No!
My brothers! Fill Princess Catue's uterus with your semen.
But of course, you must not let out a single drop, Princess Catue.
Y-You're going to put it in already?
S-Stop!
S-Stop!!
My cock feels good!
I-It hurts! It hurts-!
You're tearing me apart!
It feels so good!
It feels so damn good!
I-It hurts!
I told you to stop, didn't I?
I-I'm cumming!
Wh-What?
It's getting bigger-!
A-Again?
I'm not done yet.
I quite like you.
Get pregnant with my child.
And when it's born, I'll marry that child and make her pregnant too!
No!
N-No way... I don't want to get pregnant with such children!
Take your cock out! Take it out already!
Give it up.
Even if I don’t keep thrusting it into you like this, you'll get pregnant anyway!
What-?
You stink!
Stop it!
Get pregnant! Get pregnant!
You stink!
I-I'm gonna puke!
It's entering me-!
It feels good!
Pregnant! Get pregnant with my child!
Get pregnant! Get pregnant!
I'm cumming!
Oh my, oh my. You promised that you wouldn't spill a single drop.
I-I know!
There's some left!
Suck it clean!
Ahh, what a waste.
I came inside her so much...
Close up your pussy and keep it inside you, already!
I'm next!
Me too!
So many!
So many are coming inside me!
Please don’t cum anymore!
M-My stomach hurts!
I'm cumming!
I-I'm cumming too!
Princess Catue, what a pathetic look.
We have finally come to the grand finale, Princess Catue.
S-Stop! Don't step on me!
That's no good.
You should be saying: "Please don't spill it out yet."
Please endure it until the opening of the show, Princess Catue.
Please put more strength into your asshole and close your pussy properly.
It's such a waste if it spills out.
Well then, we’re here.
Wh-What are you going to do?
Dear soldiers!
Burn it into your minds: the semen fountain show of the proud dragon knights!
To think that you yourself are making your precious crest dirty...
No!
Stop the semen!
I'm cumming-! I'm cumming!
I guess she cums like a man, since she was brought up like a boy.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry-!
T-The semen has stopped flowing out...
Now, do you feel joyous?
As I expected, Princess Catue.
Well then, I’ll have to prepare things over there, too.
Oh my, oh my. You sure got a rough treatment by my subordinates.
Wh-Where is Catue?
I-Is she safe?
Yes. There's no need to worry.
She's lively as always.
Wh-What are going to do?
W-Why are you doing such a thing?
T-This feeling...!
I'm feeling so hot!
Oh, I forgot.
My bodily fluids cause immediate arousal.
I-Immediate arousal, you say...?
It's so hot-!
I'm getting paralyzed-!
T-This is...
This is the same as before...!
You d-deceived me again!
I wouldn't say that I deceived you.
I just wanted to make you happy, Nina-sama.
To think that Nina-sama would let out so much of her perverted fluid...
So you want a penis after all, don't you?
Th-That’s not true!
Today, I have brought something with me to appease Nina-sama's body.
T-This is...!
Ni-Nina-sama!
Ji-Jin Drak-dono!
Actually, Jin Drak-dono is upset from witnessing Princess Catue lose her virginity.
Please comfort him with that body of yours.
Jin-dono is the fiancée of my daughter.
There's no way I could do something so disgraceful...
If he's your daughter's fiancée, then doesn't that make him your son?
Son-in-law...?
Isn't it a mother’s duty to comfort her son? Or am I wrong?
Y-You mustn’t, Nina-sama!
Don't let yourself be tricked by the words of someone like him!
The only one who can mend his heart is you,
Nina-sama, she who will become his mother.
You're right.
To comfort the son is a mother's duty.
Nina-sama, you mustn't!
Please get ahold of yourself!
It's fine like this, Nina-sama.
Please stop!
We shouldn't do something like this!
So, this is Jin-dono's penis.
It's so big and hard...
I'm so jealous of Catue.
Nina-sama, p-please stop!
The penis belongs to Catue, right?
Then I will take here...
It's so raw and delicious!
We can't be doing something like this!
Please come to your senses, Nina-sama!
My pussy feels so hot-! It’s hot!
This smell.
So this is how it smells down here...
P-Please! Talk!
Please talk more right there!
Jin-dono, please comfort Nina-sama's pussy.
Otherwise...
Please! Please smell my pussy!
Stick your nose into my pussy and smell it!
Nina-sama's smell... So good...!
Jin-dono's tongue is entering my pussy!
Yes-! Th-That’s it! Right there!
So good!
A-Amazing! Right there!
Please suck my clitoris!
Ah! Lick it! Suck it!
Th-This is good!
My clitoris feels so good!
S-Stop-!
Good! So good!
Nina-sama! I can't any-
It's fine, let it out...
Nina-sama, you mustn't!
If you keep this up, I'll really-!
So this is the semen from a penis...
Fresh semen... tastes good...
Nina-sama, I beg you, please stop...
Please come to your senses-!
How cute...
I can't...
I can't take it any longer...
There's no need to worry.
Why don't you just leave it to your future mother?
Nina-sama, you mustn’t!
Jin, come!
Come into me!
It's entered me! Your penis is entering me!
Nina-sama- !
Please stop, Nina-sama!
I can feel it! Your cock feels so good!
It's so hot!
I can feel it!
A-Amazing!
Nina-sama-!
That’s it!
Amazing! I can feel it inside me-!
Please, stronger! Stronger!
Nina-sama's pussy is coiling around my cock!
M-My insides! It feels so good rubbing against my womb!
It's making me crazy-!
It's gonna come out! I’m gonna cum!
Please stop!
Your penis has gotten hard!
It's twitching!
Your cock is feeling good from me putting my finger inside your ass!
Jin, deeper!
Keep thrusting your thick cock from below!
More! Give me more!
Cum!
I can feel it!
It feels so good-!
My uterus is closing!
Amazing, Nina-sama!
N-No! I'm your mama!
Call me Mama!
Mama! I-It’s so good!
Mama!!!
Jin!!!
It's coming out! My breast milk!
Little boy, let me bweast-feed you now...
Mama! I wanna drink from your breasts!
I-It's coming out! So much is coming out!
Mama's breast milk is dewicious!
I’m at my limit-!
I-I can't take it-! It’s too much!
I can't take it anymore!
It’s coming out again!
My body's getting hot from letting it come out like this!
It’s so hot!
Mama, don’t put your finger in me...
I can't hold it anymore!
Mama-!
I-I'm gonna cum!
You’re gonna cum? You're cumming?
I want to shoot my semen into Mama's slippery pussy to my heart's content!!
Y-Yes!
Release it, release it inside of me.
Shoot your thick semen into my slippery pussy!
Please!
I'm cumming!
Come, come!
Let out your semen!!
I’m cumming, mama!!!!
My womb feels so hot... I might get pregnant...
Day 4
Today, I'll have you offer your body to this.
W-What is that-!?
This thing doesn’t even have a name.
It's one of the lowest among the demonic creatures.
Wh-What do you want me to do with something like that?
It feeds on female sexual body fluids.
You will fill its stomach.
Don't joke with me!
A-As if I would do it with something as disgusting as this!
Don't come any closer! Stay away!
W-What?!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Let go of me, let go of me!
What is this? It's all slimy...
I-It's disgusting!
S-Stop!
Cut that out!
Cut that out!!
Stop...!
T-This thing is chewing on my nipples!
It feels good...
Stop!
Oh my, oh my, Princess Catue.
So you feel good from it sucking on your nipples?
Wh-What nonsense!
I'm not feeling... anything-!
Stop...!
Let go of me! Lemme go!
I don't feel...
I don't feel aroused-!
S-Stop...
Let me go!
Please... This is...
Any more than this and I'll...
I... I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
So it's finally come this. You climax just from having your breasts teased?
S-Stop!
T-That’s-!
No!!
Don't insert something like that into me!
That place is... D-Don't...
N-No!
Stop!
Halt!
It's reaching deep inside my womb!
N-No...!
I can feel it!
I can feel it very well!
What is this...?
What-?
N-No!
That's no place for insertion!
Oh? Then what is that place used for?
I-It's...
Tell me straight.
What is that place for?
It's...
To release...
Release what?
Tell me properly, please.
It's about to enter otherwise...
Excrement...
That place is used to release excrement!
Well then, let’s have you feel good from the hole from which you release your excrement.
S-Stop-!
I-It's not possible!
It's rubbing-!
It's rubbing me inside!
It’s rubbing against my stomach-!
I-I’m gonna break!
My ass is gonna break-!
Something slimy is coming out!
What?
A-Am I being aroused?
Even though it’s deep inside my pussy and ass?
I-Its tentacles are p-penetrating my womb and intestines!
No! Don't go any further!
M-My womb and my ass feel too hot!
No!
I'm going crazy!
What? It's going to put in more?
I-Impossible! It's impossible, I tell you!
More won't fit in!
It's going to rip my pussy and my asshole apart!
It’s gonna break apart!
I’m dying! I’m gonna die!
My stomach is full!
It has enough, I tell you!
Don’t churn up my insides!
Don't rub against my insides!
A monster is moving inside of me...
W-What is it this time?!
It's hard...
Wh-What's this?!
It lays eggs within female bodies.
And you, Princess Catue, are its nest.
Nest?
For that thing?!
My stomach and my butt are full of it-!
My belly is tearing apart-!
I-I beg you, t-take it out!
L-Let it out!
What's that supposed to mean?
It's painful-!
My stomach! My stomach-!
It’s going to rip!
I'm giving birth!
I-It's coming out-!
Now I'm giving birth anally!
No more-!
The eggs... t-they feel so good!
I want to lay more eggs!
I-I can feel them coming out-!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
The eggs... they f-feel so good...
My asshole felt so good...
I want to lay more... Much more...
Next will be the moment of truth, Princess Catue.