Leticia Apple (Age: 18)
Silfie Cloud (Age: 18)
Eleanor Fortworse
Lapisu Melucurius Freya
Rachel Harvest
Cliff Cloud
The history of the Synphonia kingdom in 215 A.D
Cliff, the wondering bard, has returned home after traveling across the county.
There, he saved a girl who was being chased by the imperial guard.
Whilst gazing at an apple tree she said...
I'm Leticia Apple! Please call me Leti!
-Or so she said,
but actually she was no other than the princess of the Synphonia kingdom,
Leticia Lamew Synphonia!
Master!
What? You don't have any money?
Cliff and the rest kindly greeted Leticia,
who had escaped from royal society to see what a peasant's life was like.
And so, the princess's experience of society began by working at The Rolling Apple Tavern downtown.
Welcome!
Today is Sunday, the last day of the week which everyone takes off.
SubDESU-H
So then, we're off!
I shall go too!
You haven't had any breaks for ages, so you should at least take today off.
Even if you say so...
Am I not good enough to ensure her safety?
We're just heading back to the castle, so we'll be fine. Right, Cliff-san?
Let's go!
So that's how it is and...
Wait!
C'mon, we're off!
There's no need to hurry this much!
They'll be fine.
Alright then, go and tell them what's happened.
No, you should come in too!
Huh?
Today is Sunday, so there probably won't be too many people around.
I'll give you a tour of the castle!
But, um, I'm just a normal peasant...
No-! Don't worry about that!
C'mon!
Could you wait here please?
Then what should I-?
I'll come right back after telling father!
H-Hey!
This place seems familiar somehow...
Looking for something?
Cliff-san.
Who are you?
That's so mean! It's me! Leticia!
I'm kidding!
How do I look?
I almost didn't recognize you.
R-Really?
Anyway, that was quick.
Father says that there's no need to be so formal because it's a castle.
What a great king.
He said when he was a child, he used to escape and play outside too!
Even better! Looks like we'll get along.
Yes!
So, how about we wander back?
Yes, I shall go change.
Sheesh, so she really was a princess.
Hey!
Lapisu-san!
Hello there! Off for a walk?
Hello.
Yes, since we're free today during the day.
At night, you'll be working at the Apple Tavern, right?
Yeah, wanna come?
Yes!
Huh?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Well, I don't know about that...
Cliff-san, can you understand cat language?
Nope! Not at all!
Cheers!
Hey, hey, you're in the way! Move over!
Excuse me!
Can I get through?
What did you say?! Say that to my face!
Sure! I'll say it as many times as you want! You're just a drunken lowlife!
You guys! What do you think you're doing here?
But-! He's-!
Making excuses?! I knew you were a drunken lowlife!
What did you say?!
Like I said... You guys!
Please wait!
Huh?
We were wrong, so please don't make such a sad face...
Y-Yeah, we're sorry Leti-chan...
Will you guys make up?
Yeah...
That's good!
Rei-nee, it doesn't look like an act does it?
She's pretty good.
Who would have known that Leti had such talents...
Goodnight!
Thank you very much!
Like I said, I don't like that damn hat you're wearing!
That's right!
Hey! Say something!
Hmph, it can't be helped...
Here you go, Leti-onee-chan.
Thanks, Yumi-chan.
Cliff-san, it's okay, I'll fix it!
Huh? You can sew Leti?
Leave it to me!
Um, Ele, I can't stitch this area very well...
It's a bit difficult there, isn't it?
Could you pass it here?
You'll need to double cross it and put it through.
If you hold it here, it's not very difficult.
Can I try?
Sure, here you go.
Leti's training hard...
This is the salt, and this is the pepper.
For a traditional flavor, use these two.
Yes.
Now if you add a few of these additives, then you can enhance the flavor.
Yes!
Anyways, what's with all this?
Suddenly saying, "Leave the cooking to me tonight"...
I'm sorry, is this a hassle for you?
That's not what I meant.
Anyway, it's really helpful to have someone who can help me back here.
Thank you very much!
Since I was getting used to serving people I wanted to try some cooking too!
Is that all?
Huh?
Isn't there a specific someone that you want to eat your cooking?
T-That's not it!
I won't say anything, so how about it?
Yes, um...
Like I thought.
Then-
Good!
Yes!
Okay, dinner is ready!
Please work hard tonight!
Oh, this looks good!
Today's special!
Thanks for the meal!
It's good!
Rei-nee, it's a bit different from your normal flavor, but it still tastes good!
Cliff-san?
Yeah? What's up Leti?
I just went outside to put the trash out, and the moon looks so beautiful tonight!
Do you want to go for a walk?
A walk, huh?
Sure, that sounds good once in a while.
Yes!
It's so cool and refreshing here.
It sure is.
There's something I want to ask you, Cliff-san.
Why did you become a wondering bard?
Um, I'm sorry if you didn't want to talk about it!
No, it's nothing like that.
I think I was probably bored with everyday life.
You were bored?
The tavern and the church in this village really feel at home.
However, perhaps because it felt too good to leave,
I thought I would become old and end my life there without experiencing anything more.
I was seeking change, probably.
Change?
It's the same for you too, isn't it?
You wanted to experience more things, isn't that why you left the castle?
Ah, I guess you're right.
Should we head back?
Yes.
Ele, you wanted to see me?
Yes...
My job as Princess Leticia's bodyguard doesn't just involve protecting her from criminals,
It's also my job to see that she doesn't get involved with bad people.
Well, I guess so!
Protecting the princess, while ensuring her happiness.
So, the thing I want to ask you is...
Cliff-san!
What's wrong?
Something is burning in the oven!
Where's Rei-nee?
She went out to buy supplies!
Geez, it can't be helped.
We're not finished-!
Cliff-san!
What happened now?
I dropped my mittens in it too!
Can you get them out with the tongs?
I'll try!
Sorry about that!
I'm going to get to the point.
What do you think of Leti... No, I mean the princess?
What would you do if you decided I was a bad influence?
It depends on what you say.
Well, it wouldn't be so bad to be a stain on your sword.
Hey Cliff, Leti's this country's princess.
She's royalty!
I know that.
Are you serious about her?
Once her work here is complete, she might not be able to set foot outside the castle again.
If that happens, I'll guess I have to sneak in!
Maybe you should become a stain on my sword...
I used to sing songs like that back then.
In these songs,
the hero didn't sense any danger.
You're too easy going! Geez.
Cliff-san!
Huh?
I've never seen so many people!
It's not only the people from this village, but from across the country as well!
Did Ele enter last year's competition too?
No, she was studying the lady's manners at the castle knight training facilities.
Ele was studying lady's manners? That's not like her.
I didn't know you had to study such things to become one of the king's knights.
She said that the only way to save lots of people with her sword was to become one of the king's knights.
I see.
Since she might be able to talk directly to the king if she became one of his knights.
That's enough!
Over there! There's Ele!
Oh yeah!
From here, she sure looks like a great knight!
She doesn't just look great, she is a great knight!
Ele!
Do your best!
Start-!
Start!
That's enough!
The winner is Eleanor Fortworse!
Yes! She won that round!
Looks like things are getting settled.
Whoa, she was so fast that I couldn't see a thing!
I bet the competitor was thinking the same thing!
I didn't know that Ele was so good!
Yeah! I bet she'll get pretty far!
Right? Right?
What? The bracelet?
Now it's the finals!
Ele's amazing!
Oh what? He doesn't look very strong.
He's the captain of the knights...
He's the won the last two years.
Really?
I guess appearances can be deceiving.
Start!
Congratulations!
You did well!
Oh, looks like Ele's drunk too.
I'm not surprised, she drank so much.
Maybe she was a bit upset. It didn't look like she wasn't drinking in celebration.
Ele, hang in there...
I'll take her to her room.
I think you drank too much tonight.
Were you upset about before?
Yeah...
I see.
Sleep tight.
Yeah, thanks...
Goodnight, you did well today.
Cliff...
Huh? What's up?
The princess seems to have taken a liking to you.
Yeah.
I'm not telling you what you should do, as long as you feel the same.
Cliff... Are you listening...?
A dance party?
Please come!
I don't think I'll be allowed to!
Even I, the bodyguard, can enter it so...
But-!
Won't my pleas change your mind? Cliff-san...
Sheesh! Fine then!
I don't think I should be here!
It's fine! There are people like me amongst the royalty, too.
If it's no trouble for you, could you please dance with me?
M-Me? I mean, are you okay with the likes of me?
Yes, please!
My name is Lianna Pesca Horiairing, nice to meet you.
Y-Yes, I'm Cliff Cloud, and likewise.
Leti! You were here?
Cliff-san...
I was taking a rest because I was getting tired of meeting so many people.
Although you looked busy too...
Oh, um that was, I just went with the flow and...
Would you dance with me this time?
Please wait!
We can hear the music here too.
Sure.
Thanks for dancing with me.
The same goes for you.
I convinced you to come since I wanted to dance with you.
Please lead me better than you did with Lianna-san.
Are you worrying about that?
Maybe I am?
We're closing for the night, thanks for your work everyone
Thanks for you work!
You seem to have fun when you're working Leti!
It's all thanks to you!
M-Me?
Yes.
You're the person who saved me at the market,
and you're the person who introduced me to this place.
I can't thank you enough Cliff-san.
Thank you very much indeed!
I don't think that what I did was really all that big a deal though...
Even if I return to the castle, I'll never forget about everyone!
Of course you too, Cliff-san.
Well, as long as I'm helping you out, that's good.
You looked like you've had fun too.
Oh yeah, how about we have a farewell party the night before you leave?
Why are you being so kind to me?
Well...
It's because I'm too sensitive.
Can we be together tonight?
Sure.
Leti, Ele!
Father and I are going off to get supplies.
Oh, okay then!
Understood Rei-nee.
We're leaving the shop to you, Cliff.
Yes, master.
What's happening?!
Regures!
We've got a message from the king.
A message from father?
Yes, Cliff Cloud.
Huh?
And Leticia Apple, er, I mean Princess Leticiara Lemew Synphonia.
Come to the castle before dark.
Eleanor, that suits you.
It's been a while Cliff.
You've sure become grand, Regures.
Is that all?
That is all. Dismissed!
I'll go too-!
But we need someone to look after the store...
Hello!
Can I please have some orange peels and fish liver?
Lapisu! What good timing! Could you look after the store?
We've got plenty of fish livers you can have too!
We have come forth.
Thank you.
The man behind you is Cliff Cloud, is it not?
Yes it is.
I want to hear this directly from him.
Yes, I am Cliff.
I haven't introduced myself.
I am the king of Synphonia, Rozel Haizendo Synphonia.
I am the father of Leti, over here.
Um, that is very kind of you.
I-Is something wrong?
You've got a nice build, and you look pretty strong.
I am just a traveling bard, your honor.
Anyway, don't you think this is too sudden?
Actually, I was going to come to the Apple Tavern myself,
but the ministers stopped me.
Geez, you haven't changed, have you father?
Actually, there was someone working for me alongside you in that tavern.
Your honor?
It's not like I'm don't trust you Eleanor-kun,
but you always act for Leti's sake...
I'm afraid that's true.
Please understand that I just think that you care too deeply for her.
I thought that it would be good for Leticia-sama,
but all responsibility for this incident lies with me.
I am prepared for any punishment.
Wait! Ele didn't-!
Don't get so hasty.
I hear that you're childhood friends with Cliff-kun.
What kind of person do you think Cliff-kun is?
He may be a person who has been involved with Leticia-sama,
but he's not a bad person, your honor.
He better not be a womanizer.
Never.
Dinner should be ready soon.
You should join us too, Cliff-kun.
Um, I have to get back soon...
He has to help back at the Apple Tavern...
You will join us at dinner.
This is an order from the king.
How forceful.
Princess, I'll help out at the Apple Tavern.
Then please do so Ele.
My dream is to live as a fisherman out in the country.
I want to hurry up and give my crown to someone worthy.
But it will happen sooner or later, with or without you.
Will you become Leti's husband?
Or, do you not want to be married?
If you refuse,
I can also have you detained as someone who kidnapped the princess.
Take my place and become king!
You're fit enough to become the successor,
no, rather you have the responsibility.
When my brother passed away you were still a baby.
But to avoid getting you involved in the war, we secretly had you escape the castle with Cloud the Cleric.
As for the ultimate proof...
This bracelet signifies who you are, namely it is a key part of the last ruler's identity.
I won't let you say that you won't be my successor.
I'll give you a room to stay in, so think about it tonight.
Are you willing to run away with Leti after all this?
If you are, you'll become a lover who has cowardly betrayed the citizens.
I still can't believe what father said...
What the king said is true.
Huh?
However, I thought that I didn't think I was the type of guy who can become king.
But... Now that I've fallen in love with you Leti...
Now that you've fallen in love with me...?
I thought about escaping with you from this place...
But can you really run away from this place and all it's people?
I can't, but I don't want to leave you either!
So then...
Your father sure got me good.
I have no other valid options, other than make his dream of retiring to a fisherman come true.
Then Cliff-san-!
Yeah, it seems like I'll have to marry you and become the king.
I'm so happy, Cliff-san!
I wouldn't have dreamed that I would become king.
But ever since I met you,  my feelings towards you have steadily grown,
and I want to protect you forever.
Thank you very much!
But since I'm succeeding the throne, I must become a noble king.
Leti, will you help me in becoming a suitable king?
Yes! Of course!
Leti...
Cliff-san...
Cliff-san, you're being so mean...
If you rub it so firmly, I'll-!
I-I...
Did that feel good?
Yes...
I don't know how I'm supposed to thank you like this...
Just do what feels right.
Just accept your true feelings.
Y-Yes...
N-No, it's too embarrassing! Don't stare at me!
No-!
Leti, you don't need to hold your voice back.
But-!
I'd be happy if you let it out, since that means I'm making you feel good.
Is that so?
Leti, I'm putting it in.
Yes.
Are you okay?
C-Cliff-san...
Leti, we became one.
Yes! You're inside me...
Leti, I'm gonna start moving!
I-It's hitting me so deep!
It feels really good inside you!
Le-Leti-! I love you! I love you!
I-I love you too!
I love you more than anyone, Cliff-san!
Leti-!
I'm going to lose it!
Me too-!
Leti-! I'm cumming!
Y-Yes!
Congratulations.
Now you're the 13th king, the ruler of Synphonia.
I'm sure you know what a king should and shouldn't do.
At least, I know how to retire quickly!
For that, you'll have to make someone to take your place.
Take care of Leti, dear nephew.
You can count on me, dear uncle.
Cliff-san!
Oh, Leti!
It sounded like you were talking about me.
Um, I'll tell you about it sometime.
Geez, you two get along too well.
Really?
A new chapter in this place's history is about to begin.
I've come back.
Welcome back, Silfie!
Welcome back, Fie-sensei!
Welcome back, Silfie-san!
Welcome back, Fie!
I'm home, onii-chan.
Welcome back, Silfie.