In order to reach the realm of magic,
Production Company
TOHO Co., Ltd.
Group Tac
Executive Producer
Sai Haru
a traveler must journey far,
through the Valley of Time.
West of these lands lies a peaceful
kingdom known as the Kingdom of Wisler.
Original Creator
Ko Maisaka
(Red Co.)
Original Character Creator
So Ishida
ASCII Comics
Shueisha Fantasy Books
Director
Yoshihiro Yamaguchi
There, the great and wise ruler, Wisler the 12th,
has begat a most singular heir to the throne,
Princess ♥ Minerva
Ripped by hilander72
Princess Minerva.
Princess!
I really think you should get
a proper instructor and study
before trying to invoke the Ancient Magicks...
Oh, enough with the "study, study, study"
routine, Blue Morris!
I finally managed to borrow this magic
almanac from the treasure warehouse.
Oh, and here I was thinking you stole it.
You're such a worry-wart!
Just pretend we're out on the royal yacht!
That's what worries me the most.
I summon now the noble spirits of Mother Earth!
Imbue my sword with power!
Come, answer my prayers!
Oh yes! Here it comes! Here it comes!
Oh dear Goddess!
Here I go!
Someone stop me!
Oh, my...
An inquisitive young woman,
Minerva has ripened into a
luscious 17 year old beauty.
She is very popular, generous, sweet and...
Cheh!
What a bunch of hogwash!
Agh!
Excuse the hell out of me!
Take it easy, easy...
Hey, Blue Morris!
Yes, ma'am?
I want my own bodyguards!
Bodyguards?
That's right!
To serve as extensions of
my own hands, of my own feet.
I want flunkies who'll do
what I want without question!
Um, what brought this up out of the blue?
Just get to work on it, will you?
Dynastar, must you leave?
You cannot stop me, Master Haggun.
I've already sent Pyrocession, the fire elemental,
and Orche, the wind elemental, ahead to Wisler.
Then you may go once you have defeated me.
Giga Crisis!
Teacher!
That was magnificent, Dynastar.
There is no need for me
to continue as your teacher,
but I shall ask this once more:
Must you go?
Yes sir. My decision is firm.
I see.
Then as a going away gift, let me give you this.
These are...
Magic Net and Flowing Metal.
No ordinary magician could use them,
but I think you shall find a way.
My greatest thanks, revered teacher.
Now go.
Growhill!
You summoned me?
Yes.
I ask you to take care of this place.
Yes, madame.
Nabi is not here?
She's probably out in town, madame.
That's typical for her.
Take care.
Yes, madame.
Arien dahria,
From this formless silver mercury,
Arien ugarna!
Let form be formed.
Wait for me...
Princess Minerva!
Man, that was a close call!
I could have been burned at the stake
if I'd screwed up at all.
Geez, that's what happens when you hear
something you're not supposed to hear.
I'm starving.
Stop, thief!
Give me back my stuff!
Now I wouldn't be much of a thief
if I returned what I stole, you know!
Don't you dare eat my provisions!
I'm starving to death!
Cool your beans, babe,
it's only a couple of bites!
Here!
You little!
Oh crap! Faster! Faster!
What a beautiful time of year this is.
Everything is so lovely. Isn't that right, Tua?
What?
A vendetta over food is the worst kind!
Shut up!
This sounds like a fight.
Fighting is not good.
As a cleric,
I mean, as a former cleric, I must stop this.
All conflicts should be stopped...
Even the most forgiving of goddesses
do not like them.
You little bastard!
I'm
Pissed
You lousy fornicators of toads!
Why the hell did you jerks
have to do something like that?
I'm not a damned piece of furniture!
I'm going to beat the crap out of you!
Stop right now!
Very impressive... Chiloria, Lady Death.
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
I am the greatest swordsman in the west...
and also a connoisseur of beauty.
Surely you must have heard the name
"Linealter, the Silver Rogue" haven't you?
Never heard of it.
You mean you don't know of beautiful me?
Shock
You really don't know me?
Oh well, that's all right.
I'll just go ahead and collect that
500,000 gilder bounty on your head.
I don't have time to play games.
See you later.
I want the fame more than the money.
The fame of being the one
who killed Death herself,
a fame that will last forever!
Leave me alone!
Move it! Move it! Move it!
Wait wait wait!
I don't care what happens if you try to stop me!
Move it! Move it! Move it!
Chiloria, Lady Death! Fight me!
I shall not forgive this!
Ouch...
I've got a bad feeling...
Gimme back my rice ball!
That's top-grade rice from
the East Continent!
I've been dreaming of eating it!
You stomped on my face!
You're dead meat!
You...
You interfered with my duel!
You'll pay for that!
Excuse me everyone!
From magic protectors to fully loaded
magic spells, we carry a full line!
We are Lachloa Business Associates.
If there's something you want,
I also offer immediate delivery.
So, what do you say?
How about you, young man?
Young man?
Now this spear is extremely sharp and strong.
I'm a woman!
Don't talk to me about strength!
How about you, Lady Cleric?
This chain and sickle is imported
from the Eastern Continent.
I don't use weapons.
Damn, and I thought I was
gonna make some real dough here.
Hey, you, thief-boy.
Give me 10,000 gilders and
I'll help you out of this.
I don't have any money right now, but
I'll pay you back later. Please help me!
Sorry. I only deal in cash-on-the-spot.
Well, if all of you are going to fight,
at least wait until a lot people show up...
And then I can charge spectator fees!
Help me!
It's too late to be sorry.
Time to die!
But first both of you must pay
for stomping on my face!
Hey! Didn't you all hear me say
that I was going to fight you?!
Man, my back's literally against the wall.
What a waste!
I'm letting them hear this for free!
Mmm... I like that music!
It's perfect for my stage appearances.
Don't turn it off! Don't turn it off.
Who's that?
Shining stars flash across the dark of night.
These are the eyes of the knight
who fights for love and dreams.
The one who brightens the entire world
with the light of justice!
She is known only as the mysterious unknown
beautiful masked lady knight, Cutey Kamen!
What?!
What the hell?
How wild!
Not many women would use
"beautiful" to describe herself.
Cool!
I will not allow all of you to lynch
one poor weak little boy like this.
I'm not lynching anyone!
No, you're not that bad.
Cutey Kamen, I owe you a big one!
Hey, stop that!
Bad timing.
I look forward to fighting you
some other day. Farewell for now!
Zip, Zounds and Whoosh!
Hey, wait!
The fight's not over yet!
You are all under arrest!
This is all a big mistake.
I certainly didn't do anything!
Let go of me! Ow, that hurts!
I am getting so tired of this Princess.
Princess! Don't you remember
what the King made you promise?
Of course I remember.
But how can you still be grounded
when you're sneaking out
and fighting strangers
in such a scandalous outfit?
Oh, don't worry yourself over it.
I can't wait until that
Martial Arts tournament begins!
Don't tell me you're thinking about
entering the tournament as well?!
Of course.
I bought that "Cutey Kamen" outfit just for it!
Man, I looked good...
Oh my God...
I've got to see what abilities my bodyguard
candidates will have with my own eyes, y'know.
But Princess!
Anyway, I've already taken out ads
in all the newspapers.
Why do you keep doing this?
Especially with your father always
reading the Royal Riot Act to you.
Why, why must you keep doing
things like this to me?
For five long years,
I have struggled to make some change,
any change, in my Princess' selfish behavior...
All this time, watching my Princess
every single minute, but... but...
I don't think I can handle any more of...
What? Were you saying something?
I've never looked forward to anything more than
this year's Martial Arts tourney, Blue Morris.
Lady Fortune must hate me.
I just hope some of those girls
will see my bodyguard ads.
Gotcha!
You know, the penalty for taking
free peeks at my nice body is death.
You're that thief.
I'm not a pervert! I'm not a pervert!
I just followed Cutey Kamen to this place!
Then, since you know the secret of
Cutey Kamen, I can't let you live!
King Wisler... glug! Glub! Assassination... glub!
Let me out! Let me out!
I've done nothing wrong!
The timing of my business dealings
will be destroyed if I don't hurry.
Shut up already.
What?! It's because of the two of you
that I was arrested as well!
This is all your fault!
Yes, and I am deeply grieved for having
involved you, but it was not done on purpose.
I can only pray that our mother Goddess
will see fit to forgive us.
I'm Orlin Carey. Former Cleric.
Former?
I'm currently unemployed
due to personal reasons.
I came to this kingdom after seeing
the ads for Minerva's bodyguards.
I thought it would be something I'd want to join.
So you're going to be in the tournament?
Yes. I shall join the bodyguards
after winning the tournament.
That's not very likely...
Because I'm going to be the winner!
You want to join the bodyguard squad as well?
Not really.
It's just that there's someone I want to fight,
and I heard that she's in the tournament.
And who would that be?
Chiloria, the Lady Death.
What?!
You mean the infamous
bounty hunter, Chiloria Yurisis?
But don't famous bounty hunters
usually avoid tournaments,
because they give away too many
of their secret moves?
I don't want to believe it,
but the rumor is that Chiloria
also wants to join the bodyguards.
Oh well, if that many people are going to
participate, there's no way I could win.
That's not true. You never know until you try!
"You can't do it."
"There's no chance!"
"You've got no ability."
I've been told that by so many people,
but the fact is that I'll only live once, right?
So I choose to challenge and believe in myself!
Everybody's got that right, don't they?
I want to do this thing!
You're right!
I thought you were just another barbarian,
but you've got a little more
going for you than normal.
Lachloa Valvis, professional
businesswoman, at your service.
If there's anything you need,
I'm the one who can get it for you.
Provided you have the money, of course.
Kessley Ulga.
I won't need your services for a bit
since I don't have any money.
We're friends now, is that right?
I'm hungry.
This is Tua, the half-elf.
Half-elf?
I'm sorry, we don't have anything for you.
She's flying!
No no no no no no no!
No no no no no!
I'm sorry.
Keeping you locked up in a
nasty place like this isn't nice.
Here's some milk.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
All of you have been released.
Nice.
The opening ceremonies that have been so
keenly anticipated are finally about to begin.
Look, you know I want to do this really bad!
And you really can't stop me!
But Princess, if you're not in the royal booth,
the King will have my bones for breakfast!
Princess, what are you...
Well, then...
You'll just have to become me, instead.
What?
See? If you wear this, then no one
will be able to tell at all!
Stop fooling around!
One more selfish thing out of you, just one,
and I'll have something to give you!
What? Are you saying that you
don't want to be with me anymore?
Okay, I get your drift!
Go on, do whatever it is you want. I'll be
delighted, not being watched over so carefully.
Princess, do you really mean that?
Oh yes!
You can quit today for all I care!
Just substitute for me this one last time!
I guess I was really hard on her.
Oh well!
Change!
Here comes the mysterious unknown
beautiful masked knight!
Cutey Kamen has arrived!
It has begun.
The opening gambit of my master plan!
There could be a plot to assassinate
King Wisler going on in here!
Everyone looks so suspicious.
Excuse me, Mr. Official, sir?
I have a question to ask.
Huh?
Can you point out Princess Minerva to me?
Are you trying out for her bodyguard too?
Well... I guess.
Then come this way.
That one sitting up there is Princess Minerva.
That's her, huh?
Princess Minerva may look
all sweet and submissive,
but she's actually surprisingly strong.
Well, good luck to both of you.
I've waited for this day for a long time!
That greedy bitch looks pretty suspicious.
You! You're an assassin, aren't you?
What's that, you little Peeping Tom?
You ought to know I don't
show my body for free.
This is your punishment.
I want to do more but I don't have time now
so I'll let you off with only this.
You bitch!
And there's the finishing touch!
From now on, just call me "Queen"!
Please... forgive me, Ms. Queen...
Incredible!
Bondage Mask's big finish is the
"Call Me Queen" move.
She'll be a favorite, for sure!
You're not bad, Bondage Mask...
But I won't forgive you for
being even flashier than me!
And now it's the bounty hunter Chiloria Yurisis,
widely known as Lady Death.
The fans here are all rather intimidated
by the Death's appearance here.
Her opponent is Linealter the Silver Rogue.
You again.
I shall take over the legend!
Taking out a legendary woman like you
will make me famous!
The legend of Chiloria, Lady Death, ends here!
Not bad.
But now it's my turn.
What is Chiloria doing?
I really didn't want to do this in public, but...
Can this be her legendary "Man-eater" move?
The Man-eater... Totally awesome!
It's all over.
I must say, I'm impressed at how you
shook off my Man-eater.
Just kill me, now!
I try to avoid doing things like that.
It's such a waste to kill a man of your skill.
I mean, after all...
I am a woman, and I do like a good-Iooking man.
I don't want your mercy!
Even if you want to be all alone
I will never, ever leave you
I will always be there, right by your side
Singing my song of love, for you
So...
You can do whatever it is that you want to do
Because later on, you'll have no cause for regret
After you've done everything you possibly can
Everything will take care of itself in the end
And the dreams that you wish, you will get!
Yeah!
This one sings?!
Lady Death! Your next opponent is me!
The mysterious unknown beautiful
masked knight, Cutey Kamen, salutes you!
It's another outrageous challenger, folks!
And amazingly enough, this one's
a singing martial artist.
She must have no fear at all if she's going to
directly challenge Chiloria, the Lady Death.
That Cutey Kamen girl looks strangely familiar...
Could it be?
Blue Morris!
What are you doing here?
It's her!
That irritating interloper!
Hey, you! "Unknown beauty something or other"!
That's Cutey Kamen!
Chiloria the Lady Death is supposed to fight me.
No butting in line!
Hey, this is my show!
Kessley has always wanted to fight Chiloria,
it's her dream. Leave this fight to her.
Get lost!
No!
Beat it... or else!
Oh no you won't!
Blue Morris!
Go out there, get Minerva and stop this insanity!
Yes sir!
And this time...
begging forgiveness will not be enough!
Princess Minerva, please behave!
We told you to shut up!
Cutey Kamen is working hard at dodging
former San Anton Temple warrior cleric
Orlin Carey's kicks!
It looks as though even bounty hunter Kessley
Ulga has joined the fight against Cutey Kamen!
You know, that Cutey Kamen's a real fool
to fight all three of them at once.
Cutey Kamen is Princess Minerva!
What?
Princess
Minerva
Winning the
Tournament
Princess
Minerva
Winning the
Tournament
Princess
Minerva
Winning the
Tournament
Princess
Minerva
Winning the
Tournament
Whoa, hold everything!
Cutey Kamen!
I, Bondage Mask, shall back you up!
Princess Minerva, please allow me
to join your bodyguards!
Chiloria! Come on and fight!
Cutey Kamen, is it? How interesting.
Can you take this?
Stop the fight!
Even though I shot you with a low level attack,
I still can't believe you took all of that!
I thought that was you, Princess.
Uh, hi, Teach!
Princess Minerva, there is no need for this.
Princess?!
Cutey Kamen is Princess Minerva?!
I can't breathe!
Your information was completely wrong!
I was the target, not my father!
But you're all right now, right?
Blue Morris...
You can quit today for all I care!
Just substitute for me this one last time!
It's all my fault.
Minerva!
I have sent our forces out
to search for Blue Morris.
As for you, Minerva,
you shall not leave this room!
But...
Someday you will have to rule this land.
I understand your feelings, but have faith.
Do you understand me, Minerva?
Well, leave it all to me.
And I'll tell you just one more time,
don't leave this room!
See you later.
Father... I'm sorry.
K-2, will you do me a favor?
Of course I will, Boss!
Dynastar!
Here's that little thing you ordered!
Minerva...
I've wanted to meet you for a long, long time.
But I must tell you,
I'm very disappointed to find you at this level.
Ouch!
The nice lady who gave me milk is hurting.
Now show me your face...
You?!
Yes, yes!
Princess... Come back quickly! Hurry!
K-2 told us everything!
Let us join your plan to rescue Blue Morris!
She did a lot for us!
Thank you all!
She's over this way!
Miss Chiloria, could you please help my boss?
Pretty please?
Princess Minerva.
She has great eyes.
A unknown magician trying to kill
both Wisler the 12th and his princess...
Sounds intriguing.
All right!
Blue Morris!
Nice lady!
Princess, it's a trap!
Stay away!
One of Dynastar's four magic generals,
Orche the Wind, appears!
I summon the spirits who dwell
in the thundering clouds!
We're not going to like this!
Give me your anger, your savage hate!
Princess!
Are you all right Princess?
I'm okay!
What's that?!
Now Pyrocession, the Fire Elemental, appears!
My salamander will burn you to ashes!
O merciful Goddess, where your light shines,
evil may not remain!
Shield us!
How long can you resist my
blazing salamander attack?!
Princess!
She wouldn't be here if
I hadn't been taken hostage...
My poor Princess...
This is the end!
Princess!
Twin storm!
I can't take it!
You!
It's you!
Chiloria!
I'm here too!
Leave them to me!
You go and get Blue Morris.
Thank you, Chiloria.
Princess!
Go!
I'm sorry it took so long, Blue Morris!
Princess!
Blue Morris!
This is an illusory space,
created by the sorceress Dynastar.
An illusory space?
So, you are the famous Minerva!
I've wanted to meet you.
Thank you for coming to see me.
This is unfair! Show your face!
Who's being unfair?
You've no right to call anything unfair,
not when you're the daughter of
that coward, Wisler the 12th.
I shall teach him in explicit detail
of everything I've suffered through...
But before I do that,
I shall first toy with you!
Princess! Look out!
Blue Morris!
Well, well.
Seems you had one faithful subject, at least.
Blue Morris!
Wake up, please wake up...
I'm sorry, Blue Morris.
This wouldn't have happened
if I had just listened to you.
I was selfish, I broke so many rules...
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry, Blue Morris...
It's not over yet, Minerva.
Blue Morris!
Hurting already?
But I haven't even touched you yet!
I can't...
You are nothing!
The Kingdom of Wisler will soon be mine!
And then, I shall keep you...
as my shoe rack attendant!
It's you!
What are you doing?
What is this light?
Everybody...
You all suffered for my selfishness.
I got you all into this.
It's my responsibility, all mine.
I must...
For Blue Morris's sake!
It can't be.
How can you stand after taking so many hits?
I cannot fall now!
Because the life that is given
is that of Blue Morris!
I summon now the noble spirits of Mother Earth!
Imbue my sword with power!
Come, answer my prayers!
What? You mean you can use
the Ancient Magicks too?
Elemental!
Giga Crisis!
What's happening?
Princess?!
Boss...
Boss?
Boss!
I'm so sorry, Blue Morris,
that we're the ones who are still alive.
I'm sorry...
Blue Morris.
Blue Morris!
Blue Morris, you're still alive!
Tua saved my life.
Good work, Tua!
Oops, she's asleep.
Princess, did you really mean that?
Mean what?
What you said when you said
you'd listen to my words.
But...
I'm so glad you're still alive!
Princess!
Minerva...
I guess she won't have any problems
finding playmates now.
Let's go!
Right!
Minerva and Dynastar...
Look how much happened in
just their first encounter.
Now I have some real entertainment
to look forward to.
Look at you, all sad and sore
You really look awful, rotten and more
I will hold your kiss for you, because
Your grandfather is calling for you
You tried way too hard to reach
The star hanging from that lofty tree
Blue Star Dance, brings you light
I really felt so bad for you
The world is revolving, the way I want it to be
Everybody's flying around like butterflies
I'm a butterfly, metamorphosing, you see
But I'm getting a really bad case of ennui!
Mister Boy! Wipe the tears off your face
You look so very sad
But being so cute is no disgrace
Never surrender! Show off what you have
Stand up for your success!
I will be your Princess!
Boy, it sure is nice and quiet today.
Speaking of quiet...
Just where is Princess Minerva?
Oh, I heard that she went up to the
mountains with her bodyguards.
I hope nothing happens.
I hope so too.
Oh, Princess! Not again!
See you again!