I messed up big yesterday on stage.
I was starting to get out of sync with
everyone during the group dance part...
I ended up causing trouble for everyone...
Our manager scolded me backstage afterwards too...
I am scheduled for a private dance lesson today.
I have to use this chance to improve
and not cause trouble for everyone.
Oh... the dance instructor is here.
Are you here for today's lesson?...
First up is stretching using the bar...
I'll give you a hand... Alright! Let's get started.
I-it hurts...
He's spreading my legs so wide...
Sensei... no... it h-hurts...
My thighs... my thighs hurt...
M-my hips hurt too...
M-my spine... it's going to break...
It hurts so much...
Forgive me already, please...
Your hips are much stiffer than I thought they would be...
We should focus on stretching that out first.
No... I can't... I can't stretch anymore than this...
Stop it please...
I-it hurts...
My hips and thighs hurt so much...
They can't spread any further...
Please stop it already...
It hurts... it hurts... it hurts...!
My thigh is going to dislocate itself...
My hips are going to break...
Heheh... Your hips really are so tight... I'll
loosen them up for you.
No... please stop it...
How is touching there a part of stretching...
No... don't touch my embarrassing spot please...
No... no... no...!
No... don't rub my clitoris...
No... stop it...
I can feel it so much from his hand rubbing my clitoris...
Stop stimulating it please...
Stop targeting that spot...!
Looks like it's gotten softer from my massage...
Next we'll make it even softer with this!
No...
Don't push that against me...
How is this part of a dance lesson...
That's not my hips either...
It's rubbing me...
It's rubbing my pussy...
My clit is going to go crazy...!
No... please...
I can't take anymore...
If he keeps going, my clit really is going to go crazy...
Please...
Let me go already...
Don't target my clit that strongly...
The leotard is rubbing my clit...
It feels so good...
Stop it already...
I'm begging you... please stop...
No...
This is too much for me...!
No... I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...!
Heheh... Looks like your hips are flexible now...
I'll make your entire body and mind softer now!
No...
I don't want this...
Stop it please...
Don't squeeze my nipples...
I'm weak there...
No...
I'm going to go crazy from my
pussy and nipples getting teased...
No... no...
No...!
Don't put in your fingers...
I don't want your fingers inside me...
Take them out...
Don't stir my pussy that much...
He's touching both my pussy
and nipples at the same time...
I'm so weak there...
My tits are going to go crazy if he
keeps touching them over the leotard...
The sensation of the leotard rubbing
against them is too much to handle...
I'm begging you... I'll do whatever
you say so stop going for my tits...
Stop teasing them like that...
Let me go already...
Stop going for my tits...
Anything... is that right?
In that case, open wide!
No...
All I did was come here for a dance lesson...
So why is something this horrible happening to me...
He's raping my mouth...
No...
It feels so disgusting inside my mouth...
Just let me go already...
You're pretty good at this, aren't you?... I'm gonna cum
so swallow it all! I won't let you go if you spit it out!
My throat is getting fucked right now...
I can't breathe...
His dick is getting hotter and hotter...!
Don't cum inside my mouth!
I'm going to make you my woman so prepare yourself!
No... don't put it in...
I'm getting raped...
He's raping me right now...
No... no... no...
Don't rape me...
I-it hurts...
It's going to break... my pussy is going to break...
Please take it out...
My pussy is going to go crazy...
No...
Don't go in so deep...
Deep... it's hitting me in so deep...
It's painful...
No...
Don't fuck me so hard...
It's hitting me all the way inside...
No...
Don't rape my womb...
I'm begging you... just let me go already...
Don't fuck me so roughly...
Please, please, I'm begging you. Don't cum inside!
If you cum inside, I'm going to get pregnant...
There's no way I want to get
pregnant from getting raped...
It's cumming...
All of it is going inside me...
I'm going to get burned inside...
No... I'm going to cum from getting creampied...
I'm cumming...!
C-cumming...!
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Fogil
softsub, retiming: торрент иваниваныч