Good Morning
Morning
G-Good morning. For today's news
w-we'll bring you updates about the enacted
"Rape Legalization" law from several days ago.
I-I can't do this again today!
I can't read this... I can't keep reading anymore!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
To everyone who watches nationwide, I'm sorry!
I'm coming from being raped!
Rape Gouhouka
Rape Legalization
We Are Happy... Master!
Rape legalization.
I-I'm begging you...
Kana
Please let me go already!
If you'll keep on harassing me...
No! Don't!
Don't do that! My milk is coming out!
Th-This is embarrassing!
I don't want to feel good from this,
b-but my nipples are getting numb.
No—!
Ma'am, you should start talking
if you want to save yourself.
I'm talking about the secret behind the
organization against rape legalization.
You know it, right?
I can't! Telling you that is the last thing I'll do!
No, I can't!
Stop! Please stop this!
Then, it can't be helped.
I have no choice but to ask your body.
W-Wait, no way...
That's what this is, my cock...
...will go inside you!
Wow! You're sucking my dick inside you!
Ma'am, you actually wanted me
to do this to you, didn't you?
Y-You're wrong!
P-Please pull it out!
Pull it out already!
Isn't your husband far away and neglecting you?
Not using a terrific rare contraption
such as this pussy is a crime!
No, stop saying that!
Oh... I'm getting raped.
I'm being violated by a dick
that doesn't belong to him!
F-Forgive me, darling!
Ma'am, if you can endure this
without having an orgasm,
I'll let you off the hook for today.
But if you'll end up coming, then...
I-I won't come! I absolutely won't come!
Coming from another man's dick
is the only thing I mustn't do...
P-Please, hurry up...
Hurry up and make an end of this!
No! No way...
Don't do it that hard!
A-Any more than this and...
No way... Stop!
Stop—!
Hey, look at this! Your pussy is sucking me inside!
Aren't you about to come, ma'am?
W-Why? Even though I'm being treated violently
and he's doing it against my will...
M-My body is gradually getting hotter...
Something like this is nothing short of madness!
Don't!
Stop squeezing my milk out anymore!
I'll go crazy!
Come on, apologize!
Say that you're having sex with another man!
Tell your husband properly
to please forgive you!
Darling... Darling...
I'm sorry, I can't take it anymore!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
Forgive me!
I-I'm coming, I'm coming...
Alright, just as you promised.
Shall we have you spill the beans
about that secret, ma'am?
I-I'm sorry...
Darling, I was not good enough...
So you're the leader of the opposition,
Assistant Inspector Asamiya.
Asamiya Saki
You bastard...
Even as a joke, for a police
officer to be doing such...
What the hell are you planning to do?!
You...
You're conspiring together to repeal
the rape legalization, right?
You snoop stuff and use those to
blackmail the upper-level guys.
Of course I would!
I'll make that outrageous law repealed
as soon as possible for the sake
of all women nationwide!
That would be a problem.
Just when we're having the times of our lives...
We'd prefer you not doing
something unnecessary...
Is that the reason why my little sister...
why you abducted Miyuki?
Yes, that's right!
If you want your little sister back, well...
You already know even if
I don't spell it out, right?
I understand.
You can do whatever you want on me.
However, don't lay your
hands on my little sister!
You have quite a nice body,
Assistant Inspector Asamiya.
It looks so beautiful!
S-Stop saying unnecessary stuff!
Get it over with this already!
Wh-What is that?
You scoundrels...
What the hell are you trying to do?
It's an aphrodisiac,
so that even a straight-laced woman
like you would be able to enjoy this.
D-Damn it! These people...
I'm letting these people do
as they wish on my body...
Miyuki...
My dear little sister...
The reason that I'm able to give my best
is because I have you smiling next to me.
I-I'll overcome this...
It doesn't matter how much I get
humiliated and disgraced...
I'm... I'm going to protect Miyuki without fail!
Alright, then.
It's about time for the drug to kick in.
Wh-What's with this stimulus?
I-It's like all of the nerves in my
whole body went haywire!
I-I've become highly sensitive!
How is it? You can't take it anymore, right?
You're feeling good, right?
Stop messing around!
I-I... I'm...
Never... Not from just something like this!
N-Nee-san...
Miyuki?
Saki-neesan!
Is that you, Miyuki? Where are you?
Answer me, M-Miyuki...
Saki-neesan! Look, look at me!
Look at me!
You see, I never had any idea about it before!
Sex feels so good, am I right?
It feels like both of my head
and pussy are about to melt!
Look at that! Isn't that great, assistant inspector?
Miyuki
It seems that your little sister is enjoying it.
N-Nee-san...
It's hot... This cock is hot!
Look, my pussy already got this sloppy!
It's already squishy...
I'm in heaven right now!
Miyuki... Miyuki, Miyuki!
It went in! I shoved it inside
Assistant Inspector Asamiya's pussy!
My cock is going in and out
and making squelching sounds!
Miyuki! Forgive me!
I've... I've always been away from you...
Miyuki, forgive me!
Miyuki—!
Nee-san, why are you apologizing?
I've never been even a bit sad!
Th-That's, that's because...
Saki-neesan, haven't you always been
overworking yourself for my sake?
Miyuki!
But now you don't have to
work so hard for that anymore.
Let's both feel good from cocks together!
Let's be happy together!
Stop... Stop, Miyuki!
Don't say that I don't have
to work so hard anymore!
Miyuki, you're the one who
gives me emotional support!
If you tell me something like that...
I'll... I'll be...
We're far from done, assistant inspector.
Please don't get yourself
worn out with just this much.
This much is still nothing!
I-I can't take it anymore!
I have no one else to support me anymore!
I'm being taken over by carnal pleasure!
B-Both my body and my heart
are being taken over!
Nee-san, I'm coming again!
I'm about to come again!
Please, let's do it together!
Come together with me!
Let's come with our pussies!
No, I can't do that!
I can't—!
I-It can't stop it!
Stop that!
I'm coming... I'm coming...
I'm coming—!
Both of you, get along together
and get knocked up!
I'm coming—!
8 Months Later
Master!
No way, if you do it that much...
I'm already gonna...
It's coming out! A lot of milk is coming out!
My tits feel incredible!
The stimulus is too strong!
Wow...
Just from watching, my body is subconsciously...
My tits are tingling...
I'm throbbing down here as well!
Why...
Why did I end up having such a lewd body?
I'll settle for anything!
I can't hold myself back!
C-Cock...
I want my master's cock!
Do it, hurry!
What's this?
Did all of you get aroused
just from watching us?
Even when you're all soon-to-be mothers...
Aren't you all perverts
beyond any help, my brides?
With the help of rape legalization law,
polygyny became legal in this country.
With more than enough childbirth
and child-rearing aid funding,
everyone is able to give birth without any worries.
Just like that, my long dream of getting a bride
came true and I got a lot of them!
God is impartial.
No matter how strong or clever a woman can be,
she'll end up the same as everyone else
when her human instincts are
drawn out, just a mere slut.
Madoka-senpai is so lewd!
She's making the face of a slut.
Hikaru is licking his
dick like it's so delicious!
I'm sure... I'm sure about it!
She wanted his cock that she can't
hold herself back anymore!
I-It's because I'm pregnant that my insides...
My pussy became so sensitive inside!
I-It feels good, it feels good!
My new husband is so amazing!
Coming, I'm coming! I'm coming again!
I'm coming!
S-Stop... Please stop it already!
No!
No, master—!
Good... That's good!
It feels good!
My hips won't stop!
Cock... Give me more of your cock!
More, more, more...
More—!
I-I can't take it anymore!
To think that being forced...
That being raped feels this good...
I'm glad to be born as a slut!
Rape... Rape legalization...
...is the best—!
Master... Amazing... You're amazing!
Your cock is sliding in an out of me!
I'm gonna go crazy as well...
Shoot it out! Shoot it all out!
Cover me with your semen!
M-Master...
Thank you very much
for raping me back then!
I-I'm coming...
I'm coming already! I'm coming already!
I'm gonna come!
The men stopped being courteous
and reverted into mere studs.
The women threw their pride away and reverted into mere sluts.
But that is the epitome of happiness.
Isn't that right, everyone?
Y-Yes!
We are happy!
Master!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization