Special News Program
We are going to have a special news program now.
E-Effective starting today,
rape with an aim of procreation
Akino Yuri
has been enacted as a provisional law.
R-Rape is only allowed on women
that are capable of bearing a child.
P-Please bear that in mind.
G-Girls who haven't had their periods yet,
women who already reached menopause
and women who are still pregnant
are all exempted from getting raped.
Th-They are to be issued with verification...
No... Stop... Stop!
R-Run!
All of you women, please run away!
J-Just as you can see,
this nation has turned mad!
Hurry up and get away from
this country as soon as possible!
What are you talking about, Yuri-chan?
You fail as a news anchor.
No! No!
No more... I'm not doing this anymore!
This is crazy! Something like this is plain madness!
Rape Gouhouka
Rape Legalization
Banging Spree Anytime And Anywhere!!
Rape legalization.
S-Stop... Please stop!
Tied Hair
What molester are you talking about, miss?
This is rape. Rape has been legalized!
Here you go!
That can't be! No way...
Please, somebody...
Somebody help me!
You're so tight!
This is the best!
I get to pound in this young pussy!
No...
Y-You'll tear me up!
I'm going to be torn apart!
It's your own fault that I'm breaking you apart!
No way...
Th-That's cruel... You're so cruel!
E-Even though it's my first time...
Shut up! Rape isn't a crime! It has been legalized!
Here, I'm gonna come! I'll come inside you!
No! Stop!
A-Anything but that!
I'm begging you, don't come!
Not inside me!
Shutting yourselves inside
your house is useless!
That's because rape has been declared
legal at a national level anyway!
Mother
P-Please spare me already!
M-Mom!
Kasumi
No!
No—!
I-I'm begging you.
I don't care no matter what you do to me!
So stop doing any more
cruel things to my daughter.
Don't go any further!
Idiot.
There's no way I'll stop after coming this far!
No!
Stop! Let me go already!
I-If you keep being reckless on me...
Ouch! It hurts!
Kasumi, I'm sorry.
Forgive me for not being
able to save you. I'm sorry!
You say that but you actually are feeling good, right?
Your pussy is already sopping wet.
You're wrong, this is...
That's because you keep going on doing me...
Over and over...
No!
Alright!
We'll wrap this up with making both
of you mother and daughter come!
N-No... No, stop!
I-I can't take it anymore!
Coming, coming... It's coming!
No—!
No! Pull it out, it feels gross!
Karin
[Line Head Count: 56 people]
This is disgusting! I quit!
I'm quitting as an idol!
Why... Why?
Even though everyone is
always so kind up to yesterday!
You were all cheering a lot for both of us!
Stop! Any more than this and...
It feels good, it feels good!
This is Karin-chan's pussy
that I even dream about!
Everyone was so horny as we all
watched your live performance!
We all love you so much!
Rena
Everyone had thoughts of banging
and messing you up, you know!
Rena
S-Somebody... Somebody help us!
Manager, where are you?!
H-Help us!
F-Forgive me, Karin-chan! But if you keep
squeezing me that much...
I'm gonna come already! It's coming out!
No, no no! Stop!
I'll get pregnant!
Please don't come!
You can't, you can't, you can't!
You can't!
Rena-chan, instead of shaking your hands
we're gonna pour our sperm inside you today!
[Line Head Count: 157 people]
N-No way, if hundreds of you come inside me...
I-I'll definitely get pregnant—
[Line Head Count: 257 people]
No, no, no...
No—!
Hikaru
Madoka
Hey there, old man. Aren't you a police?
Huh?
Look at this perverted guy!
You have to arrest him.
What happened to him? Isn't he all beaten up?
This idiot suddenly jumped on Madoka-senpai!
He was spouting nonsense about rape being alright.
Uh-huh... I see.
Dammit, this idiot was looking
for someone to copulate with!
Of course, he's gonna get beaten up! Here you go!
Hikaru, that's enough.
Umm, in short...
you are the ones who have
beaten this guy up, right?
That's right...
Then you're both under arrest.
Huh?
Huh?!
That's normally called an "assault".
What the hell are you saying,
you shitty patrolman?!
Were you even listening? We told you that
this pervert suddenly jumped on us!
Isn't it considered self-defense?
You're being a nuisance.
I get it now, you're doing that.
"Obstruction of Justice".
What?!
Oh yeah. By the way, that supposedly
perverted man is innocent.
Huh?!
How about it, do you understand
the whole situation now?
Y-You're messing around! What the hell
is that "Rape Legalization" about?!
Uncuff us already, you perverted
delusional scoundrel!
Do you think that you can just get away
from doing something like this?
Your words hold no weight when you look like that.
That size of bra doesn't
fit you in the first place.
Your areolae are jutting out!
What—
Th-This guy...
Shit...
Don't touch me!
Stop! Don't put your hands on Hikaru!
Is this embarrassing for you as expected?
A-Are you stupid?! From an old man like you?
I don't have any particular thoughts from this!
Well, isn't that right?
S-Stop...
Pull your finger out!
S-Stop stirring me up inside!
Hikaru...
Aren't you both fooling around? Of course
you aren't virgins anymore, right?
I-Isn't that obvious? Stop saying
gross stuff like still being a virgin!
The only virgins at my age
are all fugly bitches!
N-No way...
Wh-What is this?
His cock is too big!
You're so tight despite being a slut!
It's usable, your slutty pussy is usable.
Shit, you dumb-ass...
I don't feel good from your cock...
...from a cock of someone like you, you hear me?
Alright...
I'm gonna give you a creampie
as a special service!
My womb... My womb!
You're poking on it with every thrust!
No, th-this is too much!
The stimulus feels so great...
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming!
You're making me come by force!
Huh... It's pouring in...
There's a lot gushing inside me...
Hey, you there!
I haven't done anything on you yet.
What are you hoping for?
But you surely have huge mounds.
Are you really a student?
Stop, that's disgusting!
Don't touch me with those filthy hands!
What's this?
It feels like electricity flows from where he's licking me!
It's zapping me... The numbness
that I feel is spreading on me!
Her nipple got stiff.
You are sensitive here.
Wh-Who the hell is...
S-Shit!
I can't let my voice out!
I'll just amuse this man whenever
I react on what he's doing!
I can't show such a shameful state
to Hikaru who looks up on me!
H-How long are you gonna—
He's too persistent!
M-My nipple feels tingly and hot!
I'm feeling strange... I'm feeling strange!
I-If this goes on, I'm...
Already...
Did you see that, miss cat ears?
She's is a perverted masochist that
comes just from her tits being teased.
Th-this can't be real...
Madoka-senpai...
S-Stop!
Not that, anything but that!
So that was it, I finally understand.
You really are a virgin, right?
No—!
You're so tight! It feels like you're
chomping me off down here!
Stop moving!
I'll die! I'll die, I'm gonna die!
It feels hot like I'm getting stabbed down there!
Am I being raped for real?!
H-Huh? Why is this happening?
Why does my first time have to be with this old man?!
Aren't you making such good moans?
That's good, Madoka. Shake
your butt even harder!
No! Stop!
Just how far are you going to humiliate me?!
Stop... Stop, stop!
Stop spanking me, no!
Your pussy tightens whenever I spank you.
I knew it, you really are a masochist!
Y-You shit!
This shit! This man does anything he wants to me!
I don't want to feel good! Even when
I shouldn't feel anything from this...
Madoka-senpai, what are you doing?
You're feeling good when he's raping you...
Aren't you nothing but an indecent woman now?
I'm feeling it... He's making me feel good!
Come on, Madoka! It's about
time to make you come!
No... Stop... Stop this already!
Stop doing this!
To climax from being raped...
No way... Something like that...
I absolutely can't do that!
I'll pour plenty of my baby seeds inside you.
Make sure to get yourself knocked up!
You can't... You can't!
Not inside me, I'm begging you!
Don't come!
No—!
Th-This is too cruel...
Wow, I can't believe this!
S-Spare us already...
Rape has actually been legalized! Alright...
Now that things turned out like this,
I'm gonna do it as much as I want!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization