Special News Program Broadcast
Welcome to today's special news program broadcast.
A-As of today, a law has been passed
that permits rape for the sake of procreation.
Akino
Yuri
H-However, you may only rape
women old enough to bear a child.
P-Please exercise caution.
Any girl that has yet to have her period
or women who have entered menopause...
Also, women who are already pregnant...
The three aforementioned types
of women are excluded from the law.
You will need to have a badge created...
St-St-Stop!
R-Run!
Please, if you're a girl, run!
As you can see, this country has lost its mind!
Please, hurry and escape from this country!
What do you think you're saying, Yuri-chan?
You can't bring personal bias into a news story.
No!
I don't want this! Stop!
Please stop!
Yesterday's Traffic Accidents
Deaths    0
Injuries   3
Stop Fraud!
RAPE has been LEGALIZED!!!
Rape has been legalized.
Act. 1 Get Raped Whenever, Wherever!!
No! Stop!
Curly
Hair
Please stop!
It's just coppin' a feel. Nothin' serious, girly.
But hey, rape's been legalized!
Take this!
No! No, please!
Somebody... Somebody save me!
Holy shit, you're tight!
You're the best!
Can't believe I get to fuck a young'n like you!
No!
I'm gonna break! You're gonna break me!
I'm gonna give it to ya good!
Gonna give it right, straight to you!
N-No, please!
I don't want this!
Th-This is my first time!
Shut up!
Rape isn't a felony!
It's legal!
Get ready, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum inside you!
No! Stop!
A-Anything but that!
Don't!
Please, don't cum!
Please not inside me!
Hiding inside your house isn't going to work.
This country's legalized rape after all.
Mother
P-Please stop! Please!
M-Mom!
Kasumi
No!
Y-You can do anything you want to me,
but please leave my daughter out of this!
You dumb broad. You think I can stop after going this far?
No! Stop!
Please let me go!
D-Don't be so rough!
It hurts! It really hurts!
Kasumi, I'm sorry!
I can't help you!
I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
You say that, but you're getting really turned on, aren't you?
It's like a river down here.
It's not what you think! This is...
But if this keeps up...
Over and over and over...
No!
All right, let's get both the mom and daughter cumming!
No! No! Stop!
I-I can't take anymore!
I-It's coming! I'm gonna cum!
No!
No! Take it out!
Karin
It's gross!
People until the end of the line
This is gross! Stop!
I'm going to stop being an idol!
Why is this happening?!
Everyone was so nice yesterday!
They were all cheering for us so hard yesterday!
Stop! I can't take any more!
It feels so good! It feels so good!
This is Karin-chan's pussy! I've dreamed of it so much!
I was always horny whenever I watched you, Rena-chan!
I just like you too much, Rena-chan!
Everyone wanted to fuck you so badly!
Rena
Somebody... Somebody save us!
Manager! Where'd you go?!
Save us!
Sorry, Karin-chan, but if you tighten up so much...
No!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
No! No! No! Stop!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Please don't cum!
No! No! No!
No!
Rena-chan, everyone here's gonna pour their semen
into you instead of giving you a handshake today!
People until the end of the line
N-No, if that many people cum inside me...
I'm definitely going to get pregnant!
No! No! No! No!
Hikari
Madoka
Hey, you. You're a police officer, right?
Huh?
See this pervert here?
Arrest him already.
What's with him?
He's all beat up.
This idiot tried to jump onto Madoka-senpai.
Everything's been a mess ever since they OK'd rape.
Hm... I see.
For fuck's sake.
These perverts think they can just jump anyone?
Of course he's gonna get beat up.
Take that!
Hikari, leave it at that.
So basically you two are the ones
who beat this man up, right?
Yeah, so?
Then I'm gonna have to arrest you two.
Huh?!
You've just assaulted someone. It's a crime.
What the fuck, you dumbass cop?!
Those ears for show?!
We said that this pervert jumped onto us!
This was self-defense!
You're a loud one.
Hm, I'm now arresting you for obstruction of justice.
Wha...
Yeah, you see, that "pervert" is innocent.
– Huh?!                                      – Huh?!
So? See how things stand now? Hm?
F-Fuck you!
To hell with legalized rape!
Take these goddamn handcuffs off, you fantasizing pervert!
You really think you'll get away with this?
You don't seem very threatening looking like that.
Do you even realize that your bra's not the right size?
Your areola's poking out.
Wha...
You...
Shit...
Don't touch me!
Stop! Don't touch her!
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Y-You stupid or something?
An old fart like you doesn't make me feel shit!
Yeah, that makes sense.
S-Stop!
Take your fingers out!
Don't move them around!
Hikari...
You guys gotta be fooling around a lot.
I bet neither of you are virgins.
Of course! Don't use gross words like "virgin"!
Only ugly girls are virgins!
No way...
Wh-What's with this guy's dick?! It's too big!
You're really tight for a slut!
I can really get off on your slutty pussy!
Fuck! Fuck you!
I... I won't get off from your shitty dick!
All right, I'm gonna do something special.
I'm gonna make you cum from my cum.
My mind's going blank!
He's thrusting it in me so hard!
Th-This is too much stimulation!
I-I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I-I'm gonna cum from this guy's thing!
I-It's coming!
I-It's pumping out inside of me!
Hey, you.
Why are you getting so hot
when I haven't even touched you yet?
These tits are huge.
Are you really a student?
S-Stop! You're disgusting!
Don't touch me with those filthy hands!
Wh-What's going on?!
It's like electricity's running through my body!
Your nipple's gotten so hard.
You're quite sensitive.
I-I'm not!
Shit! I gotta keep it in!
I can't let any emotion out! It'll just make him happy!
I can't let him see even a little of my indecent self!
How long...
H-He's too persistent!
M-My nipple's getting hotter!
I-I'm losing it! I feel strange!
I-If this keeps going, I'm gonna...
Hey, cat ears. You got a good look?
She's a perverted masochist who came with just her tits.
No way... Madoka-senpai...
No! Stop! A-Anything but that!
Oh, I get it.
You're actually a virgin, aren't you?
No!
Holy shit, you're tight!
I feel like my dick's gonna get ripped off!
Stop moving!
I-I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
It feels like I'm getting stabbed by a hot poker!
I'm really getting raped!
Why?!
Why is my first time like this?!
You have some sweet moans.
That's good, Madoka. Shake your ass more!
Stop! How much more embarrassment are you going to...
No! Stop! Stop!
I can't take anymore! No!
Your pussy gets tighter with each slap.
You're the real deal! A real masochist!
Shit! Shit!
I don't want to feel good from this man!
I don't want to! I can't let myself, but I...
Madoka-senpai, what are you doing?
Why are you feeling good from
being raped by a guy like that?
That... That just makes you a slut!
I-I feel good! I feel so good!
Okay, Madoka, I'm gonna make you cum!
Stop!
Stop already!
Please stop!
I don't want to cum from being raped!
I-I don't want that at all!
I'm gonna pump you full of my seed!
I'm going to knock you up!
No! No!
Not inside!
Please! Don't do it!
No!
Th-This is too horrible.
Holy shit. I can't believe this!
P-Please stop...
Rape really has been legalized.
Hell yeah! I'm gonna fuck until I'm dead!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshasow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч