Good morning
Good morning.
Here is today's news.
Today marks another day since
the legalization of rape was passed...
No! I can't! I can't read that!
I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm so sorry, everyone!
I'm going to cum from being raped!
RAPE has been LEGALIZED!!!
Rape has been legalized.
act. 2 We're So Happy... Master
Please, I beg you! Please let me go!
Kana
If you keep playing with me like this, I...
No!
No! My milk's coming out!
This is so embarrassing!
I don't want to feel good from this,
but my nipples are tingling!
No!
Ma'am, if you want to be let off the hook,
how about you start talking?
What's the name of the secret organization
that opposed the rape law?
You know, don't you?
I can't tell you! I'll tell you anything but that!
I can't! I can't!
Stop!
Please stop!
You leave me with no choice. I'll have to ask your body.
Wait, don't!
I'm gonna take my thing... my dick, and put it in you!
Holy shit, it's sucking my dick in!
You wanted me to do this, didn't you?
N-No!
Please take it out!
Haven't done it with your husband in a while, have you?
It's gotta be a crime not to fuck something as sexy as you!
No, don't talk like that!
Oh, I'm getting raped.
I'm being raped!
I'm getting penetrated by a man who isn't my husband!
F-Forgive me, dear!
Here's the deal. If you don't cum, I'll let you off the hook.
But if you cum...
I won't! I definitely won't cum!
There's no way I can let myself
cum from another man's dick!
Please! Hurry up and finish!
No! Don't do it so rough!
I-If this keeps up, I... Stop!
Stop!
Oh, look! You're gripping me real hard!
You're about to cum, aren't you, ma'am?
Why?! He's being so rough! He's doing this against my will!
My body's getting hotter and hotter.
How can I stay sane like this?!
No! Stop!
Don't milk me!
You're making me feel messed up!
Apologize! You're having sex
with a guy other than your husband.
Come on. Apologize to your husband!
Dear! Dear!
I'm sorry! I can't hold on anymore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm sorry! I'm cumming!
All right, we had a deal.
Time for you to come clean with all your secrets.
I'm so sorry.
Dear. I couldn't do it...
So you're the leader of the opposition, officer Asamiya?
Asamiya Saki
You bastard.
You might be a police officer,
but what the hell do you think you're doing?!
You're trying to get the rape law repealed, aren't you?
I know you're trying to blackmail the people at the top.
Of course I am!
I have to get this ridiculous law repealed
for the sake of all the women in this country!
Well, this is a problem.
We're all having fun here.
I'd rather you just let things be.
That's why you went after my little sister?!
That's why you kidnapped Miyuki?!
That's right.
If you want your little sister back, well,
you know what you have to do, don't you?
Fine.
Do whatever you want to me.
But leave my sister out of this!
You've got a nice body, officer Asamiya.
You're very beautiful.
K-Keep that to yourself!
Just get this over with already!
Wh-What did you just...
What are you doing?!
It's an aphrodisiac.
Thought it'd help you loosen up a little.
Shit! These bastards are really going
to have their way with my body!
Miyuki...
My precious little sister.
I've only been able to come this far because
you've been right there next to me, smiling.
I need to endure!
No matter what humiliation they put me through!
Whatever they do,
I have to make sure that Miyuki... that she...
That I protect her!
All right. I think the drug should
be kicking in right about now.
Wh-What is this sensation?
It feels like every nerve across my body is being touched.
I'm getting too sensitive!
So? I bet you can't resist anymore.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Screw you!
I-I...
This isn't enough to break me!
N-Nee-san...
Miyuki?
Saki-neesan!
Miyuki? Where are you?
Answer me! M-Miyuki?
Saki-neesama, look!
Look!
Look at me!
I had no idea!
Sex feels really good!
My mind and pussy feel like they're gonna melt!
Feel better, officer?
Miyuki
Your little sister seems to be having the time of her life.
N-Nee-san, it's so hot...
Dicks are so hot...
Look! My pussy's so wet!
It's practically gushing!
I'm so happy!
Miyuki! Miyuki!
I did it! I put it in!
I'm inside officer Asamiya's pussy!
My dick's goin' in and out of her!
Miyuki! I'm sorry!
I-If I could have protected you better...
I'm sorry, Miyuki!
Why are you apologizing, nee-san?
I'm not sad at all.
N-No, that can't be! You're being...
Nee-san, I know how much you've held back for my sake.
Miyuki!
But you don't have to hold back for my sake anymore.
Just let yourself feel good from the dicks,
and let's be happy together!
Stop! Please stop!
Miyuki!
Don't tell me that I don't hold back for you anymore!
You're my pillar of support!
If you take that away, I...
I... I... I'm gonna...
We're not done yet, officer.
Don't break down just from that.
We've still got a long way to go.
S-Stop!
I have nothing left.
I'm going to lose myself!
I'm going to drown in pleasure!
Both my body and soul are going to drown!
Nee-sama, I'm about to cum again!
I'm gonna cum!
Please! Cum with me!
No! No! No!
It's not stopping!
Stop moving!
I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
You two get happily pregnant together!
8 months later
Master! You're being so rough!
I-I'm gonna...
It's gonna come out!
I'm gonna squirt so much milk!
My boobs feel so good!
They feel too good!
Wow... Just looking at them makes my body get so hot!
My boobs are tingling.
My pussy's starting to throb.
How... How did my body end up being so indecent?
I...
I don't care anymore.
I can't wait any longer!
I want it... I want Master's dick!
I want it! Hurry!
What? You all got turned on just by watching?
You're all gonna be mothers soon,
but you're all irredeemable perverts, huh, my wives?
With the legalization of rape,
polygamy has blossomed in this country.
There's plenty of benefits and subsidies for child rearing,
so now everyone can have a child without worry.
I always wanted a wife,
but now I suddenly got multiple wives!
God made everyone equal.
No matter how strong-willed or smart a woman is,
they're all the same on the inside.
They were all made to be dirty whores!
Madoka-senpai, you're so dirty.
You look so dirty like that.
Wow, Hikari, you're licking it like it tastes delicious.
I... I bet you want his dick so bad that it hurts!
Ever since I got pregnant, my pussy's been so sensitive!
It feels so good!
My new husband is amazing!
I-I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum again!
I'm cumming!
P-Please stop!
Stop, Master!
So... So good!
It feels so good!
I can't stop moving my hips!
I-I want your dick!
More! More! More!
I-I can't hold on any longer!
I can't believe I feel so good from someone
forcing themselves on me... from being raped!
I'm so glad I was born a woman!
L-Legalized rape is the best!
Master, I love you! I love you!
Your dick's too good, Master!
I think I'm gonna lose my mind!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
Spray me with your cum!
M-Master!
Thank you for raping me back then!
I-I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
Guys threw away being the nice guy
and went back to being just males.
Women threw away their pride
and went back to being just females.
But that's where true happiness was.
Isn't that right, everyone?
Y-Yes.
We're so happy.
Master...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч