This is the end!
Phantasm Blade!
Here's no other way.
If I'm gonna find Hikari-chan,
I gotta take Yulang down
and get the Ghost Buster Sword.
Indomitable blades.
Magic so bright and brilliant
that it disperses shrouds of mystery.
At the spur of a certain incident that occurred
in this country, history has begun to write itself.
The warriors from the Kingdom of Leazus in the Eastern
Continent were praised as the mightiest in the world.
The Quest For Hikari
Episode 3     Cut Rance
Damn that special move of hers.
How the hell am I supposed to
defend against that?
Do you use a shield?
If you use the correct type of shield,
you'll be able to completely nullify your opponent's attack.
She's fast enough that blocking the attack
with a shield would be too slow.
I see...
In that case, it all comes down to luck.
If you're real lucky, you'll be able to
dodge her attacks without breaking a sweat.
There's no way I can just
leave it all up to luck.
I need a more tangible winning strategy.
Here ya go.
Hey man, you got any bright ideas?
No ideas, but I got alcohol.
What the hell?
Rance-san, you're going up against
the champion, Yulang-san, right?
Yeah, it's gonna be a piece of cake.
The likes of you will never
be able to beat Yulang.
Oh dear, hush.
The words of a loser like you mean nothing.
Say that again!
Don't fight! Please, don't fight!
The city guard?
Oh, Rance! Hey!
Who the hell are you?
Oh, it's me, Ninja Master.
Thanks for the good match the other day.
Wait, the flashy guy I fought against?
You're like a different person!
Being in the Colosseum is an honor, so I had to
show off a bit. Normally, this is how I am as a guard.
You can easily change your personality
with this magic scroll.
Here, take one.
Yourou Personality Change Scroll?
The finals are just around the corner.
The match between Rance-san
and Yulang-san should be pretty exciting.
How about we all think of something
to make sure that it's one to remember?
Not happening. It's gonna be over
before you can blink.
Indeed.
Her sword techniques are invincible!
That's nice to know.
Hey, can I get some California rolls?
Coming right up!
If I can't dodge her special technique,
maybe I could grease up her sword
or something so that it just slides off of me.
Yeah, that's it!
What?
That's right, maybe you could use Patty's hair
grow formula like he does, and make it all slippery.
A magnificent idea!
What are you saying?!
My hair grows just fine on its own!
You wanna fight?!
God, this is stupid.
Rance-sama!
Oh, aren't you a cute one?
Sorry, but I'm a little busy right now.
Rance-sama!
Seriously, you're one thirsty girl.
Are you one of my fans? I'll try to remember you.
Sill
Rance-sama!
Shut up, Sill!
When I call you, come immediately!
My apologies. I was in the middle
of swimming class.
An attack you can't dodge?
Let me think about that...
It's been a while.
Let me satisfy myself with your body!
Oh, I got it! If you can't dodge it,
how about you oil yourself up so it slides off of you?
Dumbass!
You really think I'd win by using the same fucking
ridiculous idea those other dumbasses gave me?!
You damn useless slave!
I'm gonna punish you!
What's that?
Today, we'll switch things up a bit and change
your personality into a slutty one with this scroll.
Then you'll take your time servicing
me to my heart's content.
U-Um, what do you mean by that?
So bright!
How 'bout it?
Feeling a bit more aggressive, Sill?
Hey, where the hell do
you think you're touching?!
Isn't it obvious? I'm touching
the thing you always make me suck on.
You're already twitching like a little schoolboy.
You really are incorrigible.
Urn, you're not exactly what I expected.
Is it just me or are you
even harder than usual?
You bitch, do you know what you're doing?!
Of course.
I know everything about you, Rance-sama.
I know that you're always so eager to cum.
Your mind is always filled with the thought of it,
and you can never get the sensation out of your head.
Get off of me...
Don't worry, I'll help you cum
until this baby is empty.
Look at it go.
Just keep cumming like this.
Sill... you bitch!
Aren't you getting a bit bigger than usual?
Maybe it's become a bad habit,
but now I feel like I have to suck it.
Hey, I told you to be more
aggressive, but not like this!
Like this...
It's coming! Rance-sama's cum
is going down my throat!
I can feel it flooding into my stomach!
I want to drink more! I want it in my pussy too!
Hey, Sill!
Can you see just how much my
pussy wants your cock inside it?
It's part of my duty as your slave
to satisfy your sexual needs
so that you don't become
some kind of sex offender.
Also, I don't mind having sex with you even
if you're not raping me... Rance-sama.
What are you say...
It's coming in! It's inside me!
Your cock is like a wild animal!
How many girls have you made cry
with this, Rance-sama?
Oh wow, you really like boobs,
don't you, Rance-sama?
It feels so good!
Oh my god, it's going so deep
and hitting me in the right spots!
I can feel your hot semen pumping into my pussy!
Rance-sama's hot cum...
You bitch, you're still going?
Rance-sama, your cock is so amazing!
Open your ears!
Rance-sama...
My stomach feels like it's on fire.
It's all his fault...
More! More!
So good! I can feel your hot stuff
filling me up so deep inside!
Rance-sama, your cock is so different today.
It's hitting so many different places inside me!
Sill, stop already!
That face you're making...
Now I understand why you like teasing me so much.
You idiot!
Oh no, I can't hold on anymore.
H-Hey...
Rance-sama, I think I'm about to cum.
Please rub the deepest parts of me
with everything you've got!
Wh-Wha...
Your cock is hitting me so
deep inside! It feels so good!
It feels so good! I think
I'm about to cum, Rance-sama!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm still cumming!
Rance-sama, you came so much inside me.
Moving by myself feels so good.
I did it the way I wanted to...
the way I wanted to.
Fuck, she got me good.
You dare play with me like some
fucking toy? You little bi...
It works.
In stock
Slippery Root
That's fucking expensive!
Oh, don't touch that.
It shocks you if you don't have enough money.
Fuck, not even my reward money
is gonna cover this!
Sorry, this year's harvest wasn't that great
and the other ingredients were really expensive.
Give me a discount.
But we're running a special event...
When you order a super deluxe yakisoba,
you can take any of the roots you don't eat home!
Are you okay, Rance-san?
Sorry, Nami-san. I couldn't get
much of the ingredient you wanted.
That's fine.
Here's a digestive.
Good luck for tomorrow!
Rance?
It's finally time, huh?
Yeah. This'll put my investigation
of the missing Hikari-chan miles forward.
Really? Good luck!
Ladies and gentlemen!
The day you've all been waiting for is finally here.
It's time to get this show on the road!
First we have the challenger, Rance!
I think you all know his opponent very well.
Indeed, it's Yulang of the Phantasm Blade!
She is the proud, undefeated champion of this Colosseum!
Listen close. After I win, you're gonna give me that
Ghost Buster Sword, and then we're gonna fuck!
Pretty confident, aren't you?
Did you find a way to beat my Phantasm Blade?
I'm excited to see whatever you came up with,
no matter how dirty or cheap it may be.
I only have one strategy...
I'm just gonna cut you down!
You're too late!
Huh?
Time for your punishment!
Rance is pushing her back!
What's this? What's going on?!
Interesting ploy.
All the battles until now
have been so boring, but this...
This is the first time a fight's been so exhilarating!
Oh no!
What? How can this be?!
By beating her Phantasm Blade,
Rance claims an overwhelming victory!
Yay!
Ouch.
Can you stand, Yulang?
Yeah.
I won. Do you remember our promise?
Yeah, I'm going to give you this Ghost Buster sword...
I mean the other thing.
I guess I did promise to let you have sex with me.
Yep, right on the money!
Now that that's over
and done with, let's do this!
Champion, give us an interview!
Hey, you painfully obvious maid.
Is this a room for guests?
Y-Yes, it is.
This is the Laplace Room.
Wait, you can't possibly...
I'm Rance. I'm an important
customer on an important mission.
I'm using this room.
Uh, yeah, okay!
Are you serious?!
I told you to wait a sec...
At least let me take a shower.
You've made me wait this long,
I'm not gonna be bothered by a little stink!
That's not what I'm worried about, I...
Strip.
Please...
You look tasty.
Wha...
I'm not used to this. I don't really
know what kind of face to make.
Huh? What are you doing?!
Sweet, your pussy's tight!
No wonder you're a swordswoman.
Sh-Shut up.
Why am I feeling so much pleasure?
Is this what sex is?
Or maybe Rance is just that good?
If he keeps going, I'll lose it!
Yulang,
take care of this.
O-Okay...
Having one of the strongest warriors suck my cock
like some kind of animal feels amazing, Yulang.
Now use those huge tits of yours
to make me feel good.
A-All right.
I'm cumming. I'm gonna cum!
Hey, get it together, champion!
Yeah...
This is where the real fun starts.
I know...
W-Wait! Wait a second, Rance.
I don't think I can do this.
It feels like it's going into someplace weird.
That just means that all the guys
you've been with were way too small.
No way... But I feel like it's coming
all the way up to my belly button.
Rance!
Okay, okay, let's have some
baby-making sex on the bed now!
Baby-making sex...
does that mean...
Yeah, it does.
Rance...
Yulang, your tits are the best.
They look like they're about to burst,
but they have such a mesmerizing shape.
You look like you're feeling good.
Wh-What?
Your cool personality is fading away.
My personality?
What's my real personality?
– It' so deep! I can feel you ramming against the end of my womb!
– Yulang!
R-Rance!
Yulang, you're better this way.
I like girls who act like themselves and don't put up facades.
Does it feel good, Rance?
Hell yeah, it does. What about you?
You don't even need to ask, do you?
Don't ask me!
I'm gonna cum!
Yeah, cum for me, Rance!
It's so hot!
Your cum is so hot!
Please, Rance... make me change who I am!
Rance, just a little bit more...
Just a little bit more and I think I'll change!
Yulang, I'm just about at my limit too.
If only everyone could see just how
wet the strongest swordswoman is now.
Your hot cock is so amazing!
Suck it.
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
That felt so fucking amazing.
Yeah, that felt so good,
my head is still in the clouds.
So this is what the strongest warrior
of Leazus really looks like?
Not quite.
I'm no warrior. Right now,
I'm just a normal, naked woman.
Right?
Already back to scowling?
I might've lost, but a swordswoman
is a swordswoman.
I need to make a face befitting
of everyone's expectations.
Here's the other part of our deal.
Thanks.
It might've been for just a moment,
but I felt like I was free from the cage I made for myself.
Why don't you try wearing
some more feminine clothes?
You're mine now.
This is an order from me,
I want you to change yourself.
No, you're Rance...
And I'm Yulang Mirage.
Wow, this place is actually pretty nice looking.
Hard to believe that there's a ghost here.
So this place really is haunted.
But that doesn't matter,
'cuz I got this Ghost Buster Sword!
I'll cut you all down!
It might be broken,
but this clock looks damn expensive.
There you are.
Are you the leader of the ghosts
that've been haunting this place?
What?
Hey, wait!
What's going on? Is she trying
to guide me somewhere?
St-Stop! Somebody help me!
Please, stop! Stop!
What's going on?!
Let's kick it up a notch.
Of course.
If you don't resist, your shoulders are gonna be ripped off
and then you'll be split in two by the wooden horse.
It hurts! It really hurts!
Please, I beg you. Let me go!
Magnificent. That face you're making
is so magnificent, Lavender!
Let's keep going.
What was that?
You wanna show me something?
This room, I just saw it!
Not again!
What a sublime voice.
You really are great, Lavender.
I'll give you a nice present today.
I think you'll really like it.
This is a cattle prod.
Do you know what I'm going to do with this?
Month X, Day X. I can't even
tell what the weather is like.
I don't know why any of this is happening to me.
It's painful.
In order to keep my mind from breaking,
I've decided to write a diary.
I'm Lavender, a freshman of Paris Academy.
Paris Academy?
That's the school Hikari-chan went to,
the same one that Sill's attending right now.
Month X, Day 0. Weather is unknown.
Those two ca again and played
with me like I was their toy.
They revel in my pain.
They're not normal.
I'm being tormented by monsters.
They laughed at me whenever I smiled.
Those pieces of shit.
Every time that clock strikes nine,
I become their toy.
And they kept going until eleven?
If it started at nine and ended at eleven,
that means I'm right
in the middle of those hellish hours.
That makes me sick.
Thank you for ending it.
You were killed in this mansion.
Did you come back to haunt it as revenge?
Yes. Without even so much as a reason,
they tormented me day after day...
Any life threatening injuries were treated
by the girl with the moon crest.
That's why I took my own life.
So that's how it is.
But even then it didn't end!
They just abducted another girl
and did the same things!
I couldn't let them do that!
I couldn't let the Princess...
Princess?
Do you mean Princess Lea?!
Yes. Please, I beg you, stop her!
I can't do anything.
All I can do is float here and cry!
It hurt! It hurt so much!
Mother, Father, I didn't really want to kill myself!
Stop crying. I'd stop that bitch
even if you didn't ask me.
Toying with a girl until you push her to commit suicide
is worse than flaunting the entire country's wealth.
She's gonna pay!
Leave it to me.
Yes.
Rance-san,
Hikari-chan is being held through those doors.
Save her!
What? She is?!
Rance-san!
I couldn't physically touch you,
but I could tell... you're really warm.
Is this it?
Hikari-chan?
Thank god, you're still alive.
Hey, you're safe now!
Rance?
Rance!
Wait, is that girl...
Yeah. This is Hikari-chan,
the girl I've been looking for.
Could you take care of her for a bit?
Thank goodness you found her.
What happened to her?
I'll tell you later.
The one who did this to her is in there.
Wait, in Leazus Castle?
I'm gonna find her and shred her to bits!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: aux
quality check: fyurie