Dad? Mom?
Shit, it's him and the maid again...
Oh master!
You like the cock...
You're definitely worth the money
I pay you.
Go ahead scream.
Move your hips.
Shit...
I can't stand him!
I hate him!
I'm coming!
I need to get out of here...
Rancou Chokyo
~ Encounter ~
Maybe I'll get lucky.
She‘s so cute...
Are you OK?
Sure...
I'm ok.
Do you want to go for a walk?
Oh sure!
Well, where?
Come on, let's go to your house!
Huh?
I heard that you live in a large Mansion,
is it true?
Oh wow, your house is really big!
You have a huge koi pond, too!
Is that your dad?
Yeah.
You want to talk about it?
Oooooh, I can tell.
You two don't get along?
I hope I'm not interrupting,
but I'm here with your drinks.
Come in!
Excuse me...
Enjoy your beverage.
Woow, is she your maid?
I don‘t know anyone that has a maid!
Dad's gets off on that costume.
Say what?
Dad insists on having a maid.
It must be nice to be so wealthy!
It's no big deal.
Your room is so big!
It's bigger than my living room!
It just looks big, that's all.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Are you sure?
Did I say something?
I really like you a lot.
What?
Stop!
Since the day I saw you.
Just stop it, NOW!
You jerk!
Come on...
– I really like you!
– Set off me! Nooo!
Ouch!
I said STOP!
I said enough already!
Come on, really.
I said NO!
Get off me!
That hurts!
Stop!
You asshole!
But, but I thought...
Being rich doesn't make you special,
you stupid fucking asshole!
You're a filthy dog like the rest!
LOSER!
You don't even have words
to defend yourself...
I heard you were a real mama's boy.
Ruined me day!
Another piece of shit looooser!
You suck!
I can't believe this!
She called me a loser.
Shit, I'm not a mama's boy!
I can sleep with whoever I want!
It's none of your goddamned business.
If you don't like it, leave!
Leave, and don't ever come back!
If you come back I'll kill you!
Oh mom!
You like that?
Oh baby, I'm coming!
Couples!
Ouch!
What the fuck!
Who the hell?
Shit, ouch!
That hurts!
Don't move!
Owowowowowowowow.
That's what you get
for fucking around in public!
She's so pretty...
Hello.
Excuse me, this is Third Street, right?
Yes it is.
I'm not from this area, so I just got lost...
If you're looking for the museum,
It's over there.
Oh I'm not looking for the museum.
Thank you very much!
She's gorgeous.
I haven't been called gorgeous
in a long time, you handsome little boy!
Welcome back, your father is waiting.
What? My father?
Yes, he's waiting in his office.
What could he want?
He didn't say.
Maybe it's about my dropping grades...
Your grades dropped again?
Is it possible to get any lower than before?
You can go now.
Shit!
How are you doing in school?
All right...
I want you to meet someone.
Meet someone?
Oh you're from...
What, you know each other?
No, I just gave her directions in front of
the museum this morning.
I got lost.
Thank you for helping me earlier...
I really appreciate it...
Again, thank you very much...
Oh no, you're very welcome.
Well, what a coincidence!
Wait a minute...
That's all for right now.
You may be excused now, son.
Excuse me.
Shit, I bet he's got sick plans for her...
Why don't you take off your skirt?
Please, I'll do anything, but not that!
Huh, what did you say?
Please, I'll do anything else,
but not this, please!
What's wrong with
what I'm asking you to do now?
I beg you, please stop!
I made a contract with your father...
you are aware of the contract
you're under while you're here, right?
I know you helped my father tremendously.
But...
But? I saved your family from having to
run from the mob...
by paying half a million dollars
of your father's debt.
I'm aware.
I don't think you really are...
So, why don't you take your top off?
No, stop!
This looks appetising!
This is getting me excited.
You might say you don't want me,
but your body doesn't lie...
You look good upset: I like it.
Nooo!
Let's see...
Please stop!
Well, well... see, you're all wet.
I beg you, stop!
I've got what you're pussy's
craving for right here!!
Have mercy!
– Please!
– I like it when you scream like that!
Stooooooop!
Nooooooo!
Ouch, ouch!
A virgin! This is truly a bargain!
It's worth every penny I spent on you!
Please!
I love the brand-new feeling
of that tight, wet, virgin pussy!
Nooooooooo!
Go cry and scream!
I know you want it harder and rougher.
Please, stop now!
I know you'd I like this,
knew you were a slutty little whore!
Scream more, scream out loud!
I like it when you scream and resist!
You're going to like this one.
Might as well fill this asshole, too...
Please, not there, pleasel
Go ahead and resist,
but I want the most of what I paid for!
I found myself constantly
worrying about her.
I also found myself falling in love
with her...
I thought about how my father
was probably raping her nightly.
I can't imagine...
Excuse me, your dinner is ready!
Why do you dine in your room?
I'm busy with my studies...
I khow how it can be:
studying can be really time consuming!
Well, it's not just only that...
This looks difficult!
I only went my first two years
of high school.
I hate this!
Don't do that! Studying is so important.
Like I'd need history...
You should be glad
you can go to school and study.
I had to leave school to work
for my family...
She's so gorgeous.
But my father's probably already...
Stop!
Stop it!
Do you mind if I read?
Well, can I ask you a question?
Yes?
I know you work for the family and all.
If It's OK...
Can it be all right if I ask you
to do me a special favour?
What?
Like, you do with my father...
If you don't mind, you know?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Her resistance and fear heightened
my arousal even more.
Please don't!
I just want to love you,
unlike my bastard of a father.
I really can't.
No...
Don't...
I loved you since the first time we met!
I just can't.
I've been already made unclean...
I don't care, I love you, I really do.
I'm not worthy of love from anyone.
I'm unclean!
That's not true!
I don't think you are unclean at all
in any way!
Thank you very much...
If you're so sure about this...
I'm all yours: every part of my body...
is all for your pleasure...
From now and forever!
I'm so happy...
You'll be mine forever!
Yes, I want to love and taste
every part of your body!
Oh yes!
Wow, you're hard again!
I can't stop before I've given
your body pleasure as well...
Thank you!
Only you have ever cared about how I felt.
You really do care for me!
Take me, I want you to take me!
All right!
Oh yes!
This feels so different!
Just keep doing that!
Fuck my pussy more!
Much harder!
I've never been this wet.
I'm so wet!
I'm getting wetter!
Hurry, I want you to come inside me!
I'm going to come!
I'm coming too.
Coming...
Oh yes!
Thank you for pleasing me!
I want you to love me like that!
I left the house to live
on my own soon after...
He was eager to get me out of he house,
so he willingly paid for the apartment.
Welcome back home.
My master!
I never would have left her there...
She obeys my every fantasy, and desire.
She'll do anything.