It's a clash of blades.
Magic envelops everything around
it with its mysterious brilliance.
Kingdom of Leazas is known as the world's most
prosperous nation of the Eastern Continent.
With each event and incident in the land,
the kingdom's gears of fate turn.
Do not investigate the matter about Hikari Mi Bran further.
What did you say?
I'll say it once more.
Your investigation on Hikari Mi Bran ends here.
But...!
Are you out of you mind?
What? A female ninja?
Your movements may be quick, but
your attacks are quite mediocre.
I can't keep up.
I'm tired after fighting all day.
Rance-sama!
Rance-sama!!
I can't have more people in here.
Wait up, you bitch!
Rance-sama!
Are you alright, Rance-sama?
I'm glad that you're alri...
Now she got away because of you!
Chase that ninja girl!
I can't!
She's already beyond the border walls.
Guess I'll have to come here by day then.
Well, it's not like I can chase her down.
I'm sorr-
In times like these, I suppose searching thoroughly
would eventually lead us to a clue.
We're done for the day.
Hey, come on, Sill!
C-Coming!
Hey, Pulptenks!
Let's close shop for today.
Okay.
I'll go once I finish cleaning up.
I'm really happy to be with my daughter every day.
Rance-san, I...
Rance-san...
Alright, the path is clear.
Hey, stop there.
Can you please show me your pass?
Hmm?
Oh? A female guard?
Whoa, you're a cutie!
Can you tell me your name?
Wh-What are you asking so suddenly?
Hey, I said you need to show me your pass!
I'm Menado.
I'm a gate guard.
Do you have any business at the Leazas Castle?
You can't get in here without a pass, you now.
And what if I try to force myself in?
Then you'll have to fight me.
Curses!
That Menado girl sure is very persistent!
Jeez!
This is all Sill's fault!
Yeah, definitely hers.
I'mm going to make her do something about this!
Hey, Sill!
Sill!
Hmm, at the back gate, eh.
Are you Sill-san's friend?
Unfortunately, she's not running any errands today.
Wow, a beauty!
But there's something off about her.
Oh, so where is she now?
At the Leazas Castle.
She went to Leazas Castle?!
Indeed, but...
It seems she's hasn't come back yet.
She's probably resting at some park nearby.
What?!
It's okay, it's okay!
I have more here, so just eat!
How cute...
I want a doggie, but I wonder if Rance-sama
would allow me to keep it?
Hey.
Rance-sama, your foot!
You're stepping on it.
Eh? Is something on my foot?
I don't see anything at all.
The doggie, the doggie is...!
I said, what are you talking about?
Anyway, I heard that you went inside the castle earlier.
You didn't tell me anything?!
B-But that's...
This is it!
A pass!
I-I got that from a teacher!
What did you say?!
Sill,
is it hard for you to understand that slaves ought
to think only about what benefits their masters?
Looks like I need to really punish you a lot this time.
You useless bitch!
Rance-sama?
Come here!
Sit here, and part your legs.
Eh? We're doing it here?
Umm, but Rance-sama,
there are people here...
You don't need to think about that, you slave.
Listen up.
A slave's responsibility is to provide their masters
with anything and everything they want.
Y-Yes...
Show your nipples now, Sill.
Alright...
Expose what's below, too.
Do I really have to?
Idiot! We're about to have sex, so of course you need to strip!
Alright, what a nice view.
This is embarrassing.
Really? It doesn't feel that way at all for me.
Let's see... how are your insides?
It's not wet, you failure of a slave!
I-I'm sorry!
Come on, get it wet already.
I can't fuck you with my big magnum if you don't.
B-But...
Where are you looking, Sill?
Focus on this!
Rance-sama, not there, please!
If he keeps rubbing me there I'll...
Hey, it looks like I'm the one servicing you here!
What the hell do you think your master is?
I'm sorry...
But I'm just so worried about our surroundings.
Mama, let's play over here!
Whoa, it suddenly got wet.
What? No way...
That can't be.
Oh? So having other people around is better for you, eh.
I never thought you had the potential for that.
Ah, never mind, let's just fuck.
Th-That's not true.
That's not true!
It's tight as usual, but I can move more freely than before.
This is great!
I never thought a park rider like this could be used this way.
Rance-sama!
There, there!
See?
Hey, what's that?
Aren't they...
They're really doing it there!
That's just so bad, and that girl's such a hottie, too!
Wow, for real?
She's even hotter than the most top class in Leazas!
Sill, are you still worried about people around us?
I-I'm sorry, but I'm just so embarrassed.
Idiot.
Well, at least you're gripping me
tighter, so it feels better for me.
Your insides feel really great now.
Rance-sama...!
All that training that I did for you feels worth it.
Alright, alright!
Now, we're about to finish!
I'm going to go faster, Sill!
It hurts!
It hurts, Rance-sama!
Deal with it.
I already said that it's your job to please your master!
B-But...
If he keeps fucking me like this, I'll lose my mind!
Okay, I'm about to cum.
Okay...
Umm... Cum inside me if you want, just please finish up already.
Gotcha! I'm going to pump it all ou-
Oh, by the way, Sill,
did you cast a contraceptive spell already?
Huh? Why the sudden question?
I'm just curious about what's holding me back over here.
Hurry! I'm alright, so...
Just cum already, please!
Oh, ordering me like that...
But if you intend to plead the same way...
Very well then.
Rance-sama!
It's cumming lots...
Rance-sama, your thing is cumming more than usual.
This is embarrassing.
It feels warm...
Now I feel refreshed!
See you later, Sill.
Just continue your infiltration as planned.
Yes. Rance-sama...
Ta-da!
You got a pass?!
You didn't do anything illegal for this, did you?
Who are you calling a criminal?
I'm Ranee!
The strongest swordsman ever, and
the adventurer who seeks the truth!
I'm currently investigating a suspicious ninja
who happened to have intruded here.
Ninja?
Now then,
I'm now heading into the very heart of Leazas.
This is a... coliseum?
Leazas Castle also has these things?
Oh, there's a fight going on.
I bet every single penny I had on you!
Come on, give it all to me!
Here's the current ranking.
At 7th is Jean Giovanni the 2nd!
6th is Alexander!
5th, Fuburi Matsushita!
4th, Ninja Master!
Ninja Master, you say?!
Ninja...
It's her!
That's the ninja girl that disguised herself as a student!
She knew about Hikari-chan.
Ninja Master?
That's the ninja you're looking for?
Yeah.
Actually, a girl named Hikari has been
missing from Paris Academy.
I've been searching for her whereabouts,
but she's got the clues that I need.
A girl disappeared...?
That's not good.
I want to get into the coliseum tournament
and face this Ninja Master somehow.
How do I get permission to enter the fights?
I have one.
What? Alright, give it to me then.
I can't just ignore the fact that there's a shady
person lurking within the King's castle.
I really wanted to participate myself,
but I can't leave my post.
I got it, I got it.
I don't care about that, so just give it to me already.
But, I want to make sure about you, too.
Can I give you some conditions?
At the graveyard over that border,
zombies have started appearing.
Help me exterminate them, and I'll give you permission.
How's that?
That's a pain in the ass, but I guess I have to comply.
Millie-chan, I'll be using the shampoo, okay?
Okay.
So, what did Ranee come for anyway?
His scabbard broke the other day so he wanted a spare.
I told him that it'd take some time because of the tournament.
He then told me that it's okay since he's
staying at Leazas for quite some time.
You've finally got a competent adventurer here, Leazas!
I hope it's not just a temporary deal.
Because those kinds of people usually die quickly.
If fate goes against him, he'll soon...
We're going to charge all the way through!
Okay!
Rance-san, you're strong.
You're not that bad too, Menado.
Alright, leaving the tournament pass aside,
why don't we have a little match?
Eh? A match?
Yup!
The one who gets the most zombie kills gets
to request any one thing from the loser.
I'm okay with that, but what are you planning to ask?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Of course, there's only thing to ask for!
Sex!
A cute girl is right in front of me,
and that means I want to have sex!
It's the basic truth of the world!
Yay!
I-I'm not really that cute...
So warm...
A warm human...
Warmth!
Just ascend already, you stinking bitch!
I-Incredible.
He won...
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah.
Okay, no serious injuries anywhere.
It'd be bad if a girl's body got injured.
W-We haven't counted our kills yet, you know.
Menado.
That doesn't matter anymore... right?
We won.
Oh crap, Rance just looked so cool.
I'm... not really cute...
At least, not like normal girls.
I've been treated like merchandise all my life, you know...
What are you saying?
You're cute.
I guarantee you.
All the guys in the entire Leazas kingdom are idiots.
Not really...
I can see it.
No...
Are we really going to do it in a graveyard?
What are you saying?
It's quite a fad for couples these days.
Life blooms at the very place where the dead are put to rest.
C-Couples?!
Is that true?
Yep, I'm sure of it.
He's touching my private parts!
It feels really firm.
You probably haven't played with it even once, right?
Eh? Played? I didn't do such...
Whoa, then it looks like I have to prepare lots for this.
I'm feeling tingly.
Your body sure is quite eager about this.
You twitch at my every movement.
No, not my legs...
Here, let me check how sensitive you are.
Try to let out your voice as I touch it.
Oh yeah, what a nice reaction.
Why am I...?
... letting out such a weird moan?
Alright, now that you're aroused enough...
No, not there, I'm really feeling weird down there right now!
It's gotten really wet now.
My body feels weird.
Ranee...
My body... is indeed female after all...
Okay! Now it's time to enjoy fucking you!
No way, you're going to put that inside?
Try to relax.
O-Okay.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Really?
It feels very great for me here, though.
Besides, this was the deal, right?
Well, that's true.
Alright then.
Rance...
Does it feel good?
Yeah, it feels really great.
I'm glad.
Just let yourself enjoy the pleasure.
Oh yeah?
I'm going to do it faster then.
Alright, that's good, Menado!
You're the best!
Rance, my insides are starting to feel weird.
So you're starting to get aroused from it.
Something's starting to well up...
Now, I'm going to reach your very
depths so that you feel it more!
It's hitting deep inside me.
It feels weird.
What is this?
Something's reverberating inside me
as his dick continues to hit me inside.
That's good, Menado.
Your womb is twitching like mad each time I hit it.
So the part where you're hitting me is in my baby bag?
That's right.
You're not just cute, but you're also impregnation material!
Your body's so erotic!
That's looks so cute.
Good, good.
I've decided to cum in here!
In your very insides!
Are you ready?
Rance!
I'm scared!
Don't let me fall, Rance!
You've already fallen for me, though.
I get it already!
I'm cumming, don't waste a single drop of it!
Cum, Rance.
Satisfy yourself with me.
Something's starting to bulge inside.
Your dick is getting even bigger.
I'm happy.
He's pumping so much after feeling so good.
Alright, time for round two.
Menado, I'm cumming again.
Go ahead and cum, Rance.
Rance, Rance!
Are you ready?
I'm cumming!
Rance, don't cum inside me anymore, please,
or else, or else, I'll cum...!
I'm cumming!
It's squeezing me really tightly.
Rance, are you taking me?
I love you... Rance...
Man, that was refreshing!
Thank you, Rance.
It doesn't feel bad being treated like a woman after all.
Listen, Menado.
It's alright with someone as great as me,
but you can't say that in front of other guys.
If someone as cute as you says that,
even a total loser would probably become arrogant.
Okay, just you... right...
What's wrong?
I just felt a surge of lonelines when I realized
that you're no longer inside me.
I'm always inside you.
That's a promise.
I'll be waiting for you.
We're now starting the battles for
the Leazas Coliseum tournament!
Battle over!
The newcomer green fighter, Rance
has made it to the upper rounds.
His next opponent should be much
harder to deal with this time.
Such technique...
Knock-out! And another victory for him!
Rance goes up in the ranks once again!
I've chased that ninja who escaped this far,
but my upcoming match is with her.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
the contender is the new green fighter, Rance.
At the other corner is a master of ninjutsu...
I wonder how I should punish that ninja girl?
Here comes, Ninja Master!
Who are you?
Bravo, bravo.
I saw how hard you worked to get here,
it truly was splendid.
I can only congratulate you once more.
However, I'm now here to block your advance.
This is completely the wrong person!
So I...
Hey, wait, I'm still introducing myself.
Get me that girl that annoyed me so much right now!
What in the heavens...?!
How...
This is a total surprise!
Rance wins this round!
I've messed up big time.
That Ninja Master's not the ninja girl?!
Now I'm completely empty-handed.
I'd even planned to grip here like this, bind
her like this, and tease her like this!
Hey...
Do you have a moment?
That fight earlier was splendid,
Warrior Rance.
Wow, a hot babe!
I wanted to talk to you for a bit.
Oh, what is it?
An autograph? Or maybe you're inviting me on a date?
We have to discuss this in secret, so please, this way.
Secret, eh? Not bad.
Isn't this Leazas Castle's main palace?
That's right. My princess seems to have taken
a liking to you and has become your fan.
She really wanted to meet you.
Princess? You mean the Princess of this castle?
Indeed.
The only royal princess of the Leazas Kingdom.
Her Majesty, Lia Parapara Leazas.
That's great then.
I guess the time I spent fighting for my
life at the coliseum was worth it.
I am her guardian, Maris Amaryllis.
Huh? Haven't we met before?
No, I'm afraid I do not go outside that often.
I've been waiting!
Good day, and nice to meet you,-.Rance-san.
I'm Lia Parapara Leazas.
Wow, you look as magnificent as I imagined.
A perfect 100 in cuteness for me.
I've been, watching your fights at the coliseum.
You're very strong.
Actually, I have a request for you
in regards to your fighting skill.
Oh, what is it? I'm ready to listen
to anything that a cute girl asks.
Tell me about it.
Thank you.
Look, see over there?
There's a villa on top of that hill.
However, it's haunted by a spirit.
A spirit?
Wait a minute.
I'm not a priest or anything like that.
You might even find the unknown
ninja that you are looking for.
Hey, how did you know that?
Intel gathering of the Leazas Kingdom is top notch.
They know every single thing.
If you agree to exorcise the ghost for us,
we're willing to give you information on the ninja.
As well as information about Hikari-chan.
What? You also know about Hikari-chan?
I thought about asking for a sex reward earlier, though.
It seems the intel concerning your personality was spot on.
Alright then, Maris.
Yes.
If you so desire,
then please do as you want.
Do you understand now?
D-Do as I want?!
No need to be so cautious.
I won't run or hide.
I'll do it!
Just leave this to me.
I'm going to exorcise it in a jiffy.
We're counting on you then.
She's got good tits.
How wonderful!
I want to be closer to her.
A spirit, thought?
How in the world would I...
Yuran-sama!
Who was that hottie?
You don't know?
She's the best fighter in the Leazas Coliseum,
Yuran Mirage.
Not a single man can beat her.
She'll protect her first place rank forever.
She's strong, beautiful, and cool!
True, she does look gorgeous and strong.
Strong women are usually like that, but...
Huh? That sword...
Oh, are you the new fighter?
I'm Rance, the man who's gonna plow through the rankings.
Remember that.
I will.
I'll be waiting for you to reach me.
Anyway, that sword sure looks strange.
Oh? So you can see it.
This is a sword that can slash even through phantasmic objects,
the Ghost Buster Sword.
Give that to me.
I want to use it somewhere.
You're suddenly asking me to hand
over my precious sword to you?
Let's see...
If you can win against me, then I'm willing
to listen to any request that you have.
You said any request, right?
Then I'll have that sword, as well as your body.
You've got some spirit.
Very well then.
But you'll have to get through the entire tournament
and face my Illusion Sword before that.
Make sure that I enjoy the fight.
She disappeared?
Hey, don't fuck with me!
Are you a phantom or something?
Finishing blow,
Illusion Sword!
Yu-Yuran Mirage wins in less than a minute!
Today's fight was instantaneous.
She used her Illusion Sword immediately.
So that's the technique...
Illusion Sword.
Bring it on!
I'm going to make that strong woman moan on my bed!
This will be the best yet!
You just wait for me!
No, please let me go...
Save me!
No~!