Pulptenks-chan, over here!
Right away!
Me too, Pulptenks-chan!
Your name was Pulptenks-chan, right?
You're goddamn hot.
The boss is gonna be proud.
...No...
No!
...Swords fly...
Magic illuminates it all
shrouded in mystery.
The gears of history have
begun to turn in this vast world.
The Quest for Hikari
Episode
Rance, Rising!
The Quest for Hikari
Episode
Rance, Rising!
The Quest for Hikari
Her name is Hikari Mi Blanc.
She's a daughter of the Blanc branch
of the famous Leazas family.
Apparently she vanished from the school
she was going to about three weeks ago.
Go find her!
A job like that doesn't suit
a genius warrior like me.
Way too plain.
Go home if you want.
You don't have to
if she's not to your liking.
Hikari Mi Blanc?
Holy crap!
She's cute!
I'm gonna make an exception
on account of her cuteness!
The most powerful warrior alive,
me, Rance, will take care of this!
I'm depending on you.
Hey, Sill!
Hurry up!
Who's ever heard of a slave
who makes her master wait?
You're useless!
I'm sorry, Rance-sama.
I couldn't find much clean water.
And there were monsters!
No excuses, slave!
That hits the spot!
Gimme the other!
...That one's mi—
It's almost noon.
Let's grab some good food in Leazas, Sill!
All righty!
Rance-sama!
So this is what the better parts
of a Leazas town look like.
Guess they're not called the world's
most prosperous country for nothing.
This look like the right place.
Rance-sama!
What's your plan?
You're going to go to the same
Paris College that Hikari-chan went to.
Go to school?
It's called infiltration.
I'm really unhappy with leaving
something like that to you,
but this school is all-girls.
I can't even enter it.
Nothing I can do about it.
...Um...
Can I just start school here?
Did you think I came here
without preparations?
I have the necessary papers.
Get going!
All right, meanwhile I will
observe the town and its girls!
The adventurer's way, part one:
The first thing you do in a
new town is gather information.
I am faithful to the tenets!
RANCE
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
RANCE
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
RANCE
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
RANCE
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
RANCE
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
RANCE
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
What a cutie!
Will you stay here?
We're an inn called Crystal Candy.
So this is what it looks like inside.
It sure looks different from the other places.
I like it.
I'm gonna stay here.
Thank you.
I am the proprietress.
My name is Horikawa Nami.
Nami-san, huh?
...Those clothes are...
amazing!
You're mine!
Takeda Jujitsu:
Wing Clipper.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm quite experienced in Jujitsu,
so this was a reflex of sorts.
Jujitsu?
Oh, my.
What is this?
Her name's Hikari-chan.
I'm looking for her.
You seen her?
No.
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
It's okay.
Thanks anyway.
RANCE
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
RANCE
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
RANCE
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
RANCE
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
RANCE
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Ocean!
I'm Patty!
Patty the Summer!
We sell all sorts of luxurious things
to make you feel better!
I'm Rance.
You seen this girl?
Who cares, you're mine now!
Never seen her.
RANCE
Next one!
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
RANCE
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
I'm Millie Lincle.
...We sell weapons and—
Whoa!
You're a bit gloomy, but cute!
Hey Millie-chan!
I brought you food!
Sorry!
Come on!
Get lost!
RANCE
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Baltic
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Baltic
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Baltic
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Baltic
Give Up
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
Fujisaki Level
Crystal Candy
Give Up
Baltic
I'm Willis Fujisaki,
and here you can level up.
Do you want to level up?
...Willis Fujisaki...
I want you too!
I did a lot of very serious investigating,
but came up with no clues
as to where Hikari-chan is.
This is seriously weird.
How's it going, Sill?
Found something out?
...Um...
She was a noble,
she was happy and a good person.
Well, did someone suspicious
have a problem with her?
Are her parents in debt?
...I...
...I don't know...
God, you're so useless.
I'll need to punish you.
I'm having a lot of trouble right now.
You're my slave,
and you will comfort me!
Here?!
Someone will see us!
Say what?
Shut up!
You're my slave! You're supposed
to think of my happiness only!
Spread your legs and stick your ass out!
...But...
Come on, get wet.
...I can't just...
...Hey...
Once the lessons are over,
let's have some fun.
I don't have time today.
What's the man doing with the girl there?
Whoa, I didn't see them.
Maybe she brought him in to make out.
Rance-sama... please be quick.
Someone will come.
You're not going to order me!
It's your job to make me feel good!
Do your job!
...But...
Be merciful!
Make me happy and I will be!
I'll just do it myself!
Rance-sama!
It's so big!
Here, let the others see it!
They'll love it!
I don't want them to see me!
Sounds like you can't stay quiet yourself.
Take this!
I love it!
I'll cum!
Take it all inside!
Rance-sama!
That hurt!
Don't act like it was your first time.
Act like the slave you are and just take it.
Okay.
Time for round two!
...But I...
I'm not finished yet!
Seems you like it too!
That ended pretty well.
You better do some
serious investigating now.
...I will...
...Rance-sama...
Better than fried eggs!
Well, I'm glad the tension's gone,
but nothing has changed.
Hey, listen to me.
Hey!
Listen, dude, I ordered stuff.
I've been waiting for thirty minutes now!
Do you want me to leave?!
I suppose it's pointless
asking someone like you,
but I'm looking for a missing girl.
A missing girl?!
Hikari Mi Blanc.
Noblewoman, missing.
The greatest warrior, I,
have been called upon.
Really?
I'm sure that's the work of
Endless Tomorrow Battle Force.
My own daughter, Pulptenks,
was kidnapped too!
What?
Endless Tomorrow Battle Force?
They're hiding out in a cave in the forest,
but neither the city nor the
people want to make a move.
You must be a famous warrior
to be given this task.
Can you please rescue my daughter, Pulptenks?
She's hot!
Yeah, I should investigate
the place for Hikari-chan too!
Ideally I can bag both her and Pulptenks!
Sounds good.
You got it, old man.
I'll do it.
Thank you!
So much!
You can have all my money too!
Fill your stomach!
You can have all this too!
...And this...
...And also this...
Listen, man.
There's no way I can carry
all that shit into battle!
Let me just have this bottle
of booze and some food.
I can trust you, right?
Don't you know who I am?
No, sorry.
What? Is that true?
Yeah, Endless Tomorrow Battle Force
have been abducting people lately.
They're hiding out in a cave in the forest.
Great!
I have some news for Rance-sama!
Sill?
Yes?
I think we should be friends.
Do you want to?
Yes!
Are you mocking us?
Draw your sword from the scabbard!
Nah.
Your blood isn't worth
putting rust on my sword.
This is going perfectly!
Hikari-chan is mine!
Pulptenks-chan too!
Rance-sama?
I want to tell him where
the bandit hideout is.
He only ever turns up
when it doesn't suit me.
When I want to see him
he's nowhere to be found.
Boss Room
Looks like the boss lair.
I know this voice!
It's a girl during sex!
Inexcusable!
Only I'm supposed to have sex with girls!
...Well, if there's no key, then—
Never seen you here before.
New recruit?
You're a sexy one.
I'm the second-in-command, Necai.
You're a cute servant.
Cute?
Hey, that's not good.
You have to tell me
if something bothers you.
I can't enter the boss's room.
Yeah, Reinhard likes the
new girl they abducted.
He's been holing up in there with her.
Abducted?
...Holy god, I am jeal—
...I mean, inexcusabl—
Er, I'm jealous.
He's not going to hear some knocking.
I have the key to his room if you want it.
Right here.
Let me have it.
Nope.
I'm taking it by force then!
Aren't you a greedy one
to assault me like that.
Oh, my!
Isn't that the famous
250 year old Yamazaki?
Hey, lemme have this for the key.
I'll make you feel good too.
For this bottle you deserve it.
I'm glad you liked it.
See you then.
Bye.
You have a great body.
You must love having sex.
...No, I don't...
If this isn't proof of your
lewdness, then what is?
Listen up, man.
What?
Who the hell are you?
You the boss of the bandits?
I've come to punish you!
This is a bad time.
I was busy making this girl
the happiest on Earth.
Happy?
You abducted her and
tormented her, you creep.
Be quiet!
Nobody has ever dared raise their sword
against the Endless Tomorrow Battle Force.
You're gonna regret it!
You're pretty quick on your feet.
He's pretty good.
Guess the bad feeling
I had was on the money.
Do you want to be cut into a
thousand pieces for your insults?
How can he be so experienced already?
He's so good!
What are you doing?
Rance Slash!
Like I'd fall for that!
Are you okay, Pulptenks?
Take a look at this!
Let me go!
I can't take any more of this!
Are you mistaking me
for the bandit commander?
This calls for my Hyper Weapon!
I'm not gonna leave you hanging!
I'm taking you for myself!
That was enough to make her cum?
Hm, gonna keep up the act.
Hehe, looks like you couldn't take any more.
I'll let you feel my genital object!
It's so big!
...No...
...It's my first time...
...But it feels so good...
What?
The boss sure let you go to waste.
You got nice tits!
No!
Stop!
You're gonna break them!
You're a pig in heat!
...No...
...I'm a normal girl...
So why are you moving towards me?
You lewd girl!
No!
I don't want to be raped by bandits,
but it feels so good!
Come on.
Here, here.
Here.
The world's going white.
I'll come soon!
Take all my cum!
No!
Don't come!
I'll get pregnant!
I'll be a mother!
Not my problem!
No crime is too great for us!
We'll get you pregnant too!
No!
I'll come!
I'm coming!
Let's go to war a second time.
...But I thought...
I'm not done with you yet!
No!
This is... is... good!
You're okay now, Pulptenks.
Let's walk you home.
...Wait, I...
I knocked out the bandits.
I'm Rance.
I'm an adventurer sent
by your dad to rescue you.
Thank you.
You're safe now.
Thanks.
By the way, did you see
another abducted girl?
No, I think I was alone here.
Guess this was for nothing then.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Please take this money!
I'll come back with more stuff for you!
Lay off!
Rance-san, thank you.
Sure thing.
Please come see us here
if you get the chance.
So long.
Guess this was totally
unrelated to Hikari-chan in the end.
Maybe I wasted the last few days.
Back to square one.
PC 9801VM, 2HD disk,
...4MB RAM, MSX, X6—
God, I have to fuck someone!
There's a girl!
He noticed me!
How?!
Wait!
Were you looking at me?
Aren't you a shy one?
That's great too!
I can feel the love!
This is childish.
Where is she?
Stop investigating Hikari Mi Blanc.
What?
I'll repeat what I said.
Stop looking into Hikari Mi Blanc.