Exclusive Video
(The Darknes of Leazas)
Good morning, my adorable pet.
It hurts!
Please, please let me be!
Why do I have to be...
Well, it's because I wanted to play with you as my toy.
See there? Everyone gathered when I
told them I'd play with my pet again.
Look at those boners, they all sure love you very much.
S-Save me... please spear me!
I'll do anything!
You say that, but I really love to hear you shriek.
Well then, everyone, do your thing.
Maris.
What is it, Lia-sama?
Stop, I'll die.
I'm going to die!
Well, I suppose I can stop this,
but alright, we'll replace them with someone much stronger.
Please, not the gorilla!
Here, I'm going to move my hips all you want,
so please just cum all you want.
I'll take it all in!
I just love dicks!
So please, anything but the gorilla...!
Looks like he didn't like being left out.
No way, no way...
This can't be.
I can't...
It hurts...
What could have gone wrong?
It seems to have broken her.
If this continues we may not be able to save her.
Shall I use healing magic now?
Just wait a bit.
it's fucking her so ecstatically.
We'll let it do it all the way.
See that? I think it's about to cum.
Cum, just cum!
Just cum in my favorite toy!
Oh wow!
It's really comming!
It's cumming lots too, seems like
my toy left really good from it.
Okay, I'll leave the rest to you then, Maris.
I want you to heal her so I can play with her lots again.
As yuo wish, Lia-sama.