Indomitable blades.
Magic that dispels doubt with its sheer brilliance.
The warriors from the Kingdom of Leazus in the Eastern
Continent, were considered to be the mightiest in the world.
Owing to a certain incident that occurred in this nation,
the gears of history are now beginning to shift.
onwards!! to the center of leazus
Quit searching for Hikari Mi Blanc.
What did you say?!
I'll say this just once more.
Your search for Hikari Mi Blanc ends here.
However!
You serious?!
What? A female ninja?
You dodge well and you're quick to go on the offensive.
This isn't looking good. I'm already tired from fighting all day!
Rance-sama!
It won't be wise to stay here and longer.
Stop! Bitch!
Rance-sama!
Are you alright, Rance-sama?
Rance-sama, I'm glad that you're fin...
You let her get away!
Go after that female ninja!
That's not really possible as she's already over the wall!
Guess we'll have to come back during the day.
Oh well, it's not like we can catch up to her anyway.
I'm sorr...
Well, even in times like these, if we
search ever nook and cranny,
we're bound to find some kind of clue.
We'll retreat for today.
Hey! Hurry up, Sill.
Y-Yes!
He Pulptenks, isn't it time to close the shop?
Yes! I'll do it right after I'm done cleaning.
I'm so happy now that my daughter's with me again.
Rance-san... I am...
Rance-san...
Sweet, it's open!
Stop right there!
Can you show me your pass?
Hmm?
What? A female guard?
Oh? She's cute!
Who are you?
What're you saying out of nowhere!
I said you can't do in! Show me your pass!
My name is Menado, I'm the gatekeeper here.
Do you have some business in Leazus castle?
I can't let you in without a pass I'm afraid.
What if I told you I'll force my way in?
You'll have to fight me then.
Damn it!
That girl, Menado or whatever, she
just had to be so thickheaded!
For God's sake!
This is all Sill's fault!
Yeah, it's totally her fault. I've got to make her pay for this!
Hey! Sill!
Sill!
Oh my, trying to get in from the back entrance?
Huh?
Are you an acquaintance of Sill-san?
I'm sorry, but Sill-san was feeling tired
so she's hot here at the moment.
Oh, a beauty! But her fashion sense is kinda off.
I see, so where'd she go then?
To Leazus castle.
She's at Leazus castle?!
Yes but, she's taking a bit too long to come back.
I'm pretty sure she's taking a break in the park.
What?!
It's alright, it's alright. I have a lot
of this left, so eat up, eat up!
You're so cute!
I want to get a puppy but I don't think
Rance-sama would arrove...
Yo!
Rance-sama, your foot, your foot!
P-Please lift it up!
Oh, is there something under my foot?
I can't feel it at all!
The puppy will, the puppy will...!
Really, what are you talking about?
More importantly, I heard you already infiltrated the castle?
Without even telling me?!
Oh! B-But that's...
This is it, that pass!
I-I got that from the teacher...
What?!
Sill, do you not understand that a slave needs
to always think about her master first?
Seems like I'll need to administer some proper punishment.
Eh?
You good-for-nothing!
Rance-sama?
Get over here!
Climb on top of this and spread your less!
No way! Here?!
Rance-sama, there are people around...
Huh?
Don't mind them, darn slave!
It's a slave's duty to offer up every bit of
herself to her master, without question.
Y-Yes...
Yes...
Alright then. Show me your nipples, Sill.
Down there too.
A-Are you sure?
Idiot! We're gonna have sex right now! How's
that gonna work if you don't take 'em off?!
Perfect! That's a great view.
I-It's embarrassing...
Is it? I'm cool with it though.
Let's see now, how's it looking down there?
It's not wet get? You fail as a slave!
I-I'm sorry!
Come on, hurry up and get wet! How else
is my big magnum gonna slide in there?
But... But...
What're you looking at, Sill?
Focus here!
Rance-sama, not over there!
If he keeps fingering me like that, I'll...
Hey! It's like I'm the one serving you!
Just what do you take your master for?
I'm sorry, but I'm just worried about our surroundings.
Mama, let's play here!
Oh, it just got wetter!
Eh? No way, that's a lie!
What? You like having an audience?
Didn't think you had that kind of fetish.
Well whatever, let me stick it in already!
Th-That's not true, that's not true!
You're tight as usual, but it's easier to move now.
This is great! To think we could play
like this in a park of all places!
Rance-sama!
There! There!
Right?
Whoa, what's this?
They're doing it?
They're doing it in a park!
And that girl is pretty cute!
Oh, for real?
She looks classy, like a noble from Leazus!
Sill, are you still bothered by being watched?
Forgive me, I feel so embarrassed...
Idiot! Oh well, you're getting tighter, which works for me!
Your insides feel was better.
Rance-sama!
It was worth spending time to make you wet.
Great! This is great!
Alright, it's time to finish this!
I'm going to let out everything I've got Sill!
It hurts, it hurts! Rance-sama!
Bear with it. I told you it's your duty
to satisfy your master, didn't I?
But... But...
If you do me so hard, I'm going to go insane!
Okay! I'm just about ready to cum now!
Yes.
Please hurry. You can cum inside me, so please do hurry!
Okay! I'll cum right no...
Wait a minute Sill. Have you used contraception magic yet?
Eh? Why ask that all of a sudden?
I was just wondering if you're using it right now.
Hurry! It's fine as it is, please hurry and cum inside me!
Huh? Giving me orders now?
But, if you're going to beg like that...
Very well then!
Rance-sama!!
So much...
Rance-sama, there's so much more than usual.
So embarrassing...
So warm...
I feel so much better.
See you later, Sill.
Wish me luck on that infiltration mission.
Yes... Rance-sama...
Tada!
You actually have a pass?!
You didn't commit a crime, did you?
Who's a criminal?
My name is Rance! I'm the strongest warrior around,
an adventurer who lives to seek the truth.
I'm going to look around for a suspicious
ninja who entered this castle earlier.
Ninja?
Now then, time to enter the very heart of Leazus.
Is this a Colosseum?
There was something like this inside Leazus castle?
Looks like some fight is going on.
A weakling like you should just quit while you're ahead!
Shut up!
Huh?
These are the current rankings!
No. 07, Jangabanni Nise.
No. 06, Areki Thunder.
No. 05, Uburi Majishta.
No. 04, Ninja Master!
Ninja Master?!
Ninja... that must be her!
That female ninja who was pretending to be a student.
She knew about Hikari-chan.
Ninja Master?
Is that the Ninja you're searching for?
Yeah. You see, a girl called Hikari-chan
disappeared from Paris Academy.
I'm trying to track her down, but...
She's the only lead I've got.
A girl got kidnapped?!
That's just terrible.
I have to find a way to participate in those Colosseum
matches and confront Ninja Master.
How do I get into the Colosseum?
I have a participation ticket.
Eh? What? Good! Give it to me!
I can't risk a suspicious tournament entrant
getting close to the king.
I wanted to participate myself, but...
I have committed myself to guarding this gate.
I get it I get, I could really care less!
Just give that to me!
But I want to make sure you're worthy.
Is it alright if we leave the castle?
Huh?
Lately, zombies have been lurking around
the Margarine tower over there.
If you help me get rid of them, I'll give
you the ticket to the Colosseum.
How's that?
Sounds like a pain, but whatever.
Mimi-chan, I'm borrowing your shampoo, okay?
Okay.
So, what did Rance want to buy from you?
The hilt of his sword was broken so he wanted a replacement.
It needs to be painted, so I told him it'll take some time.
He said he'll be in Leazus for a while, so there's no rush.
A customer who dares to venture out
in Leazus is actually here, huh?
I guess it's fine for now but...
Eh?
That sort of person may die soon.
If their luck is bad, real soon...
We're gonna get rid of every last one of them!
Yes!
Shut up!
Rance! You're strong!
You too, Menado. You aren't half bad!
Okay! How about we compete for another
prize, besides the participation ticket?
Huh? Compete?
Yeah! We'll see who takes down the most zombies.
The loser has to do whatever the winner wants.
Sounds good, but what are you planning to
ask of me? I have a bad feeling about this...
Isn't it obvious?! It's sex!
If a cute girl is in front of me...
Something perverted is bound to happen!
That is the law of this world!
Yeah!
I-It's not like I'm interested or anything.
Warm.
Who is this warm person?
Give me some of that warmth as well!
Move on to the afterlife, vile woman!
Amazing, he won!
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah...
Good, you don't seem to have any major injuries.
It wouldn't be good if a woman's
body got bruised now, would it...
W-We still don't know who won yet, right?
We haven't counted all the zombies yet, right?
Menado.
The numbers don't really matter, do they?
We have won.
Oh God, Rance is so cool.
I'm... not cute or anything, like how a normal girl would be.
I've always been treated like a boy.
What're you saying? You're cute, I guarantee that.
The men of Leazus, who don't get it, are just plain idiots.
No way...
But I get it.
No...
H-Hey, are we really going to do this on a grave?
What're you saying?
I hear lovers having sex on graves is all the rage these days.
Creating new life above the resting spirits
of the deceased, something like that.
L-Lovers? I-Is that so?
Yeah, it's probably something like that.
Rance is touching me down there!
It's pretty tight, huh?
You don't play with it often?
Eh? Play with it? No way...
I'll have to make careful preparations for this then.
Rance!
Your body is real sensitive, huh!
No matter where I touch, you manage
to give off such splendid reactions!
Don't do it...
Let's see, how about we really check your level of arousal...
Eh?
Try moaning the moment I flick it.
These are some good reactions!
W-Why am I letting out such strange noises?
Well then, now that you're starting to feel good...
Don't! That place is starting to feel weird!
You're dripping wet, aren't you!
My body is acting real strange!
Rance... My body...
It was actually that of a woman all along.
Good. Guess I'll help myself to your insides then!
Ehh? No way! Will this go in?
Relax your body.
Are you alright?
I'm fine... it's alright!
Really? Well, I feel amazing!
Besides, a promise is a promise, right?
That's true.
Well then!
Rance...
Are you feeling good?
Yes! This feels really good!
I'm glad.
Use me to feel even better, Rance!
I see, I see! Okay then. Let's pick up the pace!
Great! This feels amazmg Menado, it's the best!
Rance! My body feels really weird!
You're starting to feel the pleasure, huh?
I don't... know...
Okay then! I'll pound it in deeper and
let you experience true pleasure!
It's deep inside me! This feels so strange!
What is this? My insides are throbbing
before he even thrusts it in!
It's great Menado! Your body's giving off the right
reactions when I'm pounding your womb!
The thing you keep hitting inside me... is that my baby's room?
That's right! Menado, you're cute and
you've got a sexy body to boot!
Your body is downright perverted!
Aren't you a cutie! Alright, I've decided where I'm gonna
cum... Right here! Inside the deepest part of you! Okay?!
Rance!
S-Scared, I'm so scared!
Don't let me fall, Rance!
But you already fell for me.
I-Idiot!
I'm gonna cum! Don't still any of it!
Cum, Rance! Fill me up!
What is this, I don't get it! Your penis feels even bigger!
I'm happy he's letting out so much inside of me!
Good! Now it's time for round two!
Menado, I'm gonna cum again!
Let it all out, Rance!
Rance! Rance!
Are you ready?
Rance, I'll cum! No!
I'm going to cum, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's twitching and gripping me so tight!
Did I just cum as well? Rance, I love you!
Damn! That really hit the spot!
T-Thank you Rance. Being treated
like a woman isn't so bad after all.
Listen Menado, it's fine if you say that to a person like me, but
don't say these things to other people, alright?
Huh?
Hearing something like that from a cute girl like you, most
men will misunderstand and think they actually have a chance.
Yeah, it's only for you, Rance...
What happened?
I felt lonely thinking the place you were
just in is going to be empty now.
I'll go inside of you whenever you want.
Is that a promise?
I will always be waiting for you, Rance.
Let the battles of the Royal Colosseum begin!
K.O.!
Green robed Rance is doing well, but his
next opponent will be a real challenge.
I lose this time.
K.O.! He has won again!
Rance jumps directly to Rank 5!
I've gotten this close to that ninja, but...
We'll finally meet in the next match, huh?
Ladies and Gentlemen!
It's time for the green warrior Rance to face his next
opponent, the one using the ancient art of ninjustsu...
That female ninja! What sort of punishment
should I prepare for her?
Ninja Master arrives!
Who's this?
Splendid! Splendid!
To think that you have made it this far...
Very impressive!
But, alas!
Yes, yes, you shall experience my deadly technique.
Prepare thyself!
You're the wrong person, damn it!
Aren't you impatient!
Wait a second, I'm still in the middle of introducing myself.
Bring out that annoying, but cute, ninja!
Such regret...
Oh! This is a surprise!
Rance has emerged victorious!
What a disaster. So it wasn't that female ninja?
Now I've lost my only lead!
Argh! If we met, I was planning to do this
and that and all sorts of stuff to her!
Hello?
Do you have some time to spare?
Your victory back there was amazing, warrior Rance.
Hot damn! Pretty woman!
I just wanted to talk to you for a bit.
Oh! What about? Do you want an
autograph? Or perhaps a date?
It requires a little privacy, so please, come this way.
Privacy, huh? Not bad.
Isn't this the center of Leazus castle, the Royal Palace?
Yes, the princess became a fan after I showed
her your match. She would like to meet you.
The princess?
By princess, you mean this castle's?
Yes, Leazus kingdom's only princess,
her highness, Rea Parapara Leazus.
This is great! So stuff like this happens
when you win fights at the Colosseum?
I'm Rea-sama's teacher, Maris Amaliris.
Could it be that we've met before?
I don't think so. I hardly ever leave her highness's side.
I was tired of waiting!
Good day! Nice to meet you, Rance-san.
I'm Rea Parapara Leazus.
Oh, as expected of you nobles! You easily
score a 100 points on the cuteness scale.
I saw your fight at the Colosseum!
You're really strong, aren't you?
Actually, after seeing those arms, I have a favor to ask.
What is it? I'll listen to pretty much anything a cute girl says.
Go for it.
Thank you.
Come here, look at that.
There's a villa in that area surrounding the castle.
But ghosts have started appearing over
there, proving to be quite problematic.
Ghosts?
Wait a second. I'm not a priest, you know.
Rance-sama was searching for the whereabouts
of an unknown ninja, correct?
Yeah, how do you know that?
Leazus royalty have access to several
competent intelligence sources.
We know everything.
If you can get rid of these ghosts then,
we'll give you the information you need about
the mysterious ninja, as well as about Hikari.
What did you say? You know about Hikari-chan too?
Though, I was expecting something
a little more erotic for a reward.
You're just as my sources describe you.
Very well, Maris.
Yes.
If you so desire, you can have your way with me.
Do you understand?
H-However I want?!
Oh my, you don't have to get all worked up like that.
I won't run or hide anywhere.
I'll do it!
Leave it to me, I'll take care of this in no time!
Well then, we're counting on you.
Those were some great tits.
Absolutely lovely.
I want to get close to her.
But still, ghosts? How the hell do I cut them?
Oh?
Euram-sama.
Who is that beauty?
You don't know?
It's the Colosseum's best warrior, Euram Mirage.
She doesn't care how many men try to take her down.
She has always maintained her spot at the top of the rankings.
She's strong, beautiful, and cool.
She certainly is beautiful, and looks rather strong.
Strong women are all mostly like that.
Hm? That sword.
Oh, you're the new fighter if I remember right?
Yeah, it's Rance, the one who plans to
win every match with just one strike.
Remember that.
I will remember.
I shall wait for you to reach me.
By the way, that sword. It's special, isn't it?
You have quite an eye for things, don't you.
This cuts things that have no physical shape.
A ghost buster sword.
Hand that over. I have a place I need to use this.
You want me to hand over my precious sword just like that?
How about this... If you manage to defeat
me, I'll listen to anything you say.
You said "anything", right?
Well then, but that sword and yourself in the bet.
You sure have confidence!
Very well. But it's only if you can make it to
the top spot, and break my Gen Muken.
Make sure you don't disappoint me.
She disappeared?
Hey! Don't mess with me! You aren't even here?!
Certain kill...
Gen Muken!
– Eu-Euram Mirage wins and defeats her opponent in a single strike.
– It ended pretty quick, didn't it?
Gen Muken right off the bat?
That technique is... Gen Muken?
Bring it on!
I can't wait to have the strongest woman
moaning like an animal in bed with me!
Wait for me!
No... Forgive me...
Help me...
No!!
Translator: Maq-kun | Hikarukon
Timer | MrMew
Editor | Punk4real