Pulptenx-chan, over here!
Yes, right away!
Pulptenx-chan, over here, too!
Hey, you were Pulptenx-chan, right?
You have an incredible body just like I thought.
Our boss will be very happy with this, too.
No, no...
No!!
Blades fly and bash against each other.
The magic, mysteriously...
Continues to grow its radiance.
Right now, in this wide world,
Translation: Snake   Timing: MrMew   Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
In Quest of Light
Chapter 1 Rance, Stand!!
Right now, in this wide world,
the dears of history start to turn.
Chapter 1 Rance, Stand!!
Her name is Hikari Mi Blanc.
She the daughter of a prestigious
family of Leazas, the Blancs.
About three weeks ago, this girl disappeared
from the school she was studying in.
Go find her.
What? Not suiting to the genius warrior I am,
that is such a boring job.
Go home if you don't want to.
Or does removing bee hives or cleaning kitchen
extractor hoods sound better to you?
So, Hikari Mi Blanc...
Wait, Hikari-chan turns out to be cute!
Alright. This time, for the sake of Hikari-chan's cuteness,
the most power and undefeated explorer, Rance-sama
will get things done in an instant.
I'll leave it to you.
Hey! Sill!
Hurry up, Sill!
How dare a slave like you let your Master wait?
You useless girl!
I'm sorry, Rance-sama.
I lost time looking for a place that sells clean water...
And also, monsters...
Don't make excuses, you slave.
Ah, this is refreshing.
Give me that one, too.
That one is m...
Well, it's almost noon.
Let's have a delicious lunch at Leazas, right Sill?
Alright, now that's decided let's run!
Huh? Rance-sama!
So these are the streets of Leazas...
As expected from what they call the
wealthiest region in the world.
Oh, so it's here.
Rance-sama!
What are we doing next?
You are going to enroll in the school
Hikari-chan was in, Paris Academy.
Huh, enroll?
It's an undercover investigation.
I'm unsure about handing it all to you,
but Paris Academy is an all girls' school, no guys allowed.
It can't be helped.
Um, can we really enroll just like this?
C'mon, did you think that of anyone
I would come without a plan?
I've gone through all the procedures.
Now just go already!
Well then I will now go check out the town,
and investigate in all the beauties!
Explorer's Tip Number 1:
At a new town, start with collecting information.
The pro that I am sticks to the basics like this!
Ice Sugar
Oh, there's a beauty.
Oh hello. Are you looking for a place to stay?
We are the Inn, Ice Sugar.
So this is what it looks like inside.
It's got a strange atmosphere. I like it.
I'll stay here.
Thank you very much.
I am working as the hostess here,
my name is Horikawa Nami.
Nami-san... the Japanese outfit is indeed...
Great!
I cannot hold back anymore!
Takeda Style Jujitsu: Tebasaki Otoshi.
I'm sorry. I'm practicing Jujitsu, so I couldn't help but...
Ju-jujitsu...
Oh... this is...
It's Hikari-chan. I'm looking for this kid.
Have you seen her before?
No... sorry for not being any help.
Don't worry about it. Thanks.
Baltic
The Seaside House: Baltic
The sea!
Huh?
I'm Patty! Patty The Summer!
This a new and innovative tool store!
I'm... Rance-sama.
Whatever... have you seen this girl before?
Whatever but this is a chance!
I'm digging in!
I don't know her.
Next, next!
Akirame
I'm Millie Lincle.
This is the weapon store Akirame...
There you are!
A little gloomy but still cute!
Hey Millie-chan, it's lunch time!
Oh, Rance!
Why...
Geez, next!
Fujisaki Level
I'm Willis Fujisaki from Levels.
Would you like to level up?
Um... Willis Fujisaki C...
Just ready to eat!
Damn it... no matter how seriously I investigate...
There are no clues about Hikari-chan...
Not even a single one... what is going on?
Sill, how's is going? Did you get anything?
Um, she's from a noble family...
And they say that she's an outgoing and friendly person.
Anything about being hated by suspicious people,
or something like her family being in debt?
That's... I didn't get anything about that.
How useless, time to punish you.
I have quite the buildup right now.
As a slave, you must comfort your Master any time!
Here?
What if someone sees?
What? How dare you!?
A slave should only think of her Master!
Spread your legs and stick your butt out!
That's...
Hey c'mon. Hurry and get wet.
Even if you say that...
Hey, wanna go have fun after school today?
Huh? I can't today.
Hey, what are the girl and guy doing over there?
Eh? I didn't see.
Did she sneak in a guy?
Rance-sama, if you don't hurry, someone will come...
What?
Are you trying to give me orders!?
A slave's job is to make me feel good!
Anything else hardly matters!
Th-that's...
That's... please forgive me, Rance-sama!
Then, you'd better satisfy me here.
Well, I plan to satisfy myself no matter what.
Rance-sama...
Big...
Hey, you're completely exposed.
Let your friends watch this!
If they see... something like this... it's embarrassing...
You've completely lost control of your voice.
Well then, charge!
It's good...
Alright, I'm cumming!
Cumming inside!
No! Rance-sama!
It... it hurt...
It's not like it was your first time.
If you're a slave, then be like a slave.
Shut up and take in all of my stuff.
Yes...
Alright, one more time.
But, I'm still...
Up until I'm satisfied, we're having sex!
You're starting to feel good right?
You're squeezing tight!
The last time was quite good.
Well then, you'd better work hard to gather information.
Yes...
Rance-sama...
We're tastier than tamagoyaki!
It's good that I got refreshed, but it doesn't
change the fact that we're stuck.
Old man, get me a gorotti.
Hey, old man!
I've been ordering for a while now! Get to work already!
You've been leaving me here for thirty minutes!
I'm going to write a horrible review of you
guys about this! You okay with that!?
Well, although I think it's useless
asking a cold person like you,
I'm looking for a girl who's gone missing.
A girl gone missing!?
Hikari Mi Blanc.
The daughter of a noble family has gone missing.
The most powerful warrior and undefeatable
explorer, I, have been asked to find her.
Really!?
Isn't that the works of the Endless
Tomorrow Combat Group?
My... My daughter Pulptenx was taken by them, too!
What? The Endless Tomorrow Combat Group?
Apparently they have their HQ in a cave in the forest,
but they're tough, so no one's willing to help.
You there! A noble family's hiring you,
so you're a known warrior, right?
Please! Could you go help my daughter Pulptenx?
Oh, isn't she cute!
It seems like Hikari-chan could be there, too.
I'll get Pulptenx-chan on the way as well, and...
I don't hate this...
Okay, I get it, leave it to me.
Oh, thank you so much, it's all up to you.
Of course I'll give you all my money.
Mhmm.
And also take this as well.
– And this, all this... and this...
– Eh?
– This, too... please... and this.
– No, no... hey, dude... are you listening?
– This, too... please... and this...
– And this...
You fool! I'm going to battle, how
can I take so much stuff?
I'll just take the money... and let's
see... the drink and snack.
I can depend on you, right?
Who do you think I am?
Sorry, I have no idea.
Eh? Really?
Yes. Apprently recently there's been
a group kidnapping people,
called the Endless Tomorrow Combat Group,
and have their HQ in a cave in the forest.
I see...
Yay, I've found something to report to Rance-sama.
Sill-san.
Y-Yes.
We seem to get along well.
I wonder if we can become friends?
Yes!
Don't look down on us! Take your sword out!
I refuse.
I don't plan to rust my sword on pawns like you guys.
Alright! I'll keep this going at
get to Hikari-chan in no time!
And on the way I'll get Pulptenx-chan, too!
Rance-sama! Rance-sama!
I wanted to tell him about the HQ of the thief group...
Even though he'll be here when I need his help,
for some reason he's never here
when I want to see him...
Boss's Room
Looks like this should be their boss's room.
No...
This erotic voice... girls are here.
What an unforgivable person!
I'm the only one who's allowed
to do erotic things with girls!
Dammit!
Guess I need the keys here...
Oh, a face I haven't seen before.
Are you new here?
My oh my, a sexy onee-san.
I'm the vice-captain Necai, cute boy.
Cute?
See, the things like that make you cute.
If you're troubled ask me, okay?
I can't get into Captain's room.
Oh, Captain Riechardt.
He seems to really like the girl recently captured,
and he's been in his room playing with her all the time.
Captured...
Dammit how jealou... I mean unforgi...
I mean jealous I am...
He won't notice just a knock.
I do have the spare key to Riechardt's room.
Here, you see.
Give it to me.
Nope.
I'll take it then!
Attacking me at the same time? How greedy.
Huh? Oh my!
Isn't that the legendary Sake, Yamasaki from year 250?
Hey, will you give me this in exchange for this?
I'll make you feel good.
If it's for this drink, I'll make you feel good right away.
It's great that you felt good.
Well, see you around. Bye!
What a great body.
You've got a really perverted body, girl.
No... I'm not perverted...
If this isn't your lewdness showing, what is it?
Hey, you.
What is it?
Who are you, coming in without permission?
So you're the captain of the thief group.
I, Rance-sama is here to bring judgement!
Geez, not at a time like this.
I'm busy here!
I'm about to give this girl the best present of pleasure!
The best you say?
A pervert like you who kidnaps them against their will,
and torturing them with tools has no right to say that!
Geez.
To think that you'd go against us, the
Endless Tomorrow Combat Group!
You are way too full of yourself!
How annoyingly fast you are.
He's really strong. The uneasy feeling I had was right.
The way you talk... you sure don't know your limits.
How can he be so experience at such a young age!?
This is one heck of a brat!
Wh-What are you doing?
Rance-slash!
Don't look down on me!
Are you okay, Pulptenx-chan?
Oh, this is...
No... forgive me already...
If you do anything like before... I'll...
Is she mistaking me for the perverted captain?
What a tasty situation!
I won't tease you or anything.
I'm digging in!
Did you cum just from putting it in?
Oh, I have to pretend to be the perverted captain.
Ohohoho, you can't take it already?
Have a good taste of what I have!
It's huge...
Take that!
No...
I... even though it's my first time...
why... why does it feel good!?
What?
How I pity that captain.
There. There, there!
What great boobs!
No... don't...
If you rub so hard... they'll break...
You slut! You're a bitch!
No! I'm not a slut!
So, why is it that you're squeezing tight on my dick?
It's proof that you're slutty!
No...
I hate it because it's with a thief... but... why?
I can't take it anymore...
Alright.
– C'mon, cmon. C'mon!
– No...
My head... going blank...
Alright, I'm going to cum!
I'll let out everything inside for you!
No! Not inside...
I'll get... I'll get a baby...
Like I care!
I'm a ruthless criminal, so I do what I want!
No, no...
Cumming, cumming...
Cumming!
Then, let's go one more time.
No way.
I'll do it until I'm all satisfied!
No...
This is... is... good... it is.
It's all alright now, Pulptenx-chan.
Now, let's go home.
Um, I...
I've taken care of the criminals.
I'm called Rance.
I'm an explored your father's paid to come save you.
Thank you very much.
You can be at ease now.
Yes.
By the way, was there another girl who was captured?
No, I think I'm the only one here.
No way... I come all the way here but nothing...
Thank you. Thank you! Thank you!!
I've never thanked someone this much ever in
my life please take this as my thanks please...
Geez, don't be so whiny!
Rance-san, thank you so much.
If you want... please visit the store again.
See you.
But it turned out to have nothing to do with Hikari-chan...
I did so much but it was still a miss...
Miss... empty... TC9801vm=NHD4disksMSX6...
I don't care who it is I just want to do it!
I found a girl!
He noticed me following him. How?
Wait up, you!
You were looking at me just now, right?
All you can do is watch over me, what a shy girl!
But that is good, tool
I sense love!
Unbelievable. How fast.
Where in the world...
Get out of the case of Hikari Mi Blanc.
What you say?
I'll say it one more time only. End your
investigation of Hikari Mi Blanc here.