Oh, what's wrong? Bringing something like that.
Well, this might come in handy.
Is that so?
Target... acquired.
My, Rance, good work.
Do you need something?
Yeah.
I have something to report.
I wonder what it'll be about.
Let's hear it.
The ghosts at the mansion have disappeared.
Oh, thank you.
Now I can use that mansion again.
To play with your kidnapped girls again?
Indeed.
It's not good for your body to endure too much.
She just let it slip without any hesitation.
Why?
Why, you ask?
Why did you torture girls to their deaths?
That's because... it's fun!
They resist and fight back at first, though.
Then they slowly succumb to it.
"Please", "Forgive me", "Stop it already".
There's nothing to forgive, though.
I just wanted to see their faces while I'm doing it.
You said you'd give me info about Hikari-chan.
But you actually kidnapped her yourself, correct?
Indeed!
I specifically built Paris Academy here
in Leazas to search for my "toys".
Maybe I should go for that Sill girl?
Wha...
What did you do to Sill?
She's probably been captured by my ninja now.
So you'll meet her soon.
Now I see.
Now I finally understand... you perverted lezzie queen!
So, about you.
A crazy bitch like you.
Needs some spanking!
Lia-sama!
Holy Disintegrator!
Magic?!
What?
Looks like we can't leave things as is anymore, Rance-san.
I'm not sure what caused you to go nuts like that, but oh well.
You see, I actually am really fond of you.
Strength, fighting capability, dullness, and spirit!
You're basically the perfect pet for me!
Pet, you say?
That's right.
A pet that would rape-women as I see fit.
Not a bad idea, right?
That Sill girl, Hikari,
all the other girls,
you can fuck them all day and night.
Isn't it the ideal life that you want?
Hmph, I refuse, idiot girl.
Oh, I see.
Such a bothersome dog.
Oh well, you're not going to be able
to resist eventually, anyway.
That ninja!
What's going on so suddenly?
F-Forgive me, Lia-sama.
The target has escap...
O' flame.
Sill!
Magic?
And it's quite powerful.
Rance-sama!
Over here, Sill!
Break these off with your magic.
R-Right away!
What's that?
It seems like an explosion.
That sound just now,
it's quite near.
It's inside Leazas castle!
Lia-sama, in here.
What? That's such a bummer.
The explosion was over here.
Yes, it's probably here.
Rance?
Oh, it's you, Menado.
Rance, you said?
That super cocky guy?
Why are you here?
Just a bunch of onlookers.
Perfect timing.
Help me find it.
Just what are we supposed to find?
I was able to corner the culprit,
but they escaped using a hidden opening!
Damn.
In that case, use this to find it quickly.
Oh, that's a lifesaver!
Wait,
you two are also here?
My shop extends over the back side of this castle.
I was on my way to deliver some weapons at the coliseum.
Jackpot, jackpot!
It says over here.
Alright, let's chase them, Sill.
Okay!
Wait, wait!
The item from earlier costs one hundred gold!
Oh well, I'm gonna be paid big time after this, anyway.
Here.
Big time?
I can feel the sound of income coming!
Why are there so many monsters in this place?
Rance-sama, here's your sword.
Gotcha.
I'm going too, Rance!
This is quite interesting.
Yulang!
Got it!
I'll show you my phantom blade!
Millie-chan, let's go too!
Gonna fight yer way out, eh?
I'm gonna clean this up on the double!
This is good training for me.
Let's go!
Take this!
Hame.
Flash!
Wow, even though you're a monster girl.
No!
Be careful.
They're still monsters!
Copy that.
Leave the big one to me!
Here I go!
Don't let go, Patty-chan.
That was dangerous.
We've gotten past the monster army.
We're safe now, Rance-sama!
Hmph, I can handle all of that by myself, though.
You may have taken me by surprise
at the park with my lack of sleep,
but today I'm at full power!
Now then,
it's punishment time.
I'm going to make this sloppily slimy wet...
Rance-sama.
...is what I wanted to say,
but I want you to say where your boss is.
I'll let if you off then.
Lia-sama's location?
Then I have just one answer.
I'll protect Lia-sama, and kill you!
I might also die, but.
Ten!
Katon no Jutsu!
What the heck is this?!
Magic?
I'm not sure.
But it doesn't seem to be the case.
What the hell?
Sill, can't you do something?
But all three of us will be in danger!
I'll defeat you.
Rance...
Attack!
I never knew she was prepared to sacrifice herself.
Do you really have an obligation to do
that much for that perverted queen?
She saved my life before.
She's actually a good woman.
I don't know about that.
Now, spit it.
Where is Queen Lia?
Of course I won't say it.
Just where in the world would you find a ninja that was tricked
by her enemy to reveal anything about her master?
So you won't say, huh.
Then it can't be helped.
Yes, I'm afraid it can't.
You seem to be looking forward to this, Rance-sama.
I'll ask your body directly!
No way!
Alright then,
I wonder how many fingers will go in before you say it.
Rance-sama, your face is starting to look villainous.
Maris.
Hey, Maris!
Hey, let's rest for a bit.
We've been walking fon a long time and I'm tired already.
Ria-sama.
But that man may still be chasing us down.
I'm too tired to walk!
Maris, can you bring me something cold?
Certainly, Ria-sama.
In...
At the end of this hallway, there is a passage
that only the royal family takes.
Gave up after four fingers, eh.
You've endured well.
Rance-sama, your face, your face!
Alright! Let's go, Sill!
Oh, yes! Rance-sama!
I'm not letting you get away!
How lucky!
The queen is captured!
I thought you'd be with your attendant.
Lia-sama!
Wait up.
Aren't you concerned that something might happen to her?
Gotcha!
Maris!
Hey, don't be too noisy.
Come on, let me go, you brute!
I said hold still!
Sill, make her sleep.
Eh? O-Okay.
Now then,
it's punishment time.
You said I could do it however I want, right?
A smart woman like you knows what will
happen if you don't comply, right?
Ria-sama will.
Hey, hey, hey!
Now this is something.
I never imagined that the Leazas castle's head attendant
would have such a voluptuous body.
What's with those boot (остальное уехало вправо за экран, сабдесу задаёт новый стандарт качестава.).
Those boobs make it seem like their owner
can't resist sucking men's cum.
Such foolish words.
Move that arm away.
The queen is precious to you, right?
You're Maris, right?
My thing down here is already so
lively thanks to your erotic body.
So, what do you want me to do?
Let's take this one first.
It's so supple to the touch.
I wonder how it tastes.
It's truly great.
I love your style, woman.
Let me give you my mark.
This man is just casually fondling another woman's breasts.
How much does he plan on sucking them?
Alright.
Straddle me.
Hm? It's not wet yet.
Get it wet and put it in already.
I can't just get it wet on a whim.
Then let's change plans.
I think I wanna rape the queen in her sleep instead.
Hey, Sill.
Y-Yes!
Wait.
Come on, my big bomb here is up and ready.
You can use it freely if you want to.
Use it.
It's drilling... into me!
Good, good.
It's gone deep and it's gripping me very nicely.
Come on, start moving.
It feels good that way,
but your movements are unrefined.
Fuck more intensely.
Even if you say that.
Okay, Sill.
Hit the queen.
Huh?
Hit... the queen?
Just pick any rock there and slam it on her.
Choose something very rough.
That's terrible, Rance-sama!
Shut up.
Just do it!
Oh?
Whoa, you've gotten better all of a sudden!
Good, good!
It's pleasant, tight, and it drives me crazy.
Does it feel pleasurable to you too?
Yes.
It feels... good.
You've gotten the hang of it already.
You know your stuff, woman.
I love that, you know.
Okay, let out your voice more and moan!
It's stiff, and hot.
Yeah, that's right.
You need to make me enjoy this, Maris!
This feels great. So easy.
But still very great.
It's great seeing a prideful woman moan like this.
No matter how much they fake it,
the moment that accept it, they've already submitted to me.
Are you about to cum too, Maris?
Yes, I'm going to cum.
So please.
Alrighty.
Huh? I'm...
Lia-sama!
Wow, it's squeezing me!
Maris... huh?
What's wrong, Maris?
Your punishment's not done yet.
Whoa, this is terrific!
Huh? Wait, Maris, what are you doing?
Shut yer mouth.
Sill, make her shut up.
O-Okay.
Sorry about this.
What's wrong, Maris?
You're suddenly squeezing me so tightly.
Did you get aroused when the queen saw you like that?
No... I wasn't.
Ah well, whatever.
That aside, I'm about to cum!
If you want it, you'll have to properly squeeze it!
Its rubbing my depths so hard!
Lia-sama is.
Lia-sama.
Please don't look.
Maris is already head over heels for my big bomb, you know?
Alright, then let's show it to her clearly.
Oopsie.
Stop!
No, please end this already.
Release it... please release it.
Cum lots, please!
Where exactly? Say it!
Please.
Please cum lots of your hot stuff inside me.
Inside me, please!
Okay, here I go!
Out it goes!
So hot.
It's pumping slowly inside me.
Oh, it's coming out, and just keeps pouring inside.
It's coming out.
It's filling my insides.
Indeed.
So hot.
Come on, drink what's left.
Hey, it's spilling! Such a waste.
Maris, Leazas castle's head attendant,
you're looking really good there.
Remember this and never forget.
Now then, time for the main dish.
Sill, gimme the queen.
Eh? Well.
Okay.
Mari...
Lia-sama.
Hey!
Just when I finally got her!
This is the last.
Healing Nine!
What willpower.
This woman's really tough.
Hey, hey, hey.
Healing Nine?
It's a spell that rejuvenates your body
so much that it makes you berserk.
I'm not letting you get to Lia-sama!
Li-Lia-sama is,
an unfortunate girl.
She was very kind as a child.
But ever since her brothers started competing for the throne,
her heart started to shatter.
That doesn't mean she can just do as she pleases!
I'm...
I'm going to defend her, no matter what.
You said her heart shattered, right?
You simply left her in that state.
You really are amazing.
I was surprised!
Victory is yours.
That's all that matters now.
Hey, being a pet is really a waste.
Why don't you just become my direct subordinate like Maris?
You'll be treated marvelously.
If it's status you want, I can just grant
you the highest military position,
and I'll give you whatever woman you desire.
R-Rance-sama's dream.
You'll never have to worry about a thing, right?
Let me hear your answer.
Yeah, I'll answer.
That hurt.
Hey.
This can't be!
It's punishment for such a stupid queen like you!
Well? Have a full taste of this!
You've never even shown restraint in torturing
all of the girls that you've kidnapped.
These handles are perfectly positioned for this.
Those aren't handles!
Whatever!
Wait!
No, please stop this!
What are you saying?
Your mouth's just warming up, and we're
just about to pick up the pace!
What a sight.
I wonder how all of those who were tortured
will react when they see you like this.
Alright, for my first shot!
How terrible!
This is terrible. So stinky!
I've been soiled.
What are you saying?
We're just getting started.
W-Wait, what's the meaning of this?
I said what I meant.
Whoopsie!
Another whoopsie!
Just wait!
Wow, such a nice view.
N-No.
It's amazing.
There probably won't be another chance for
me to fuck a kingdom's queen like this.
S-Stop.
Th-This is a joke, right?
Here we go.
No way.
What are you putting that dick in me for?
You're doing something completely outrageous!
Do you really think you'll be forgiven for this?
After hearing that, there's just one more thing left to say.
And that's.
That I love sex!
That's great, Queen Lia!
I-I never imagined that you'd really!
Did you think I was the type that could be stopped by threats?
When I do something, I see it through till the end!
No, it hurts.
Don't move!
Nope.
Doesn't feel good if I don't.
And it feels so good when I do!
Ow, ow, ow... please save me!
Didn't those tortured girls say the same thing to you?
And what did you say to them?
That's.
That's why I'm not stopping either!
Why are you drilling my insides like that?
My insides are getting completely massaged.
Oh, did I find a tender spot?
Please, stop pushing in further.
No... any more and...
It hurts, it hurts.
Please, please forgive me.
I'm sorry!
You did bad things, so nope.
This feels good.
I'm about to cum now.
C-Cum?
Wait, that's!
I'll be cumming inside, of course.
S-Stop!
So good!
No way... you really came inside.
I already said I'm sorry.
I sure came lots.
This looks great.
I'm not going to forgive you.
Doing something like this!
Huh? You really think this is over?
Wait, I thought men weren't supposed to
cum for a while after they came once?
Your punishment still continues!
No way!
No!
Forgive me. Please forgive me already.
Okay, here I come... wait, how many times is this now?
Oh well, forget it.
It's inside again, please don't cum inside me.
Looks like you got used to this already.
It's getting easier to fuck you now.
Please, I beg of you.
Any more and I'll.
Okay, let's see.
Do you repent for your actions now?
I-I do!
So please!
Nope!
Please!
You're cumming too much.
Please.
I just asked if you feel guilty or not.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum again!
It's pumping into me again.
This is amazing, my Queen.
I didn't even break a sweat while raping you on and on like this!
I can still go a long, long time!
No, please, no more.
Come on.
I-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, please don't, I'm already sorry!
I'm going to pump it all again. Feeling happy?
Yes... please do.
This.
The hammer of
justice!
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
I guess I went overboard.
Well, still very erotic, though.
Alright, let's cum one last time.
Please fuck me more!
Darling, darling!
Whoa, that's kinda sloppy for a queen, don't you think?
I've cummed my last now.
I think that may have been the most I've ever cum.
As expected of the Queen, you're very delicious.
Case solved!
Rance-sama, is the Queen going to be alright?
Yup. Though I may have fucked her a bit too much.
Wh-What are we going to do?
Wanna go back to Ice?
On foot.
Wh-What about the Queen?
Just let her be.
Case solved.
I punished her.
It felt good.
Everything's back in order.
Let's go!
O-Okay!
My job is done.
I've prevailed without failure.
After acquiring the large bounty from the Keith guild,
I've now come back safely to my own home in Ice.
Nothing like a gold bath after saving Hikari-chan.
It kinda hurts, though.
Rance-sama!
Hey, come on and take a dip too.
It'll kinda hurt, though.
This is bad!
Don't ignore me.
That, that.
That queen from Leazas is!
Rance-sama!
It's me, it's Lia!
I've finally come to realize my affection for you!
I can no longer live without you!
Marry me, darling!
Ow!
The dispatch guards,
as well as the bodyguards,
are now at your disposal.
Okay, thanks, Maris!
You look so beautiful, Lia-sama.
Uh oh.
Things are getting out of hand.
Hurry up and bring my clothes and sword!
Right away!
From the back door.
Rance!
Hey, Rance, what's the meaning of this?!
You did something outrageous even to the Queen!
W-Well I, uh, actual...
Get out and explain this to me!
Rance-sama?
Can't be helped, then.
Let's blow it up.
Boom!
We're gonna boom!
What are we going to do, Rance-sama?
Why escape, of course!
I'll never be bound to one woman!
Rance-sama, but where are we going?
Anywhere!
Let's go anywhere!
Let's go, Sill, come with me!
Okay!
Wherever you want!
Yeah!
So lively.
Is this a festival?
Rance-sama.
What?
I-It's nothing.
Is that so?
Damn those kids.