Brought U By JPz Records
Rance-sama... Wasn't that a girl's scream just now?
Anyone there?! Somebody, help me!
Please, help me!
Those guys suddenly attacked me...
Ah, here they come!
Oh, there ya are!
We ain't gonna let ya off the hook!
The fun part's gonna start here!
Hey, ya! That chick is...
For scums like you guys to talk to my supreme presence is a trillion years too early...
What the fuck?!
Everybody! It's best you all hurry and apologize to Rance-sama!
Shuddap!
Although you're unworthy, be grateful that I'm about to give you the honor of my name.
I'm the strongest hero in history...
RANCE!
C... Cool...
You weaklings should die already!
Staaaaabbing!!
Rance Attaaaaack!!
So weak...
P-Please, spare me!
No way.
Sill, what are you waiting for?
Take everything that's valuable from their corpses.
Umm... Well, Rance-sama... I think that would be considered desecration of the dead.
Sill! As my slave, don't you dare contradict your master's order!
I'm sorry, Rance-sama!
Well then...
Umm... Thank you very much...
How can I show my gratitude?
Gratitude? Then how about...
Showing gratitude with your body!
Hey! Shut up and stay still!!
Save me!
Rance-sama... is doing it with another girl again...
So good!
More! More!
No matter what, I'll do whatever it takes to revive you...
And then, we'll kill all those fools at the Oasis!
Rance-sama! We are so glad you came after a long journey.
Well duh, I journeyed from afar... Show some more gratitude.
Oh-oh... yes... A-Anyway, the mistress is waiting...
I've brought Rance-sama.
This way.
Welcome, Rance-sama.
Note: Sheikh is Arabic title of a person who is a Islamic scholar.
I'm the Sheikh of this Oasis.
You may call me, Ani.
S-S-Something wrong?
I wanna fuck you...
Huh?!
Rance-sama has a bad habit of talking to himself from time to time...
It's nothing... Just a mental note...
More importantly... Since I'm history's strongest fighter and most handsome man around...
You must have had a good reason to call me here, right?
Right.
Rance-sama, do you know?
Three months ago, there were bandits attacking this Oasis.
I want to discuss with you about the Green Scorpion.
So, what gives about this "Guri-Guri Suko-Suko"?
It's "Green Scorpion", Rance-sama!
The Green Scorpion has captured...
Around 20 virgins from this Oasis over the last three months...
What?! Virgins, you say?
Yes.
Many others have fallen victim to them as well.
How horrible!
All we know about the Green Scorpion is that their leader is a woman.
We tried to defend ourselves, but it was no use.
Their combat skills are just too great...
That's why we have no option but to rely on a professional.
I got it!
Don't say any further!
I'll get rid of those "Guri-guri suko-suko" bastards!
Oh, Rance-sama!
And then I'm gonna catch that girl-leader,
and we'll be doing it over and over...
Rance-sama... You're drooling...
No...
You MUST kill that woman, no matter what!
Huh?
In memory of all the victims she has killed, we can't forgive her!
What a waste, but if you insist, let it be that way.
I'm gonna cut off that fuckin' bitch's head
and decorate this table with it!
Thank you very much!
It's nothing, nothing!
Hahahahahahahahahahahaha!
By the way, what about the reward?
As I promised, we have those 20,000 gold pieces ready for you...
Of course, I'll take the money, but I do have another wish.
If it's something you can get in this village,
you can ask for anything...
You mean it?! You really mean it?!
Good, good, good, good, good!
I'll be sure to remember those words!
Nahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha!
I'm gonna kill those bandits like "one-two-three",
and then fuck Ani-chan...
Wh-What are you doing?
Ani-chaaaan!
Didn't you say you'll do anything?
Eat this!!!
I can't wait...
Rance-sama! You're nosebleeding, nosebleeding...
Umm... Rance-sama...
Ani, rest aroused...
Nooo, I mean...
Rest assured that I'll do what I have to do so wait here!
Aha-aha...
Hahahahahahahahahahahaha!
Hi, welcome! What's it gonna be?
How about ordering our Scorpio special dish?
Is something wrong, mister?
How much would you be?
Huh?
If you like it raw, it's 30 gold pieces...
That's fuckin' cheap!
Yeah, I'll take it!
Okie dokie! Be right back!
I wonder if she's gonna go ready the room or something.
Nice, very nice!
Oh, Sill, you wait here.
Rance-sama...
Thank you for waiting!
What the fuck is this?
Note: Rance asks for the price of "kimi", the Japanese word for "you".
However, "kimi" also means "egg yolk".
And so, the waitress incorrectly assumes what he meant.
Like you said...
It's a yolk!
An egg Y-O-L-K!
Where's the master owner of this joint?!
Yes?! Here, I'm here!
Yes? Here I am!
What the fuck are you?
I'm the master owner of this place, Idabashi!
What the fuck?!?!
Son of a bitch! You're being too stupid for a Haniwa?!
I'm gonna fuckin' slit you in two!
Rance-sama! Please, spare him mercy, mercy!
Fuck no!
Is this how you fuckin' train waitresses in this joint?!
Please, forgive me, forgive me!
Shut the fuck up!!
My innocent heart has been hurt fuckin' badly!
Pay me 300 gold pieces as compensation!! Got that?!
Count it properly, will ya, Sill?
Yes, Rance-sama!
Good...
Well then, Idabashi, I'm gonna question you about several things now, so be grateful.
Oh, I see...
How did I end up like this...
Did you say something?!
No, no, it's nothing!
That's what I thought!
Obedience is the best quality for humans!
But I'm a Haniwa, you know...
Fuck with me again, I swear you'll be deadmeat!!
Y-Yes!
Well then, tell me all you know about the Green Scorpion.
Huh?
Don't you fuckin' "huh" me!!
Didn't I just fuckin' tell you to tell me all you know about the Green Scorpion?!
Yes!
T-The Green Scorpion...
Usually appear from the desert on nights with a crescent moon to attack the village...
And then, return to the desert once again!
Nights with a crescent moon, you say?
Hey, Sill, what kind of moon is it tonight?
Crescent moon, Rance-sama!
I'm so fuckin' lucky!
For sure, the Goddess of Luck really wants me to fuck her that badly!
Hahahahahahahaha!
I guess, I'll get going now...
Wait up!
There's also one more thing I wanna know.
Tell me what you know about the Sheikh of this Oasis, Ani-chan!
You mean, Mistress Ani?!
She's the most caring person...
That ain't what I wanted to know.
What I wanna know if she has any weaknesses!
Rance-sama?!
She may have agreed to the fee...
But she might protest if I ask for her body...
That's why I'm here...
M-M-Mistress Ani doesn't have any weak points at all!
Hey, you... I feel like you're hiding something!
Tell me the truth, or you're dead!
I'm not...
Mistress Ani was once attacked by some bandits in the middle of the village!
So? Did they stick it in?
To be frankly speaking, they did...
They were so strong, all the people who witnessed it pretended they didn't see anything.
All right! If I kill those fuckers,
Ani-chan will definitely let me fuck her?
N-No, coz they're already dead.
What?! Who curtained 'em?! Tell me who interfered?!
They were all killed in the first attack of Green Scorpion!
You fuckin' asshole!
There's no point on doin' this shit then!
Noooooo!
Why the fuck would you tell me something useless?!
Rest in peace...
Noooooo...
Is there anything else you wanna fuckin' tell me?!
Noooooo!
Nooooo!
Somebody! Somebody, please, help me!
NOOOOOOOOOO!
That was a good workout.
Rance-sama, I've made some tea.
Nah, forget about that.
Let's fuck.
Jeez, you're such a numskull!
Suck on this! Hahahahaha!!
It's the Green Scorpion!
I-I have to warn everybody fast!
That was pretty good, Sill.
Rance-sama...
Now, for the 3rd Round!
Let's do it doggystyle!
Ah... Umm... Rance-sama...
Can we rest for a bit?
Fuck that!
There's no word "rest" in the dictionary of my huge Hyper Weapon!
Let's fuckin' do it, Sill!
Rance-sama!
What the hell?!
I've been waiting for you, bastards!
They call me...
The defenders of women!
The destroyer of demons and all those evil stuff!
Rance-sama, the Swordsman!!
Rance-sama, you're so cool!!
Hahahahahahaha!
Hey, you sons of bitches!
You should be grateful that I'm gonna send you all to hell myself!
Here I go!!
Rance-sama! We're on the...
Rance-sama! Are you all right?!
Go get 'em!
Rance-sama!
Damn you, motherfuckers!!
Stabbing!!
Rance Attaaaaack!!
These bastards ain't human!
They're just a buncha armors being controlled by magic!
Rance-sama! Watch out!
Fire Lazer!
Good! Well done, Sill!
Yeah! Rance-sama praised me!
Bastard!
Rance-sama!!
What the fuck is that tower?
Take this!
Ya alive, Sill?
Yes, Rance-sama!
Now the show is about to begin!
That man who came to kill me is approaching!
Kill him!
And then destroy the village!
Rance-sama, it has been two hours already.
Those bandits haven't made a move at all, right?
Yeah... They gotta be...
Afraid of me?
I don't think so.
I'm sorry, Rance-sama!
As long as you understand.
Even so, those bastards...
If they won't come out, we'll make a move from here!
We'll face them head on, Sill!
That's being reckless, Rance-sama!
Leave it to me.
I have a plan.
Excuse me, Mr. Green Scorpion?
You got mail!
Didn't work, huh?
Plan B...
Do you believe in Jesus Christ?
Sir, JPz Records got a new remix for you.
Rance-sama! There's an open door here!
Enter if you dare.
I'll take you to the darkest pits of hell.
Rance-sama, why is there a jungle in a place like this?
No idea.
This is a rather strange place, if you ask me.
Ra... Rance-sama...
You shouldn't... It's too sudden...
Don't do it, Rance-sama... Now's not the time...
Wasup with you?! I didn't do shit!
Really?
Then, this is...
So you finally deicded to show up, huh!
Rance-sama!
Sill!
Damn it!
Cut it out already!
R-Rance-sama! Are you okay?
Do I look like I'm fuckin' okay?!
There are stairs over there!
Wanna check it out?
Yes!
Damn you!
However, but it's not over yet.
If we fall, it's game over, right?
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Rance-sama! It's the Hello Army!
That's Rommel!
Okay, Sill! I'll leave the Hello guys to you.
I'm gonna kill that Rommel!
Fire Arrow!
Helloooooooooooooooo!
Firaga!!
I'm gonna kill all of ya!!
Gahahahahaha!
He's not bad...
That man... Rather than killing him, using him would be better...
If he reaches all the way here.
Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die!
Rance-sama became a psychopath!
Idiot! I'm a decent human being!
I was just making sure that I had finished 'em off properly.
Well then, after rampaging that much,
I've gained enough experience.
It's been a while since I 've summoned her out.
Level Goddess, Willis!
Heed my call!
I summon thee!!
I am the Great Level Goddess, Willis.
Thou art the one who summoned me, is it not?
That's right!
Give us our level ups!
Please do.
I understand.
Well then, let the ritual begin!
Hey, c'mon, c'mon! Shake that ass more!
Please don't touch the dancer.
Rance-sama, according to the experience, thou became level 45.
Obviously.
As for Sill, according to the experience, thou art now level 40.
Yeah! Thank you so much!
Well then, after thou hath conjured more experience, please summon me again.
For now, farewell!
What a nice woman...
Once I'm level 99, I'll rape her.
Oh, how cute!
Who the hell are you guys?
We are the Detection Hannys!
We don't allow intruders here!
We don't!
Gahahahahahahahahahaha!
And what can you pipsqueaks do to stop us?!
Like this!
Your little attack...
Are these pipsqueaks made up of Youkai fluid?
Why you!
Damn these pipsqueaks!
Rance-sama, please leave it to me.
Since I just leveled up,
I should be able to use a new magic!
All right! Do it, Sill!
If you fail, I'll punish you!
Okay!
*Chanting*
Tornado Flame!
I did it, Rance-sama!
Damn this fuckin' shit!
With my Rance Attack, I'll...
Oh fuck!
It looks like that's the end of it.
After coming all this way...
Stop it! Release those people at once!
What's goin' on?
Woah! We're saved!
Were they so impressed by my greatness?
Now's our chance! Let's run, Sill!
Y-Yes, Rance-sama!
Woah, this place is...
What, what is this? A Ranko party?
Let me join as well!
Wait a second, Rance-sama!
Take a closer look!
For what reason are they doing this?
Fuck this!
Do you think I'm gonna fuckin' let 'em do all the fun without me?!
It is I who should be fuck 'em!
Rance-sama!
Ani-san?
Why is Ani-san doing in such a place?
Sill, you idiot!
It's pretty obvious that she wanted to see me!
Is that so?
Rance-sama... Let's hurry and take those girls outside!
Before he wakes up.
He?
Come on, hurry...
What's wrong, Ani-san?
Rance-sama, before we go outside...
The two of us alone have something to discuss.
Now I'm fuckin' horny!
Sill! Save those girls and head outside first!
Ah! But, Rance-sama!
Don't talk back to me!
Come, Rance-sama, over here.
Was there a room like this?
Oh, Ani-san...
Come here, Rance-sama.
Let's fuckin' do it, Ani!
I'll let you fully taste the true power of my Ultra Super Hyper Weapon!
Take this, this, this, this, this and this!!
Come on, everyone, hurry up and run!
Rance-sama...
There you go, there you go...
Oh! I'm cumming!
Cum!!
HERE I CUM!!!
Ani, that was the best.
Rance-sama, do you know why the virgins were gathered in this tower?
This tower is actually a giant living being.
And to move this tower,
the sexual energy of virgins is needed.
What?
But I couldn't revive it only with that.
In the end, a triggering explosive was needed.
Which was, a strong man's semen...
It's what you gave me just now!
What the fuck are you plannin' to do?!
With the semen you gave me,
it will soon revive...
The strongest Atlas Hanny in history!
What the fuck?!
Rance-sama!
Alas, the Atlas Hanny has finally revived!
Now I can kill everyone in the village!
What did you fuckin' say?
I can't forgive all those who deserted me to be raped!
I planned to kill them all sooner, but...
The "good other me" keeps getting in my way!
The "good other me"?
Rance-sama!
That you, Ani?
It's me! Before it's too late,
I should tell you everything.
Because of the shock from back then when I was raped, my personality split into two!
Split personality?
Exactly...
At the time when I was raped, my personality split into two...
Another part of me started to hate those people in the village who didn't save me.
Under the influence of my other half,
I gained the ability of telepathy.
There I learned about Altas Hanny.
Furthermore, the other me...
Borrowed a small amount of power that leaked out from the seal of the Atlas Hanny.
There, the other me created the Green Scorpion
and started to attack the village.
There began the gathering of virgins to revive the Atlas Hanny.
At the same time, completely destroying the village to annihilation.
To stop it, I tried killing myself many times...
But I couldn't because the other me got in the way.
The only option I had left was for someone to kill me.
So that's the reason why you hired me.
Even so, the other me took advantage of your disposal to revive the Altas Hanny.
But I can't let her do as she pleases anymore!
I beg you, Rance-sama!
Please kill me!
What?
I'm now one with the Atlas Hanny's Central Nervous System!
If I die, the Atlas Hanny should return back to being a tower.
Rance-sama, blow me from this wall and kill me!
Hurry up, Rance-sama!
Kill me!
Kill me now!!
Ha! I will not let my other half interfere anymore!
I'll kill everyone who tries to interfere with me!
Rance! The same goes for you!!
Oh shit!
Good job!
One more blast and the town will be done for.
Tsk, that's some power you got there!
Rance! I'll have you dead before the village people die!
This time I will not miss!
Rance-sama!
Fire Lazer!
What?!
Rance-sama!
Sill, you're late!
Are you okay, Rance-sama?
Sill, blow up that wall!
What? But...
Don't fuckin' talk back to me!
Hurry up and just do it!
What are you planning to do, Rance?
Planning to kill me, Rance?
But if I die, my other half will die too.
Can you live with that guilt?
Rance! This is the final blow!
You fuckin' idiot!
Do you think...
I wouldn't fuckin' listen to the wish of a woman I just fucked with?!
Sill!
Y-Yes!
Extra Large Fire Lazer!
R-Rance-sama...
Thank you...
What a pitiful person, isn't she?
W-What are we going to do, Rance-sama?!
The village has been destroyed!
Well, there's nothing we can do about it, Sill.
This kinda thing happens often.
B-But!
At times like this, it's best we do something else to forget about the subject.
So...
Sill!
Let's fuck!!
Nooo!!
Let's fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!!
Translator & Editor: Enosioph Leviticus
Encoder: Yuu
Karaoker: Lexica-chan
DJ: Xenoglossia
Timer & Typesetter: Enosioph Leviticus
Quality Checkers: Shunrai, Ray & Ron
Distro: Webbmaster62