Oh? Bringing that thing out, is something the matter?
Yes. I may be needing it, after all.
Oh really?
Target acquired.
Oh my, Rance! Good work.
Do you need anything?
Yeah, I have something to report.
Whatever could it be? Care to let me in on the fun?
The ghost in the mansion is gone.
Oh, great. Thanks!
Now I can use that mansion again.
Are you going to use it to play
with the girls you've abducted?
Yes! It's not healthy to hold off
on something you love doing!
This bitch, saying it so lightly.
Why?
Why what?
Why do you torture girls to death?
Because it's fun, you see!
At first I just wanted to punish those who oppose me,
but it really grew on me.
They all say things like "Stop this, please! Forgive me!".
There was nothing to forgive, though.
I just wanted to see their reactions.
You told me you had information on Hikari-chan,
but are you the one who actually abducted her?
Why, yes!
Paris Academy was built as my own garden
to help me pick out my next toy.
I think it'll be that Sill girl next.
You bitch! What did you do to Sill?!
She's probably been captured by my ninja.
You'll be able to see her soon.
Now I know what kind of person you are,
you sick fucking queen.
So, moving onto you...
Perverted, twisted girls like you deserve a good spanking!
Lia-sama!
Holy Disintegration Wave!
Magic?!
The hell?
Good morning. It's time to take care of you now, Rance-san.
I have no idea why you were suddenly
so violent, but that is no matter.
I am actually quite fond of you.
You possess strength, will, avarice, and intelligence.
You are the most fit to become my pet.
P-Pet, you say?
Yes.
The pet that will violate the girls on my command.
Not a bad thing to be, right?
Whether it's with that girl named Sill,
Hikari-chan, or any other girl,
you can play with them all you want,
until you're bored of them!
Isn't it all you've ever wished for?
I refuse. Dumb cunt.
Oh?
You're quite an annoying puppy, aren't you?
You'll change your mind soon enough.
Is that the ninja?!
What do you want?!
M-My apologies Lia-sama,
but I came to report that the next target has...
O, flames...
Sill!
Magic? That's a powerful spell!
Rance-sama!
Sill, get over here!
Use your magic to release me!
R-Right away!
What?!
It sounded like an explosion.
Did you hear that sound just now?
It came from somewhere close.
That's from the Leazus castle!
Lia-sama, let us go this way for now.
Eh? How anticlimactic.
The explosion came from here!
Yeah, most likely!
Rance?!
Oh, is that you, Menad?
Did you say Rance?
That conceited guy?!
Wh-Why are you all here?!
Just passing by.
Good timing. All of you, help me search.
Search for what?
I cornered the kidnapper,
but she used a secret passage to get away!
Shit!
In that case, you can use this to find it immediately!
Oh, thanks a lot!
What the hell? You guys are here too?!
My yakisoba's killing it at the castle!
I came to deliver weapons to an assassin.
They say it's this way.
Right. We're going after them, Sill!
Yes!
Wait, wait! The item you just used costs 100 gold!
Whatever. I'll be paid after this is over anyway. Take it.
More money? I can smell a profit!
Why the fuck are there so many monsters?!
Rance-sama, here's your sword.
I'll help too, Rance!
This looks like fun!
Yulang!
You got it!
I'll show you my Phantasm Blade!
Millie-chan, let's go too!
Eh?
Is there money in this?! Let me in too!
This will be good training, let's do this!
Honey Flash!
There's a naked woman right here!
Stay on your toes, we're dealing with monsters here!
Yes...
Leave the big one to me! Here I go!
Patty-chan, stay close to me.
Whew, that was close.
Yeah...
We've slipped past the monsters!
They really helped us, right, Rance-sama?
Whatever. I would've been fine by myself.
I was tired so you caught me off guard last time,
but right now, I'm at full strength!
I think it's about time you were punished.
Let's get real down and dirty on this one.
Rance-sama...
That's what I would've liked to do,
but if you tell me where your boss is hiding, I'll spare you.
Where Lia-sama is hiding?
I have only one thing to say to you.
I'll kill you, and protect Lia-sama!
I may even die, but...
Release!
Conflagration Technique!
What the hell? Is this magic?!
I'm not entirely sure, but I don't think it's magic!
The fuck?! She can't control it?!
We'll all be in trouble if this keeps up!
I'm ending this.
Rance Attack!
You were prepared to sacrifice yourself, huh?
Do you really need to go that far
for such a perverted queen?
She saved my life.
She's a very kind person.
She really is.
I don't care. How about you tell me
where she is? Where is Queen Lia?
Why would I tell you?
You really think a ninja would
compromise her master's safety?
Oh, so you want to keep your mouth
shut until the end, huh?
Then, I guess I'm out of options! I guess I have no choice!
You look like you're enjoying yourself, Rance-sama.
I'll just ask your body!
You're kidding...
Now, now. I wonder how many fingers you can take?
Rance-sama, you look like a villain.
Maris! Hey, Maris!
Can't we take a break?
We've been walking for so long, I'm tired!
Lia-sama... That me could still be chasing us.
I'm so tired, I can't take another step!
Maris, bring me a cold drink or something.
As you wish, Lia-sama.
I-If you go around the corner, there will be
a path that takes you out to a courtyard.
Losing to four fingers, huh?
– I must commend you for lasting this long.
– Rance-sama, your face! Your face!
All right, let's go, Sill!
Ah, yes, Rance-sama!
You're not going anywhere!
Whoa, lucky! I got the queen.
I thought you'd have your maid around, though.
Lia-sama!
Not so fast! Aren't you worried
what I might do to your Queen?
You're mine!
Maris!
Don't struggle!
Hey, let go of me! You're being disrespectful!
Calm the hell down!
Sill, put the Queen to sleep.
Huh? Okay.
Okay, it's punishment time.
I believe your exact phrasing was "do as you will".
You're a smart girl. You know what'll
happen if you don't listen to me, right?
Lia-sama...
Come on, clock's ticking.
Oh? Isn't this a sight for sore eyes.
Who would've guessed that the queen's
maid had such an amazing body.
What's up with your breasts?
They look like they've taken in more lust
from men than they know what to do with.
Quit your drivel.
Drop your arms.
Don't you care about your queen?
What was your name again? Maris?
I'm already like this because your body is so sexy.
And? What are you going to do?
We'll start here.
They fit perfectly in my hands.
I wonder if they taste as good as they feel.
Yeah, these are really great.
I really like these nipples of yours.
I'll put my mark on them.
This man is playing with my breasts like he owns them.
How long is he planning on sucking it for?!
Now. Mount me.
Hm? You're not wet yet.
Make yourself wet and then put it in yourself.
You think I can just do it on command?
Well then, change of plans.
Let's skip to the part where we violate
the queen in her sleep. Sill?
Y-Yes?
Wait!
Yeah, you better. My dick is more than ready to go.
You can use it if you want.
Use it!
Thi...
Good, good. Take it in and squeeze it, tightly.
Now, start moving.
Feels fine, but your movement sucks. Be rougher!
You say that, but...
Fine, then. Sill, you can start playing with the queen.
What do you mean by that?
Find a rock to play with her or something.
It can be as jagged as you want.
Y-You're so mean, Rance-sama!
Shut up! Just do as I say!
Oh, this is better!
Yeah, just like that!
Up, down, up, down. Push it deep inside you!
Does it feel good for you, Maris?
Yes! It feels good.
You're clever, and you learn fast. I like women like you.
Let me hear your moans!
It's so hard and hot!
That's right! You need to keep me entertained, Maris!
This is great! I'm having a blast. It feels so good!
I love seeing uptight women break down like this.
The further they fall,
the more proof I have of their submission.
Are you about to cum too, Maris?
Yes... I'm about to cum!
All right!
Huh? I...
Lia-sama!
Oh, your pussy got tighter!
Maris? Huh?
What's the matter, Maris? We're not done yet!
This is the best!
Hey, wait, Maris?! What are you doing?
Oh, shut up! Sill, shut her mouth.
Y-Yes!
Sorry.
What's the matter, Maris? You're tightening up even more!
Does being watched actually turn you on?
N-No, I...
Well, whatever. What matters is that I'm about to cum!
If you want it, squeeze with all you've got!
It's throbbing so deep inside me!
Lia-sama...
No! Please, don't look at me!
Maris is totally hooked on my cock right now!
Okay, let's give her a good look.
Like this.
No! Please, end this! Please give me your cum! Cum!
Give me lots of your cum!
Tell me where you want it.
Please... inside me.
Please flood my pussy with your hot cum!
Here we go!
It's hot. It won't stop flowing into me.
Oh. I'm cumming. I can't stop cumming.
Yes, you're cumming. You're cumming so much
inside me, it's filling up my stomach.
It's so hot!
Here, take all of it.
Hey, you spit some out. What a waste.
Maris, Leazus' Royal Maid, was pretty fucking great!
I'll be sure to remember you.
Now, I guess I'll go for the main dish.
Sill, strip the queen.
Huh? Um, okay...
Maris?
Lia-sama...
What the fuck? We just caught her.
End of the line!
Healing Nine!
What the hell? You're tougher than I thought.
Hey, what's going on?
Healing Nine is a spell that rapidly heals the body,
but leaves it in a berserk state!
I won't let you get any closer to Lia-sama!
L-Lia-sama deserves pity.
She was so kind as a child...
Due to stress from competing with her
siblings for the throne's succession,
her mind broke while she was young.
So?! That gives her the right
to do all these horrible things?
I will protect Lia-sama, no matter what.
You said her mind broke, right?
What did you do about it?
You really are impressive. Color me surprised.
I'll let you win this time.
Making you a pet would be a waste of your talents.
Would you like to be one of my
direct servants, just like Maris?
It pays well, you know?
If you want a title, I can make you a minister.
You could also have sex
with as many women as you'd like.
Th-That's Rance-sama's dream...
Do you really need to think about it? Tell me your answer.
Yeah, my answer is...
Ow! Wait! You're kidding, right?!
A dumb queen like yourself
needs to be punished, thoroughly!
How is it? Get a good taste of it!
You didn't show any sympathy
to the girls you abducted.
Oh man, these handles are perfect.
It's like they were made for this!
Stop, they're gonna break!
Like I care about that!
P-Please, forgive me!
The hell are you saying?
If you can still use your mouth to talk,
then that means I can be rougher!
This is what you get.
I wonder how the girls you tortured
would feel if they saw you like this!
Here goes round one!
You're horrible, you're so horrible!
It stinks! You've soiled me!
What're you saying? The real fun starts now.
Wh-What are you doing?!
I'm doing what I said I'd do.
Wait!
What a view!
No...
What's even better is that I'm doing a queen.
I don't get to do this everyday!
S-Stop! You're not serious, right?
Upsie daisy.
No... What are you doing?!
What you're doing is unforgivable!
Do you really think you'd be able
to get away with doing anything else?
There's truth in what you said.
It's that I love to have sex!
Yeah, that's good, Queen Lia!
No way, this can't be happening!
Did you really think I'm someone that would bluff?
I'm a man of my word! I do what I say I will!
No, stop! It hurts! Don't move!
Not happening. If I don't move, it won't feel good.
If I move, it feels great!
No, no, it hurts! Stop!
Don't the girls you torture say the same thing to you?
What do you say to them?
That's not...
I'm not going to stop, either!
No! It's moving and rubbing me so deep inside!
Hm? Is this your weak spot?
No, stop! No! If this goes on any longer...
Ow, ow!
Please, I'm begging you, stop! I'm sorry!
You were a bad girl.
I'm not letting you off the hook that easily!
This feels great, I'm about to cum!
Cum?! Wait, no, you can't!
Of course, I'll be cumming inside you!
No, don't!
That felt great!
No way, you really came inside! I even apologized!
Oh man, I let out a lot. It's pretty thick, too.
I won't forgive you for this!
Hey, we're not done yet, you know?
What? I thought guys couldn't
have orgasms one after the other!
Your punishment is nowhere near over!
No!
Please, forgive me already! Please!
Here we go again!
Wait, how many times have I cummed now?
Ah, whatever.
Stop! Stop cumming inside me!
Finally getting used to it, huh?
It's getting easier to thrust in and out of you!
P-Please, I beg you. No more!
Oh, I see? Does that mean
you've learned your lesson?
Yes, I have! So please...
Nope!
No!
But you said...
All I did was ask if you learned your lesson.
I'm gonna cum again!
No, not again!
You're the best! No matter how many times
I fuck you, my cock just won't calm down!
No, I can't take it anymore!
Here!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry! It's all my fault!
All right, I'm gonna shoot it all inside you again!
Doesn't that make you happy?
Yes! Thank you very much!
This is...
The Cum Stream of Justice!
I'm sorry. It feels so good...
I guess I went a bit too far.
Well this is hot in its own right.
Okay. Let's go one more time!
Yes! Please use me as much as you want! Darling! Darling!
What an unbecoming sight for a queen.
That's all of the cum I have.
I think that might have been
the most I've cummed in my life.
I expected nothing less from a queen.
That was the best fuck of my life.
That's one more case solved!
Rance-sama, is the queen okay?
Yeah, I might have gone a bit too far, though.
Wh-What are you going to do about it?
How about we go back to Ais?
What?! What about the queen?
I don't care.
We solved the case, bestowed punishment...
I feel great. We wrapped everything up nicely.
Let's go!
Yes!
My work here is done. I didn't leave anything out, either.
With the fortune we made from
this Keith guild's job, we returned to Ais.
My reward for saving Hikari-chan
is a bathtub of gold coins!
This actually kinda hurts.
Rance-sama!
Hey! You should get in, too... even if it kinda hurts.
We have trouble!
Spit it out.
Leazus' Queen, she...
Rance-sama! Rance-sama! It's me, it's Lia!
I was reborn after experiencing your whip of love!
I can no longer live without you!
Let's get married, darling!
What?! Ow.
The army and bodyguards
have surrounded the perimeter.
Great. Thank you, Maris!
You are so beautiful, Lia-sama!
Looks like something really annoying
is going down. Bring me my sword, Sill!
Coming!
Let's go out from the back door...
Rance!
Hey, Rance! What's the meaning of all this?!
What horrible things did you do to the queen?!
I wouldn't say horrible...
Get out here and explain yourself!
Rance-sama?!
Well, I guess we can't help it. Blow the door.
Blow it up!
We're gonna blow it wide open!
– Rance-sama!
– Wh-What should vie do?
– Rance!
– We're going to run away, obviously!
I'm not gonna let one woman tie me down!
Rance-sama, where are we going to go?
Wherever! It doesn't matter!
Let's go, Sill! Follow me!
Y-Yes! I'll follow you wherever you go, Rance-sama!
It's so lively here. Is there a festival going on?
Rance-sama...
Oh, it's nothing...
If you say so.
Geez, fucking brats.
The Rance World Continues...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч