Finishing strike.
Illusion Sword
Genmuken!
In order to search for the missing Hikari-chan,
I'll definitely need to defeat Yulang
and obtain her phantom-slaying sword.
It was a clash of blades.
With magic enveloping everything
around it with its mysterious brilliance.
The Kingdom of Leazas is known as the world's
most prosperous nation of the Eastern Continent.
With every event and incident that occurs,
the gears of fate in this kingdom turn.
Genmuken, huh.
Just how in the world,
will I defend myself against that?
Are you using shields?
It's possible for you to reduce or negate damage if you use a
shield imbued with the same element as your opponent's attack.
I don't think I'll even have the
chance to defend with a shield, though.
Is that so?
I think your luck will really be important here.
With luck, you may be able to dodge attacks easier.
No, no, this really can't be just left to luck.
I need a decisive victory.
Thanks for waiting.
Hey old man,
do you have any ideas there?
Nope, but I have beer if you want.
Say what?!
Rance-san, your next match is
with the champion Yulang-san, right?
Oh, yup!
Just leave it to me, and the rest is easy!
You don't stand a chance against Yulang.
My oh my.
That doesn't really have much weight
from someone who lost his very first match.
What did you say?
Please, don't fight!
The Coliseum Defense Corps?
Oh, why if it isn't Rance-san.
Who are you?
It's me, Ninjamaster.
I was the one you fought before.
You're that super flashy guy?
Your character's completely changed!
The coliseum's a place for honor after all.
It's the duty of public servants such as
I to make sure the place is always lively.
With this mystical scroll, you'll be able to switch personalities.
I'll give you one.
Personality Flip Scroll?
Alright, the next match is the finals.
Rance-san and Yulang-san's
match is sure to be lively tomorrow.
How about this?
Why don't we think of a nice strategy
to make their fight one hell of a match?
No can do.
It'd just be a one-hit-KO.
Agreed.
Genmuken's invincible!
A strategy, huh.
Excuse me, I'd like to order a California Roll!
Oh, coming!
Genmuken, the attack that can never be dodged.
How about I just make myself as
slimy as jelly and let the sword slide away?
That's it!
Well, let's see.
If you need something slippery, why don't
you check out the slimy stuff at Patty's shop?
Oh, that thing that's slippery smooth?
That's a good idea.
Just where are you looking?
I have mine grown properly, you know!
Wanna taste my honey crush?
Man, such dunces.
Rance-sama.
Oh, why it's cutie over here.
Too bad for you, though, I have something important to do.
Rance-sama!
Oh, this one seems like she's ready to be fucked anytime.
My fan, eh?
Alright, I'll try to remember you then.
Rance-sama!
You're so late, Sill!
When I call you, you make sure to come here right away!
I'm sorry, but we're in the middle of swimming class.
Umm, an unavoidable thrust?
Let's see.
Looks like I've built up since last time,
and I'm going to refresh myself with your body!
Oh, Rance-sama!
How about trying to deflect the sword with something slimy?
Hey!
You fool.
You just said that same thing as those dunces!
I'm not going to win with that ridiculous strategy!
You useless slave!
I'm going to punish you right this instant.
What is that?
We're going to change things a bit today,
so I'm going to use this Personality Flip
Scroll to make the totally slutty you service me.
Umm, that's.
Just how would you?
It's so bright!
Well? Feel like going on the offensive now?
Whoa, hey!
Where do you think you're touching me?
Where else, of course?
The thing that you're always forcing me to suck on.
It's already twitching.
You really are such a sloppy man
Huh? This is different from what I expected?
Oh?
Aren't you getting far more uptight than usual?
Hey, do you have any idea what you're doing?
Of course. I know every single thing about you, Rance-sama.
You're just an airhead who thinks of nothing
else but cumming regardless of the situation.
Quit the act already!
Please, worry not.
I'll just have to squeeze every drop
until this "head" becomes dry as well.
Now, now, I want you to cum lots, okay?
Sill... you!
Looks like you're a lot weaker than the usual Rance-sama,
and I'm somehow compelled to drink your love juices.
Hey, I told you to go more on the offensive,
but this is really different after all!
This is.
Here it comes.
Rance-sama's cum.
It's pumping straight from my mouth deep into my throat.
I want to drink more.
I want to drink it from every opening I have.
Hey Sill!
See there? Can you see how it
twitches in anticipation for this big thing?
That won't do.
As your slave, it's my duty to help you with your sexual desires,
so as to prevent you from committing any sexual crimes.
Besides, I don't really hate it, so long as it's not rape.
Doing it with you, I mean.
What? I didn't ask you for...
H-Hey!
It's pushing into me as usual.
It's in!
I'm gripping your thing inside me.
Just how many have you already
made cry with this, Rance-sama?
Oh my, it feels ticklish.
You really love breasts, don't you?
So good.
Oh no, it's superbly hitting my soft spots!
It's pumping inside.
Your hot thing, that is.
You...! You're still going?
Rance-sama, this is truly amazing!
Just listen to me, hey!
Oh wow.
My insides feel like they're on fire.
All because of Rance-sama's.
More, more.
More of it is coming out.
More of your hot thing is pumping in me.
Your dick feels so different than usual.
It's hitting me in different spots today.
Sill, cut this out already!
That expression,
looks like you now understand how.
I feel when you constantly tease me.
You idiot!
Oh no, I can't hold back now.
Hey!
Rance-sama, I think I'm about to cum.
Please rub me down to my deepest spot up to the very end.
Wh-Wha!
It's hitting deep inside me, Rance-sama.
Oh yes.
So good, so good that I'm about to faint, Rance-sama!
I'm... cumming!
I'm cumming, and I'm still cumming.
Cum lots... Rance-sama.
It feels so good to have sex at your own pace.
Engaging in sex that suits my desires.
The way that I want to.
Damn.
That was completely one-sided.
Damn you, moving and doing things
on your own while sitting on top of me!
You!
To slip, huh.
Such a crazy price!
Oopsi...
Oh, you can't touch that.
It's been set so that you can't get
it if you don't have enough money.
Curses!
Hey, everything listed here's just too much!
Sorry.
Crop harvest's been a bust this year so every stalk is expensive.
Give way, then.
Special Event!
If you can eat all of these super serving yakisoba,
I'll just let you have it for whatever you can pay me!
Are you all right, Rance-san?
Nami-san, I'm sorry.
I think my rent's gonna come quite later.
Alright then.
Okay, here's some medicine.
Good luck on your match, okay?
Rance!
It's already finals, huh.
Yeah, and now I'll finally be able to
make progress in finding Hikari-chan.
Good luck, then!
Ladies and gentlemen!
The day has finally come.
For the match that everyone across Leazas has been waiting for.
The amazing newcomer, Rance!
In the other corner,
yes,
Yulang, the famous wielder of the Genmuken technique!
Our coliseum's pride, and the invincible champion!
Listen up.
If I win, you'll hand over that
phantom slaying sword, and have sex with me!
You sure sound confident.
Have you found a way around my Genmuken?
There are no rules here.
You're allowed to use whatever means necessary.
I'm gonna win!
That's all there is to it!
Gotcha!
Rance is pressuring her!
What is this?
What in the world is happening?
Interesting.
I've been bored fighting weaklings for a long time.
This is the first time a match felt so enjoyable!
This can't be!
Whoa!
Such an ending to a match!
The Genmuken destroyer,
it's victory for the contestant Rance!
Can you stand, Yulang?
Yeah.
Hey, I won.
So you're gonna keep our deal, right?
Yeah.
I'll hand over this phantom slaying.
There's something else more important than that, right?
We're going to have sex.
That was also part of the deal.
Exactly.
Now that it's settled.
Let's go now!
Champion, one interview, please!
Hey.
You girl over there that definitely looks like a maid.
Is this a guest room?
Y-Yes sir.
Indeed it is.
This is the Laplace room.
Hey, don't tell me we're doing it here?
Now, now.
I'm Rance.
I came here for something important.
And I'm an important guest.
So I'm going to use this room.
Eh? O-Okay.
A-Are you serious?!
I said wait!
Let me shower at least!
I've worked hard up to this point.
I'm not letting this go on any longer.
That's not what I meant.
Hurry up arid undress.
Come on.
Such delicious legs you have there.
J-Just wait.
I'm not used to this.
I'm not even sure what my expressions should be.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh wow, you're squeezing very nicely here.
As expected of a gladiator.
Don't be ridiculous.
No way
Why am I getting so aroused?
Did I feel this way when I was touching myself?
Or maybe,
Rance is just that amazing.
No use.
If this keeps up, I'll completely lose it.
Yulang.
Here, over here.
O-Okay.
I never thought that I'd actually get a blowjob
from the Leazas coliseum's greatest warrior lady.
This feels great, Yulang.
Alright, you're going to use those gigantic boobs next.
I understand.
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
Hey now.
You're not going down just yet, champion.
We're just getting to the main course.
I know.
Eh? W-Wait.
Just wait, Rance.
I can't, Rance.
It feels like it's in a weird spot.
It's okay, the one's you probably
played with before are just too small.
No way.
But, it really feels like it's gone up beyond my belly button.
Rance!
Alrighty.
We're going to do this all the way on the bed till I cum inside!
Cum inside.
You couldn't be.
Exactly.
Rance.
Yulang, your boobs are the best.
They bulge so much, yet maintain a very firm form.
You look like you're in complete ecstasy.
What a waste from your usual very cool attitude.
My usual
my usual?
What was my usual expression again?
So deep!
– I can really feel your thing inside me!
– Yulang!
Ra-Rance!
Yulang, this suits you much better.
I love women who embrace their natural self!
Does it feel good, Rance?
It's the best.
How about you?
You can pretty much tell, right?
So don't ask anymore.
I'm going to cum again.
Okay, just cum.
Rance.
So hot.
Your thing feels so hot.
Please, Rance.
Envelop me completely.
Rance, a bit more, just a bit more.
I'm about to finished here.
Yeah, me too, I'm about at my limit already.
Our strongest gladiator here's completely wet already.
Rance, your hot thing is really amazing.
Come on.
Oh no!
No!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
That felt so good, I thought I'd
reached the end of my rope there.
Yeah.
Even now it still feels so good that my mind's still muddled.
Looks like the strongest gladiator of Leazas is ruined.
No.
Right now, I'm just another naked woman.
Am I not?
Going back to your nonchalant attitude, eh.
A loss is a loss, but a gladiator is still a gladiator.
I can't just take for granted the
identity that everyone now looks up to.
Also, this is another part of our deal.
Yeah.
It may have been transient,
but it felt like I was released from the cage that I built.
How about wearing something feminine for me for once?
You're already mine, you know.
Change a bit, because I want you to.
Rance, is that right?
I'm Yulang Mirage, you know.
Looks like it's been maintained quite well.
It doesn't really seem like a
place where spooks would come out.
Oh, so this really is a ghost mansion, huh.
I have this phantom slaying sword now, though.
I'll just have to dice you all to bits!
It's no longer working, but it looks like an expensive clock.
There it comes.
Are you the boss of all of the
ghosts that are haunting this mansion?
What?
Hey wait!
What was that?
It's as if it's actually guiding me to some place.
No... save me.
Save me!
Somebody please.
Please stop.
Stop!
What the hell is this?
Okay, turn it once more.
Understood.
If you don't hold it, your shoulders will get torn
and you'll press down hard into the wooden horse.
It hurts, it hurts!
I beg of you, please stop already.
How wonderful.
That expression is very wonderful, Lavender.
Now then, lets continue... with your feet.
What the heck was that?
Do you want to tell me something?
This room.
This room was the one from earlier!
Here it comes again!
Such a nice voice.
You really are very cute Lavender.
I'm going to give you a very special present today.
I'm sure it will suit you well.
See this? It's a branding iron.
Do you know what I'm about to do with it?
Month X Day 0.
I don't know what today's weather is like.
I don't know why I'm supposed to suffer like this.
It's so hard.
I wrote this diary in secret in an attempt to maintain my sanity.
I'm Lavender.
A first year student from Paris Academy.
From Paris Academy?
That's the school that Hikari used to attend,
and the same school that Sill is currently at.
Month X Day 0.
I don't know what today's weather is like.
Those people came again and toyed with me.
She was enjoying it.
This isn't normal.
I was raped by a monster.
She cackled in delight as she watched me.
This is just so sick.
Whenever that clock strikes nine, my hell begins.
I was a toy.
It continued until the eleventh.
And then.
From nine o'clock to eleven o'clock, huh.
And right about now is supposed to be her "hell time".
I can't accept this.
That time finally ended.
Thank you.
Were you killed in this mansion?
Did you come back to haunt this
place because of what happened?
Yes, I was just suddenly kidnapped.
After that, each day.
The woman she was with always
healed me whenever I was about to die.
So I committed suicide.
I see.
Despite that, she never stopped.
She just kidnapped another girl in my stead.
I just cannot allow it to continue further.
The queen's just.
Queen?
You mean Queen Lia?
Indeed.
I beg of you, please stop her!
I can't do anything.
I can only ever haunt this place and continuously weep.
It was so hard, so painful, it felt like an eternity.
Mom, Dad!
I really... I really didn't want to die.
Don't cry.
I'm going to stop that bitch even if you don't ask me to!
Treating women like her playthings and slowly killing them.
She's basically wasting the world's most important treasure.
I won't forgive her!
So leave this to me.
Okay.
Rance-san,
the room beyond this is where Hikari-chan is being held.
Please save her.
What?
Hikari-chan, you say?
Rance-san.
I wasn't able to directly touch you, but...
You still felt warm.
So this is the room, huh.
Hikari-chan?
Are you Hikari-chan?
She's still alive.
Thank goodness.
Hey, you're safe now.
Rance!
Could that girl be?
Yeah, it's Hikari-chan, the girl I've been looking for.
Can you keep her with you for a short while?
So you found her.
Thank goodness.
But what in the world just...
I'll tell you the details later.
The culprit is in the vicinity.
Wait, you don't mean the culprit is inside Leazas castle?
I'm going to catch her, and tear her to shreds!