Pulptenks, over here!
In a moment!
In here too, Pulptenks-chan!
Hey, you're Pulptenks-chan, right?
Your body's far more alluring than I imagined.
Boss would surely go crazy for you.
Blades clash,
and magic wields the light amidst its mystery.
The gears of history have started their revolution in this vast world.
Rance, Rises!!
This is Hikari Mi Blanc.
She's the daughter of the prestigious Leazas family's Blanc line.
Reports say that she disappeared three weeks
ago at the school she was attending.
I want you to find her.
This boring job doesn't suit a warrior prodigy like me.
It's much too simple.
Then just leave if you don't want to,
or would you rather be scrubbing
things and carrying stuff instead?
Hikari Mi Blanc, eh?
Oh, Hikari-chan!
She's a cutie!
Alright, in the name of her cute appeal,
I, Rance-sama, the strongest warrior prodigy ever
will search for her right away.
I'm counting on you.
Hey, Sill!
Hurry up!
What kind of slave makes her master wait like this?
Useless bitch!
M-My apologies, Rance-sama.
But I wasn't able to find a good source of water.
And there were also monsters!
Stop complaining, you slave!
This tastes great.
Give me that one too.
But that's mine...
Hey, it's almost noon already!
Why don't we grab something to eat in Leazas, Sill?
Okay, here I go!
Rance-sama!
So this is the prestigious Leazas town, eh?
Guess it really does have the reputation
for being the best in the world.
Here we are.
Rance-sama!
What are we going to do?
You're enrolling in this Paris Academy,
the school that Hikari-chan attended.
I'm enrolling?
This is an infiltration operation.
I don't really want to leave this to you,
but this place is off limits to guys,
so boys can't enter it.
No can do.
But I'm doing it right now?
Hey now, do you really think I came here unprepared?
I already worked out these papers.
So just get going already!
Now, all I need to do is to look around
town, and infiltrate some beauties!
Rule number one in the way of the adventurer.
Gather information immediately after reaching a new town!
And I am loyal to its basics!
One beauty found!
Oh, will you be staying?
This is the Crystal Candy inn.
So this is what it looks like inside.
Feels quite different from other locales.
I like it.
I'll be staying.
Thank you very much.
I am Horikawa Nami,
the head hostess of this place.
Nami-san, eh?
Eastern clothing is really...
Great!
I can't hold back anymore so here I go!
Takeda Juujutsu.
Tebasaki Otoshi.
Ow, ow, ow...
My apologies.
I am quite experience in Juujutsu.
My body just reacted reflexively.
Ju-Juujutsu.
Oh, what is this?
She's Hikari-chan.
I'm currently looking for her.
Does she look familiar to you?
No.
I'm sorry I'm unable to be of assistance.
No, it's fine.
Thanks, anyway.
Sea House Baltic
Sea!
What?
I'm Patty.
Patty the Summer!
We have lots of stylish things and items here!
I'm Rance.
Forget that, do you know anything about this girl?
Forget that, I see an opening!
And I'll be taking it!
I don't know her.
Next, next!
I'm Millie Lincle.
This is a weapon and armor shop.
Straight hit!
You seem aloof, but you're still cute!
Hey, Millie-chan, I've brought lunch!
Whoops.
What the hell?
Next, next!
I'm Willis Fujisaki and this is the level up shop.
Would you like to level up?
According to Willis Fujisaki...
A mystery girl, eh, lemme have some!
Spark**spark.
Damn, even after my serious investigation,
I still don't have a single clue concerning
Hikari-chan's whereabouts.
What the fuck is going on?
So how was it, Sill?
Were you able to get anything?
Well...
I heard she was an aristocrat.
And a cheerful one too.
Does she have any link to suspicious people?
Or are her parents in debt?
I, I don't know about that...
Useless bitch.
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
I've been holding in my pent up frustration lately.
Slaves should always be able to comfort their masters!
Right here?
Wh-What if somebody sees us?
What did you say?
You cheeky bitch!
Slaves should think only about their master's well being!
Now part your legs and show me your ass!
No way...
Hey, get wet already.
Even if you say that...
Ow...
Hey, why don't we hang out somewhere after school?
But I can't today.
What are those two doing over there?
Huh? I didn't notice.
Maybe the guy brough her there?
Rance-sama, we must hurry,
or people will come.
What? Are you ordering me?
As a slave, you should be pleasuring me instead!
And attempt to do all of your other duties properly!
B-But...
Please forgive me, Rance-sama!
Satisfy me then.
I'll still be satisfying myself here, though.
Rance-sama...
It's big.
Look... you're completely exposed.
Why don't you call over some friends so they can see you?
It'll be embarrassing if they see me here like this.
You seem unable to hold back your moans any longer.
Then, here's the main course!
This feels...
Yes...
Alright, I'm cumming inside!
Ra-Rance-sama!
Th-That hurt.
It wasn't even your first time.
Just take it all like the slave that you are.
Yes.
Alright, one more time!
But I'm still...!
Well have sex until I'm completely satisfied!
It's starting to feel better.
That's good.
That last one was quite great.
Now, continue with your investigation.
Yes... Rance-sama...
Tastier than eggs!
I do feel refreshed,
but I'm still stuck at square one.
Hey, old man, give me something strong.
Hey!
I already said my order!
Get on with it already!
You've been like that for the past 30 minutes.
I'm gonna leave without eating or drinking anything.
Are you okay with that?!
Well, I guess it's pointless to ask this of a pathetic old man like you,
but I'm looking for a missing girl.
A missing girl?!
Oh, uh, y-yeah.
Hikari Mi Blanc.
She's a noble, and she's currently missing.
And it is my job, as the strongest warrior prodigy to look for her.
Is that true?
Maybe it's also the work of the Endless Tomorrow Fighting Squad!
You see, my daughter Pulptenks was also kidnapped!
What? Endless Tomorrow Fighting Squad?
I've heard they're holed in some cave within the forest.
But there's not a single one who's willing to take them on.
If you were given this job, then you must be
of considerable caliber as a warrior, right?
I beg of you? Would you rescue my daughter Pulptenks?
Wow, she's really cute!
Yeah, and Hikari-chan might be there too, anyway.
I'm going to grab Pulptenks as a bonus as well!
I like it.
Alright, I accept.
Leave this to me.
Please,
please do!
I'm going to give you my entire stash!
I hope these can fill you up as well!
Take all of these too!
– This too, and this too...
– Hey wait.
– Are you listening?
– This too, and this too...
Idiot! I can't carry that much into battle!
Just give me the stash, and some of these drinks and food.
I can leave this to you, right?
Just who do you think I am?
Uh, no idea, sorry.
Eh? Is that true?
Indeed. Some group named the Endless Tomorrow Fighting Squad
have taken a cave in a nearby forest
and turned it into their hideout.
Is that so...
Alright! Now I have something to report to Rance-sama.
Sill-san?
Yes?
It seems we get along really well.
Shall we become friends?
Yes!
This guy's fucking with us.
Pull your sword out!
No can do.
I have no intention of soiling my sword with a lowly thug's blood.
Alright!
Let's just keep going straight until I get Hikari-chan!
And Pulptenks too!
Rance-sama. Rance-sama!
And I was so eager to report to him about the bandit's hideout.
He only ever comes when it's inconvenient for me,
and never when I really want to see him.
Boss Room
This is the boss room alright.
This erotic voice.
There's a girl inside!
Boss Room
What a lecher!
I'm the only one who can have sex with girls!
Looks like I really need a key to open it.
Oh? You must be new here.
A fresh recruit?
Wow, you're quite sexy, miss.
I'm Necai, the vice-commander here.
Mister cute underling.
Cute?
See, that's what I meant.
Don't hesitate to let me know if you've got a complaint.
Okay?
I can't get past the boss room.
Seems boss Reinhard has taken a liking
to the recently kidnapped girl.
He's been holed up in there ever since.
Kidnapped?
Damn, I'm really jeal...
I mean, really upse...
No, I'm really jealous.
He won't notice even if you knock.
I have his spare key here, though.
In here.
Give it to me!
Nope.
Then I'll take it from you!
For you to try and assault me like that... how greedy.
Oh? My oh my!
Is that a 250-year old Yamazaki?
Hey, will you be willing to part with this for my key?
I'll even pleasure you as a bonus.
I think it's a fine deal for this treasure.
Refreshed? Good then.
Alright then, bye!
What a nice body.
It has such lewdness, milady.
No, I'm not lewd...!
If this is not a sign of your lewdness, then what is it?
Hey, you.
What?
Who are you to just enter my room?
You're the boss of this bandit group, right?
I've come to punish you!
I'd rather not this time.
I'm currently busy right now.
Busy in giving this girl the best pleasure that she'll ever experience.
The best pleasure?
You kidnapped her against her will, and played with her.
What kind of nonsense are you blabbering about, you pervert?!
Good grief.
I never thought there'd be someone foolish enough
to challenge the Endless Tomorrow Fighting Squad.
You're getting too full of yourself!
You and your crappy side tricks!
He's really good.
The bad feeling I felt earlier was absolutely spot on.
How about dicing you up a thousand
pieces in exchange for your insults?
Why is this goofy guy so good?
What an outrageous jerk.
What are you trying to do?
Rance Slash!
Stop fucking with me!
Are you alright, Pulptenks-chan?
Wow, this is...
No, please let me be!
I can't take any more of that.
Does she think that I'm that perverted boss?
This is quite the delectable situation!
I'm not going to keep you waiting then!
I'm digging in!
You came already after I put it in?
Woops, gotta keep pretending.
Guhehe, seems you can't hold back anymore.
Now have a taste of my ultimate weapon.
It's big.
Here.
No...
It's my first time and yet...
It feels so great!
Oh wow!
Now I feel sorry for the bandit boss not being able to fuck her.
Here, take this.
Your boobs are really nice.
Don't...
Not right there.
They're going to break if you keep doing that.
You bitch, you're just a sex swine.
No, I'm not a bitch...
Then why is your pussy trying to firmly wrap around my dick?
You're clearly a bitch!
No!
I didn't want to do it with a bandit, but it just...
Oh no...
Here we go.
Here, here.
Have some more.
My mind's going blank.
Alright, I'm about to cum.
And I'm going to let it all out inside.
N-No!
Don't cum.
I'll become pregnant.
I'm going to become pregnant!
I don't really care.
We're really, really evil so we can do whatever we want!
Don't... don't...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Let's go for a second round then.
Just wait...
We're going to do this until I'm completely satisfied.
No!
This is... really great...!
It's alright now, Pulptenks-chan.
Okay, I'm going to take you home.
Umm... I...
I just took out the baddies.
I'm Rance.
I was the adventurer sent by your old man to rescue you.
Thank you very much.
No need to worry now.
Alright.
By the way, was there another girl that was kidnapped?
No, I think I was the only one.
Crap, I came all this way for nothing.
Thank you. Thank you!
I can't really repay you back,
but here's everything that I can give you, so please take it.
Geez, it's really getting annoying now!
Rance-san, thank you very much.
Yeah!
If you can, please drop by our shop again.
See ya.
But that was totally unrelated to Hikari-chan.
I just did all of that for nothing.
All for nothing, and back to square one.
PC-9801 VM, 2HD Disk, 4MB RAM, MSX, 6000...
Man, I really want to have sex with someone now!
Oh, there's a girl over there.
He sensed me.
But how?
Hey you, just wait!
Were you just looking at me earlier?
Not being able to face me directly... a shy type, eh?
But I dig that too.
I'm starting to feel love!
That gal sure is fast.
Where did she go?
Stop searching for Hikari Mi Blanc.
What did you say?
I'll say it once more.
Let your search for Hikari Mi Blanc end right here.