One over here, Pulptenks!
Okay, right away!
Another one here, Pulptenks!
Hey, you're Pulptenks, ain't you?
Just as fuckin' sexy as I thought you'd be.
Damn, the Boss should love her too.
No... No...
Nooooo!
The clashing of blades.
Magic growing increasingly bright within a mystery.
In this vast world, the gears of history are now beginning to turn.
Her name's Hikari mi Blanc. She's the daughter of Leazas's prestigious Blanc family.
Apparently she suddenly disappeared from the school she attends about three weeks ago.
Go look for her.
That's a pretty bland job for a genius warrior like myself.
If you don't like it then get out. Or would you rather take care of beehives and clean out range hoods?
Hikari mi Blanc...
Wow, she's pretty cute, isn't she?!
Alright!
This time, in deference to Hikari's cuteness, I, Rance, the invincible strongest adventurer, will put things in order.
It's in your hands.
Hey, Sill!
Hurry up, Sill!
What kind of slave makes her master wait? You're useless!
I'm sorry, Master Rance. It was hard to find a place where I could get clean water.
Also, some monsters--
No excuses, slave!
That's refreshing.
Give me that one too.
That's my--
Well, it's almost noon. Maybe we'll get some good lunch in Leazas, huh, Sill?
Alright, let's hurry there!
Master Rance!
So this is Leazas's castle town.
Everywhere you look you can see why this is called the most prosperous country in the world.
Is this it?
Master Rance!
What do we do now?
You're going to be studying abroad at Paris Academy, the school Hikari went to.
Studying abroad?
This is what we call an infiltration operation.
I'm uneasy about leaving it to you, but there's no men allowed in Paris Academy, so I've got no choice.
Um, can I really just suddenly start studying here like that?
Did you seriously think I came without a plan?
All the paperwork's in order.
Now get going!
Now, maybe I should operate around town and thoroughly investigate the hotties they've got here.
The number one thing any adventurer knows is that the first thing you do when you come to a new town is collect info.
I always do the basics!
Oh, hottie sighted!
Ah, are you staying as this inn? This is Koorizatou.
Huh, so this is how it is inside.
It's kind of weird. I like it! I'll stay here.
Thank you very much.
I'm Nami Horikawa, the owner of this inn.
Nami... JAPANese clothes are really...
Good!
I can't wait any longer!
Takeda Jujutsu: Tebasaki Drop.
I'm sorry, I have a fondness for jujutsu and found myself doing that by reflex.
J-Jujutsu...
Oh, what's this?
That's Hikari, a girl I'm looking for. Have you seen her before?
No. I'm sorry I can't help you.
Nah, I understand. Thanks.
The beeeeeach!
I'm Patty. Patty the Summer!
This is a chic, modern item shop!
I am Rance.
It doesn't really matter, but do you know this girl?
It doesn't matter, but you let your guard down! Time to eat!
Don't know her.
Next, next!
My name is Millie Lincle.
This is Resignation, a weapon shop.
Here we go!
You're gloomy, but pretty cute, aren't you?!
Hi Millie! It's lunch time!
Oh, Rance!
Why?
Next, next, next!
I'm Willis Fujisaki, a leveler.
Would you like to be leveled up?
Um, Willis, Fujisaki, sheeroado...
You look like a ripe young lady!
Damn, even after all my super serious searching, I haven't found a single clue about Hikari.
The hell is going on?
How's it going, Sill? Found out anything?
Um, I learned she's from a noble family, at least.
It sounds like she was a nice, carefree person.
Was there some weirdo that hated her, maybe?
Or her parents had debt or something like that?
I don't know about anything like that.
You're worthless. I'll have to punish you.
I have a lot of things stored up right now.
A slave needs to be ready to comfort her master at any time!
Here?
What if somebody sees?
What did you say?! Know your place!
A slave only needs to think about her master!
Open your legs and stick out your ass!
I don't like this!
Hey, hurry up and get wet.
I can't just do that, though...
Hey, wanna go do something after school today?
Sorry, I can't today.
Uh, what are those two doing over there?
Huh, I hadn't noticed them.
Did she bring him here?
Master Rance, you have to hurry or people are going to come!
What?! You think you can tell me what to do?!
It's my slave's job to make me feel good, you know!
Just deal with everything else!
B-But... But...
Please forgive me, Master Rance!
Then use this to satisfy me.
Well, I'll satisfy myself regardless of what you do.
Master Rance!
It's big...
Here, show everything. Let your friends see!
If anyone saw this...
I'd be so ashamed!
Sounds like you can't take any more of this.
Then it's time to spurt!
I don't need that...
Alright, gonna cum inside!
Master Raaance!!
That hurt...
It's not like this was your first time.
If you're a slave, then act like one and take in all my jizz without complaining.
Okay...
Alright, one more time!
But I'm still--
We have sex until I'm satisfied!
This has gotten good!
It got pretty good at the end there.
Now try to take your info gathering seriously!
Okay...
Master Rance...
More delicious than tamagoyaki!
That felt nice, but it doesn't change that I have no leads.
Hey old man, I want gorocchi.
Hey, old man! I've been trying to order for a while now! Pay attention!
You've been ignoring me for thirty minutes now!
I'm going to write an unfavorable review of this place. Are you listening?!
Well, I'm sure there's no use in asking a cold old man like you, but...
I'm looking for a girl that went missing.
A girl that went missing?!
Yeah.
Hikari mi Blanc.
A young noble that went missing.
I, the strongest warrior and peerless adventurer, received a request to find her.
Is that true?!
Was it the work of the Endless Tomorrow Combat Team?!
They... They kidnapped my daughter Pulptenks too!
What? The Endless Tomorrow Combat Team?
I hear their hideout is in a cave in the forest, but nobody does anything about them, not even the city's defense force!
If you really got a request from nobility, you must be a talented warrior, right?!
Could you please save Pulptenks for me?!
Well isn't she cute?!
Yeah, it sounds like Hikari might be there too. And I'll get Pulptenks at the same time!
Sounds good.
Alright, got it! Leave it to me.
Please, I'm depending on you!
I'll give you all the money I have!
You can have this to sate your hunger too!
And take all of this also!
And this. Please! And this.
Yeah. Uh huh. Okay.
Uh, you listening, old man?
This too!
Idiot! How am I supposed to carry all this when I'm going off to fight?!
I'll take the money and, let's see...
This alcohol and the snacks. That's enough.
Can I rely on you?
Who the hell do you think I am?
Sorry, I don't know.
Really?!
Yes, so I hear.
A group called the Endless Tomorrow Combat Team that's been kidnapping people around here recently supposedly has a hideout in a cave in the forest.
Is that so?
Yay, now I can report to Master Rance!
Sill.
Um, yes?
We get along well, don't we?
I was wondering if we could be friends.
Okay!
You're underestimating us! Draw your fucking sword!
No.
I don't plan on making my sword rust on small fry like you!
Alright, I'll keep this up and get Hikari!
And I'll get Pulptenks too while I'm at it!
Master Raaance!
Master Raaaaance!
I want to tell him about the thieves' hideout, though.
He always shows up at bad times, too.
Why can't I find him when I want to?
Sign: Boss's Room
Looks like this must be the boss's room.
This sexy voice... There must be a girl here!
What an asshole! Only I can have sex with girls!
I guess I'll need a key.
My, I've never seen you before.
Are you new?
Well if it isn't a sexy lady?
I'm Necai Sys, the vice boss.
Cute little boy.
Cute?
You've definitely got your cute points.
If you have any problems then just tell me, okay?
I can't get in the boss's room.
Oh, Reihard, the boss.
I guess he took a liking to a girl we kidnapped recently. He's been playing with her in his room since.
Kidnapped?
Damn it, I'm jealous--no, I'm disgusted--no, I'm jealous.
I suppose he wouldn't notice if you knocked.
If you want a key to Reihard's room, I have a duplicate.
Right here.
Let me have it.
Nope.
Then let me fuck you!
And trying to assault me, too. How greedy.
Huh? What? Wow!
That's the elusive famous whiskey, 250 year old Yamazaki, isn't it?
Hey, would you trade this for the key?
I'll make you feel good, too.
In exchange for whiskey like this, I'll make you feel really good.
If that was good for you, then I'm happy.
Until next time. Bye!
Nice body.
You have a naughty body, young lady.
No... I'm not naughty...
If these aren't the qualities of a pervert, then what in the world are they?
Hey, you.
Oh, what is it?
Who's entering my room without being let in?
Are you the boss of the thieves or whatever?
I, Rance, came to punish you!
You came at a bad time. I'm busy right now!
I'm in the middle of giving this girl the gift of the greatest pleasure.
Greatest, huh?
Pretty self-serving for a pervert that kidnaps girls against their will and teases them with tools!
Dear, if you're opposing us, the Endless Tomorrow Combat Team...
Then you're going too far!
Damn, you're quick, and you don't let up.
He's pretty skilled. Guess the bad feeling I had was spot on.
Perhaps you wish for me to cut that big mouth of your into a thousand pieces.
How is this youth so familiar with battle? Damn obnoxious brat!
What could this be?
Rance Slaaash!
Don't underestimate me!
You okay, Pulptenks?
Well look at this.
No... No more...
If you do more of what you just did... I'll...
Is she mistaking me for that pervert boss?
What a delectable situation!
I'm not going to tease you or anything!
Time to enjoy!
I just put it in and you already came?
Oops, I have to act like the pervert boss.
You can't resist it anymore, can you?
Have a taste of my cock!
It's good!
Take that!
No!
It feels good!
It's my first time, why does it feel so good?!
My god! I pity that boss!
Here, take this!
Nice boobs!
No... Stop... If you're that rough with my boobs, you'll crush them!
So naughty. You're a pig!
No, I'm not naughty!
Then why ever are you so tight on my cock?
That's proof you're naughty!
Nooo!
A thief is raping me, so why...?
No!
Up you go!
Feel that! Feel that!
My mind's going blank!
Alright, it's about time to cum!
I'll let it all out inside you!
No, don't cum!
You'll get me pregnant!
Why would I care?
I'm an evil, villainous thief, so I do whatever I want!
No, no!
Cumming!
Cummiiiiing!!!
Now, perhaps we should do it again.
N-No way...
I won't stop until I'm completely satisfied!
No!
This... This is... Wonderful, isn't it?
Are you okay now, Pulptenks?
Huh?
Now, how about I take you home?
Um, I...
I beat the villains.
I'm Rance. The adventurer your dad asked to come save you.
Thank you.
You're safe now.
Okay.
By the way, was there another girl that was kidnapped?
No, I think I was the only one here.
Well, this was all done in vain, then.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
I've never been as thankful to someone as I am today! Here, take your reward!
God, calm down!
Rance, thank you.
Yeah!
If you don't mind, please come to our bar again sometime.
See you.
That didn't end up having anything to do with Hikari, though.
Was it all a waste of time?
Waste of time, back to the drawing board...
After its release on the PC-9801VM, a four disc release for the MSX2 and an X68000 version were--
Now I want to fuck someone! I don't care who!
Girl sighted!
He noticed me pretty easily.
Why?
Hey, wait up!
You were just looking at me, weren't you? You must be too shy to do anything else!
But that's fine, too!
This feels like love!
What a student. She's fast. Where the hell did she--
Cease pursuing Hikari mi Blanc.
What?!
I'll only say it once more.
I'm telling you that your investigation of Hikari mi Blanc ends here.