Translation: HAM
Editing: Dio
Time while fapping: Lucky-7
Encoder: Random British tosser
Random perv: MDX
You damn whore, using me only for money...!
You toss your victims once they're outta money... you dump'em!
I'll remember this... It's going to be YOUR turn to suffer!
I'll humiliate that slut even worse than she did me!
I'll show her how I suffered!
It's useless.
You will spread your legs.
No!!
For GREAT JUSTICE, from all the men you've deceived.
Who are you?
Who am I? WHO AM I?
I'M THE FUKKEN RAPEMAN!!!
#MANLY-SUBS
we bring you HARD HITTING SHIT
Ooookay ladies, stretch your legs.
Good ladies, push out your hips.
Ahh, raise my damn pay.
Look at that Yuka, Keisuke was out late again.
Yeah, he looks really tired.
Geez, is this really the attitude a P.E. teacher should have?
I don't care if he's cute, it's disgraceful!
I don't mind.
Why?!
Men are only worth as much as their looks.
I'll forgive any man with a beautiful face.
But ugly men are worthless, like garbage.
You and your lust for cute guys...
Hey, you two!
Keep  talking and you hips won't grow out.
When you say that, you just wanna feel'em up, amirite perv?
You lot are friggin' restless.
Hurry.
The Rape signal.
Sorry, I have to make a quick phone call.
You lot jog around the track.
We don't wanna sweat!
Ichimonji Yuka?!
That's right.
Your target this time is Ichimonji Yuka, a senior from Onozomu High School.
Long-story-short, you're gonna rape the fuck out of your student.
Say what now?
The client is her mother.
Technically speaking, her step-mother.
She wants you to rape her at their apartment.
She worries about her because she like useless men.
Earlier today she went out so you're on stake out.
Her father is still there, so exercise extreme caution.
Wow, she made him blow his load in such a short time.
She must be a real cockhound.
Looks like their ride's here.
Brother Masazen, thanks for coming.
Where's the Boss?
He'll be out soon.
Good, we're not late.
Phew, that was close.
Keisuke, the target's on its way.
She's with Tatsuo, a pretty-boy Yakuza.
Come up later.
Aight.
Target's arrived.
Welcome home, young miss.
Tatsuo.
Brother Masazen, good evening...
Shit like you don't deserve to address me as Brother.
Now fuck off!
Father!
Yuka, why don't you knock next time?!
I didn't think family needed to knock.
You've never knocked on my door either.
I'm only paying you back.
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb!
Yuka, forget about Tatsuo already.
I get it, you're the one who wants us to break up!
He's not good enough for you.
I'm the one who wanted Tatsuo out.
No way in Hell I'll let some thug have my daughter.
We're in love!
Yuka, have you tried Masazen?
You're a perfect match.
I agree, I've decided that Masazen is best for you.
Mom, dad, don't go choosing my husband for me!
Thinking about being married to that gorilla face makes me sick!
Yuka, there's more to men than their looks.
Then what are they good for?!
Men are about their bravery and determination!
Well said honey~
Bullshit.
Tatsuo and I aren't breaking up.
If you keep interfering, we'll elope!
She acts a lot different than when she's at school.
They're leaving... finally.
All according to plan... now there's just Tatsuo.
Will he come to her room?
I'll take care of it.
I think it's about time for RAPEMAN to appear.
Lets begin.
Ow!
Who are you?! I'll scream!
Be quiet, woman.
I am TEH RAPEMAN.
Oh no, I forgot the Chairman's sword.
Turn around.
But we'll be late...
It's fine, just turn around.
Dear, we'll be late. Why don't we send for it later?
Dumb ho! I can't ignore an order from the Chairman.
Turn around now.
FUCKING HOMOS, WHAT THE SHIT?!
Niggah say what?
N..nothing sir, have a safe trip...
Men require this kind of rush, 'else it's not good.
On the other hand, Tatsuo is pathetic.
Why would Yuka fall for a shit like that?
It's because she has no experience with men, that's why she's naive.
She wouldn't understand the beauty of men like Masazen.
No... no!!
Please stop!
Stop! Stop!!
I'll scream if you don't!
Please, someone save me!!
It's useless.
No one will save you.
The music is too loud.
I own you now.
Good girl.
Stop it!
Oh snap!
Back already?!
I'll go get it!
No, I will. It's in the safe anyways.
I'll be back soon, but keep the car running.
Tatsuo!
Ah, good evening Boss!
What the fuck are you doin' here?!
Get out of my sight, fag!
Boss, forgive me for trying to enter Yuka's room!
You motherfucker!
Shit!
Who the hell are you?!
Prepare yourself you shit!
Boss, what's going on?!
Dickwad!
Hold it!
ASSHOLE!
Scum...
B-Boss...
The odds have turned against you!
Tatsu! Kill this fucker!
Ehh?! I-I can't...!
What the fuck are you doing?! Kill him!
You useless shit!
Where'd that fuck go?!
What... the fuck?!
It's this!
You useless shit, you let him get away!
S-Save me...!
Such a useless shit of a coward!
It's because of you that Yuka was raped!
Never go near her again!
Father was telling the truth...
Dear, the Chairman is waiting...
Yuka! What happened?!
She was raped, while we were gone.
I'll stay behind and look after her.
Take care of her.
I will.
I don't want your sympathy! Get out!
I have none to offer.
What happened may seem complicated, but you're an adult.
As an adult, you will think about what happened.
"It's your own fault for getting raped, you deserved it!"
There are people who would think that, but I don't.
As the daughter of the Boss, you're supposed to be a strong woman.
Emotions do not weaken you, and words do not hurt you.
As an adult, you're going to go through the Hell of Adulthood.
One of the hardships you will go through is love.
But lobe is not so fickle as you see it.
Even if you were wrong, you shouldn't hurt yourself over it.
Understand?
Understand!?
Mother!
I can't let you get away.
I will capture you!
You knew... I would rape her.
Yes, I had a feeling someone was scheming something.
You knew that, and let me rape Yuka on purpose?
So she could see Tatsuo for the shit he was.
It was for the sake of the group.
You think that if you two got together the group would thrive?
I'm grateful to the Boss, and I'll do what he wants done!
Admirable words.
That is what we call pride!
I wouldn't know of pride.
Die!
You lost on purpose, didn't you?
No, you beat me!
It's my fault the young miss was hurt.
But this was the only way to separate her from Tatsuo.
Don't worry, I didn't COMPLETELY destroy her pussy.
I-Is that true?!
Yeah.
Your Boss barged in before I could do some MASSIVE DAMAGE.
I see...
Y-Young miss!
I'm gonna throw these flowers out, 'kay?
Please do! Please use that vase too!
I never thought you would come to visit.
Those flowers are beautiful.
You don't have to thank me for them.
You're not really gorilla-like after all.
Hello? This is Haraouka Fudou.
Oh, the Boss' wife!
Yeah, we almost messed up back there.
I'm sorry, my husband suddenly wanted to return to the apartment.
It's no problem, I'm just glad we got outta there alive.
Thanks to you, my daughter doesn't love Tatsuo anymore. Now, the group is fine.
Well, that's good news.
With Masazen, our group will the best in all of Kanto!
Thanks again.
What a lying bitch.
You're too much Yuka!
So this Sunday, you wanna go on a roller-coaster date in Harajuku?
Yuka, what's wrong?
Oh, I was thinking about how useless good-looking men were.
Hey, what happened to you loving good-looking men?
I prefer reliable men now.
Whoa, what made you change your preferences?
I just wish Keisuke was more reliable.
#MANLY-SUBS
Who's there?!
Someone's around here...
There's no way... a mannequin can move.
Dang, mannequins these days are really well made.
This softness...
It fells real...
What about here?
Amazing!
This softness and moistness... It feels real!
It's wet!
What a sweet scent.
It tastes like...!
Ow!
Geez!
You dick...
Shut up bitch, you love it.
Hey, you wanted to fuck in here, didn't you?
Be gentle...
Suuuuuuure I will...
I'll rip it apart.
You cockhound.
Rip it more! More!
How this?!
Shameless bastards...
Well, he'll be off duty for a while.
Rip it more!
MOAR!
Infra-red lasers huh?
New model too, a Concord.
The LAZOR's CHARGIN' panel is over there.
As long as that's intact, she won't get into the glass.
Thanks for the food.
No problem.
I'll wash the dishes.
Okay.
I'm gonna use your toilet.
Uh huh.
Come on in.
Hey, sir.
I don't care if you...
Yo.
Mr. Odan!
Haraoka, it's been a while.
Geez, don't be so distant.
Ya should've given me a call, I would've picked you up myself.
There's no need for such formality.
Formality?
You trying to be sarcastic?
How's you work behind the shadows going?
It's going well.
That's good to hear.
So what brings you here today?
Read the front page.
Oh, it's about Red Cat's latest burglary.
I see, so Red Cat's a woman after all.
I couldn't tell from the mask...
I didn't know you had an interest in her work.
She's...
my daughter Maki.
Then, she's your prodigy?
Wow, that's some dangerous conversation going on.
I see, so you ordered this to be stolen.
I haven't taught her a thing.
She's a bloody thief, I'm not into that sort of thing myself.
Mr. Odan, are you against your daughter being a thief?
Of course I am!
Who in this world would want their child to be thieves?!
Haraoka, you know where I'm going with this.
Thievery is a dangerous business.
She'll be branded as a /a/tard in Heaven for working in the shadows!
Look at me, I can't even work 'cause of these legs.
Maki is all that matters to me now.
So Haraoka, do me this favor.
Mr. Odan, you can't mean...!
That's right, do this job for me.
What the fuck?!
She's still in shallow water.
Make her turn back while she still can!
You mean you want us to do the job while she's doing hers?!
Of course that's what I mean! She'll understand once she's caught red-handed!
Haraoka, do this for me.
Oh shi-!
That was close.
She's greedy alright, cute tits though.
That's no guard!
That was some nice work back there, Red Cat.
There's nowhere to run, pussycat.
I exact GREAT JUSTICE on evil females such as you.
And what do you plan on doing what with that?
This!
Rooftop chase eh?
This'll be fun!
What the fuck are you doing?!
Ca-Captain!
Y-Y-You dumb shit!
Captain, lets get going!
You're fired!
Let's go!
Sir!
F-Fired?!
Dumbass.
Heh, that tool can't keep up with me.
Nice tits.
What's wrong? You're done running already?
He's strong!
Quit embarrassing yourself already.
How fitting!
Well then, lets get the RAPES started.
Noooo!!
Nice position.
Prepare yourself...
RAPE TIME!
Noooo!!
The cops will hear your screams.
Now keep quiet and take it all.
You villain!
I've drunk too much...
Rain...?
W-W-W-What the fuck?!
Fucking up there?!
How depraved!
Excuse me, excuse me!
Yeah, there's been a burglary at the site.
Officer, would you take a look at that?
Piss off.
Just look up there you dyke! There's people fucking! Go arrest them now!
What? Sex? Where?
There's no one there.
You little shit, are you mocking me?!
Owwie.
That was fucking trippy...
Get ready, here comes the main course!
TRIANGLE...
INFINITY...
MAGNUM .31!
Listen up.
If i catch you out here again, you gonna get gangbanged.
Work like this isn't for you.
Never pull shit like this again, understand?
Filthy beast!
Old man, why we driving out this far?
'Cause we're going somewhere along the way.
Gimme a break...
That girl called me a beast...
If didn't feel too good.
Oh well, your job can't feel the same all the time.
Why stop?
Here they come.
Maki.
Maki, it's about time the flowers to bloom.
Could you go look for some?
Huh? Flowers?
Okay, just wait here Father.
She's beautiful.
She's really gone back to being a normal woman.
Keisuke, get your eyes off of her and look at him.
Dammit, showing his gentle side...
Aren't you my former boss?
Father!
The flowers haven't bloomed yet.
Heh, of really?
What's wrong Father? You have tears in your eyes.
Oh something got in my eyes, that's all.
Well, I think it's time we go home.
Yeah.
Old Man.
I'm glad those two are back together.
Yeah...
Let's go drinking tonight!
Fuck yeah!
We'll drink 'till morning!
Let's go!