Ayaka-chan hurry and cum.
Please stop dear.
Why is...
Move your boobs.
TL note: wtf... Giberish
Incredible, it is filling her up.
Mom... Mom...
My My Chita-chan is such a sweet child.
What is this all of a sudden.
This feels so good.
It... went in.
Im cumming again.
Its alright, its alright, inside is alright.
Tak-chan, I was surprised you liked me.
So it was like that a childhood friends room.
Gez.. don't do that.
Isn't also with you too?
Ayaka.
hmm, I'll make sure this is delivered.
This is for Yurnie's sake.
Don't worry so much.
Hey wait...
I'm so embarrassed, I can't go to school tomorrow.
But...
If it is ok, Izugomi-tan will be there.
Yurine, Im so happy
I also...
If that was true, I'd be happy.
Tak-chan?
No Don't!
Lets be silent here.
Don't move now.
If you don't.. I'll...
I'll mince you.
Stop! No Don't!
NO!!!
I'll kill you if you scream!
Stop.
Please. No!
Cute underwear.
Yet...
the vulgarity.
Please stop.
???
There... not...
NO! not there.
Please, please stop this.
This is nice that expression... see.
I can see some embarrassing shit now.
DON'T!!!
You need to keep what is Important to you.
It hurts..
Ow!!
It hurts!!!
This is awesome, I cannot get enough of this.
Stop...
This is feels fucking good.
This is the greatest feeling.
Inside?
That suprising feel good to you?
If you do that I'll.
Don't really I can't/
I can't, I can't, can't!
No.. No...
I beg you, please stop this.
Forgive me forgive me please.
I'm begging you.. Inside th..
Something like this..
Too fast, its going too fast.
Stop I'm begging you.
Why...
Why am I being raped?!?
Didn't it feel good?
No, something like that..
Look its all flushed.
Don't say weird things.
Please stop.
But you seem so lonely.
Or is your husband not there.
No he.. something like that isn't true.
No... No!!!
Ma'am you look sad, so I'll cum for you.
No not inside.
Not Inside..
Alright alright.
But you really want to feel what it is like to be cummed inside right?
I CAN'T ANYMORE!!!
Inside... Inside!
Its coming out!
Cum... I..
cummed liked this.
There is so much inside.
This..
If you cummed so much..
of course it would feel good.
ooh did you like it.
Whatever...
It hurts, my abdomen hurts.
Its going to burst!
Help me!
Ambulance call and ambulance.
Its going to burst.. BURST!
Hey! That hurt.
You better let go!
Hold on.
Won't you let me see what is inside that bag?
Haa?!?
Isn't that a breach in privacy?
Hey!!
Just hand it over!
Your name?
Its Hoshino.
Hoshino? what...
Hoshino Momoka
Thats a cute name.
Are you making a fool out of me!
Calling the police, calling your parents, calling the school to get you expelled...
Or letting me rape you to drop all the charges...
Which one would you like?
Shit!
Rape me or do whatever is fine to you!
Stop!
You fucking pervert.
Stop...
Cold..
You where going to eat this no?
You're wrong..
Dont put it in!!
Oh god stop..
Whichever one it is it feels good.
Ahh Shit!
Forgive me already.
I'm Sorry
Here it comes.. Its coming.
Its coming! coming!! coming!!!
I'm.. beg.ing.. I'm beg..ing you.
plea..se.. s.to..p.
Sto...
This feels disgusting.
Let go, Let me go!!!
That hurts!!
Sucking he's sucking..
Don't.
ther.. there..
I.. just realized.
that your cuteness, queen like stature, society acceptable Ayaka-chan.
Is what I love.
You.. you can't be..
Inside Ayaka-chan, I'm..
Its going in...
Ayaka-chan finally we're..
Ayaka-chan, Ayaka-chan.
IN.. I finally penetrated Ayaka-chan.
Please no...
It hurts, it hurts...
it.. hurts...
I love you, I love you, I love you... Ayaka-chan!
it hurts.. it hu..rts..
Ayaka-chans body feels so good..
It does feel good at all..
It hurts! It hurts! I beg of you to stop..
Please... stop...
Ayaka-chan's first time...
I took it...
No thats...
Please stop.. I won't tell anyone.
Let me feel more..
See..
I was inside you for so long... can't you see that.
This time...
I'm putting it in.
Its bleeding again.
Look theres a nice color on my penis...
It loves it when I am inside.
No.. you're wrong..
Something like that can't happen...
You should know... that I go in, you come to me.
We are having sex you know..
Its tightening.. tightening! Ayaka-chan.
This ... Why is it happening to me.
Ayaka-chan, you're a bad girl because you don't listen to other peoples feelings.
I.. I.. look out for others, listen to them yet..!!
I truly know that Ayaka-chan is a good girl.
Thats why I love you.
Love you so much to have sex, and it feels so good.
I can't... hold
Not inside, just not inside!!!
Don't say that, it feels so good, its alright to cum inside.
Don't a child... a child!!
A child? A child with Ayaka-chan, if that happens lets get married.
Please forgive me!!!
I'm so happy that Ayaka-chan is begging me to stop.
be.g.ging.. I'm beg..ging
Please not inside please...!! Mibohara-kun!
Ayaka-chan you know who I am?
WE are meant to be together Ayaka-chan!
You're wrong!!
I...!!! can't HOLD it.
I'm cuming, Cuming, CUMMING!!
Ayaka-chan.
Its inside..
Its coming out..
Its our first picture together...