Kou-chan,
I'm excited for the festival.
One of the accessory shops there, you see,
has something really cute and I want to buy it.
Alright, but only if you use your allowance to buy it.
Okay!
Yay, yay!
A dream... with Kou-chan?
The Cores.
The Vessels.
The world's demise.
Too many things happened.
Yunna, Miyu, and I are the Cores,
and in order to be captured by a Vessel,
we're to be raped.
Please stop.
Seiya-san, I beg of you, stop this!
No, my breasts are being fondled.
I've yet to show them to anyone, let alone have it touched!
These breasts sure are big.
No, please don't!
He's licking me!
This can't be!
Your nipples are getting a hard-on.
Feeling horny already?
As expected of a Core.
No, no I'm not!
This is gross!
It's starting to seep through.
No, why? Despite me being.
Oh?
Your pussy is already wet, I see.
Looks like we can capture you any time now.
What, you're not doing it?
Huh? Seiya-san is talking to someone else.
Then the one licking wasn't!
Your big boobs sure are something, Azusa.
I can really fit it inside.
A man's dick, of course.
A dick? No way!
No, let me go!
Don't, don't!
Please don't!
No!
What?
Something sticky is on my mouth.
What is this?
It started to push faster.
No, no.
What is this? I'm scared.
Wait, what is he trying to do?
It stinks.
Something just squirted on me.
Is this?
Your face is completely covered with cum!
I'm going to pump lots inside your pussy next.
Even though they did all of that to me.
Azusa, are you alright?
Who tried to heal me when I lost consciousness?
A Vessel?
I don't want to be exposed like that.
I'm scared, Kou-chan.
Good Morning.
Morning.
What's wrong?
Miyu, you look rather glum.
I never imagined you'd be that tough.
Waking her up is always a battle.
That's a terrible way to talk to someone older than you.
We're childhood friends, and you're just older by a little bit.
Hey, we'll be late for school.
Let's go.
Right.
We need to investigate the matter about Sakohira, anyway.
Y-You're right.
We're going to keep on doing it until I capture you.
Because that's all you Cores are good for.
Stop fooling around!
For the world to end because of that.
That's something I shall never!
We're about to change the entire world.
Come on!
The fact that we've challenged this destruction
many times is proof that we can stop it!
It's prophesized in the Oosakaki family's writings.
That's why this time too.
Shut your cheeky mouth with this!
I-I can't breathe.
My throat is forcefully!
The way your tongue rubs the underside feels really great!
Too bad.
Only beings like us can hurt each other,
so we can't really be killed any other way.
That means they can never be defeated
until the Summer Snowfall?
I'll turn you into a bitch slave that'll crave for it on her own.
And this is the ritual of truth that
will lead to the world's demise!
Th-This is.
It smells raw and stinky!
No, this feels gross!
I don't want this, and yet.
I still can't breathe properly.
All of you Cores shall never escape.
Where is that place?
The empty room on the third floor?
Sakohira!
I was hurt?
Wait, you're also?
Trying to hog all the Cores with your sweet position, eh.
I won't let you do that.
As same Vessel as you!
Are you alright, Itsuki-san?
Yes.
How about you? How did you find this place, Oosakaki?
It seems it's all because of the power of this book.
When I focused on finding you,
I saw where you were located.
Is that in your temple's archives?
Then he was.
Thank you.
For saving me.
The Innocent Core - Azusa - The Fleeting, Endearing Taint of the Flesh
Himegi-sensei seems to be absent.
I'm sure Sensei also knows about the book.
And I'm sure that she also knows about
the tradition that surrounds this town.
Sorry for getting you involved in this.
No.
Anyone who's connected to this book is
already involved in this from the start.
It's not your fault.
According to the book,
we need to stop the world's destruction,
before the Summer Snowfall comes.
The Vessels will then attempt to capture all four Cores.
Miyu, Azusa, Yurina.
Onii-chan!
Th-They said Onee-chan was absent from class earlier.
Azusa?!
Oosakaki-kun!
This isn't right.
It looks all fuzzy.
The place looks like a toilet... and somewhere else?
Alright.
I'll go search the restrooms.
Then you search for the other rooms.
I'll be waiting at the classroom.
Contact us if anything happens.
Okay.
U-Unde,
why?
Your uncle here, you see, is such a nice guy
after supporting your entire family.
Please... stop.
It's all twitchy, and it stinks!
What a fortunate event for me to become a Vessel,
for me to violate you completely as a Core.
No!
I can't believe even unde is...
is now a Vessel.
Don't!
Not there, please, unde!
I beg of you.
Your breasts felt really great earlier.
You sure grew up nicely.
Earher? With Seiya-san?
So you were the one.
My spiritual energy isn't that great,
but I've already stopped trying to hide my presence any longer.
Uncle, please don't push it further on my panties.
No, my breasts are being fondled again.
Please don't fondle them.
That's.
Don't lick it.
Uncle, please stop.
Don't touch my tender spots.
You see, I became like this because of you
in order to pleasure you.
Unde, you tongue!
It's fondling it on both sides.
Oh, the way you get aroused.
So you know how.
Have you been playing with yourself here?
No, I haven't.
I don't know anything about that!
Not my tender parts, please!
It feels gross, and yet.
I don't like this, and yet.
This is.
It's all drenched now.
How sloppy and indecent.
You're such a bad girl, Azusa.
Please,
if you continue licking there... I...
It's going faster!
Oh no, if this goes on,
it's going to make me... I'm going to cu...
So you came, Azusa.
I'm going to pleasure you more with my dick next.
No, please let me be already.
No can do.
I'm here, solely because I want to rape you.
Damn, that guy!
Azusa!
Even the principal is now!
Kou-chan.
No, don't look, please don't look!
Azusa!
The Vessels have done something terrible to Azusa.
Are we Cores totally incapable of fighting back against them?
If...
He decides to hold me.
Oh no...
No...
I have to get out now.
I-I'm sorry!
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Oosakaki-kun.
He's greatly helped us ever since he
came to this place to investigate.
If we're unable to defy our fate as Cores like this.
I'm.
Why have I.
They did all sorts of terrible things,
yet I don't want this.
I'm going to be captured as a Core if this continues.
In my mind, we were going to do it until the end.
I was thinking of the terrible things they're going to do,
my feelings just rushed to the surface.
And I just froze there.
They were doing things I didn't want them to do,
all those terrible things,
yet my body actually wanted them to do it.
What's wrong?
Well.
This may come off as rude,
but are you dating Azusa?
Eh?!
We've known each other for a long time as childhood friends.
But it's not what you think.
I see.
You two aren't dating.
Umm.
This may seem imposing,
but I want you to... make me yours.
I understand.
That this will just hasten the coming end.
Still,
if this continues, it'll soon all be taken by a guy that I don't love.
And so,
I love you, Oosakaki-kun.
I love you so much that I can throw everything else away.
I want to offer you my first time, even if it's just a thought.
Me too, I love you, Itsuki-san.
Right from the first time we met.
Please, make me yours, Oosakaki-kun,
then I'll be able to endure anything.
We just did it.
Lots of things might have happened,
but that was actually my first time.
I'm happy.
Yeah.
The way you agreed, you only do that
with people whom you trust.
I've also.
You're beautiful, Miyu.
Kou.
Oh no.
If I keep on doing this.
I'm...
I'm sorry, Kou-chan.
I'm a such a bitch.
Kou-chan, I want you to!
I'm happy.
Being able to give you my first time, I.
Go ahead, Kou.
Move.
Even this pain still makes me happy.
I'm connected with you now.
Wow,
I'm filled with you, my insides are completely filled with you.
Your dick is making me full.
Miyu, I'm not stopping now.
Kou, it's alright.
Just keep going in.
Make me crazy with it.
Kou, make me.
Kou, this is amazing.
I'm happy, Kou.
Kou-chan's fondling my insides.
I'm.
Kou-chan, Kou-chan!
It's overflowing.
My lewd juices are.
Kou-chan...
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
Kou-chan.
I... I...
Kou, you were amazing too.
Well, sorry.
Someone like me just.
No, it's alright.
I'm also happy that you love me.
Jeez, you're finally awake, Onee-chan.
I'll be preparing Azusa's then.
Oh, sorry about that, Miyu.
Don't mind it.
Just sit tight.
Is this okay?
Yup.
Kou-chan.
The principal is also a Vessel.
And everyone's getting rowdy over the absence of Sakohira.
It can't be helped if they don't know the details.
Yeah.
Kou-chan, so Miyu and him are.
Maybe they just became closer recently?
If I had just been more aggressive,
I never would have.
At this rate, I'm going to be completely violated as a Core.
They're going to capture me.
That's just.
Azusa.
Wandering around by yourself like that,
what are you thinking?
I did contact you properly and tell you I was here.
I knew that you were coming right
away, so I thought it'd be fine.
Now for the reason we're here.
Are you dating Miyu?
I see.
I knew it.
Umm... did you hear that from Miyu?
You're so casual with her now.
Kou-chan, you're also a Vessel, right?
Despite that, you're with Miyu, who's a Core.
I see, then that's about it, I guess.
I didn't hear it from Miyu.
I just knew while looking at you early this morning.
And I've also confirmed it now, anyway.
I really can't hide anything from you, can I?
Yup.
Because.
I've loved you for a long time.
Eh?
I love you, Kou-chan.
I'm sorry, I know that I'm supposed to be happy for you
I never really... intended to tell you.
I always thought,
that we'd be together forever.
It's alright, you already did it with Miyu, right?
Was it your first time?
Y-Yeah.
Miyu, decided to do it with you,
before she finally gets violated by the Vessels.
Even I want you to be my first.
I don't want anyone else, but the one I love... you.
I want to do it even if it's just once!
Kou-chan, please.
Take my virginity.
What are you saying?
I know,
that this will hasten the world's demise.
That this act will be a betrayal toward Miyu.
But.
I love you!
I'm really, really afraid of being violated by the Vessels.
But somehow my body years for what they do.
Crazy, huh.
I don't want all of this.
Please, I beg of you.
Even just for a bit.
Azusa.
Sto...
Please, be mine, Kou-chan.
Kou-chan, your.
It's quite limp.
But if I do this.
Azu...
Kou-chan, it's gotten really stiff.
And it's also hot.
Completely different from when we were kids.
It reeks of Kou-chan himself.
My breasts are being fondled by him.
Is he about to cum?
His dick is now twitching wildly.
It's okay just let it out.
Cum in my mouth.
Azu...
I drank your cum.
It's bitter, but when I think that it's yours.
I like it.
Kou-chan, I have a request.
Give it to me.
But if I do that, the world's demise will.
You are my entire world.
You're still kind and gentle.
That's why, I'll be the one to do it.
You're not going to be blamed for this.
I will take your dick in me,
of my own accord.
Kou-chan.
It really looks amazing.
After licking it, after getting my breasts fondled.
It became like this.
Don't do anything.
I'll do it myself.
That's why.
You're not the one to be blamed for this.
I'm about to.
Give my first time to you.
Azusa.
No, Kou-chan, I'll!
It's alright.
I'm going to take away your virginity.
Kou-chan!
You're filling me up.
I'm happy.
Being able to give you my first time like this.
That's why, at least for now.
At least for now, I want to feel you completely inside me.
Please, go.
Your dick is going all the way inside.
Every spot you touch sends a wave of
pleasure rushing through my body.
Kou-chan, this is amazing.
I'm happy that we can become like this.
Kou-chan, it feels great!
Your dick feels good.
Kou-chan.
It's deep inside!
It's going all the way through me.
Give it all to me, Kou-chan.
Penetrate me with it!
It's pushing farther and farther.
I'm really happy.
Kou-chan!
I'm going to cum.
Kou-chan... I'm cumming!
Lots of your cum is pumping inside me.
Kou-chan... Thank you.
Preliminary preparations are done already,
so just enjoy the rest of it.
This helped me a lot.
As expected of your spiritual energy's
ability to lure her in, Himegi-sensei.
She can still feel aroused even while asleep
What a slut she is.
Sorry to spoil your moment there,
but she became a woman just last night.
That damned brat from the shrine!
He just took her virginity?!
Bad girl, Azusa.
We ought to punish slutty bitches like you.
What?
Why? Where am I?
That hurts!
No!
Himegi-sensei!
Uncle, why are you?
Where am I?
And why is this?
Because you're a bad girl, Azusa.
Losing your virginity and not even telling me about it!
No form of punishment is adequate for that!
Uncle, please, anything but that.
Anything but that!
So you already got a taste of his dick, eh.
I can't just resist with this erotic body
right in front of me, you know!
I'm being licked!
No, that's just too strong for me!
Please don't!
Uncle, don't.
He's going to make me crazy again
with that weird and long tongue.
It's sweeping in circles on it.
If my tender spots continue to be licked like that.
This is really intense!
This is just!
Pushing your ass onto me like that.
How slutty.
Stop it already.
Kou-chan, save me!
Why are you yelling out the name of another man?
So that you can show him how wet
you are down there right now?
No, I could never do that!
Oosakaki-kun has the ability to pinpoint his targets.
He might just have a good view of this as he finds you here.
No, this can't be.
Kou-chan will see me completely exposed like this.
No, no!
Did you get aroused from the thought of being seen?
Seems like you're just about ready to cum.
No, not there.
If this continues.
Don't.
Anything but that, please, Unde!
It's no use resisting.
This is!
It went in.
Something that's not Kou-chan's is inside me!
If you try to push that big thing in me, I'll.
For the perverted you, this punishment
may have actually become a reward.
Seems he's already noticed your absence.
He's now trying to find you.
No way, if Kou-chan sees me here,
no, please, no!
You'll already be bursting with my
own seed once he finds you here.
No, it's pumping inside!
He's cumming inside me!
I'm going to make you cum lots of times while I cum!
I'll be filled with cum.
And the sensation of Kou-chan dick inside me will.
No.
This big and thick thing will overwrite
what I felt with Kou-chan!
Please don't push this huge thing inside me anymore.
Or I'll completely forget Kou-chan!
Azusa, and the principal are.
There's also someone else.
Damn, I can't see well.
This is too intense.
If this continues Kou-chan will be gone inside me.
Just let yourself be captured by my dick.
No, Kou-chan will be gone.
My insides will forever be changed.
He can't pinpoint the exact location.
We might be able to go against it if this continues.
H-He... stopped?
Is it over?
This can't be, I'm.
No, if he tries to push it again it'll be completely gone.
Kou-chan's presence will disappear inside me!
You seem to be craving for something.
Please, I don't want Kou-chan's presence to leave me.
The Kou-chan inside me!
Kou-chan is disappearing.
Are you not satisfied?
If you want more, then you'll have to plead for it.
Damn! Not here.
Azusa.
Please.
Give it to me... I want your dick, Unde!
My pussy is getting completely stirred!
I don't want this,
yet it just drives me crazy.
It's getting better and better now.
Azusa... damn.
That place is!
In the guest room!
This can't be, Kou!
No, please don't make this feel good for me anymore.
I won't be able to resist it any longer.
I don't want to, yet I'm about to cum again!
With my pussy completely wet.
I'm cumming!