I'm looking forward to the festival, Kou-chan!
One of the accessory stalls has something
really cute! Can you buy it for me?
Sure, if I use my allowance.
Yay! I'm so happy!
A dream about Kou-chan?
Fruits, monsters, the destruction of the world.
Too many things have been happening.
Me, Yunna, and Miyu are all fruits.
And in order to harvest us fruits, the
monsters are trying to ripen us up.
Seiya-san, please stop!
Oh no, he's fondling my breasts.
Though they've never been seen or touched before!
You have huge tits, don't you.
He's licking them? No way!
Starting to feel good? Your nipples are getting hard!
As expected of fruit.
No, you're wrong! It feels disgusting!
Oh no, he's sucking on it. Why is he doing this to me?
Oh? Now your pussy's getting wet?
Looks like I'll be able to harvest you soon.
What? You're not going to do it?
Huh? Who's Seiya-san talking to?
Wait, so the one licking me wasn't Seiya-san.
Your tits are amazing, Azusa. They're
a perfect it for a man's dick.
Wait! By dick, he means...
No way!
No! Let go of me! No! No! Stop! No!
What is this wet thing that's trying to get in my mouth?
His hands are... No! What? I'm scared!
What is he going to do to me?
It stinks! Something is sticking onto my face. Is this...
Your entire face is plastered with my cum. I'll make
sure your pussy gets the same treatment.
Even though he did all of that to me...
Azusa, are you okay?
Before I knew it, someone had cleaned everything up.
The monsters...
I can't believe they saw my...
No, I'm so scared, Kou-chan!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Good morning...
What's wrong?
You don't seem like yourself, Miyu.
Ugh, I didn't think you'd be so tough.
Well, Azusa's job is to wake people up.
I'm like your older sister! How can you be so mean to me?
You're just a slightly older childhood friend, right?
Well...
Come on, we're going to be late for school. Let's go.
Yeah, we have to look into the Sakohiras anyway.
G-Good point.
I'll do you good and ripen you up.
This is your duty, as a fruit.
Knock it off! Saying that the world
is destined for destruction...
That kind of thing is definitely...
We are going to change the world.
Come on!
We can prevent the world's destruction if
we stop you whenever you come at us!
Osakaki-kun's book says it all.
So now, like before...
Little shit! Don't talk back to me!
I-I can't breathe! He's forcing it down my throat!
I can't get enough of the way
your tongue feels on my dick.
Hate to break it to you, but no one can hurt me except
a fellow monster... So until then, I won't die.
Is he saying that we can't do anything
until the Summer Snow comes?
Getting you to do this by yourself is an important
part of the ritual to destroy the world!
T-This stinks like fish!
No! This is disgusting!
No! Even though I don't want this,
it keeps coming in. I can't breathe!
I'm not going to let any of you fruits get away.
Where is that? The classroom on the 3rd floor?
Sakohira!
You hurt me? It can't be, you're also a...
Are you trying to snag all the fruits
by getting close to them?
I'm not gonna let you do that.
We're both monsters, after all!
Itsuki-san, are you okay?
Yes. How did you find this place, Osakaki-kun?
By using the power of this book, I think.
When I thought about trying to find you,
the book showed me where you were.
Was this the thing from the temple's storeroom?
Then you saw... Him, with me...
Thanks, for saving me.
Dystopia of the Spiral Regression
Natural Fruit Azusa ~ Turns Easy for a Dirty Cock
It looks like Himegi-sensei isn't here.
Sensei knew about this book, so I was hoping
he'd know about this town as well.
Sorry, I brought you into all of this.
No, everything written in this book
is about us, so we're all involved.
It's not your fault, Itsuki-san.
If the book's right, that with the Summer Snow, we
can stop the destruction of the world, then...
The monsters will need to harvest three fruits.
Miyu, Azusa, Yurina.
Kou-nii chan!
Onee-chan never came to class.
Azusa hasn't?
Osakaki-kun!
This is strange. It's hard to see, but
the locations are a bathroom and...
Some kind of room?
Ok, I'll go check the bathroom and
you can go check the classrooms.
I'll wait in the classroom.
Call me right away if anything happens.
Right.
Why, Oji-san?
I'm a nice guy, raising and nurturing you lot.
No, please stop it.
It's throbbing and it stinks.
After accepting the lustful power of monsters,
we're able to rape you to our heart's content.
No! No!
I never thought even he would become a monster.
No! My shirt! Oji-san, don't!
I'm begging you.
Last time, your breasts felt splendid.
You're growing up well.
By last time you mean, Seiya-san?
Then the other person who was there was...
My sorcery wasn't really working out, so
I just decided to stop trying to hide.
My panties! Oji-san, don't posh it into me!
No! He's fondling my breasts again.
Don't play with them!
Don't lick them!
Oji-san, stop!
Everything you touch is so embarrassing! No!
You know, I accepted this power for you.
All in order to make you feel good.
Your tongue is...
The tips are stroking me!
Oh, you know that feeling? Have you played
with yourself down here before?
No, I haven't. I haven't!
Please, don't touch me somewhere so shameful!
No! Even though it feels disgusting and I don't want this...
You're getting so wet. Dirty slut. You're a bad girl, Azusa.
Please, I beg you. If you lick me anymore, I'll...
That's too fast!
No! At this rate, I'm going to cum...
I'm cumming!
Azusa, you came, didn't you? I'll make
you feel even better with this dick.
No. No more. Please let me go.
That's not possible.
You exist solely to be raped after all.
Shit! He's coming!
Azusa! In the headmaster's office?
Kou-chan? No!
No, don't look! Don't look!
Azusa!
That monster did such horrible things to Azusa.
Is there no way for us to fight back?
Being held by him... I...
Oh no!
No!
I have to get out soon.
S-Sorry!
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
Osakaki-kun.
Ever since we began our investigation as travelers,
he's been helping me out all the time.
At this rate, if we aren't able to defy our fate as fruit...
I...
Why was I...
Even though he did those horrible things...
No! At this rate, I'll become a ripened fruit.
To think that he almost went all the way...
Even though I knew he was doing horrible things to me,
I suddenly came and then he stopped
before he could go any further.
Even though he was doing horrible things I didn't want
him to do, my body was actually waiting for it.
What's the matter?
This might be weird of me to ask, but...
Are you and Azusa going out together?
We've been friends for as long as I can
remember, but we're not like that.
Oh, you aren't? So it isn't like that...
This might put you in a difficult position,
but... I want you to make me yours.
I understand doing that would hasten
the destruction of the world but,
at this rate, I'm going to have everything
stolen from me by someone I don't like.
If that's how it is, then... I love you Osakaki-kun!
I love you enough to let everything get destroyed!
This is a first for me. Even if it's just
how I feel, I wanted to tell you.
I love you too, Itsuki-san.
Ever since we first met, I've loved you.
Please make me yours.
If you do, I'll be able to bear anything.
We did it. Even though a lot was done to me,
that was my first kiss.
I'm so happy.
Yeah.
Could you say something to me that
you'd only say to the one you love?
Miyu, you're beautiful.
Kou!
Oh no. If I keep doing this, then...
I...
Kou-chan, sorry. I'm so dirty.
I want you...
I'm so happy that I can give you my first time.
It's okay Kou, you can move.
Even this pain makes me happy.
I'm connected with you.
This is amazing. There's so much of
you inside. You're filling me up!
There's so much cum inside me!
Miyu, I'm not done yet.
That's fine, Kou. Do me more.
Make a bigger mess of me!
I want you to do that!
Kou, you're amazing!
Kou, I'm so happy! Kou!
Kou's playing with my special place!
I... Kou-chan! Kou-chan!
I'm shaking! I feel so dirty...
Kou-chan...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Kou-chan... I...
I... I...
Kou, you were amazing.
No, I'm sorry.
I did so much to you...
No, it's fine.
I'm just happy to be loved by you.
Oh, so you're finally awake Onee-chan?
Okay then, I'll make you breakfast too.
Oh, sorry about that, Miyu.
It's fine. Just sit back and relax.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
Kou-chan...
The Principal ended up being a monster as well, and
the Sakohiras have disappeared. Everyone's on edge.
No one understands what's going
on, so it's not really surprising.
So Kou-chan, you and Miyu are really...
Maybe I was too distant. If I was a little more aggressive,
maybe it wouldn't have ended up like this.
The way this is going, I'll end up
being ripened and harvested.
I don't...
Azusa, you shouldn't be here by yourself.
What are you thinking?
I told you I'd be here.
I thought it'd be okay because I
knew you'd come immediately.
So, now for the real reason I called you here...
Are you going out with Miyu?
I see. So you really are...
Did you hear that from Miyu?
You started calling her by her first name, so...
Kou-chan, you're a monster too, right?
Even so, with Miyu, you...
I see. So you two already went that far?
I didn't hear this from Miyu.
I just kind of figured it out by watching you this morning.
And now I'm convinced.
I can't hide anything from you, can I?
Of course you can't. After all...
I've always loved you.
I love you, Kou-chan.
Sorry. I should be congratulating you, but...
Even though I really had no intention of telling you this...
I always thought that I'd be by your side forever.
It's okay. You did it with Miyu, right?
Was it her first?
Yeah.
Miyu, before a monster could take you...
Before one of them went all the
way, you did it with Kou-chan...
Even I want Kou-chan to be my first!
If it's not with you, the one I love...
I wouldn't be able to stand it.
Just once is fine!
Kou-chan, please take my first time.
What are you saying?
I know that this'll bring about the end of the world faster.
I know that this will be betraying Miyu.
But, I can't help that I love you!
Even though I'd really hate to be
violated by those monsters...
I feel that deep inside, part of me wants it.
That's weird, right? I can't take it anymore.
So, please.
Just a little of this is fine.
Azusa, sto...
Please, Kou-chan, be mine!
Kou-chan...
It's pretty soft, but if I do this...
Azusa!
Kou-chan is so hard and stiff now.
It's so hot!
It's so different compared to when we were children.
It's so cute.
Kou-chan's touching my breasts.
Is he going to cum soon? A lot might come out, so...
It's fine. Kou-chan, let it all out in my mouth.
Azu...
I drank it!
It was bitter, but when I think
about how it's yours, I like it.
Kou-chan, please. I want it.
If we do this, then the destruction of the world will...
To me, you are the world, Kou-chan.
You're just as nice as I thought. That's
why I'll take the initiative.
This isn't your fault.
I'll just...
Treat myself to your dick.
Kou-chan, this is amazing.
Just by sucking your dick and having my breasts rubbed...
I got like this.
You don't have to do anything, Kou-chan.
I'll do it all by myself.
That way, none of this will be your fault.
I'm going to have you take my first after all.
Azusa...
Kou-chan, I...
Azusa, don't worry.
I'll take your first time.
Kou-chan!
There's so much of you inside me...
I'm so happy you're taking my virginity, Kou-chan!
That's why I want to make sure that you
enjoy yourself as much as you can, okay?
Your dick is filling me up to the limit.
Everything you're doing feels so good!
Amazing, Kou-chan! I'm so happy we're doing this!
Kou-chan, it feels so good!
Kou-chan, your dick feels so good!
Kou-chan, you're in so deep!
You're pounding me deeper inside!
Kou-chan, give it to me. Make me go crazy with your dick!
Kou-chan is reaching all the way in. I'm so happy!
Kou-chan!
I'm cumming. Kou-chan, I'm cumming!
You came so much inside me!
Kou-chan, thank you.
I've finished the preparations, so please enjoy yourself.
That helps a lot. With your sorcery, Himegi-sensei,
I didn't even have to lure her out.
Still getting off though you're asleep? You're
such a dirty girl, aren't you, Azusa.
Sorry to interrupt you when you're having so much
fun, but she became a woman last night.
The one who stole her virginity
was that temple brat, wasn't it?
Azusa has been a really bad girl,
and bad girls get punished.
What? Why? Where am I?
That hurts! Stop! Himegi-sensei?
Oji-san, why? Where is this?
Why?!
You've been a bad girl, haven't you?
You lost your virginity without even telling me!
No matter how much I punish you, it won't be enough.
No! Please, Oji-san. Anything but that!
You already tasted his cock, huh?
There's no way your dirty body can hold back anymore.
You're licking me! It's so rough!
No! I don't want this, Oji-san!
He's going to make me go crazy again with that tongue.
No!
It's moving around!
If you do that in such a shameful place, I'm going to...
This is amazing!
Moving those hips on your own? You're so dirty.
No more! Kou-chan, please save me!
Calling another man's name? Do you want
me to show you just how wet you are?
No! I don't want that!
Osakaki-kun has the power of clairvoyance, you know.
He might see you like this when he tries to find you.
No way. No! I don't want him to
see something so embarrassing!
Did you just get excited from thinking that you're
being watched? Are you going to cum soon?
No I can't! No I can't do that! If I do...
No! You can't do that! Please, Oji-san!
No point begging.
Ahh this...
He went in! Something that's not Kou-chan's is inside me.
If this big thing churns up my insides... No!
For such a dirty girl like you, this punishment
might actually end up being a reward.
He seems to have noticed that you're missing.
Looks like he's trying to find you.
No! I don't want Kou-chan to see me like this! No!!
When he finds you, he'll see how much of my
seed is gonna be planted inside you, Azusa.
No! You came! You came inside me!
I'll make you cum as many times as I want.
There's so much cum...
The feel of Kou-chan is starting to fade away!
No! It's so big and thick! It's wiping away Kou-chan!
Don't move your giant dick around anymore!
I'm going to forget about Kou-chan!
Azusa! The Principal?
And there's another!
No good. I can't see!
This is so rough! Any more and Kou-chan will disappear!
Just become a slave to my dick.
No! Kou-chan's going to disappear!
You'll take over everything inside me!
Looks like he can't figure out where we are.
Like this, it shouldn't be hard to counteract him.
He stopped? Is it over?
No! I... No way!
No! If he puts it in again, I'll really lose it!
Kou-chan is disappearing from inside me!
Looks like you really want something.
No! I don't want to let him disappear!
I don't want him to disappear from within me!
Kou-chan's disappearing!
Was that hot enough for you? If you
want more, you'll have to beg.
Shit. It's not there either!
Azusa...
Please, Oji-san! My pussy wants your dick so bad.
You're messing up my pussy so much!
Even though I don't want it, his dick is making me crazy!
Looks like you've developed pretty well.
Azusa... shit. That place is...
The storage room!
No! Kou!!
No! Don't make me feel any better!
I'm really going to lose it!
I'm going to cum again!
My pussy is so wet!
I'm cumming!!
Translator: Hikarukon
Timer: v1touch
Editor: Punk4Real | Sill