Azusa's asleep now.
Kou, please don't be so hard on yourself.
You're doing what you can.
You're different from them,
and you're trying to save the world from its destruction.
Please.
I want you to.
Give me your dick, mister!
Looks like you haven't remembered everything yet.
And that's the proof.
You are the same, one of us.
Until the summer snow falls,
he will never be harmed.
What... is this?
Where am I?
I was supposed to be sleeping.
You're looking good there, Miu-chan.
But, we're inside a dream so don't worry.
Himegi-sensei!
We're in a dream?
Wh-What is this?
What is happening?
No, pull it out!
Calm down.
It's simply to pleasure you.
Since this is a dream, you can simply get horny all you want.
No way,
for this to be a dream.
I just can't allow myself to freely.
No!
Let me go!
I don't want this, even if this is a dream!
I said pull it out!
This is a place where you can simply drown in your pleasures.
Nobody will blame you for it here.
No one will.
No!
Sensei, stop!
This is.
Don't!
Still trying hard, I see.
Well then,
I'll just have to let you see something else that's pleasurable.
Yurina!
Huh... a man?
What is this?
Yurina.
Miu-chan!
I... I was sleeping.
Why am I with this person?
No!
I don't want this.
Yurina.
It feels good, right, Yurina-chan?
That's how sex is.
Sex?
Why... this can't be.
I don't want to do it with this guy,
I want to do it with Kou-niichan!
My oh my.
Oosakaki-kun is Miu-chan's now.
You didn't know?
Kou-niichan is?
No way.
You gave him up already because you knew I love him.
Why?
If it's for sex, then I can openly accept you.
Allow you to pleasure him using your body.
Pleasure him, using my body.
With me, Kou-niichan will.
Yurina, snap out of it!
Don't be fooled by her words!
Yurina!
You did it already, right, Miu-chan?
I too... I want to have sex with Kou-niichan!
I want to have the sex that this mister will teach me.
Good girl, Yurina-chan.
Just get horny.
Get as horny as your body wants.
Yurina, stop!
Take this!
Just be pleasured with my dick and everything's gonna be fine.
Hey, I demand you to pull this out already!
Getting all aroused with a total stranger,
these Cores sure are sloppy.
Looks like all of you will be captured very soon.
I shall never let that.
I'm going to stop the destruction of this world!
Then try to fight with all your might.
Mister, wait, any more and I'll!
I'm... about to go crazy!
Yurina-chan, you seem quite confused
with all of these sensations.
It's alright.
Just let yourself go.
This is... no... I'm scared!
I-I'm going crazy!
No, someone please save me!
No!
What in the world?
Oh, that's too bad.
Looks like she regained consciousness.
I should have made it a bit more moderate.
Why don't you help yourself with just Miu-chan over there?
No, what are you doing?
Stop!
Don't touch me in weird places!
Is it your first time here?
Of course!
That spot is!
It feels gross!
Feel the pleasure even deeper.
It's coming inside!
This can't be.
It's really going inside there!
It hurts.
This is very good.
It's getting even tighter after you
started fucking her in there, boss.
Both my pussy and ass feel so tight.
This is too intense!
Don't resist the pleasure.
No, I shouldn't be.
I'm surprised, so you can still resist at this point?
We're going to pump in lots of cum.
Don't... stop!
Th-This mustn't be, and yet!
It's pushing hard inside, rubbing me raw all the way.
You say your don't want it, but your stupefied
expression says otherwise.
That's... not true!
But, it's getting even bigger inside!
It's pumping lots inside me.
Lots... is flowing inside.
Just a little more.
We'll meet again, Miu-chan.
Was it really a dream?
Oh no.
My body feels hot.
The wind feels good.
I have to go back to Kou.
I should not be going anywhere else... but.
It seems we have successfully lured her in.
Sensei, what is this?
Please stop!
Oh, you came back to your senses already?
That was surprisingly quick.
Or maybe because it is you.
You are bound using phantasmal
arts, so you cannot make a move.
You sure are beautiful.
So this body has been tainted with cum.
No need to hold back.
I'm not holding back.
Besides, you are a woman.
I really want you to feel pleasure with this.
What? My body... it feels hot.
Something between my legs is.
Do you like it?
No, return me back to normal, please!
Feeling horny yet?
You've made it very stiff already.
I wonder how long you will last?
You're already starting to be captured, you know.
Your entire body, I mean.
I'll... definitely put an end to this!
You're already this wet.
And your body has no capacity to resist.
Your dick is starting to bulge even more.
Seems you cannot hold on much longer.
I will not... no.
Don't hold back, just cum.
What is this?
Something's... strange.
No, it's coming out!
It's squirting out of my dick!
This is cum you just squirted out.
Isn't it wonderful for a woman to taste her own cum?
Now that you've experienced the pleasures of a man, you
will now let yourself be caressed well as a woman.
Principal!
You... let me go!
It's throbbing quite well.
No, let me go!
I said let me go!
That reaction, it looks like you are really being captured now.
I shall rape you until the end, then.
No... no, no, no!
Kou-niichan!
She's nowhere in the house!
Damn!
She went ouside?
No.
My ass,
don't caress it like that.
How you look now is completely exposed as he uses his ability.
I'm being seen by Kou right now.
No.
Kou, don't look.
Himegi-sensei was there too.
If I make a mistake again, then.
I can't worry about that now!
I'm going to save Miu.
You two just wait here.
I'll go as well.
I'll probably be raped by a vessel, but
I don't want that to happen, but
I have to go.
Yeah, we might get raped, but we are the Cores.
If we don't, then the destruction of the world will.
Huh, what was I?
You're right.
In order to prevent the world's demise,
the Core has to be raped, and then captured.
Huh?
Was that it?
I'll be back soon.
Wait here!
I don't want any more of this!
I've had enough.
Stop... not there!
Please stop doing this already.
I'm...
Just a wee bit more.
The Cores who are now in the process of being
captured are losing their minds one by one.
Wait... don't!
Please don't put it in!
That big thing is not going to!
It's now inside.
And it's sloppily rubbing in me.
For you to feel aroused already at this point,
as expected of a Core.
It keeps on rubbing.
It's going wild inside me!
Feels good, doesn't it? Quite different
from when it was just a dream.
Just keep on feeling that pleasure.
I'll definitely... never.
I'll...
Your ass is starting to get totally wet as well.
What a lovely sight.
You cannot endure any more of this, right?
I'm going to make you cum all the way through.
No, not there!
Don't push harder, please!
You came, right?
Now defy what is written.
No, don't fondle it like that.
No, stop, don't... if you continue.
Kou... I'll never give up.
That's why.
You desire to be saved by him, and yet your desires
are going to fuel this world's destruction.
This is going to be exciting.
Pops, switch with me already.
I want to rape her too!
You'll have to do it later.
Follow the plan.
Damn,
oh hey, he's already here.
I... will never yield!
He found us quite quickly.
Has he become stronger than before?
This is too intense.
It's ripping me apart.
Feeling at ease now? Your spirit seems to have faltered.
This is so intense.
It's driving me nuts.
So shameful of me.
He came so much.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Seiya's just!
K-Kou.
Miu!
What is going on?
It has begun.
The destruction, the world's demise.
Is this because we started to become captives as Cores?
Can't we do something about it now?
Do vessels truly wish for this destruction to happen?
I could not bear to restrain myself any longer.
I too, desire Miu as.
Kou.
Well...
If we somehow stop the world's demise,
I want you.
I want you to love me to the utmost.
Jeez, Kou,
I was trying to stop feeling embarrased while saying that.
S-Sorry.
That's why...
Kou, I want to go with you.
Do it with me... one last time.
Alright.
Let's both do our best.
Se-Sensei.
What is really going on?
What can I do?
You still can't remember?
I see.
This has been repeated many times as scripture.
This is also directly related to your lineage.
Was this... ail because I wasn't able to remember?
Was the destruction of the world fated to happen?
The vessel that I accepted experienced it many times.
Which is why there may be some way around this.
Is that true?
The last vessel remaining has the right to choose,
if you are willing to relinquish it to me.
Do you understand?
I cannot comply with that.
I made a promise with Miu.
That I will struggle until the end.
That's why, it's what I have to do.
I'll...
My body?!
Too bad.
If your memories had just returned, I
would not have been able to do this.
But the way you are now.
You've already gotten it big.
If you start feeling pleasure here, won't
Miu and the others feel lonely?
No... this is just.
Why?
Amazing.
My very insides are also being stirred.
Yurina, this is amazing, don't you agree?
It hurts! No... this is.
No!
Please stop.
We shall greet the coming apocalypse as we continue.
Continue raping you all until the end, I mean.
Oh yes.
If you keep fucking my pussy this hard, I'll.
I'll completely lose it.
Mister, not just me, please caress Miu and Yurina well, too.
Onee-chan, why are you?
I don't want this!
Onii-chan!
Azusa, Yurina,
Miu.
No!
Kou... please put an end to this!
I... I simply cannot lose here!
You've just made it stiffer after watching
Miu-chan and the others earlier.
Now I feel jealous.
You're actually the strongest,
but you did not remember,
so every single beginning became the very end.
Amazing.
Such thick cum.
That's good.
Now go and die... in pleasure.
I'm sorry, but this is also part of my power.
Principal.
Any more and I'll!
No, please not there.
Don't!
Don't push it in together.
I'll keep on getting horny if it keeps on pushing in.
It's now stirring me deep inside.
My ass included.
All the while Kou watches this.
It's driving me crazy!