Dystopia of the Spiral Regression
The tentacles that wrap around Miu ~ The busty futanari, Squeezed and Rammed
Azusa's asleep now.
Kou, don't let it get to you.
You're doing the best you can.
You're different from those guys.
You're actually trying to prevent the world from ending.
Please, stick your dick in my pussy, oji-san!
You might not have your memories, but
that, right there, is proof enough.
You're a monster, just like us.
Before it first starts snowing in summer,
the monsters can't be harmed.
What's going on?
Where am I?
Wasn't I asleep...?
Looking good, Miu-chan.
We're in a dream right now, so don't worry.
Himeki-sensei?
This is a dream?
How?! What's happening?
No... Take it out!
Calm down.
I'm just trying to make you happy.
This is a dream, so you don't have
to pretend it doesn't feel good.
Just because it's a dream, I don't have to...
No!
Let go of me! Even if this is a dream, I don't want this!
Take it out!
You can let yourself go here.
Nobody will judge you.
Nobody... Will judge me?
No! We can't do this, sensei!
No!!
You're fightihg hard, aren't you?
Let me show you another way to have fun.
Yurina?
This... Oji-san?!
What is this?
Yurina!
Miu-chan?
Why? Even though I was sleeping...
Why is he doing this to me?!
No! I don't want this!
Yu-Yurina!
It feels good, doesn't it?
This is called sex.
Sex?
Why am I doing this with him? I
wanted to do it with onii-chan!
Oh? Oosakaki-kun is Miu's man. Didn't you know that?
Onee-chan's?! You're wrong!
I gave up on him because I knew she liked him, so why?!
You can use sex to get him to like you.
You're using your body to make him feel good.
I'm using my body to make him feel
good. With onii-chan, I can...
Yurina, stay calm! Don't let her words confuse you!
Yurina!
Miu-chan, you did it with him, right?
I want to do it with him too!
I want you to teach me how to have sex!
You're such a good girl, Yurina-chan.
Embrace the pleasure and satisfy the cravings of your body.
Yurina, don't do it!
Hey! All you have to do is focus on satisfying my dick!
Yuina! Get that filthy thing out of me!
You're getting this turned on by having a guy you
don't even know fuck you. You fruity sluts.
You'll be our slaves in no time!
I won't let that happen!
We'll save the world from it's destruction!
Struggle all you want!
Oji-san, no... no more!
I'm going to go crazy if you do!
Yurina-chan, you're confused about what
you're feeling for the first time, right?
Just relax and let your body take over.
No! I don't want to! I'm scared! I'm going to break!
No! Help me! No!!
No!!
What happened?!
Oh, what a shame.
It seems she has regained consciousness.
Looks like that was her limit.
How about you comfort poor little Miu-chan over there?
No! What are you doing down there?!
Don't touch it!
Have you never used this before?
Of course I haven't! Why would I?!
That feels gross!
I'll show you even more pleasure.
It's going in! Why is it going in there?!
My ass... No!
Feels good, doesn't it!
She's even tighter now that you're in her too!
My pussy and ass are being drilled so hard by their dicks...
You shouldn't hold yourself back if it feels good.
I won't... from this!
I'm surprised you're still able to resist.
I'll fill you up with my cum.
No! Stop! You can't do that!
They're thrusting and rubbing deep inside me!
You say you don't want it, but
your face is telling me to do it.
No! Stop! Stop!!
They're so big!
They came inside! I can feel their cum inside me!
There's so much inside me!
Just a little more.
Let's meet again, Miu-chan.
Was that really a dream?
Why is my body so hot?
The wind feels so nice.
I need to go back to Kou.
I can't go on like this...
Looks like she accepted our invitation.
Social Studies Preparation Room
Sensei?
Why?
Sensei, what's going on? Stop this!
Oh, you're conscious already?
That was faster than I expected.
Maybe it's just because of who you are.
I'm using magic. You can't even budge.
How beautiful. This is the body that
was defiled with cum, huh?
Don't hold back.
I'm not holding back.
We're both girls anyway, so I won't feel a thing.
I'm going to make you feel good, no matter what.
What? My body feels hot!
There's something between my legs...
Do you like it?
No! Change me back to normal!
Does it feel good?
You got hard instantly.
I wonder how long you can hold out for.
Your body is starting to turn into our slave.
I'll never let that happen!
You say that, but you're so wet.
Your body is being honest.
Your penis is getting even harder.
Looks like you're at your limit.
I'm not... No!
Stop fighting and just let it flow out.
No! Something's, something's...
No...
No... I'm cumming from my dick!
This is the cum you just let out.
Having a girl taste her own cum
is wonderful, don't you think?
Now that we've taken care of your manly needs,
let's take care of your feminine side.
Principal? You... Let me go!!
You're really wet.
No, let me go! Let me go!!
Such a reaction... You're already well
on your way to becoming our slave.
I'll just keep fucking you until your
transformation is complete.
No! No, no, no!!
Kou-onii-chan!
She's not in any of the rooms!
Shit! Did she go outside?
No!
No, not there, not my ass!
That boy is using his power to look.
No, I don't want him to see me like this!
Kou, don't look at me! No!
That's Himegi-sensei's office.
But if I'm wrong again...
I don't have time to worry about that!
I'm going to save Miu.
You guys stay here.
Let me go too. I might be raped by them,
but I can't sit around. I need to do this!
Yeah, we might get raped, but we're fruits!
If we don't do something, the world will end!
Huh? I...
That's right, in order to stop the end of the world,
the fruits are raped and turned into slaves...
Huh? Was that how it went?
I'll be back soon! Wait for me!
No, I don't want any more!
I'm...
Not there!
Don't do that!
I...
Just a little more. One by one, the fruits are ripening.
My ass! No, don't put it in! Don't put it in there!
It's going inside me! It's making me so wet!
You're getting this turned on from
your ass? No wonder you're a fruit.
It's rubbing up my insides! It's going crazy inside me!
It feels better than it did in the dream, right?
Just let yourself go.
I will never... let myself do that...
Your ass is getting so wet. This is hilarious!
You must be at your limit. I'll let you cum.
No, no more! If you're any rougher than this, I'll...
You came, didn't you? You can't fight against the truth.
No, don't move! Don't move right now, I...
I will never... give up!
You believe that with his love, you girls
will be able to save the world, right?
Sounds great.
Dad, hurry the fuck up. I wanna fuck her too.
You're right after him. Just stand guard for now.
Shit. He's here.
Kou? I don't want him to see me like this!
That was fast.
Have his powers improved?
Not like this!
I'm gonna break!
Are you relieved he's coming here? You've loosened up!
This is too rough! I can't...
Save me! Kou!!
There's so much...
What the hell's happening??
Seiya!!
Kou?
Miu!
What's going on?
It's begun! The world is ending!
Is it because we've started to turn into their slaves?
Is there nothing we can do anymore?
Do these monsters really want the world to end?
I couldn't wait any longer so I had sex with her too.
Kou?
When we're done saving the world...
I want you to give me a lot of loving.
Come on, Kou.
You made me say something so embarrassing.
Sorry...
So, like... Kou...
I want to be with you.
Let me be with you until the very end.
I got it. Let's do our best.
Se-Sensei?
What in the world is happening?
What can I do?
You still can't remember anything?
The endless memories of this world's laws.
Those memories, and the ones of your family,
which intricately tie in with them.
Is this all because I can't remember anything?
We cant avoid the world's destruction because of that?
The monsters under me have experienced
this over and over again.
So, we might be able to do something different this time.
You think so?
The last monster standing is the one who decides that.
If you're willing to give that up, that is.
I cannot do that.
I promised Miu that we'd keep fighting until the end.
So if it's my destiny, I'll...
I can't move...
That's a shame.
But then again, if your memories had returned,
I wouldn't be able to do this.
The way that you are now...
Look how big you got.
Doing lewd things all the way out here by
yourself, won't the other girls get lonely?
No! Why is this happening?!
This is amazing! It's going all the way
into my stomach and stirring it up!
Yurina, doesn't it feel amazing?
It hurts! No! I don't like this!
Stop!
I'm going to keep fucking you, just
like this, until the world ends!
If you're so rough with my ass and
pussy, I'll get really turned on!
Oji-san, you're taking such good care of Yurina and Miu!
No! Onee-chan, why? I don't want this! Onii-chan!!
Azusa, Yurina!
Miu!!
No! Kou, don't look at me! I can't lose to this!
Miu and the others are being raped,
so why are you this hard?
You're making me jealous.
You have so much power in you,
but you don't even realize it.
Everything will end, along with the beginning.
This cum is amazing!
Thank goodness.
Now, just like that, while cumming... Die.
Sorry. This is also one of my powers.
No, principal, please, no more!
No, not there!
No, Kou! Stop watching! If you watch, my body gets so hot!
They're rubbing deep inside me.
They're even going into my ass!
I'm going to lose my mind while Kou is watching!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: bis | punk4real