Men: All right, all right. Who could it be at this hour?
Mmm. right now... I guess you're...looking at me
through the peep hole...aren't you?
I'm being watched, aren't I?
Men: (Wha!? Who is this!? And what's with the underwear? She's naked???)
You're peeping on me... with your dirty little eyes. I can tell.
You're looking right at my pussy and you're
making it...so wet I'm dripping.
Rape me with your eyes
Make your cock...hard...I want it to fill me up.
I want you to get turned on by watching me touch myself.
Ohhh. is it a big naughty cock?
I can't help thinking about it. Ohh,
just thinking about it...My pussy gets so wet... Ohh!
I'm so hot now.
It's so hot...to finger my pussy...
right in front of a stranger's home...while
you give me that dirty look...I just can't stop...
Ohh, this is so dirty, I want you to get a good look at
my pussy...Can I get it...even...wetter...for you?
I get so turned on when guys watch me masturbate.
I think about some man I don't know slamming
his cock into my pussy...and I just can't stop.
I think about what would happen...
if someone comes along...and finds me masturbating right here...
What if someone takes advantage of me...takes me to his room...
Ohhh...and makes me his prisoner...
and screws me with his cock from morning to night...
Just thinking about it gets my pussy juices flowing...
I can't stop it.Ohhh, I'm overflowing.
Are you starting to feel from watching me be so naughty?
Men: Well yeah... If someone as hot as this girl
starts masturbating right in front of my eyes...
Ohhhhh, I knew you were watching me! I'm so excited.
You even got hard from watching me be naughty. I'm so lucky.
Ohhhhh, my pussy is so wet, it feels so hot... Can you tell?
Oh yeah, that's it, look at me like I'm your dirty little slut.
Ohh, I'm trebling. It makes me so hot,
my pussy juice is dripping. It's so easy for me to fit this vibrator
up to the base. I want it to go all the way inside and go wild
inside me. I want to hear that dirty sound! Ohh,
just thinking about you watching me...Oh no!
Ohhhh! I'm cummming!! I'm cummmming!
Men: (Oh no... If the neighbors see her here then
I'm going to be the one who ends up being branded a pervert...
What am I gonna do... Okay! I don't have a choice!)
Men: Umm, excuse me... If someone came along
right now this is going to cause problems...
Men: (Wow, she really is in her underwear...
It's really hot... but this isn't the time)
Men: Hey, listen to me... Whoa, what!?
My pussy is tingling...
But I just can't stop knowing you're giving me that dirty look...
I'm going to start dripping everywhere.
Men: Wow... She's so wet..
Men: Er, um... So are you... one of those...
Nymphomaniacs or something?
Yeah...I just can't stop myself when I start to think about sex...
I always end up like this...wanting someone to screw me...
screw me hard. Ohhh, I want you to fuck me hard right now.
Men: Wait! What are you doing!?
Men: Well, this isn't the place! Give me a break!
Oh yeah, it's so hard. It looks like it's going to burst. Did it get
this hard, because you were thinking abut screwing me?
I'm so...excited. Please, punish me for being such a bad girl.
Wow...it's so big and hard. I could cum so easily...﻿just by thinking about getting hit by your big hard cock...
Aaah, being fucked by this thick cock might tear me apart! ﻿Ohhh, but I want it like crazy.
Oh yeah, move your fingers all around me... My pussy is so wet,
squeeze that juice out! It sounds so dirty! I can't stop!! Ohh,
you dick is so hard! I want it so bad!!
Ohhh!! Ooooh! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum like this,
rubbing your dick. I'm cumming! I'm cummmming!
Men: Oh no! I'm about to cum too!
Ohhh, ohhh, I'm sorry., I just...l felt too good.
I already came I'm sorry, I came already.
Men: Aaah, I'm a mess. I came in my underwear...
Ohh, I'm so sorry. I got you so messy. Let me clean you off.
Ohhhhhh, this cock is so sexy up close.
Wow, it,s covered in cum...
It smells like sex, it's so hot. Let me clear it off for you.
Ohh, there's some cream coming from the tip.
Your cum tastes so good, it makes me so hot.
Your huge cock is too big for my mouth. Oh yeah, I love it.
It's making me drool, it tastes so good! I love your cock.
Men: This is just too amazing... I feel like I'm about to cum again.
Yes, yes, just fill me up with your dirty cum!
Shoot your load all over my face! Get me messy!
Men: I'm cumming!
Ohhhh, it's so hot... And there's so much...Amazing...
The smell...It smells like raw sex... My face is so
sticky with your cum. I'm a pervert aren't I?
Yeah, I love it. I want you to punish me for being so dirty.
It makes me so hot. I just lose my mind.
Please, I want you to have your way with me.
Men: Oh! Wait what!?
Do my breasts turn you on?
Men: Ohh, wow! So soft, this is totally turning me on.
Ohhhh, that's such a sexy sound. It's turning me on.
I'm just a slut that loves big hard cocks. I'm crazy for
cock and I want it all the time.
I'm so embarrassed to admit it... but your dick...
It's so thick and hard...it's just what I want...
It's just what I want inside me, pounding every one of my holes,
I want it so bad...
Men: Every hole?
I love it in my pussy and my butt.
I want them both pumped full of your hot cum.
Ohhh! I love tasting men's cum!
Men: You... really are a slut aren't you?
You like being called that. Oh, here it comes!
Men: Ohhhh!
Ahhhh...Wow...you came so hard.
Your semen tastes so good...
Oh yeah...the smell of your cum is driving me wild.
I can't control myself any longer...
Can my pussy have a taste?
Men: Is it really ok... to doing this?
Please, don't tease me like that!
Not when I want your cock so bad I'm going crazy.
Ride me hard with that steel dick of yours.
I can't control myself any longer.
hard and fil me up with your cum.
I want you to drive it into my pussy
Ohhhhh, it's so hard!
Just pressing against the entrance...
Ohhh ..I just can't help myself any longer.
Oh yes, I feel like I'm floating.
Your cock feels too amazing.
Ohhhhh! You're inside me!
Your cock is inside me!
It's in so deep! I can feel you hitting my womb, it's amazing!
Your dick is exactly what I need right now!
Oh, it sounds so dirty!
No, don't stop! Don't ever stop!
Oh, oh, ohhhh! It feels so good I just can't control myself.
Oh no! My pussy is leaking!
I'm overflowing! I can't stop!
My slutty pussy...it's tingling!
You dick is going to stretch it out!
Men: Then pleasure me good.
Oh, you're so wild! I'm being abused by you!
It's so hot! I'm so turned on!
My poor pussy is getting punished! Oh! I'm cumming!
Men: I'm not going to stop even if you cum, okay?
Ohhhhhhh! I get so turned on when you talk dirty to me!
Yes, punish me! Call me names!
Your cock just takes my senses away, I go wild.
Oh, you're going to break me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Ohhh! I'm cumming!
No, please, ohhh! You'll tear me apart...
Ohhh, let me rest...this is too much...
Ohh, I'm gonna cum again!
Ahhh! My pussy feels so good!
My pussy wants it so bad!
Oh no! I'm gonna cum again!
Men: This is awesome... You really want to go until morning?
Ohh! I'm gonna  cum again too!
Fill my pussy up with your cum!
All the way into my womb! Fuck me hard! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My pussy is orgasming again!
Pump me full of semen, all the way into my womb!
I'm cumming!!
Men: Yeah, I can't believe I had this much in me.
I'll have to clean it up later...
Ohhh, ahhh... I'm sorry.
Let me make sure...you get all clean.
Men: You... really are a dirty girl...
Ohhh, your cum...it tastes so good...
it smells so good...I can't think about anything else.
Men: (Oh yeah... She mentioned that she'd
take it in the ass too...)
You want to do it from behind this time...
Ohh!! Ah! Not there!
Owwwie! Anal!
Oh-oh-oh! I'm cumming already!
You're making me cum just by being inside me!!
Men: Yeah, my dick is covered in cum, so it went right in.
Ohhhh, my ass is taking your giant dick
all the way up to the base!
I'm getting anally fucked!
Ohhh, I just can't think any more.
Just make me your bitch and give it to me.
I can feel the vibrations from every
thrust all the way in my womb!
I﻿'m tingling inside.
Oh, it feels so good my brain is going to melt!
My body is melting, with you anal sex.
Your dick is going so deep inside it's driving me wild...
I'm a slut... I'm a slut that's hungry for your cock!
Ohhh! Make me even wilder..
Oh yeah, my pussy wants thick cock too!
Oh yeah, I can feel it in my pussy while you ride my ass!
You'll make me bad!! You'll turn me out!
My pussy and my ass are orgasming!
I﻿'m cumming! I'm cumming! Oh, I'm cumming!
Ohhh-oh-oh! I...I can't even breathe...
It-it feels so good! You've totally made me an animal!
I feel like I'm going to pass out!
Oh my God your cock is amazing! Anal sex is wonderful!
You fit it all the way in! You'll tear me apart!
You'll rip up my hole! My asshole is torn up! You're too big!
Wow, amazing. Both are so wet and sticky, I love it!
I love having strangers take advantage of me and fill
my holes with cum!
Men: Wow, it's like you're sperm bank or something.
Oh yeah, I love hearting, you say that! It makes me so horny!
Yes, that's right, I'm your cum bucket!
I love having all of my holes pumped with semen!
I want it again and again!
Even anally I... Ohhh! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! Oh my God, I'm cumming!
Fill my ass with your hot semen now!
Ohhh, ohhh, my ass...
I can feel your cum...
your cum is filling me up...
Oh yeah... Love it, I absolutely love it...
Men: I haven't had enough yet...
I'm really gonna have my way with you.
I can't take it anymore, you're going to tear me apart!
Nooo! Ahhhh-ahhhhh!
I can feel your cock hit my womb!
My pussy is so wet and sticky with your cum.
Ohh, my pussy is right out in the open!
You're even wilder than before! It's too rough!
I really am going to tear apart!
Wow, you're so hard, even though you're cum much!
I love your cock! Tear my pussy apart with your big fat cock!
Fuck me hard and make me scream!
Your thick cock is stabbing me in the pussy!
Oh, no, you'll make me even more wild!
Oh yes, yes, I love it when men see me like this!
I'm overflowing! I'm squirting pussy juice, I'm going to break!
Ohhhh! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Yes, I'm cumming!
I have an orgasm every time you thrust your hot dick into me!!
I can't even count how many times I've orgasmed!
I'm cumming again!
I can't stop cumming, you're making me melt!
It feels too good... Oh, my womb!
You keep hitting my womb!
Ohhhhh, it's hitting me even harder!
My pussy is so full of cum!
It sounds so dirty! I can hear it echoing inside my body!
I've never heard it like this before!
I can hear your dick thrusting inside my pussy!
So rough! I'll never walk again!
Your cock will ruin me for other men!
AHhhhh, I've cum so many times,
I don't even know how to count!
Oh, it sounds so dirty!
Wow! You're invading my womb!
Men: Ooohh! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Ohhhh, yes! Fill my womb your semen, I want it so bad!
Please, quench my thirst for your cum!
Oh no, you really are... g-going to...break me.
My pussy is going to melt! It's going to melt!
It's going to melt into pussy juice. Ohhh, amazing!
I'm your perverted cum slut, tear my pussy apart!
Oh my God, this is the biggest one yet! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! Oh my God!
I'm cumming!
I'm cummmmminnngggg!
Men:......Huh... Did I fall asleep?
Men: Wait...Even though we did all this...
you know...Actually...l have a friend coming over so...
Oh... your friend?
Men: Ok. So...You're not going to?
Ok, so you're going to let me get to know your friend,
and you'll both make me yours then right?
Men: What!?
This time I'm going to take dicks in my pussy and my ass...
Just thinking about it makes me... Ohhh I can't wait.
Men: (Whoa...She's really going along with it...)