This is strange.
I just wanted to get over my hobby
for the sake of a girl I am in love with.
Why did things turn out into
something similar to a porn game?
That's right, it all started on an after class in the classroom.
Amasaki Ayame.
She's a usual gal on the surface,
but she loves anime and porn games.
She confessed to me while
rubbing herself onto my desk.
And just like that, she tempted me to have sex with her.
Wait, what even was with that situation?
Miyanoue Kanna.
She's a classmate of mine who is
a jealous girl and doesn't like otakus.
She's my first love and the reason why
I want to get over my otaku hobbies.
...or that's how it was supposed to be.
Satogami Yuri.
She's my childhood friend who lives next door.
She can get wild at times.
She peeps and masturbates or
waits in a restroom to give blowjobs.
She is a real pervert!
Student Council Room
Our homeroom teacher Miru-chan have finally
found out about our days of messing around.
Hey, Nagato-kun!
Would you stop bringing any more
shame into our school?
Dammit... You thoughtlessly sleep with just anyone...
Just man up and pick any one of them already!
I can't ignore this as a disciplinary committee member!
And so, I have to until the school festival to decide.
How long are you gonna decide? Jeez...
I got thoroughly lectured up to the smallest detail.
Choose Kanna-chan already!
If you're a man...
Kanna-chan is...
However...
There's no way that I can choose
one among the three of them.
I might be able to move forward and decide
if there'll be some kind of catalyst.
That's right, some kind of a catalyst.
I knew it! It's you, onii-chan!
Huh...
U-Umm...
It's me! It's me!
It's me, Tori'i Ui! I used to live next door!
I never thought that we'd meet again in a place like this!
This can be nothing else but fate!
I-I guess I should be glad that I kind of got a catalyst...
Real eroge situation 2!
Wow! It's you, Ui-chan!
Yuri-chan! I missed you!
My, my... You've grown up Ui-chan!
Huh, she has nowhere to stay for the night?
Yeah, so I was thinking of letting
her stay over for a while...
Of course, she's very welcome to do so!
Moreover, this is your house.
Then, I'm gonna have a shower!
I'd leave her up to you, okay?
Ui-chan!
You have a thing for Nobu-kun, right?
Of course, you do!
Huh?! Th-That's right...
Nobu-kun is a heartthrob, so you'll lose
him if you keep dawdling around!
You have to take advantage of
staying together under one roof!
Alright, go for it, Ui-chan!
Mama's rooting up for you!
O-Okay!
What are you trying to pull off, Nacchin?
Oh, I'm just giving a little push on a girl in love!
Hoah!
Ah... Ouch!
So, this is onii-chan's dick...
U-Ui?!
That's right! It's me, Ui!
No, that's not what I mean...
You're quivering here as well!
Wait... Ui! Do you know where you're licking?!
I know!
Onii-chan, do you like being licked here?
I-I think men generally like that.
They're rolling around so much.
Then, I'm gonna lick you a lot more!
You're so cute, onii-chan!
Tell me if I'm making you feel good!
I'm gonna come already!
It's okay, right in my mouth... Shoot it... shoot it!
I'm coming!
Hey, Ui!
Onii-chan... It's fine, right?
I can't hold myself back anymore!
It's going inside!
It went inside!
A-Are you alright?
I-It hurts a little.
But other than that, I'm happy!
Your dick is going in and out of me...
I'm having sex with you, onii-chan!
Ui, your pussy feels great!
My pussy is feeling great too!
Even though it's my first time, I'm feeling this way...
This is terrific! So this is
your pussy... It's so amazing!
Good... It feels so good, onii-chan!
It really doesn't hurt, right?
Yeah, it's alright.
Despite the pain, I'm happy
to feel you being inside me!
More... do it more intensely!
I want you to yearn for me!
Onii-chan, onii-chan...
Onii-chan!
Like this?
Your dick went in a deep part of mine!
I can feel it, I can feel you inside!
I can feel your thing inside my pussy!
This is amazing despite being my first time!
Aren't our bodies perfect for each other?
Yeah... It's just as you said.
So intense!
It feels good!
This is like a dream!
This isn't a dream, but it feels like one!
I never had anything like this before!
More, rub your dick more in me!
Make my body... my pussy...
...feel good even a lot more!
Onii-chan, your dick is making my pussy
feel so great!
Me too... I'm already...
It's alright, let's both feel good just like this!
Onii-chan!
My mind is going blank!
Huh... Ui?
It's alright... Inside me... Shoot it inside me!
Please give it to me!
I want to have lots and lots of your sperm!
Onii... Onii-chan!
You're spurting inside me.
Onii-chan, your semen...
It's flowing inside my pussy!
That's how it is. This is my childhood friend
who's staying in my house since yesterday.
I'm Tori'i Ui!
How cute!
I want her!
A-Another busty girl?
Just how many rivals should I
have before you get satisfied?!
Kanna-san? You're making a scary face!
Th-That's how it is. Try to get along together, okay?
Okay! Let's get along together, onii-chan!
That's not what I meant!
Ui?!
Ui?
Ui...
Amasaki, not in this place!
Huh?
Was that onii-chan's voice?
It was from around here...
You twitched in my mouth just now.
You're so cute, Shinobu-kun!
Onii-chan!
And if I'm not mistaken, that's... Amasaki-san?!
What are you doing to my onii-chan?!
This feels good...
You're naughtier than usual today, Ayame!
Your blowjobs feel better now as well.
Of course, since I had lots of practice
from giving you heads, Shinobu-kun!
What?!
You see, I can't think of anything else
besides you all the time.
Delicious!
I'm gonna come already!
If you're gonna come, I want it in my pussy!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
It's reaching deep inside me!
My hips won't stop!
My pussy feels good!
I-I'm gonna come!
If you feel like you want to come,
shoot lots of it inside me!
So good... Your dick feels so good!
Your dick is so amazing that it's driving me crazy!
Wow, wow, wow!
Shinobu-kun, your penis is so terrific!
No, no, no!
I love you penis so much that I'm now losing it!!
I'm coming!
Me... Me too, I'm coming!
Your dick is making me come!
I'm coming—!
Onii-chan...
Jeez, Shinobu... Does my pussy taste that good?
Your pussy is so tasty, Kanna!
Wow, your dick got this big already!
Look, I'm gonna give your dick a good rubbing!
Does it feel good when I rub your dick
while I'm pressing my pussy down on your face?
But not yet!
Your dick is scraping my pussy!
No, you heard me? You can't move!
I'm the one who will do the humping instead!
How is it? Does it feel good?
Does rubbing your dick inside my pussy feel good?
You don't have to hold back. Feel free to
let your voice out if you're feeling good!
Oh no... It feels great right here!
It's grinding and churning my pussy!
That face you made looks cute!
You're so cute, Shinobu!
I want you to show more of that to me!
You're not allowed to move! I'm going to
devour your penis on my own, Shinobu!
Kanna, your pussy feels heavenly!
Not yet!
You're not allowed to ram my pussy yet!
I-I'm already...
Can't you hold yourself back anymore?
It can't be helped.
Alright then, shake your hips a lot more!
Keep ramming your dick inside me!
No way! I'm coming already! I'm gonna come!
T-Together! We should come together! Both of us!
Let's come together, Sh-Shinobu!
No! Coming! I'm coming!
Well then, time to eat!
Huh? I-I knew it!
This has your flavor in it, Nobu-kun. It's delicious!
Okay then, Nobu-kun.
I'm gonna rub your dick and make you feel good, okay?
Your dick became so hard!
Yuri, your tongue is...
You're so cute, Nobu-kun!
I'll squeeze it in between my tits
and make you feel good, okay?
Am I making you feel better than Ui-chan?
Do my tits feel better than Ui-chan's?
H-How did you know about that?!
Nobu-kun, you cheater!
Nobu-kun, your dick is squishing against my pussy!
Your dick throbbing again!
I wonder if you're about to come...
It's alright. If you start to feel like coming,
squirt it inside my pussy, okay?
First, I'll do it like this
and take my time savoring your dick!
Your hard dick is hitting me right there!
Yu—
Nobu-kun, you're so cute!
I'm gonna squeeze you harder with my pussy!
So intense! Nobu-kun, you're so intense!
It feels good!
O-Oh no! No... No way...
I'm going crazy!
I'll immediately come with this!
It's alright, you can come anytime you want!
I want you to spurt it inside my pussy
and come lots and lots!
I wanted it all along!
I wanted lots of your thick semen
to fill my pussy up!
But we're not done yet if I spray
it onto you instead, right?
Th-That might be true...
You perverted girl!
I'm fine with either of the two!
Come a lot wherever and
however you want, Nobu-kun!
I'm coming... I'm coming from my pussy!
I-I'm coming!
Nobu-kun, your penis is the best!
All of them are so lewd!
I have to be more assertive too, or else...
Good morning, onii-chan!
Huh? Ui?
Hey, onii-chan...
Don't you want to try touching my tits?
I want you to touch them by yourself.
B-But...
You don't want to?
O-Of course I want to!
Onii-chan, your dick is so hard and slippery!
I'll start by moving slowly, okay?
I'll move my tits back and forth like this...
One... Two...
Wow, the tip of your dick
is gradually oozing a lewd juice!
This smell makes my head feel dizzy
and makes me feel excited!
Onii-chan... I'm gonna lick your dick, okay?
Your penis loves it!
I'm glad!
Here... Come a lot!
I'm coming!
He's filling me up with semen in my mouth!
Onii-chan, my embarrassing place is in your full view!
Don't you want to feel good as well, onii-chan?
You're so lewd, Ui!
Hurry... Put your dick in already, onii-chan!
Your dick is a tight fit in my pussy!
Your dick is rubbing against
the deepest part in my pussy!
I love how it feels getting
pushed inside there! I love it!
Ui, your pussy feels so hot!
N-No...
My mind went blank from the excessive pleasure!
Onii-chan, more!
Come on, thrust it into me.
Ram me with your dick!
You're coiling around me!
Onii-chan, your dick started to quiver.
Could it be that you're about to come?
Are you about to come and squirt in my pussy?
Here you go, come! Fill me up inside, hurry up!
Th-There's no way that I...
Let's come together! Don't hold
it in! Pour it into my pussy!
I'm already at my limit!
Come! Come in my pussy!
I'm coming!
Y-Your hot stuff is flowing into
my deepest parts, onii-chan!
Huh?!
Wait... Onii-chan?!
Ui, I still haven't had enough!
Y-You just came inside my pussy!
No!
Don't move!
Don't ram your dick yet!
Onii-chan, you're being too rough!
No!
Onii-chan, I can't take it anymore!
I-I became weird! I can't think of anything
else now besides dicks and pussies!
I became a lewd little sister!
It's okay for you to feel way even better, Ui!
Onii-chan, your smell got rubbed in my pussy!
It's okay, I'll rub it in even more.
Yes! Give me more of your semen!
Spurt and pour it into me!
Onii-chan, your dick is throbbing!
I'm coming!
I'm coming from your dick!
And finally, on the day of the school festival... I...
The choice I made is...
To have a harem ending... It's just as one
would expect from you, Shinobu-kun!
In the end, I was unable to choose one over another.
Getting rubbed by both of our tits...
You're so greedy, Nobu-kun!
Having sex with everyone is fun and it feels good!
That's because I love every one of them so much!
Where does it feel better, on the tip or the underside?
Of course, that would be wherever I am licking him.
Onii-chan, does this feel good?
Do both of our hands feel good?
This feels way different from a pussy,
so make yourself feel good from this.
Our lewd daily lives keep going on and on.
Shake your hips more, Shinobu!
It feels good when your rub us with your dick!
Do my tits taste good, Nobu-kun?
Damn, you lucky guy!
That's because this is our...
Shinobu...
Nobu-kun!
Onii-chan!
Shinobu-kun!
Give it to us!
"Real Eroge Situation"!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization