This is amazing...
More... More!
Shinobu-kun... Shinobu-kun!
What's happening here?
Why is my classmate
raping my desk?
Hey... can you show me yours too?
Eh? Mine?
Of course, I'm talking about that!
I'm talking about the way you masturbate!
W-Why should I?
Why, you ask? Your dick will hurt if you won't.
Let's both relieve ourselves!
Shinobu-kun, your penis is amazing!
To think that you got hard watching me
masturbate makes me feel kind of happy!
Alright, start fapping too, Shinobu-kun!
Hey, hey, Shinobu-kun!
What stuffs do you usually masturbate on?
Porn sites? Or porn games?
Or could it be... that you fantasize about a girl you like?
Th-That's up to me to decide!
But you know what, Shinobu-kun...
Just fantasize about me this time.
Rub one out and make yourself feel good!
I'm kind of a klutz, you see.
I kinda messed up the order of
things on how to approach you...
Well...
You see, I...
I... I am in love with you! Please go out with me!
Why are you saying that now?
I'm gonna come already!
Ah... Hey!
Show me how you ejaculate!
I'm coming!
Shinobu-kun...
Real eroge situation!
A confession in the classroom
afterschool while masturbating.
This eroge-like situation started from this letter.
You really came! I'm glad!
Well then, let's do some very lewd stuffs!
She's Amasaki Ayame, the popular
girl in our class who called for me.
M-Me too! I love you so much, Nobu-kun!
I'm also fine with doing lewd stuffs!
She's my childhood friend Satogami Yuri,
who got assertive after hearing about Amasaki.
I-I'm in love with you as well!
If Nagato-kun wants to, I am...
And I got an unexpected confession from
my unrequited love, Miyanoue Kanna!
And so, my real but eroge-like youth begins.
I even gave up my hobby since
Miyanoue-san doesn't like otakus.
How did things turn out like this?
Student Council Room
I guess I'll ask Ren for some advice.
You changed yourself for Miyanoue,
yet you can't help but worry
about Amasaki and Satogami?
Yeah.
Then, how about turning her
down and starting over again?
But that won't be fair to Miyanoue-san.
Will you let this kind of
relationship with them go on?
Isn't this whole thing all your fault?
Yeah, you're right.
I finally found you!
N-Nagato-kun, if it's alright with you...
Shall we go home together?
Geez... Then how about you settle this
with your scores in the periodical exam?
Exam?
W-What does the exam
have to do with Nagato-kun?
He might not look like it but
Shinobu actually has good grades.
Whoever can get a higher score than
Shinobu can have him for a whole day.
What do you think?
I'm not good at studying.
I can't beat Nobu-kun's score...
I'm not confident that I can do it too.
Didn't you all love Shinobu?
Then use those feelings for the upcoming exam!
I'll do! Even though I hate cramming!
If it's for Nobu-kun's sake!
I'm on it!
I'm looking forward on how will this turn out.
You're really enjoying this, aren't you?
Yes?
Wow! It's Shinobu-kun's bed,
and Shinobu-kun's pillows too!
Hey, didn't you come over to study?
It's because this room reeks with your scent!
Anyway, let's get started. Open your textbook.
Boo...
H-Hey! Amasaki?!
I... I can't...
I can't take it anymore!
A-Amasaki! What are you—
Shinobu-kun, let's do lewd stuffs!
It will be unfair for the other two if I do this.
But it's okay if we won't do the real thing, right?
No, it isn't!
You got this big already.
Is it something like this...
I'll rub you plenty with my tits, Shinobu-kun.
Alright then, should I try to do it better?
Your dick is already rock hard
and it's twitching between my tits!
Stop that, Amasaki! I'm already at my limit!
Don't worry about it!
You can shoot it out whenever you want to!
I'll be taking all of it.
Let me watch you ejaculate as much as I want!
Amasaki!
There so much of hot stuff!
This is bad, Shinobu-kun!
If you keep grinding your hips that much—
O-Oh no! His dick is so slippery.
My pussy is sloppy.
I'm feeling dizzy!
No... I'm close to coming!
I'm gonna come!
Shinobu-kun, together... Let's feel good together!
I'm coming!
Me too... I'm coming... Coming!
Your penis juice is so hot, it's wonderful!
Nobu-kun... No... No...
That's not fair!
I also want Nobu-kun's dick!
If that's how it is...
I need to take action!
Amasaki is quite a handful.
Well, it felt good in the end.
It's Nobu-kun's dick!
Y-Yuri?!
Thanks for the treat!
H-Hey, Yuri-san?
Why are you doing such a thing?
My mouth-pussy only belongs to you!
Squirt your white pee out!
You can pour it in my mouth!
Good! It tastes good!
Your dick jerks up on pleasure
whenever it slides in my mouth!
Shoot it out!, Shoot it out!
Pour a lot deep in my mouth!
There so much of Nobu-kun's semen!
Next will be...
I'll make you feel good using my tits!
Here you go!
Your dick got devoured by my tits.
It's like your dick is gonna burst, it's getting
pushed outward when I squeeze my tits!
How is it? Does my big breasts feel good?
Yeah... That feels amazing, Yuri.
Alright then, I'll try to do even better!
I'll do this, and squeeze your dick with my tits...
It reeks of lewd scent!
Yuri, that's too much!
Are you coming again?
Are you gonna squirt more semen?
It's okay, make yourself feel even better on my tits!
There so much of Nobu-kun's semen!
Thanks for your lewd penis juice!
Infirmary
Alright, Nagato-kun.
Are you ready?
W-Well...
What's the meaning of this?
It's not happy on the idea that only I
haven't had my way on you yet.
I need to give a punishment
on a cheating Nagato-kun, okay?
Wait! I haven't ever decided
to go that much far yet!
Are you talking about the condom?
It would be bad if the bed gets stained so...
Oh, I got it!
Well then, I'll never let you run away!
Nagato-kun, you're already like this!
It feels good, but that's not just it...
What could it be then?
Well...
It feels good 'coz it's your hands squeezing me!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?
I-It's too late to try making up
to me by saying such words!
That's too much! You're being too rough!
Your making such a wonderful face!
You're even drooling in pleasure.
You're feeling amazing, right?
What's this? Was Miyanoue-san
always this much of a sadist?
While you're making such pathetic moans,
squirt it all out and ejaculate!
C-Coming!
W-Wow! It's amazing!
It's like the condom will break from its force.
There's this much semen... And after
taking the trouble making you come.
We can't let it go to waste.
Boys like this kind of stuffs, right?
My tits are small though
so it might not feel as good.
No, I'll say it felt rather very good if you'll ask me!
B-But when compared to those two,
I'm lacking in the breast department, right?
Miyanoue-san! I'm... already...
Already, you say?
I wonder what you mean, Nagato-kun?
Those eyes are so lovely that it's a crime!
It's okay. Don't worry and let me see
how you spray out your semen!
Come on, Nagato-kun!
Shoot your semen out! Come a lot!
Oh! It's so warm!
You came a bunch!
Your outrageous and lewd scent
has already been infused within my body!
Take responsibility if it never wears off!
Student Council Room
Eh—!
S-Same scores?
Yeah, this is an unexpected outcome.
It seems that everyone gave their best.
La la, la la la, la la...
Yay! Yay! Yay...
Same score!
Ain't this a problem? What should we do now?
Don't you just need to divide
the day with each girl separately?
Then, I'll have the noontime!
Maybe I'll take the afterschool.
I want to go and see Nagato-kun's room.
I'll have the nighttime!
I can sleep over your place
since I just live next door!
Isn't this great, Shinobu?
Just wait a second... Eh...
It's your beloved harem ending.
Shinobu-kun... Let's eat lunch together!
Alright, I'm fine with it.
Will we eat here?
Let's go there, okay?
2D
Lovers
Club
Room
Key
How is it, Shinobu-kun?
Doesn't it feel nostalgic?
You really joined the 2D lovers club.
That's right!
And I was thinking about having a fun
otaku life with you when I joined...
S-Sorry...
Otaku life?
That's right! For example,
doing something like this...
A-Amasaki! Wait—
You dick got this hard already.
You really have that kind of fetish!
Well then, I'll try a technique
I learned from ero-games on you—
I'll do this, starting from the tip of your dick...
I'll lick it all over up to the base!
Amasaki! I'm already...
Shoot it out!
Shoot a bunch of your lewd penis juice.
If you do it that much, I'm gonna come again—
I want you to squirt in here next!
Can you see it, Shinobu-kun?
I've always been fantasizing
about us doing something like this!
Today, even if just for this moment,
make me yours, Shinobu-kun!
Y-Your penis is entering inside me!
Amasaki, you were...
Are you surprised that a gal
like me just had my first time?
I decided that I'd only give
my first time to the man I love!
I'm honored to be the one that
took your first time, Amasaki.
No... Ayame!
You're thrusting hard!
Your dick is thumping me inside!
We're connected! Your dick is penetrating me!
Your pussy feels so good, Ayame!
Your dick feels so good too!
I'm losing my mind!
I'll do the moving this time.
It's too much! Your insides feel incredibly good!
Really? I'm glad!
Shinobu-kun! It's good, it feels good!
Ayame!
It's okay, shoot it out!
Squirt your semen out, shoot a bunch of it!
Come! Take this!
Take this! Take this!
I-I'm coming!
Your penis is hollowing me out!
You came so much!
I want you to make me come next!
So intense! Your penis is poking inside me!
Your penis feels so strange!
I love you, Shinobu-kun!
Shinobu-kun, Shinobu-kun!
Ayame, I'm already gonna...
Me too... I'm gonna come so let's do it together!
C-Coming!
It's like a snake! You're pouring it into me!
My pussy is being pumped so much with your semen!
We came together at the same time!
After-
school
Afterschool.
Sealed
You really went to such great lengths just for me.
I'm totally
gonna stop
being an
otaku!
Umm... Well, yeah...
I see...
Hey, Nagato-kun?
Did you just left such a book out on purpose?
Did you want to try doing things like this on me?
Th-That's...
Don't you want to?
That's... Well...
Indecisive boys needs to be punished.
How is it?
Does this feel good?
Yes!
Oh, you're getting off from a footjob.
You're a pervert!
Here you go!
Oh my, are you coming?
You don't have to hold yourself back!
Hurry up and do it!
But you can still come more with this, right?
Nagato-kun...
What are you planning to do?
What, you ask? Payback time!
No! Not your tongue!
Want me to stop?
Stop! I'm gonna come!
Your dick...
I want to come from your dick!
No—!
Alright then. I'm putting it in, Miyanoue-san.
No... Kanna!
Okay... Put it in. I want to have
sex with you, Nagato-kun!
You're going inside me!
Kanna, are you alright?
It really does hurt on the first time.
But I'm fine already,
so you can start moving.
Just tell me when it becomes unbearable, okay?
Yes... Thank you.
Nagato-kun, does my pussy feel good?
Yeah... It's the best!
Your dick is pulsating so hard!
You're feeling good that much ...
I'll give you more pleasure!
Kanna! Wait... You're being too rough!
Could it be that you're close to coming?
Your dick is twitching!
Kanna, I'm already at my limit!
I'm gonna come too, let's come
together at the same time!
You're messing my pussy up!
So intense! I just came earlier!
If you do it this wildly, I'm gonna come again!
This is bad!
Shinobu, this is bad!
I'm coming!
Come here! Right here, Shinobu!
Come and make my pussy feel good!
Kanna, I'm gonna come again!
Come in me! Spurt it a lot into my pussy!
You shot a lot of creamy semen!
Kanna... You're so lewd!
You're no better, Shinobu.
To shoot out this much, you're so lewd!
Night
time
Nighttime!
You took your time eating, Nobu-kun.
Umm... Sorry for waiting.
I'll be making you feel good a lot!
Oonya~!
Ohh... You're full of motivation too, Nobu-kun!
How does it feel when I do it like this?
Yes... They're soft and they feel good!
Can I try moving as well?
Okay!
Nobu-kun is feeling good!
Yuri, I'm already—!
Okay, give me a lot!
Yuri!
You're semen is so warm!
I want you to have my first time, Nobu-kun!
Yuri... You...
Before we have sex,
can you grant me a single request?
Yuri... Are we really gonna record this?
Of course!
We need something to keep
our first time together into.
Well then, Yuri.
Okay. Come here, Nobu-kun!
Nobu-kun, just like that... Deeper.
Push it up to my deepest parts!
Yuri!
Nobu-kun just inserted his penis inside me.
That's good, Nobu-kun!
More... Make your penis kiss
the deepest parts in my pussy!
Even though it's my first time, my first time,
It feels good!
Your penis is reaching my deepest part of my pussy!
You can come anytime you want!
I want you to fill me up inside!
Yuri!
This feels way beyond heavenly!
I'm losing my mind!
Nobu-kun, can I make another request?
A-Alright then.
Hump on me more! Mess me up!
More! Rape me violently!
Outdoor anal fuck... Just how
much of a pervert are you?
That's because I am a bitch.
I'm your personal perverted bitch!
Please punish this indecent
bitch using your penis!
Where does it feel better,
in your pussy or in your asshole?
Both... Both of them feels good!
Yuri! I'm about to...
Shoot your semen!
Make me yours using the stench of your semen,
Give me your seminal marking!
I'm coming!
I did something outrageous...
It's too late to say that!
Student Council Room
And then?
In the end you couldn't
decide who to go out with?
I know I have to make a decision...
Hey, Shinobu?
If you can't choose among those three,
how about trying me instead?
Y-You three—!
Shinobu-kun!
Shinobu!
Nobu-kun!
That's absolutely not allowed!
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project