Arrow Two.
Section 8 complete.
Audio manipulation clear.
Can you hear the sound of the helicopter?
No.
It's gotta be the newest model.
I can only hear the sound of the insects here.
Are you sure it's really there?
Are you still okay with all of this?
Yep.
As usual, she doesn't know the meaning of the word "fear".
Why don't you try it once, Mune-san?
You'll get used to it.
I'll take a rain check.
Arrow One.
Preparations complete.
Roger.
Rei, move just as I command you.
No ad-libbing, okay?
I'll try my best.
Arrow One, begin!
Roger.
Rei Zero
Episode 01: Capture the Special Investigator!
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Anonymous | Timing: Zetsuei | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
They've switched to the backup generator.
Ten seconds, okay?
I got it.
Arrow One reporting.
Power has been restored.
Arrow Two, infiltration successful.
Okay.
Arrow Three, move it.
Excuse me.
Some rookie cut the power accidentally.
Um, this isn't a good time...
Just as you predicted,
I don't see any security guards posted on the 30th floor.
Once I'm in, it's all ours for the taking.
If you run into three or more guards, retreat.
Roger.
I'll retreat if it's five or more guards.
I'm cutting communications for a while.
Rei?
Rei!
This is the place.
This can't be...
It's a power outage, I hear.
Ah, but the backup generator is working now,
so there shouldn't be any problems.
Five of them, huh? Well, whatever.
Hey, I wonder where that stupid brother of yours went.
Shit!
For BDW, you're a bit slow.
North Cartel's boss, Joaquin Knight, right?
Who are you?
I'll ask the questions here.
You're Joaquin Knight, right?
Correct.
I didn't want to partici...
I didn't give you permission to elaborate.
I thought this place was a drug factory,
but it appears I was wrong.
What were those things?
Machines that will make us money.
Are you a narc?
Just answer my questions.
What's your name?
I swear I'll kill you!
I'll fuck you up and fuck you up. You'll be so fucked up,
that you'll regret ever being born into this shithole of a world.
That's right.
I'll start with you... then your family!
Then everyone you know!
I'll fuck everyone up to death!
Is that so?
Let's talk more later.
Arrow Two speaking.
I've captured my target.
I'm pulling out.
I suppose I shouldn't have knocked him out.
14F   Firearms Investigations Department
13F   Narcotics Investigations Department
12F   International Investigations Department
Joaquin Knight...
The boss of the international terror group, North Cartel.
Also known as "the General".
Age unknown.
In the second peninsula islands dispute,
he led the guerrillas against the government.
His enemies call him the "Red General".
After the war, he fled to his homeland in South
America, where he took up drug trafficking.
Surrounded by a wealthy and militarily powerful organization,
he built up his terrorist movement over the
years and achieved international infamy.
In recent years, he migrated to Japan.
He formed a new criminal organization here,
and within the span of a year, he'd consolidated all the
minor players of organized crime in the Kanto region.
On the surface, he owns an expensive hotel chain.
Inside his hotels, there are unusually strong pipes.
Then a faction of the Japanese
government got wind of his activities,
and they started putting the pressure on him.
There's a 48-hour hold on sentencing him.
Until that time limit is up, gather 200% of his materials.
You sure talk crazy, Chief.
It makes my ears bleed.
Rei.
I think a former soldier is the most adept
at communicating with a former soldier.
So the guerilla unit you once commanded
is now controlling your narcotics trade.
Oh, how the mighty have fallen, eh?
Young General.
Twelve times.
Eh?
You hit me twelve times.
In the time between the hotel and
here, you hit me twelve times.
Now it's thirteen times.
I'm happy that your memory is so good.
Then you'll be able to answer my questions easily.
What was that?
Last night, I observed that tacky interior,
but everything disappeared within the span of just one night.
We gathered and analyzed the data from the property owner.
We have an expert drawing up a report as we speak.
Which means we'll have our answer in time.
But if you just tell us cooperatively, less harm will come to you.
Gee, I wonder about that.
Maybe I ought to wait thirty... no,
I think forty hours should do it.
My friends are already working to rescue me.
Then the data you stole from us will
be of no use to you whatsoever.
You understand what I mean, right?
Thirteen hits,
Ms. Investigator.
Stop the interrogation.
Why?
We just received new intelligence from a spy.
A spy?
You've heard of the spy Uemachi, haven't you?
Yeah.
The tacky watch that rat wears...
It's a bit hard to forget,
and he's a better gunman than anyone I know.
This is the first time I've heard of
a spy who's not afraid to fight.
That means we can trust his intelligence all the more.
But isn't it a little odd that Uemachi
came to assist us personally?
I think it's very dangerous intelligence.
I'm going to question him.
I want you on a wire listening in.
Don't you think the timing is a little too good?
Even if it's a trap,
I think it's worth the risk if this gives us yet
another card up our sleeve to blackmail Knight.
If it gets dangerous, back out right away.
Yeah, of course I will.
Inside a crowded train, eh?
He's good.
Be quiet.
He's coming.
Roger.
Oh sh...
Wha...
What?
What resistance she has.
Usually it just takes one hit to turn them into a doll.
Stop... it...
Oopsie.
It would be troublesome if you were to contact anyone.
Hey...
Don't tell me...
The passengers on... this train are all...
What a smart lady you are.
Yes, they're all our men.
And also...
This is the thing you guys are looking for right now.
It's a brain-control nanomachine.
It's a machine that controls your brain.
Completely.
But a complete lack of reaction sure is boring.
So I'll let you at least experience pleasure.
Well then.
Have some fun with her.
Stop... No...
Don't... Not so... Stop!
Don't pinch them.
Stop.
My nipples...
Don't pinch them so...
Stop. Not so...
No...
It's so sticky.
The cock too... and my pussy.
So we've encountered them.
It's time for the exchange.
You've heard of the spy Uemachi, haven't you?
The tacky watch that rat wears...
It's a bit hard to forget.
Rei.
What's wrong?
Answer me.
Tell him nothing is wrong.
How did you...
Just tell him.
Tell him, "There's nothing wrong here, sir".
Do it.
There's... nothing wrong... here, sir.
I see. Then continue.
Wait!
That wasn't me just now!
It... It couldn't be...
It's time to teach this strong woman the proper way to fight.
Let her keep her voice.
And also let her keep her pleasure sensors.
So she wears this sort of thing under her civilian clothes?
How exciting.
You assholes!
Let go of me!
Oh dear, oh dear.
Perhaps not enough drugs?
We manufactured this especially to increase a woman's
pleasure level while inhibiting her muscle strength.
What's wrong?
You can scream as loud as you want.
Maybe when your friend hears your
pitiful oinking, she'll come save you.
Who would want...
I won't give you the satisfaction of...
You asshole!
How dare...
Your mouth may complain, but your pussy
is pretty honest with your feelings.
I can't take this.
But I swear I'll...
Oh? So you're still not screaming yet?
Good girl, good girl.
Let's show your tolerance to that sexually
depraved investigator boss of yours.
Stop it.
I'm exhausted, but I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum again.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
Cumming. Cumming!
Rei...
N-No.
Stop.
Don't look.
Don't look at me like that.
Do you know just how you're being fucked?
Explain to us!
In my pussy...
In my pussy.
There's a big cock in there, hitting inside.
All the way to my womb.
Good.
Here's your reward for saying it well.
Don't look. Don't look!
I'm cumming.
I'm gonna cum...
in front of everyone... in front of everyone.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
They're injecting her with that?
It's my... It's all my fault!
Watch me.
It feels so good. Watch me!
I love being watched!
Look at me!
The next one to fall will be you.
She came from the first thrust?
But we've just barely started.
Yeah!
You'll get plenty pregnant, old hag!
The sperm is coming out again.
All the white cum from your penis is spilling into me.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming again.
I'm gonna get knocked up. I'm going to be pregnant!
This feels so good.
My womb... My womb feels it!
That hurts!
My womb hurts.
Come on.
You cum too.
Cum all over the place!
Why would...
Who would want to cum from this?
It's coming.
It really is coming.
From deep inside... deep inside my womb,
I feel his cum flowing in there.
Why you... Why you...
Let me go!
My womb... The inside of my womb is being stirred around!
I can't think of anything else!
No!
You're being too rough!
If you pound me so vigorously, I'll...
Just say it.
Say it.
Say that you're turned on.
I'm not...
No one would be turned on by this.
Scream it out!
Here's my cum!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Lots... I'm cumming lots. I'm dripping in cum!
I'm gonna get pregnant from your cum!
Oopsie.
Don't think about biting it.
Good.
Suck on it gently.
Let me go.
Don't cum on my face.
Stop it!
Oh, not again.
I'm cumming!
Mark my words... I'm going to kill you...
Well then.
I guess you'll get off at the next station.
We're keeping your partner.
If you want to save her, you know what to do.
Come on.
Time to go.
Whoa, look. What's going on?
Is this a photo op?
What's she doing?
Unreal!
The last...
What did you just shoot her with?
A new drug.
It's a shame we can't observe her reaction to it.
I can't hold back.
My body...
My entire body is...
Not enough...
I can't...
I must get to a bathroom.
Will you let me go?
Hey, you...
It's coming.
Coming...
My pee...
I peed in public.
While peeing...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming from pee.
I will kill...
me ga samereba itsu datte kuri kaeshi ni mieru hibi
When I open my eyes, days endlessly repeating seep in.
daiji na mono wa ushinatte hajimete kizuku rashii kedo
People say you don't miss something until it's gone.
hari tsuketa you na mainichi ni
In these monotonous days,
narete nakushite kizuita tte
even if I notice the apathy and loss I feel,
koukai nante shinai to omotte ita
I think I'll never regret anything.
sono hitomi mou ichido
Those eyes, once more
kowashite shimatta
I broke them
dou ka watashi o utsushite
Please reflect me somehow
ano hi no koto
The way we once were
kono omoi mou ichido
These feelings, once more
omoi daseba
If you remember
dou ka anata ni todoite
I hope they reach you somehow
kuyashikute
It's so frustrating
mou nido to
Never again...
kowashite shimatta
I broke them