How's her condition, Doctor?
Rei...
I have to go.
What am... I doing?
What's happening... to me?
Hi.
I've been waiting for you.
I waited 40 hours.
You know what you must do.
Yes.
Rei Zero
Episode 02: The Female Investigator Turned into a Slutty Pig!
Translation: Voldemort | Edit: Anonymous | Timing: Zetsuei | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
Come on.
In you go.
Thirteen.
You understand what I'm talking about, right?
Yes.
I release you.
Thirteen men.
I've assembled as many men as the
number of times you hit me.
Make them all cum within thirty minutes.
Who could do that?
Can you still say that after seeing this?
R-Rei.
Sh-Shoko!
See? You need to satisfy them soon.
Otherwise, that bitch dies.
Why, you...
I don't really care either way.
But in all of history...
I don't suppose anyone's had as pitiful a death as that.
Come on!
Let's start this shit!
Fine.
Say, "Please let me suck your dicks".
Please let me suck your dicks.
You look like you're enjoying it!
Do these unfamiliar dicks really taste that good?
This is degrading.
Hey, hey, if you really want it that bad, then
take my dick all the way down your throat!
Awesome! She's really sucking of her own free will!
Come on!
Suck till you drop!
You really wanna suck that bad?
Is one dick really enough for you?
You fucking slut.
Come on, suck mine too.
Yes.
Come on, come on, take this more seriously!
If you don't, your little friend will be in trouble.
Come on, come on, don't stop!
They all need it.
I need to hurry and make them cum.
This bitch, she's sucking two cocks at the same time!
And she looks like she's really enjoying it.
You fucking slutty pig.
Very nice.
Show us your specialty.
Drink all of our cum!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming deep into your throat!
Come on, drink it up!
There's no time for a break.
Don't struggle.
Now, time for me next.
N-Not there...
Relax your muscles.
I don't care how loud you scream.
I really feel everything all the way down my rod.
It's totally in there.
How is it? Feels good, eh?
That... That's not... possible.
I feel like... everything is... breaking.
I'm moving now.
That hurts!
It's scraping against my butthole.
My butthole is going to break!
I'll die!
Please don't kill me!
I feel your dick... breaking my ass apart.
I'll die!
What? What? You're already sloppy
wet from having your ass fucked.
Want it in here too?
No!
Oh, please have mercy.
I can't. I really will die.
I can't. I'll die.
You fucking liar.
You're squeezing my dick really tightly.
You don't want it out.
You're... ravaging me!
My pussy... and my ass-pussy... are
being ravaged by your dicks.
Okay, here I go.
I'm gonna cum.
I'm gonna cum lots.
You like it, right?
You love having your holes filled with cum, don't you?
Don't cum!
Please don't cum!
If you cum that much, I'll...
It's coming...
So much...
My pussy and my ass-pussy are being filled with cum.
I'm gonna die.
Hey, hey, why are you slacking off?
There are still some men left.
If you try hard, you'll be able to take it.
Right?
Okay, 29 minutes.
I guess you just made it.
Actually,
after you hit me thirteen times...
You kicked me. Remember that?
That makes fourteen.
And then the 14th guy... is me.
No way!
It's time for me to test the full impact of that
new drug created from female sex hormones.
Time's up.
Rei...
Don't worry about me.
Th-Thank you.
You did so much... for me.
Shoko!
I'll kill you!
I'll fucking kill you!
All right!
This is it. This is it!
Can she really be a special duty agent?
Apparently, she's been captured by some drug dealers,
and every day they upload progress
reports on her training to this site.
I guess she's there because she likes it.
Yeah.
I bet they're punishing her for finding
them out and being so smug about it.
She deserves it.
Dude, this bitch is fucking a lot of guys on her own.
There's sure a lot of toys here.
Just how much are they training her?
It seems like many months worth have been deleted,
so it was really hard getting all of these files together.
But whoever collects them all gets a lucky prize, I hear.
So she's lasted three months, eh?
Guess I lost the bet, then.
I guess it's time to start today's session.
Come on.
Open your fucking mouth.
Squeeze mine too, you pig.
Yes.
Next up is this hole.
Come on.
I've had enough.
Just stop it.
Come on.
Clean it up nicely.
She's been entertaining dicks every day for months,
but she's still so tight!
S-Stop it, I'm going to break.
I can't...
I'm going to cum!
Hey, I'm about to cum.
It's your favorite thick semen.
Drink it all up with your dirty mouth!
Oh, no...
I'm cumming!
Just stop it.
It hurts...
Come on.
There's so much.
You really don't wanna get pregnant, do you?
In that case...
Come on!
You'd better get it all out, or you'll get pregnant.
Okay.
Time for your feeding.
Oopsie, don't eat it yet.
Under the General's orders, we're prohibited from feeding
you anything without a nice topping of cum.
Good. Eat up, girl.
I know I say this over and over again,
but you can refuse to eat it if you want.
Your big brother's daughter is Yukari-chan, right?
We can invite her over here anytime.
Here's more!
That's it.
Thanks to your complaints earlier,
your subordinate, Saki-chan...
is fucking so many foreign pervs that
she's forgotten her own name.
I don't think your crimes can get any worse.
She's really eating it!
Is it yummy?
You like our special cum sauce?
You fucking bitch!
Yummy, it's very yummy.
In that case, taste more of it!
See?
Come on, come on, come on.
It's time to change.
Who's this woman?
She's a special investigator who was captured
by the drug organization North Cartel.
And this is Joaquin Knight,
also known as the "Red General".
What a nuisance.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Oh, no.
I'm cumming.
I'm breaking.
No, no, no.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Open wide.
Drink it all up.
It's coming, coming!
Taste it well, you fucking pig.
Stick out your tongue, pig!
What a pretty face!
Suck it with a smile!
Yes, that's right. Suck harder.
They're all beasts.
And I am too.
I don't think I can go back to the way I was.
Hey, keep smiling, you fucking pig.
Yes, sir.
Damn you, Knight.
I'll save you for sure, Rei.
Please wait for me.
I'll avenge Shoko for you.
Chief!
There's a report from an enemy snitch!
What?
Thank you very much,
my master.
Here's your reward.
That's a very nice expression.
Looks like you've finally learned how to be a good slave.
Tell the General at once!
We've got intruders!
What the hell?
Fucking noisy.
Shit!
Move in!
Yes, sir!
So the intelligence from the other
crime organization was correct.
Rei, I'm coming to save you!
You're the Red General, also known
as Joaquin Knight, aren't you?
Where are you, Rei?
Wait, Shien.
Yes, Koryuu-sama.
Who... are you?
Koryuu-sama, please hurry.
After them!
Rei!
Rei, are you okay?
Arrow Two has been rescued.
Captain...
You don't need to explain anything.
Everyone's waiting.
Let's go home.
Chief!
This way.
Take care of the rest.
Hurry!
me ga samereba itsu datte kuri kaeshi ni mieru hibi
When I open my eves, days endlessly repeating seep in.
daiji na mono wa ushinatte hajimete kizuku rashii kedo
People say you don't miss something until it's gone.
hari tsuketa you na mainichi ni
In these monotonous days,
narete nakushite kizuita tte
even if I notice the apathy and loss I feel,
koukai nante shinai to omotte ita
I think I'll never regret anything.
sono hitomi mou ichido
Those eyes, once more
kowashite shimatta
I broke them
dou ka watashi o utsushite
Please reflect me somehow
ano hi no koto
The way we once were
kono omoi mou ichido
These feelings, once more
omoi daseba
If you remember
dou ka anata ni todoite
I hope they reach you somehow
kuyashikute
It's so frustrating
mou ichi do
Once again...
kowashite shimatta
I broke them
So a year has passed.
At last she's back at work.
You're late!
Wait for me, Rei-senpai!
I'm leaving you behind, Fuko.
Senpai!
Wait for me!