Hurray!
Meiou!
Hurray! Hurray!
Nyaako!
It seems like the school headmaster has called for us!
It might be about the club expansion matter!
R-Really!?
It's gotta be that.
Let us hurry to the school headmaster's office, Nyaako!
Roger that!
I Want To Do It With This Girl
Translation: VoidGenome | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
School Headmaster's Office
Cheerable!
School Headmaster
You see... Because you two are getting along so well,
some of the staff members have become suspicious.
When you two are alone together during club activities...
You aren't... doing anything perverted, are you?
Of course not!
Just because we both are doing club activities together,
why would I do such a thing with
this shady looking man?
It’s painful, but I have to pretend to
be on bad terms with Kogorou...
Same here!
Why would I embrace a girl with such a sloppy body!?
That's mean Kogorou! That's what you thought of me?
This is my first time hearing I'm shady looking, too!
Excuse me, you two...
Anyways, just be sure not to do anything that
might make others suspicious, okay?
Kogorou, what you said earlier was mean!
What's wrong with saying calling a sloppy girl sloppy?
Cheerleading Club
I lied because I was thinking about you!
Well, your words still hurt me even though it was a lie!
T-Then take a good look, and see for yourself
if my body is really sloppy or not!
I can tell without looking, that useless lump of meat...
E-Especially around your chest..
Now that I look, the balance between the muscle
and the fat is perfect it's an fantastic body...
Hmm? Kogorou, that face...
Wh-What is it?
I just thought of an idea.
Apologize to me about before.
Th-Thats something I won't do!
If you apologize...
You can do anything you like to my body!
Th-That’s not fair Nyaako!
Even though you said I have a
sloppy body, this part of you is...
telling me something completely different.
This sweet smell...
The soft feeling of skin that rubs
against my clothes... I... I...
H-Hey, Kogorou...
M-My hands! My hands acted on their own!
J-Jeez.
Your honest self is cute!
Even I, have a man's pride...
Does this mean that you are apologizing for...
But, I can't hold it in anymore!
H-Hey, Kogorou!
Hold on, Kogorou. Wait...
If you lick it directly like that...
No... Didn't he hear What I said?
His hand, it's perverted beyond my imagination!
I'm ended up being the one thats feeling good!
I'm cumming... I'm cummingl
What's wrong? What happened to that spirit of yours?
Or rather are you going to apologize to me?
As If! Because of something like this...
I'm going to make sure you apologize.
H-How is it Kogorou?
Being kissed by me while your dick is being stroked...
A lot of slippery stuff is coming out from the tip.
Nyaako, right there is...
See? See?
Well, that's...
Kogorou's penis is so big...
Calling him shady looking was a lie.
Well, how about this?
If it's like this... I'll be the one who will want it more!
Oh, no... His penis...
Nyaako, she has some insane techniques...
N-No... His penis... His penis is...
I'm at my limit...
S-Sorry! What have I done without thinking...
I'll pull it out right now!
P-Please wait!
I'm sorry for being mean earlier.
After being called a slob from the
person I love, I was too stubborn.
So... Please give me more.
No, I also...
I'm sorry... Nyaako!
Because of my insensitivity, I made you sad.
Kogorou... I love you... I love you.
Please make love to me more!
When I get penetrated by you, my feeling
of love towards you flows through me!
Kogorou, it's hitting me...
I'm almost.. I'll let it out outside...
W-Wait!
P-Please don't take it out...
N-Nyaako...
As proof of our love, please let it out in my lewd pussy!
Nyaako!
Is it really okay for me to cum inside?
Yes, let it out!
Let out all your sperm inside me!
Here it comes!
Kogorou, I love you!
Nyaako, we will always to be together.
Kogorou, I'm so happy.
Th-Thanks to your suspicion, our hearts
and bodies were able to become one!
Hey, Rin-kun! Grab me some napkins from the back!
S-Sure!
Rin, I have an favor to ask...
What is it, I'm busy here.
I have plans I can't cancel next week,
cart you please sub in for me?
I'll have to refuse.
P-Please Rin! We are friends right?
Sheesh... All right. So, when next week?
R-Really?
We don't have many part timers
here, so it can't be helped.
H-Hey... You need help?
I-I'm okay!
Rin!
Negative x Positive
Kenji, I'm sorry... Are you okay?
Wake up!
H-Hey!
Seems like he just unconscious...
Now is the perfect time to...
Huh? This hard thing is hitting me?
Even though he's unconscious... What a pervert he is.
Well, I have to thank him for saving me earlier.
I'll look after him today.
Isn't it getting fatter down here...
That's weird... Am i doing it wrong?
It's not calming down.
It has a dangerous smell to it.
I don't really want to do this, but it can't be helped.
What is this? its getting hotter and twitching a lot.
If this goes on, I'll...
W-What's this? It has an intense smell, and it's sticky...
Hey, Rin?
You...
I didn't do anything!
Yeah, right.
Rin-san, what is the meaning of this?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is that right? Then...
H-Hey!
Why is this part so wet?
I-I don't know that...
Hey Rin, mind if I continue?
You're acting spoiled now...
W-Well, it's partially my fault that we ended up like this...
Even though I don't want to, I guess it can't be helped.
So dishonest...
I'm putting it in, so tell me if it hurts.
O-Okay, sure.
C-Crap, it's so tight...
Wait, Kenji... You're so rough...
Sorry, I can't stop now!
Kenji, the excitement is making everything turn white...
No!
N-No!
Your big one is rubbing me...
Go ahead, mess me up.
I want to let it out inside you.
You're acting so spoiled...
Can I?
It can't be helped...
This is special, okay?
If you do it that rough, my mind will turn blank!
H-Here I come!
Hurry!
Let it all out inside!
Rin, I love you.
No fair...
You sure know how to act spoiled.
I-It's embarrassing if you say it in front of me, idiot.
Please look over here a little more!
It's excellent!
Kurohime Yuna. She's a very popular idol right now.
Yuna-chan! Please smile!
Puff up your face a little!
Okay!
Well then, we'll be having break.
Thank you very much!
Well done!
Shou-nii!
Let's eat In the dressing room and over the today's schedule.
I, Madarao Shouma, am her manager
due to certain circumstances.
Okay!
Pretty Break!!
Here's how it happened.
Absolutely no!
Father, it's my wish!
The world of idols is very dangerous, please understand!
Why? You're the president of the studio!
But...
I want to be an idol!
Uncle! Mother told me to bring some rice...
Oh, I see! Shouma!
You are looking for a job, right? Right?
Well, yes... What about it?
Shouma, work as Yuna's manager at my studio!
Whaat!?
Yuna, lucky for you!
If our cousin Shouma stays with you,
it should be fine! Do your best!
Really!? I love you two!
Yes, and also...
If anything happens to Yuna, I might kill you. Good luck!
Yes...
And that’s how it happened.
After that I started to work with Yuna as her Manager...
With Yuna's sense of style and cheerfulness,
she had begun to rise in popularity.
A Studio | Yuna-sama | 001
Good work Yuna, let's go home.
Hey Shou-nii, am I really that ugly?
What?
Just now, the seniors said they were
embarrassed to perform with me.
I should quit being an idol...
Yuna!
Have a little more confidence in yourself!
No matter what happens, I'll always be with you.
Our relationship as cousins was already good, but
becoming lovers was just a matter of time in this situation.
Shou-nii...
I want to go all the way.
You can't... This is the dressing room.
But your house's security is too high, and
this is the only time we can be alone.
B-But we are still working!
You're the one who said you want to kiss.
That's because I...
Shou-nii, this...
I-It can't be helped right? Your nipples are hard too!
H-Hey, don't say that!
I'm coming in!
Shit!
So Yuna-chan, you've changed into your swimsuit, right?
We'll be starting our afternoon photo session.
Shiyama-sensei is the photographer this afternoon,
so please relax and try not to be nervous.
Y-Yes!
Well then, manager. I'll be headed there then.
No no no!
Your facial expression is too stiff!
How many times do I have to tell
you to make a womanly face?
I'm sorry!
You got it wrong again!
You're supposed to appeal as if you are giving
your everything to the man you love!
There he goes again.
His skills are amazing, but he's too serious...
Like this?
No.
How about this?
No!
I'll never put out half-assed gravure.
This?
No.
How about now?
No, no!
Cancel the afternoon photo session!
What!?
If you keep playing around, one day your boyfriend
will see through the act and will leave you.
She's hopeless.
Shiyama-sensei, where are you going!?
Ask her.
That's...
Sorry, please give me 30 minutes of break time.
I'll go fix my makeup.
Yuna-chan, please be back in 30 minutes!
Okay!
Oh Yuna, that was fast.
Shou-nii...
I do too, have the resolution to give
everything to the man I love!
Yuna!?
What happ...
Yuna...
Hey, what's this about all of a sudden?
I was told that I'm half-assed and can't
bring out the charm of a woman.
I don't know, so I'll get you to teach me!
What are you talking about...
H-Hey, an idol shouldn't be touching there!
It's fine, just be quiet for a second.
We can't, uncle will kill us!
I'm going crazy...
I've been enduring this all the time because
you are both my manager and cousin.
That's...
But I won't hold back anymore.
Shou-nii's is hot and hard. It must be unbearable, right?
I'll let it out.
Amazing.
Y-Yuna!
Your nose it hitting...
C-Crap...
The feeling of the soft chest and
the slippery tongue is too good!
The smell of her moist pussy...
I can't endure this!
All right, I'll teach you the charm of a woman.
First off, show me you important spot.
T-Thats...
There we go, we have to make
this lewd spot more visible.
N-No... Don't look when it's spread open.
This lewd liquid is gushing out...
That’s not true...
How about this then?
No!
So much is flowing out.
How is it? Do you feel anything?
I-I can't tell...
Your butt is twitching like crazy.
No... My butthole... It's embarrassing!
D-Don't put your tongue in! I'm feeling it!
It smells lewd here.
No... I didn't take a shower so don't sniff it!
So good... It feels so good down there.
Do it. Please mess up my perverted parts...
Yuna!
Shou-nii's thing came a lot but
it's still hard and twitching.
Wow... This taste and shape...
I wonder if this is the feeling Sensei was talking about.
Hey Shou-nii, use your parts to mess me up!
My body wants your cock!
Y-Yuna!
It's rubbing...
Does it hurt?
I'm okay...
I'm okay, so...
Give me... Give me more of the hot stuff inside!
Shou-nii's cock is in deep...
I'll get addicted!
Please do me harder, please!
It feels so good!
Yuna, look here.
The makeup stand mirror.
See? I can perfectly see it going into your pussy.
I'm making a perverted face...
Is this what a woman's face looks like?
It's twitching so much after holding in my everything...
Does it feel good?
Yes... Because I'm spreading my
legs in front of you, how lewd...
It's embarrassing but it feels so good!
Yuna! Tell me what you want lewdly.
I want... I want your child, Shou-nii!
P-Please! Just like this, let out your lewd milk inside me!
A lot... Shoot it all out!
I'll get pregnant!
I'll give birth to your child!
I'll give birth lots!
Yuna, do you get it now?
N-Not at all...
Let's start over from the kiss.
Teach me more.
Wow!
Sexy sexy, come on!
Come on, come on, go!
Oh, one more! Come on!
Come on, yeow!
All right, this is great!
You turned into one hell of a girl after your break!
Okay great, lets finish this up.
Wow! Amazing! Come on, come on, come on!
Oh, yes! Yes! Yeow!
Okay!
And were finished! Good work!
Yuna!
Huh?
Shou-nii! Shiyama-sensei praised me!
H-Hey...
Hey! This is a workplace, don't fool around!
I'm sorry!
S-Sorry!
I see now. It's thanks to him, huh...
You have a great partner.
W-Well...
I'll tell the president about you guys!
There isn't anything going on,
we're just manager and idol!
Yuna-san, did you tell him something?
Of course not!