You...
I heard you want to know about that
abandoned mansion in the forest...
You'll pay me for that information, won't you?
Pay me and I'll tell you everything I know.
I'll tell you about what happened there.
A few months ago
Hey, take a look at this necklace, Zack!
This'll definitely fetch a pretty penny!
Yeah, there's some good shit over here too.
We hit the jackpot.
Hell yeah. With this much, we'll be able to fuck girls all day.
My cock's rarin' to go!
It's been buildin' up.
You men... are unpleasant.
Wh-What was that?
A girl?
Is there a girl here?
What, Tick, could that be the monster we heard about?
You really believe that crap?
That's just gotta be someone pulling a prank.
Y-Ya sure?
That was such a sweet voice.
Hey, come out and play!
Let's all have some fun together!
You dumb or something?
If you wish to lay with a woman that much, I'll help you do it.
A-A woman?
Tell me Zack... are you really a man?
Huh? What the hell are you talkin' 'bout?
'Course I am.
No, you're not. You're a woman.
You just imagined it, didn't you?
She just... She just called you a girl!
Wh-What the hell's going on?!
Z-Zack became a girl?!
I'm a horny prostitute who's been
bought by a man and brought here.
A-A girl?
Wh-What's up with these tits?
Did you not want to lay with a woman?
Come now, you may shove your dick in her as much as you'd like.
But this is... Zack.
Just by looking at a man, my head,
my body, my pussy get so excited.
I want a cock so bad.
Go ahead. Just like that.
Take your friend's virginity with that dick of yours.
My body's movin' on its own!
– Your cock! Your cock!
– What's up with you? Zack!
I can't resist! I wanna put my dick in you so bad!
I can't hold myself back!
Girl!
Cock! Cock!
I'm a prostitute! I've slept with so many men, but I...
This cock is flooding my body with pleasure!
What are you doing getting so pleased from another man?
But I guess you've no choice.
Enjoy the pleasure of being a woman.
Your cock feels so good!
Yes, that's right.
Keep going until you satisfy one another.
Your cock's coming all the way inside me!
I don't care about anything anymore!
I'm just gonna keep fucking this girl in front of me!
Here! I'm almost shovin' my way into your womb, aren't I?!
– It's getting so tight!
– That feels good! Your cock's coming so deep!
I'm gonna cum!
Very good. Imagine it...
Imagine the best climax ever.
I'm cummin'... I'm cummin'... I'm cummin'!!
Your cum's being shot into my dirty pussy!
Alright then. What's gonna pop up? Demons or monsters?
Illusion Within the Room
It's an illusion.
Huh? What's that?
A defensive technique monsters use to trick threats to them.
Whether they use it against a
human or monster doesn't matter...
it's the same weak ass spell used by C-dass monsters.
The name's Bullet.
I'm a pretty big name hunter.
I came here after hearing the rumors involved with this mansion.
The monster here isn't something worth
the time of a hunter of my caliber, but...
After hearing that there's an item that's sought after
by all hunters, I can't really turn a blind eye, now can I?
This should be a piece of cake as usual.
Is it there?
An illusion?
What's a maid and their master doing here?
How nice of you to make an illusion just for me.
I've been waiting for you ever since I saw
you enter the mansion through the window.
I know what you're here for.
This, right?
That makes things simpler.
I don't mind giving it to you.
However, in exchange...
What?!
Would you mind becoming my maid?
What's her game? Mental warfare?
Doesn't seem like that.
What? Does she want me to cross dress or somethin'?
Yep.
Oh, so that's what you're into?
I'd prefer you not to make any strange assumptions.
Well, actually, let me clear up one more assumption you made.
I'm not an illusion.
What? Can she read my mind?
She can not only read minds, but
can transform herself into a human?
No, she could have even more powers than that.
Hey, Bullet I have a favor to ask.
Could you tell me what kind of girl you like?
Don't worry, you can just imagine her in your mind.
This girl... What's she up to now?
There's too much uncertainty about her.
Should I retreat?
I'll use my escape item, and go there...
You're too late.
You already imagined her.
What's goin... My body's on fire!
This seems like fun, so I'll only change your body.
Ch-Change?
D-Don't tell me you have the power to
change a man's body into a female's?
Shit! Are you gonna turn me into a monster?!
My consciousness is... fading...
Residence.
Th-This is...
Is this the tavern I go to all the time?
Did I use the item?
Was I able to get away?
Anya?
So this really is...
My name's Bullet.
What's going on?!
I'm Anya?!
So that girl's name is Anya, huh?
You!
I'll let you know now, but this isn't an illusion or anything.
I created this space and your body from your imagination.
What?
She created this space as well as my body?
I-If that's true, then...
Is she an S class?!
Cute girls like you shouldn't be making those scary faces.
Y-You little...
Now imagine...
– Now imagine yourself doing crazy things to
that body of yours now that you're Anya.
– What are you going on about?
– Now imagine yourself doing crazy things to
that body of yours now that you're Anya.
Now it's time for you to start moving.
My fingers are moving on their own!
That's good. Gently rub your clitoris through your panties.
Doesn't it feel good? It should feel even
better than it did when you had a dick.
My body's doing what she's saying...
I can't stop my body's arousal!
Alright then, let me help you.
Let me help your pussy and those big boobs of yours.
These are such cute pink nipples.
S-Stop!
What's with these boobs?
Did my body really turn into Anya's?
Did you know?
The nipples on women are much
more sensitive than the ones on men.
See?
Just because it feels good, doesn't mean you
should crouch down like that. It's so unseemly.
Your pussy's drenched with your love juices.
Your crotch is so sticky and it's tingling
so hard, you can't take it anymore, right?
Your clitoris is so slimy from all your love juices.
Your body must feel so light and
fluffy from the pleasure right now.
I can feel it building up.
This is bad.
Pleasure's radiating from my crotch...
My hand's moving on its own again!
No! Stop!
No! Not directly!
What is this sensation?
You are a woman now. You can go as crazy as you'd like.
I-It feels so good!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I loved seeing you let go like that. It was very adorable.
But you're not satisfied yet, are you?
Well how about you imagine what you want done to you next?
Wh-Who the hell would want some dude's dick inside them?!
That's quite a warped imagination you have there.
So I guess that means your desire to lay with a woman
and your desire for a dick mixed together, huh?
No! Don't think of anything!
Don't think!
It's futile.
No matter how hard you try to resist, you
can't resist the callings of your womb.
My mind doesn't want this at all, but my body is begging for it!
I'm a guy! I don't want... I don't want a cock!
Make sure you savor it.
S-Stop!
Stop rubbing that strange thing against me!
Alright then, I'll put it in.
S-Stop it! Don't put it in!
Don't run away. Come on, imagine it.
Imagine yourself not even being able
to move from the pleasure you feel.
Imagine the pleasure from the dick
just rubbing against inside you.
The pleasure's spreading! My body's going numb!
It's getting hot! The dick's coming inside me!
Look, just a little more and it'll all be inside you.
Don't tell me you came just from it being put inside you.
That's so adorable.
I wonder how long a man in a woman's body can endure this for.
Come on! Take this!
You're a strong warrior, aren't you?
Shit. All of this for that dumb stone.
You're the best!
I can't get enough of how you're trying to overcome
the womanly pleasures you feel as a man.
This doesn't... feel good... at all...
Endure it!
I won't let her have her way!
How adorable!
You're trying to act tough, but your pussy's hugging me so tight!
Come on! Tell me!
What do you want? Imagine it.
Like I would do that. There's no way I'll cum!
You imagined it, huh?
Very good.
There's no stopping now!
No! Stop!
I can't do that. You're the one who imagined me cumming.
How's the womanly pleasure of being cummed in?
You know it now, don't you?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Bullet if you so desired it, I could let you feel
this womanly pleasure whenever you'd like.
I'm getting so hot! My mind's going blank!
I can feel this pleasure... whenever I'd like?
Get it together! I'm a man!
I'm the invincible hunter, the great Bullet!
Wow, that's impressive.
I can't believe that you still haven't fallen
even after experiencing this much pleasure.
You have quite the mental fortitude.
I want you even more now.
S-Stop!
What is she?
A human child?
She was born a human? So she's not a monster?
Thank goodness. I wasn't sure what
I would do if you disappeared.
I finally have a fairy.
You're my very best friend.
This is the monster?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
encoder: nino
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч