This is a tale of the ancient memories
that dwell in this residence.
Oh?
Are you a fairy?
Are you here to be friends with me?
Th-That was close.
Valessa! Valessa!
Your mother really treasured that pendant, you know?
You're too young to have it.
Thank you for the meal.
H-Hold on, I'm not done talking with you.
Master?
Earlier in the garden...
I see.
That's something a bit difficult for me to do as her Father.
Valessa, I'll leave that matter to you.
As for tonight...
M-Master?
M-Master!
So good! Your dick is so good!
Squish my boobs and mess them up!
Valessa!
Shove it deeper inside! Please give it to me!
So deep!
I'm going to get pregnant!
Let me bear a sibling for the young lady!
M-Master!
Can I talk to you again?
Thank you. Are you here to cheer me up?
A fairy, huh?
Or maybe not?
Fairies are more...
Splendid!
You really are a fairy!
This is her story
Residence.
I'm so adorable.
A Certain Girl's Story
Beautiful hands.
Beautiful hair.
Beautiful face, beautiful body...
Beautiful everything.
Who would wish to trade places with someone
when you're blessed with a body like this?
That's not what you meant when you wished that?
Looks like I don't have complete control just yet.
But that's okay.
I'll be just fine.
Because everything will become mine!
I've been talking with Valessa.
She says you have been restless as of late.
Did something happen?
My apologies, Father.
A squirrel crawled through my window earlier.
We played together for a while,
but now it's gone off...
I'm sorry to hear that.
But never mind that. Tell me a story, Father.
Once in a while is okay, don't you think?
Let's see... I first met your mother many years ago.
Back then, I was...
Sorry.
Let's leave it at that. I think I've spoken too much tonight.
Quite the opposite.
Do you wish to see Mother again?
Yes.
If I were able, I'd take her back from the Lord.
I yearn to embrace her once more.
Then...
I'll let you meet her again.
You can have the sex you've missed so much with her.
C-Claire?!
It's been a while, my beloved.
What's going on?
You...
My, how time flies.
You're an old man now.
But you're still just as wonderful.
C-Claire?
You're just as beautiful as you were back then.
Your perfect body and enticing scent...
Thank you, my beloved.
Come, my beloved.
Would you mind licking my foot with that mouth of yours?
Like how a hungry pup sucks its mother's teat.
Or can you not even do that?
N-No, of course I can!
You've been dying to do this, haven't you?
I've always yearned for you to do something like this.
But there was no way I could ask.
You had too much pride back then.
But you understand now, don't you?
You no longer cling to your foolish pride.
That's good. Be honest with yourself.
It's just as beautiful as you remember, right?
C-Claire!
I don't care if you're a hallucination!
I don't care if this is the last time!
Right there! That feels so good!
You've become quite the lecher,
getting aroused by tonguing my pussy.
Allow me to do the rest.
It's so hard.
I guess this is one thing you haven't lost with age.
It's throbbing, waiting to cum at any second.
Your fellatio technique is just as good as I remember.
P-Please, I can't wait!
"Please?"
You have to try harder than that if you want to go further.
Now, try again.
Please don't tease me.
I'm begging you, Claire.
Only because you're a good boy.
I'm going to put your dick...
into my young, beautiful pussy...
The one you so fondly remember.
Savor it while you can.
Savor your beloved wife's pussy!
This is no hallucination.
I can feel you with my dick!
And I can feel you throbbing inside me!
Does my pussy riding you fill you with complete ecstasy?
There's no doubt! You really are my Claire!
My beloved!
Now, feast on my breasts.
You're getting me so aroused!
My beloved! My beloved!
Please thrust as deep as you would back in the day.
Make me feel that good again!
C-Claire, wait!
That's...
Amazing, I can feel them swelling.
It feels so good! My pussy is going crazy!
I can't hold on anymore... I'm going to...
Give it to me! Give it to your wife's pussy!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!
C-Claire?
You really weren't a hallucination.
Now we're...
Father?
W-Wait, this can't be!
What have I done?!
You finally gave me your love, Father!
I've been so lonely.
You always treat me like I'm a child...
You'd rather spend your time with Valessa!
C-Claire?!
I won't forgive you, my beloved.
You're still doing that?!
You've laid your hands on so many women.
How many decades have you betrayed me now?
This time with a maid?
If you have semen to spare, give it to me, not her!
S-Stop!
Incredible! You're getting hard in a situation like this!
You're hopeless.
What a hopeless dick!
If I continue to let you do as you wish,
you'll bring ruin to this residence.
Allow me to change that!
I'll make this into a residence of my liking!
How does it feel to have your own daughter riding you?
Come on, you love pussy, don't you?
So keep it cumming!
C-Claire...
I don't want to leave you... I want to be with you forever...
I saw your desire.
Your wish shall be granted.
What's going on?
I've never felt something like this before.
Now then, let's live together for eternity!
In your memories, that is.
Now, I'm the master of this residence.
Right, Mother?
translator: hikarucon
timing: ragingheartsexcelion
typesetting: ragingheartsexcelion
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Begone demons!
You do not belong here!
Who's our guest, Bullet?
He seems to be an exorcist.
Someone probably complained about us to
the church, and they sent this poor sap.
You know so many things, Bullet.
No need to be afraid.
This is really simple.
What do you desire?
Are you really a man?
Or are you...
A woman?