You.
Wanna know something about that ruined castle?
Gimme an intel fee, then.
Then we have a deal.
I'll tell you what happened there.
A few month ago
Hey, check this out, Zack!
This necklace will definitely sell for a good buck.
There's lots of stuff we can sell here, too.
We've just hit the mother lode!
You bet!
With this much, I can do it with all the
high class ladies as much as I want.
My dick is twitching with anticipation.
I've had a dry spell lately.
You all...
annoy me.
Wh-What was that?
A woman? There's a woman in here?
Hey, Tick.
Could it be that rumored monster?
You diggin' that kind of stuff?
Someone's just playing a prank on us.
A-Are you sure?
Jeez, that's some cute voice she's got there.
Hey, come over here!
Come and have a round of fun with us.
Are you an idiot?
If you really want to have sex, then I shall give you a woman.
A-A woman?
Say, Zacky-kun,
may I ask if you are really a man?
What the fuck are you saying? Of course I am.
No.
You are a woman.
You imagined it for a moment there, didn't you?
She... just said that you're a woman!
Hey, what the hell is going on here?
Z-Zack, you really became a woman.
I-I'm a slutty prostitute.
Owned by a man, and brought here.
A-A woman?
Wh-What in the world are those boobs?
You wanted to have sex with a woman, correct?
Here, you can fuck her pussy all you want.
But, this is Zack.
I... as a woman.
Just by looking at a man,
my mind, body, and pussy just can't stop tingling.
I want it. I want a dick right now.
Go ahead, do it.
Take your friend's virginity for yourself.
My body's moving on its own!
– Dicks... dicks.
– Wh-What the hell is happening?
Z-Zack is!
I don't know,
and yet I'm unable to resist in front of this woman.
Put... my dick inside!
I can't hold out much longer!
A woman, a woman!
Dicks, dicks!
I'm a prostitute.
I've been fucked by countless guys,
and yet I can still clearly feel the pleasure coming from this dick!
My oh my, why is the very tool that's made
to make men happy drowning in pleasure?
But, I guess it isn't an unprecedented outcome.
It's your first time experiencing a woman's pleasure.
Oh yes.
It feels so good.
Yes, that's right.
Fuck until you two climax.
Your dick is pushing deep into me!
Man, I don't care about anything anymore.
I'll just savor the hell out of this woman in front of me.
Here, it feels like your womb is getting fucked directly, right?
– What the hell? This pussy is sucking me in so much.
– There! Keep that up!
– It's penetrating into my very depths!
I'm about to cum!
That's good. Visualize it.
Visualize your greatest climax.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming while you cum hard inside.
Now then, am I about to enter heaven, or hell?
It's an illusion.
Huh? What's that?
There are those in this world that survive
by deceiving others with their visions.
It doesn't matter whether it's a human, or a monster.
However, it's often used by lower C-class monsters.
The name's Bullet.
A well-renowned treasure hunter.
I gathered information about this mansion.
Well, it's really nowhere near my level,
but I suppose I just have to get that
item that's coveted by all hunters.
Looks like this one will be a piece of cake once again.
In there, huh?
An illusion?
A lady and her maids in this abandoned mansion?
Such detailed interior for an illusion, I see.
I saw you coming in by the window,
so I waited.
I know what you're after.
See?
Then I guess I don't need to explain myself.
I'm willing to give it to you.
In exchange.
What?
Won't you become... one of my maids?
What's your angle?
It doesn't seem like a psychic attack.
So, you want me to play girly dress up?
That's right!
You're into that kind of kinky play, eh.
Hey, you're having weird ideas about it!
Well, just like your misinterpretation,
you're wrong about me being an illusion.
This girl... did she just read my thoughts?
Not only can she assume a human
form, but she can also read minds.
Wait... her class' abilities might surpass all of that!
Hey, Bullet.
I have a request.
Please tell me what type of girls you like.
It's okay. You only need to think about it for a second.
What is she suddenly blabbering about?
She's a complete enigma.
Should I retreat now?
With my escape item... to this route.
To that place.
Too late already.
You just let me read your mind.
Wh-What's happening?
My body feels hot!
This seems interesting, so I'll just transform your body for now.
Transform?
Are you... capable of altering physical states?
Damn!
You're going to turn me into some kind of monster?
My consciousness is being warped.
Residence.
Th-This place.
The tavern I usually visit.
Was table to use the item?
So I escaped?
Huh?
A-Anja?
So this place really is.
My name is Bullet.
What in the world is happening?
I-I'm Anja?!
Oh, so that girl's name is Anja-chan.
You!
Oh, I should remind you,
this is certainly no illusion.
I altered space, as well as your body, according
to your blooming thoughts.
What?
You altered my body, and this space?
I-If you can do that.
So she's an S-class?
Cute girls shouldn't make such scary expressions.
Wh-Why you!
Come on, visualize.
– Think of what you'd like to do, now that
Mr. Bullet here is now Ms. Anja.
– What the hell are you saying?
– Think of what you'd like to do, now that
Mr. Bullet here is now Ms. Anja.
It's time... for our "G" session.
What?
Damn.
My fingers are moving on their own.
That's right. You caress your clit gently from up your skirt.
See? It feels much better than a dick,
with this tingling sensation.
My body is getting aroused as she says,
and I can't do anything to stop it!
Okay, I'll help you out, then.
From now on, those big tits and that pussy are all yours.
Such cute pink nipples.
S-Stop!
What are these breasts?
Did I really became Anja?
Did you know? A girl's nipple is much
more sensitive than a guy's.
See?
Hey, that's lewd of you to part your
legs just because it feels so good.
Your fingers are soaked with love juices,
and your crotch is just as sticky.
Your entire abdomen must be tingling so hard by now.
A gushing wet clitoris, bathed in its love juices.
The pleasure has sent your body into nirvana.
It's getting more intense.
This is bad.
The sensation in my crotch is resonating throughout me.
My hands are moving on their own again!
H-Hold it.
Hold it.
No, not directly!
What is this sensation?
Right now, you're a woman,
which is why you don't need to hold back.
It's... so good.
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Your body looked so cute as you climaxed.
But, you haven't had enough, right?
Well then, try to visualize what you'd like to happen to you.
Wh-Who the hell would crave for some jerk's dick?
Quite a twisted idea, I see.
So your desire to fuck this woman, and
your craving to be fucked melded.
Stop.
Don't think of anything.
Stop thinking!
Once subjugated, no matter how manly your heart once was,
you'll no longer be able to resist your womb's urges.
My mind knows,
and yet, my body still craves it.
I'm a man!
A dick will never.
Savor every bit of it, okay?
No... stop rubbing that weird thing onto me!
I'm pushing it in, then.
Stop, don't!
Oops, no running away.
Come on, visualize.
Imagine being unable to move due
to the overwhelming pleasure.
The way it rubs your exposed and tender flesh is just irresistible.
The pleasure's seeping through, and it's making my body tingly!
So hot... a dick is really going inside of me.
Here, just a little before all of it is in.
You came after I just put the tip in?
How cute!
I wonder how long before you faint, with your
male heart residing in a woman's horny body.
Here, have some more.
You're a strong warrior, right?
Damn, all because I coveted that stone.
This is.
You're the best.
The way you desperately try to resist
a woman's pleasures as a man,
I absolutely love it.
This... couldn't possibly... feel good.
Endure.
I won't let her have her way!
So cute.
Your womb is still pulsating even as you try to resist!
See? See?
So what do you want? Try to visualize.
I'm not going to cum.
I won't cum.
So you did imagine it.
How lewd.
Here, we're not stopping!
Please stop this already!
No can do.
Your imagination pushed me to climax, too.
Your womb writhing in pleasure as I cum inside.
Can you feel it?
– I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
– Bullet.
I can give you all this womanly pleasure
anytime, so long as you wish for it.
My body feels hot.
My mind's going blank.
This pleasure... anytime.
Get a hold of yourself!
I'm a man!
I'm the great Bullet, the invincible treasure hunter!
Oh, incredible.
You still haven't completely lost yourself
even with this much pleasure.
I commend your mental fortitude.
Now I want your for myself even more.
J-Just who is this girl?
A human girl?
She wasn't a monster in human disguise?
I'm glad.
I wouldn't known what to do if you were gone.
Finally, a fairy of my own.
My precious friend.
It's... a monster?!