This is a tale from when I was still a treasure hunter.
A tale about the pleasure I experienced
in this abandoned mansion.
I will pass its ancient memories on to you.
Listen to my story...
Of the time that I was still a man...
That was delicious!
I will be retiring to my room now, Father.
I must return to my studies.
Hold on, I'm not done talking with you.
She's been awfully cheery as of late.
Do you know what she's up to?
No...
I'm back, Mr. Fairy!
I wish Father would stop treating me like a child all the time.
I'm a full-grown lady already!
You think so too, don't you, Mr. Fairy?
Oh, are you laughing?
I'm so jealous that you can live so freely, Mr. Fairy.
I wish we could trade places.
As you wish.
Did you just talk?
Wait, Mr. Fairy are you...
I saw your desire.
Your wish shall be granted!
Desire's Reward
Dammit! Damn it all!
How is it? Like how my pussy wraps around your cock?
Don't worry, you can do me as hard as you'd like!
You're so cute when you're turned on.
Enjoy this to your heart's desire.
It's okay for a man to indulge in pleasure.
Aren't you glad I turned you back into one?
Dammit!
Damn it all!
I know I'm living every man's dream right now, but...
Don't hold back.
Why do I feel like I want something more?
It's not enough!
Something is missing.
What feels so off to me?!
It feels so good!
More! Give me more!
What was I thinking just now?
You were imagining yourself being raped, weren't you?
Y-You!
You can't hide anything from me.
Something's felt off ever since
I gave you your body back, right?
You want your pussy to be fucked by a dick again, don't you?
Who, me?!
Like hell I'd want that!
Then let's do this.
I'll grant your true desire night now.
If you want to escape from this mansion, you
better start wishing from the bottom of your heart!
But, Bullet...
If you wish for it, I can turn your body back into a woman's.
You know I have the power to
materialize a person's deepest desires.
Remember it!
Think back to the pleasure you felt
of having your womb thrusted into!
If you stay here, I'll let you experience that pleasure forever.
Stop! Don't think about it!
Just ignore what this monster is saying!
I'm definitely getting out of this mansion!
I can't...
I won't...
Shit, you tricked me!
I'm a woman again!
I tricked you?
You should know best that's not what happened.
You're even more womanly than last time.
You're way more beautiful now.
But your body is still hanging onto its identity as a man.
You have quite the mental fortitude.
This isn't good. If this keeps up...
she'll have me wrapped around her finger!
I'll just have to escape looking like this.
Where the hell did you come from?!
Let go of me!
You don't recognize them?
These are the maids you were just having fun with.
M-Maids?
L-Let go of me!
How are you so strong?
No use struggling.
You're nothing but a frail, helpless woman, after all.
Stop! Don't rub that disgusting thing against me!
Stop... Stop it!
Stop!
Residence.
Wh-Why am I moaning like a woman?
Stop! I'm a man!
Don't rub your disgusting dicks against me!
You're a man?
Or are you really a woman?
I'm a man!
I don't wanna get it on with a bunch of dudes!
D-Don't lick down there! Stop...
Why? Why did my dick disappear and turn into a pussy?
Huh? I'm a guy, aren't I?
The pleasure's making it hard to think straight.
N-No, wait... Hey!
S-Stop!
Your pussy?
What's happening to me?
My mind's going completely blank.
A complete stranger is plowing my pussy!
Pussy! Pussy!
Cumming! I'm cumming!
N-No! Sto...
I'm cumming!
Fuck, I can't believe a dude's dick just made me cum!
Feel good?
L-Let me in on this too!
Me too!
It hurts.
It's painful, but being filled with dicks feels so good!
Have you noticed, Bullet?
You're acting more and more like a woman.
Let me ask you again.
Are you a man? Or are you a woman?
What is she saying?
I'm a...
That's right...
You're a woman, right?
No guy would ever look so happy
while having so many dicks inside him.
I'm a... woman?
My head's going blank...
No, I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming so much!
Please, stop!
Stop!
I don't want to cum anymore!
Dammit, my body's craving their dicks!
Let me ask you again.
Are you a man? Or are you a woman?
Huh?
What is she talking about?
Can't she tell by looking?
I'm a...
I'm obviously a woman!
That's right!
You're a woman, Bullet!
You're going to become my personal knight!
I'm going to become your personal knight!
I'm milady's doll!
That's right. You're my doll.
You love only me. You live only for me.
Now that you've been reborn,
I have a present for you.
Milady...
Thank you so much!
You're so cute.
It took a lot of work, but it's fun to watch
someone lose their own sense of being, isn't it?
If you want more, you must obey my every command.
I order you to wring out all of these men's sperm.
As you wish.
I'll do anything you command, milady.
What? Is that all you've got?
Cum already!
That's good, Bullet!
I've prepared all these guys just for you.
Thank you very much! I'm so happy!
You did all of this just for me!
My pussy feels amazing, doesn't it?
I'll put it in for you, so you better fuck my goddamn brains out.
Still vulgar as always, huh?
Cocks feel so good!
Why did I ever try to resist such pleasure?
I've never been happier in my life!
Come on! Fill me up with your cum!
These guys are letting out such sweet moans.
It's kind of cute.
– One down.
– I'm cumming!
Two down!
Three down!
Come on, cum!
Shoot your load inside my pussy!
Come on! Hurry up!
My own knight.
I can feel milady praising me!
That alone makes my heart race!
It's coming again!
My pussy's trembling again!
Please watch, milady!
Watch me wring all the sperm out of this man!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
May I have my reward now, milady?
All right, Bullet. What would you like?
What do you desire?
That's a wonderful wish, Bullet.
All right, let's get started.
Let's begin the knighting ceremony.
Yes, milady.
And that is the end of my tale.
Why, you ask?
That's because... I'm Bullet.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч