3D Animation Production
himei.
Sechs Academy.
Character Voice Acting
Amane Shiina.
Reversed Sex Violation Club.
Chemistry Lab.
Oh, it looks like you've woken up,
my sweet senpai.
Ok then, let's get started.
Oh, look at our senpai's... thing...
look at how naughty it is.
You have such a cute face,
but you're still an evil boy down here aren't you?
Is that something coming out of the tip?
What is this?
Does it feel good?
Is it OK to go faster?
Your little marbles are moving.
Oh!? Something came out?
Aw, it's squirting, how cute.
Wow!!
So much came out.
But it's still so... energetic.
Pweeze... let it awl out... in my mouff... OK.
Is he almost ready to explode?
It's OK to shoot it all in my mouth.
Wow, so much came out again.
Oops, I swallowed it.
Come on!
How come you get away with shooting all that.
Your son is such a bad boy.
You shot all that semen into the mouth
of an innocent underclasswoman,
and you're still not satisfied?
Bad boys like you need to be punished.
Hey? You got harder,
does it make you even more excited
to get smashed under my shoes?
Take a took.
When you were in my mouth, you got me all wet.
Hm? This is the first time
you've ever seen a girl's pussy isn't it?
Come on, take a good look.
It's been aching to swallow you up for a long time.
There's something you should know
about this part of a girl.
It's there for boys to stick their dicks in and go wild.
Okay, senpai.
That's enough! Look at it! Smell it.
How is it? What does the pussy
of your dirty underclasswoman smell like? Hmm?
You get all the fun...
It can't be over... Aww, this isn't fair.
It's your fault.
I just can't stop.
I'm putting it in...
Look... You're inside me...
Feel it, we're connected to each other.
My hips... I can't stop myself...
I can't stop... Ohh.
It feels sooo good.
Let's... cum together... my sweet senpai.
Did that... feel good for you?