Dead already?
How boring.
Our next conquest shall be the planet Lyon.
Lyon?
lt is a foregone conclusion that we shall rape that fertile land.
Not that Master Glode has ever been too discriminating...
The scent of blood is what we live for.
That was the last one from Bamuda.
How long until the next planet fall?
Lyon is but two or three days distant.
Our warriors already hunger for the taste of flesh.
Proceed with all speed!
Yes sir!
The cold feels so good.
Where did you come from?
l told you not to come here.
Oh well, whatever will be...
This feels so good!
Princess!
Neris!
Princess, you do know what day it is, don't you?
This is not just a splash in the pool, you know.
lt's a very important ritual for your upcoming marriage.
The Princess' marriage should be the most auspicious of occasions,
so why do l feel such an ominous sense of foreboding?
Why, when all of Lyon is full of peace and joy?
To Prince Zeke and Princess Flare! Cheers!
Cheers!
Can you believe so many people have come out to celebrate just for the two of us?
How right you are, my Flare.
But those assembled here are not the only ones who celebrate tonight,
all the land shares our joy.
Though our lands may be limited and our numbers few,
our population is blessed with a beautiful green planet and pure, clean water.
And of course, the loving and caring nature of our people is well known.
What?!
You again...
Poppet!
lt tickles!
You naughty Poppet!
What's going on?!
We don't know, Your Highness!
Word from the east! Everything's on fire!
Neris, take care of Flare!
Right!
Prince Zeke...
Princess, hurry!
Prince Zeke!
What's that?!
Hurry! This way!
Kill them! Burn them! Set them on fire!
For every man you kill, there will be another woman in your bed!
Who's there?!
Neris!
Princess!
Save me!
No!
N..No!
No...
Lay one slimy tentacle on my princess and l'll kill you, no matter what!
No, stop!
Poppet!
Prince Zeke...
Flare!
Y..You bastard!
You'll never touch my princess!
Neris!
Re..Release me!
Such spirit. You might even survive the pleasures l have planned for you.
And if l'm still alive at the end, will you spare my princess?
lf you can outlast me!
Consider it a promise!
Neris...
So cruel...
Stop...
You promised not to touch her.
Stop!
No!
St... Stop...
No, no! No!
What's happening?
NO!
Flare!
For this, you shall die!
Princess...
Princess!
What the hell is this?
lt may seem as though l've lost,
but l still accomplished my primary goal.
Your goal?
My goal... my...
Princess! Princess!
Flare!
Prince Zeke, the princess...
Flare...
l failed to...
lt isn't your fault, Neris.
This place is collapsing. We must leave.
Yes...
Let's go.
lt's over, we've lost everything.
That's not true, Neris.
We still have our lives.
l wonder if everything is like this?
When a whole planet has been raped,
nature's wrath can be brutal.
Poppet!
Flare!
Zeke?
Zeke...
Your body warms me so...
Can the beauty that was Lyon ever be restored?
You're right! Of course it will be reborn!
As it was in the beginning,
it shall be again!
l believe that even the saddest dreams
Are like the clouds up in the sky
They disappear
Like the tails of a comet
Whispering as they go by
When l can tie a ribbon in my hair
A ribbon made of light
Then l can promise
l'll love you forever
Forever is a long time
Do it to me harder
Take me again roughly
Will it be long enough
For my love?
Please, place it against my cheek
l'll hold it
So gently
l will hold
Your feelings
Deep inside my heart
Gather up all the pieces
Of my scattered tears
Some day
Some way
l will be happy too
Please, place it against my cheek
l'll hold it
So gently
l will hold
Your feelings
Deep inside my heart
Gather up all the pieces
Of my scattered tears
Some day
Some way
l will be happy too