NO!
We shall be reborn!
We must be reborn to once again to terrorize this land.
And then, when the blood of all the hated humans waters the ground like rain,
we shall again possess the true source of the power of Lyon.
Flare...
Flare!
l must stop him here.
We are born once more,
spawned by human suffering from the energy of the planet itself.
We are reborn!
Eon, what's wrong?
Princess Flare...
You must have had quite a nightmare.
Where is my big sister?
Don't worry about her.
Neris is more than capable of taking care of herself.
That's true.
She's got more guts than a little kid like me.
When she gets back, l promise to wake you up.
Why don't you go back to sleep?
Right!
But...
Neris...
Princess Flare!
Lori!
Prince Zeke is back!
Zeke!
Flare!
Welcome home, Zeke.
Did you find anything?
No...
l searched the east wing of the old castle from top to bottom,
but there's no sign of the missing people.
Where's Neris?
She's not back yet.
l'm having terrible premonitions about this.
Prince Zeke...
What happened?!
...and then, a force, strange and unearthly, appeared in front of us.
We tried to oppose it, but we were annihilated.
And what of Lady Neris?
l think Lady Neris was among the survivors.
Neris!
Gather the soldiers!
Yes sir! Gather the soldiers!
Hurry!
Hey, let's go! Get a move on!
Sister...
Sister!
Once, this castle was a beautiful place.
ls that...
Could it be?
Wh..What is this?
l don't remember the inside of the castle being like this.
What's that light?
This is...
Amazing!
When was it built?
That looks like a chair...
What is it?!
lt's nothing.
Must have been the wind.
Eon...
Who's that?
ls that you, Lori?
Lori!
Prince Zeke, what is it?
lt was nothing.
What did you find?
Sir, it's as we suspected.
This was the work of no natural beast or human.
Could it all be happening again?
Prince Zeke!
Prince Zeke, it's an emergency!
Princess Flare was...
Princess Flare was kidnapped by a monster!
What?!
We've got to get back now, sir!
Flare...
Eon...
Sister!
ls that you, sister?
You have nothing left to worry about, Eon.
Let me go!
Where am l?
The ones missing from the castle!
How horrible.
Princess Flare...
Eon?
ls that you, Eon?!
Why are you here?
Flare...
Eon?
Flare, how nice of you to come for me.
What's wrong with you, Eon?
No, get away from me!
What is this?! Let me go!
Eon...
Eon, what are you doing?
No...
Stop it, Eon!
NO!
Stop!
Eon, no!
NO!
Stop...
Stop, Eon.
lt's time.
What's that?!
NO!
l can't believe what's happened to the castle.
Don't let your guard down.
Who knows what may pop out.
Let's go!
You are so beautiful, Flare.
Flare, l have been waiting for you...
...since that moment....
...for this day!
Prince Zeke...
Nami! Shiro!
l'll kill you, you monster!
l can't pull it out.
Sorry for being so late, Prince Zeke.
Neris, you're alive!
Almost...
What's that?!
lt's moving!
Finally, l am reborn.
Enough! Be gone!
And now, Flare, shall we go for the coup de grace?
l must suck up the energy that pours from your body.
There, give your energy to me!
That's it! That's the stuff that l want!
lt's almost over.
l will consume your energy, Flare.
l'll have your last bit of...
Hold it!
Get away from Flare!
Prince Zeke, let me handle this!
You can't hope to defeat me with a sword.
See!
Prince Zeke!
Neris...
So, you wish to have me again?
What?
Don't you remember?
Sister!
Flare!
What have l done?
Zeke...
You monster!
Stop!
Sister...
This thing has taken control of my body.
Please, while l hold him down, you...
Eon? What are you doing in here?
You fool...
l'll burn you out of my brain once and for all!
Eon!
He'll kill us all!
Hurry! Kill him!
l won't let you...
l won't let go!
Release me!
Sister!
The sphere!
Eon!
Stab it!
Hurry!
Sister!
Eon?
Sister...
How is Princess Flare?
She's fine.
Good, l'm glad.
l'm glad you're okay too, sister.
Eon...
You pathetic humans!
l cannot be destroyed.
As long as my consciousness remains,
l shall never let you go free!
Your pitifully tragic existences end so quickly.
lt your destiny to die!
Even with this kind of life...
Even with this short existence...
All life is still sacred!
The light!
Flare!
lmpossible! Flare has taken back her power!
Everyone!
l'm using everyone!
The power of the planet!
The mountain is glowing!
Prince Zeke!
Get out of here, Neris!
You fools...
Prince Zeke!
lt's all right.
Flare, it's over.
Zeke...
Flare...
The castle is crumbling!
Prince Zeke...
lt's over.
Prince Zeke, Princess Flare...
Poppet!
Thank goodness...
lf we could be with each other again
Just one more time, then l could say
Goodbye, despite the tears falling from my eyes
l would promise never to forget
The shape of your sweet smile
l'll carry it with me
And keep it always
But hey
The stars are shining down
They shine down
They shine on and wisper amongst themselves
My love
lt will never go
l want to sleep
Among the stars
Surrounded by cloud dreams
Until the day
The two of us
Are one
l want to dream
Up in the sky
Covered by the starlight, but until then
Make love
To me again
lf you find
A new aurora
Burning up in the night sky
Then you'll know
That it must be me
lf l hear
The stars above
Call me with their whispering
Then please
Come to me
Again