Kokudou Academy
So this is Kokudou Academy...
I didn't hear many good things about it,
but I never thought it d be this bad.
Takayuki-san, I haven't had a good night's sleep since that day.
Nice to meet you, ma'am.
My name's Kijima Yuuji.
I want to talk to you about your fiance.
Umm, did something happen to Takayuki-san?
Do you know about the money Saijou-san owes?
It seems like his business has failed.
The grace period for him to pay is over,
but the money's nowhere to be seen.
Takayuki-san s failed business? Debt?
Don't tell me I've been signed on a joint liability loan...
It'll be five million yen including interest.
Five million? Seriously!?
The problem is that Saijou-san has gone missing.
That's why I'm here to see you, the other liability holder.
But how on Earth am I supposed to pay such...
Ebihara Urara-san.
Yes?
Your occupation is teaching at a private school.
That's your sole source of income, am I correct?
How did you...
Oh, I know.
Since you have this elegant air about you,
I know a perfect way to settle this easily.
I don't have an elegant air...
My friend's school is currently looking for a teacher.
Have you heard of Kokudou Academy?
If you work there for a month, you can
at least pay off the interest due.
If I work there I can pay off the interest due?
How does that work?
Doesn't sound bad, huh?
Well, if you don't want to, you can always pay back the five million.
In the end, I promised Kijima-san Id work
at Kokudou Academy for a month.
At the time, I didn't realize it was a well set up trap.
RIN x SEN
~ Opaque Teacher and the Rascal ~
Part 1
Even though Takayuki-san hasn't contacted
me, I'm sure he's trying to make money.
Moreover, I'm a teacher.
As long as there are students, I shall stand and teach them.
Staff Room
I need to pee...
I hate this body of mine.
I need to relieve myself whenever I get excited or nervous.
What a bad habit.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, you are...
I'm Ebihara Urara. It's a pleasure to meet you.
Oh, just as I thought.
I'm the school principal, Hirukawa Keizou.
Welcome to our school.
Thank you.
You are so young and pretty.
As long as you are here, this all-male school will be spirited again.
Smells nice.
Umm...
The smell of a young woman.
Oh, anyway.
You'll be homeroom teacher for class 3-C.
Homeroom teacher?
But I'm only working here for a month.
Of course, I know.
But we have our problems as well.
This might be too big a request...
Yes, I understand.
There are a few delinquents in this school, but believe me,
they are all honest kids down in their core.
I understand.
See you tomorrow.
Watch where you're going.
I'm sorry.
Who the fuck are you?
Sorry...
I'm Ebihara Urara.
Oh, I see.
What's up?
I'm a new teacher here, starting today.
Starting tomorrow, I'll be class 3-C's homeroom teacher~
Oh, 3-Cs homeroom teacher.
Y-Yes...
So it's you.
I'll be looking forward to it.
What's up with him? Does he know me?
Oh.
You must be the new teacher, Ebihara-sensei.
Oh, yes.
I'm Ebihara Urara. Nice to meet you.
Same here.
I'm Okita Asuka and I teach PE.
I've been teaching here since I graduated college.
I'll be glad to help if you have any problems.
Thank you.
Urara's such a cute name.
May I call you Urara-sensei?
Sure.
Then, may I call you Asuka-sensei?
Call me whatever you want.
But why would a person like you come work at this place?
Well, that's because...
I think you understand already.
This is a terrible place.
Long periods of peace don't exist here.
I'm more passionate about teaching undisciplined kids, I think.
Really?
We'll definitely make great friends.
Good luck tomorrow.
Thank you, Asuka-sensei.
Unknown number?
Perhaps Takayuki-san changed his number!
Yes, hello?
It's Kijima.
Oh, did I interrupt your shower?
Kijima-san, is there anything you'd like from me?
Don't be like that.
I have a message to pass on.
What is it?
It's simple.
Just be good and follow the instructions of your cute students.
"Be good and follow instructions"?
What's that supposed to mean?
You'll find out tomorrow.
Oh, and I think we're going to find your cute fiance pretty soon.
Really? Where is he?
Did he mention anything about me?
I'll contact you again.
Wait! Please, at least let me speak to him!
Take this in mind, young adults are unpredictable
and I don't know when they'll explode.
Be careful.
Umm...
Takayuki-san...
Today's the first day.
I need to do my best.
Jeez, I need to pee again...
I'll wait until homeroom's over.
Good morning.
Who the fuck are you?
Excuse me,
I'm this class's new homeroom teacher, Ebihara Urara.
Urara-chan, huh?
Please return to your seat.
You've got a hot body.
Great tits and a nice ass.
Stop!
Please return to your seats and we'll take roll.
Is this the whole class?
This amount is more than usual.
You're...
I'm Kurose.
Kurose Tatsuya.
Nice to meet you, Urara-sensei.
He's different from the rest.
He must be their leader.
By the way,
everyone's happy that we've got a young and pretty teacher.
R-Really?
Come on, take a look for yourself.
Look at the bulges in our pants.
Hey Sensei, my cock got hard from just looking at you.
Cock? You mean penis?
I shouldn't have...
Is "cock" too embarrassing for you?
Are you an airhead?
Fuck, this is turning me on.
No! Return to your seats! Homeroom is going to begin!
It's already begun.
It's only going to get better from now on.
What's wrong with these kids?
What should I do? Tell me, Takayuki-san!
Sorry, but homeroom's over.
Whoops.
Homeroom's not over yet.
Urara-sensei, you still need to introduce yourself.
Hey, Iwaki.
Kurose-kun, what are you doing?
Let go of me!
Let's take a look at what type of panties she's wearing.
No! Stop! Stop!
Stop please! No!
Let go of your teacher!
Please! Let go!
You can't do this to your teacher!
There's no need for you to be so hostile.
We just want to understand you.
And I suppose you understand what'll happen if you resist.
Just be good and follow the instructions of your cute students.
He can't be referring to this...
Come on, let us take a good look.
Wait! Don't tell me~
We're just looking.
No! Stop!
I can see them! I can see them!
Don't look! Don't look!
Damn, a teacher's nice, fresh panties.
This is so fucking hot.
Takayuki-san hasn't seen it yet..
And yet, these students are getting an eyeful.
Not again?
Oh, what's this?
No! Don't look!
My, my, somethingls soaking through.
I can't hold it in anymore because they're looking so closely.
No!
Whoa!
Are you getting wet because we're all taking a good look?
No! Please, let go of me!
No, Sensei.
I can't hold it in!
Wait, this is different.
Shit, this is a strong smell.
Oh God...
No! It's coming out!
No... I can't hold it in... No!
Not in front of the students!
It's soaking through!
She's peeing herself.
No!
No! Stop! I can't hold it in!
Please don't look!
Sensei, if you wanted to use the restroom you should've said so.
It'll be easier this way.
No!
Guess we're in luck today.
Don't look! I said, don't look!
Sensei, look at the mess you made.
I'm sorry... Please forgive me.
Hey guys, wanna check out her pussy?
Of course!
I'm getting hard by just imagining it.
Hurry up and show us.
Hey... Please tell me you're kidding.
Kurose-kun, please! Don't do this!
All righty.
No!
No! Please!
Not this!
You've got such a pretty cunt.
No!
Are you a virgin?
No! Please, don't look!
If that's the case, I'm taking it away.
I'm scared...
If they find out that I'm a virgin...
I wanted to have my first time with Takayuki san.
By the way, Urara-sensei, do you masturbate?
Don't ask weird questions.
You do you realize you're the one in trouble.
No...
Kurose-kun is definitely in this with Kijima-san.
Not every day... But yes, occasionally.
No!
Don't!
Wow, you look innocent,
but you actually masturbate.
You're a teacher and yet you masturbate.
Please... Stop doing this to me.
All right, then show us how you do it yourself.
I can't do that!
I really can't! I mean, I'm a teacher!
So you're not going to listen to me.
I didn't mean that, but...
But what?
But masturbating in front of my students...
Are you really sure you don't want to listen to us?
Wait! All right, I'll do it!
All right, hurry up and do it.
Our teacher's little show has begun.
Right.
Put your finger inside.
No...
Please, Sensei.
They're going too far!
But if I refuse...
Put it in deeper and start moving it faster.
Takayuki-san, please forgive me.
It's like she's in her own little world.
We're all rock hard.
No! What are you doing!?
Put it back inside your pants!
We want to show you as well.
Sensei, let's have the time of our lives together.
Cut the dirty talk...
No... People are looking at me doing this...
This is feeling better than usual..
All because my students are watching.
Use your other hand.
Yes...
No way...
Please let me go...
I don't want to do this! I can't do this!
Sensei, do you know how troublesome it is for you to cum before us?
Wow, you're a quickie.
No...
Come on, continue.
Sensei, when did you have your first period?
When I was fourteen.
When did you learn how to masturbate?
When I was about twenty.
Hey, please...
This is enough, right?
Can we stop? Please?
Who did you masturbate to?
Takayuki-san.
Who's Takayuki-san?
My fiance.
Why am I doing this?
What's wrong with me?
I'm about to cum.
May I unload on you?
Me too.
Let's go.
All right, take your best aim.
No, you can't do that!
I can't hold back.
I'm cumming.
Hey, let's unload on her!
No! You can't do that!
I... don't want this!
I cant hold back...
Please, stop looking.
Don't look at me.
Don't... Don't... Don't...
Ebihara-san.
I mean, Urara-sensei.
Kijima-san...
You don't look well.
Did the kids bully you?
I...
Don't tell me you're going to stop.
You hold liability as well.
I'm Takayuki-san's fiance, and I'm a teacher.
There's no way I'll give up.
I'm glad to hear that.
That's the spirit, Urara-sensei.
Also, be sure to listen to your students.
Why are those two...
What did you say?
These kids are all virgins, so they've never been sucked off before.
So, I want you to teach them.
Sucked off?
Right, Takayuki-san was it?
I'm sure you've sucked his cute little dick.
Well...
So? You're not going to do it?
What are you saying?
There's no way I can do that.
So you can't, huh?
Well, I don't really give a shit.
In order to save Takayuki-san, I'll have
to comply with the craziest requests.
But...
Sensei, can't you teach us with your "experience"?
I can't...
No matter what happens, sexual conduct between
a student and a teacher is forbidden.
On top of that, I'm already engaged...
No! Please!
Don't be rough.
Urara-san, you're gonna regret saying no.
No, Kurose-kun!
No violence!
Come on.
No!
Don't touch me!
Don't be so rough!
No!
Please! Don't rub them!
You guys are about to cum, right?
Hey, let it all out on her.
No!
You can't do this to your teacher.
Wait! No! You can't do this!
Please!
I said no...
You're too cruel.
Come on.
Wait, no!
Oh my gosh, it smells really strong.
And it's huge.
It's different from Takayuki-san's.
I can't breathe...
It's hitting my throat...
I've done this to Takayuki-san.
But, that was to fulfill his sexual desires.
I want to remain a virgin before marriage.
But this is...
Oh, I'm going to cum.
Urara-sensei, you'd better drink it all.
I'm using my mouth as a relief for their desire.
I've never drank Takayuki-san's semen before.
And now I'm going to drink my student's?
I don't want to...
Sensei, this is not all.
We've got a few more here.
No!
Please... Make this stop.
All right, why don't we take this chance to lose our virginity.
Stop... Please.
Please... No more.
Crap! Asuka's coming
Let's go!
Takayuki-san, I want to see you.
Please let me go! I'm going to break...
What is this?
No! I'm going to cum!
That's going to happen to me.
I came to a terrible place.
Study session out of the blue?
But if I don't go...
Asuka-sensei left early due to some matters.
No one will be here to save me if yesterday repeats itself.
But...
Sensei, you're late.
I'm sorry for being late.
Come on, change into this and teach us.
PE clothes? W-Why that?
I don't teach PE... I teach English.
It's your punishment for being late.
Everyone's looking, so hurry up and change.
Oh, and you have to remove your underwear.
If I don't listen to them, Takayuki-san will...
And if I don't listen to them, the same thing will
happen to me as that girl from yesterday.
I need to keep myself pure.
My virginity is the only thing I can give to Takayuki-san.
This is embarrassing...
Please don't look.
This is too small.
I don't want to do this.
All right, let's start our lesson.
What?
Wait...
No, let go of me!
Let go! Let go!
What are you doing?
Do you really need to ask?
K-Kurose-kun, please tell me this is a joke.
No! You can't do this!
Right, guys? Right?
No... If this happens...
I won't be able to give my first time to Takayuki-san.
I know already.
Despite your age, you're still a virgin.
How did you...
Seriously? Urara-sensei's a virgin?
You're 24 already.
Nan, this is a miracle.
You must be an endangered species or something.
No! Stop! Wait!
I'll doing anything but that!
Please, not that!
I'll make sure you never forget me.
It's time to begin.
Please... I'm begging you.
Please, not that! Anything but that!
No!!
It hurts! Stop!
Please don't do this!
It hurts! It hurts!
Please, stop!
No! No!
I'm a teacher, but why is this happening to me!?
How does it feel to have your cherry popped?
Wow, she's bleeding.
She's the real thing!
Please stop...
Takayuki-san, I have nothing to offer you anymore.
You don't have time to cry.
Take this!
Please stop moving!
It hurts! Stop! It hurts!
Stop moving! It hurts!
No!
Let go of me, Kurose-kun!
Please!
It really hurts!
I'll be done in a bit, so hold it in.
Are you going to cum inside me?
Wait! Kurose-kun!
Wait!
Take your penis out! Please!
Here I go.
No! You can't do this!
Not inside, please! Not inside!
No...
No... I'm going to pee again... No!
Please, let go of me.
Peeing again?
I wanted to cum inside.
But I won't do that.
You'll have to thank Kijima-san for that, Urara-sensei.
Takayuki-san, please forgive me...
I've been raped.
Hey, you guys give her some love as well.
It's not over yet?
No!!