No! Don't put it in me anymore!
This feels so good!
So this is what Urara-sensei's pussy is like!
Please just cue us up, Urara-sensei.
Me too.
Then I'll do her mouth.
Don't-!
It hurts!
No-!
Urara-sensei, is it difficult to keep up?
However, we're just getting started.
Stop it-!
Don't cum anymore!
Please let me go!
P-Please stop this already!
Someone... Someone please help me!
S
ub
D
ESU-
H
Although I was only talking to Urara-sensei about my ex-husband...
Why does it throb so much?
I couldn't hold back any longer!
I shouldn't be doing this at school...
But when I think about my ex-husband, I...
Kenji! I'm doing this because we're not together anymore!
No-! Someone will hear me!
B-But-! I'm gonna cum!
I-I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming-!
I did it again...
I must return quickly...
Y-You two...
W-What are you doing here?
Same goes for you, Atsuka-chan.
You "did it again"?
So you were masturbating to the thought of your ex-husband!
How long were you here for?
We were here from the start.
Kijima-san was looking for the bathroom, so I led him here.
M-Moreover, this is a staff-only toilet!
Please leave immediately.
We've got a favor to ask you, Atsuka-chan.
I'm your old teacher, will you hear me out?
If you've got a favor to ask me, then act properly.
Hey, do you know what'll happen to your younger brother if you say such things?
If the employers knew that he caused that violent incident, it wouldn't be good, would it?
H-How do you know about that?
Well, I have my ways.
Anyway, can you hear my request?
How cowardly...
S-So, what do you want me to do?
It's simple. Don't get involved with Ebihara Urara. That's it.
With Urara-sensei?
Kijima! What are you plotting?
Oh, and one more thing...
Hey!
Sensei, let's have some fun.
Hey, Kurose! Get away from me!
Don't resist, otherwise something bad might happen to your brother...
W-What are you going to do?
Let's have lots of fun, Atsuka-chan...
C'mon!
Stop this!
How is it, Atsuka-chan?
Does your old teacher's cock taste good?
Kijima's cock is entering my mouth-!
Such humiliation-!
I'm gonna cum in your mouth!
Make sure you drink it all!
No, don't-!
Stop it!
N-No! Not in my mouth-!
It tastes raw and it's sticky...
It's disgusting!
Hey Atsuka-chan, did you drink my semen?
Are you serious? Does he really think I'd drink this?
Huh? What's with that look?
If you don't care if your brother's fired from the bank, then spit it out.
Well, with this slow economy, it might be hard to get another job...
Why is he such a coward?
I haven't even drunk Kenji's!
Doesn't a teacher's semen taste exceptional?
On to the next...
K-Kurose-! You too?
I'll return the favor from before.
Make sure you cry and scream!
D-Don't! Anything but that!
Don't!
No way!
How can a teacher be having sex with a student?!
Kurose-! Hurry up and pull it out!
No-! Stop moving!
K-Kijima-!?
What are you-?
H-Hey! Not there!
It's fine!
I already decided when I was teaching you
that I'd put it in your ass the first time we had sex.
W-Wha-?
What are you talking about?
T-There's no way that it'll fit-!
But it will! Quite easily, too!
Stop-!
It hurts!
D-Don't-!
There! It's in your ass now!
Stop it-!
It hurts!
K-Kijima! Pull it out! Pull it out now!
Looks like this was your first.
O-Of course it is-!
So you were an anal virgin!
Well, I'm sure that since you're as lewd as you are, Atsuka-chan,
then you'll start feeling good in no time!
Kijima-! You-!
Don't-! Stop moving!
W-What's this?
My butt... It hurt just a moment ago, but now...
Looks like you're getting used to anal now.
I'm gonna cum soon!
Me too-!
Eh?
N-Not inside!
What would I do if I got pregnant?!
You mustn't-!
You mustn't!
Pull it out! Hurry up and pull it out!
Not inside! Anywhere but inside-!
No-! Don't cum, don't cum!
You two are the worst...
Atsuka-chan, remember our promise.
If you break it, you know what'll happen, right?
There was a phone call from your fiancée.
Looks like he's trying to make some money, too.
T-Takayuki-san is?
He was worried about you.
He said "Please don't do anything to the cosigner."
"I will fully reimburse you."
Takayuki-san-!
I'm probably not worthy of being loved by him any longer...
But I'm the only person who can save him!
The debt is decreasing steadily, so keep at it.
Oh, and one more thing. Do what the principal says from now on.
Y-Yes...
Urara will try her best!
Takayuki-san, this is my way of showing my love!
Urara-sensei, thanks for all your work today.
Yes, thank you too...
I heard from Kijima-san that you're under some financial difficulty with your fiancée...
So, I'll be helping you out.
For now, please come to the staff social gathering tonight.
I'm sure you'll feel better.
Social gathering?
Is this what Kijima-san was talking about?
Um, are you coming too, Atsuka-sensei?
I-I have some other matters to attend to tonight, so...
I see...
It'll be happening after all of the students leave.
Got that? Please be there.
Urara-sensei, I'm sorry...
At this social gathering, we get the youngest teachers to provide the entertainment.
I've already prepared the details, so Urara-sensei...
Please change into this.
U-Um-!
Why do I have to change into a sailor uniform?
Urara-sensei, your fiancée is having trouble, yes?
So change into this right now!
Whoa, you've got a wonderful bust!
The curves of her hips are very nice too...
Very much so! She's got a delicious body!
No...
This is embarrassing, so please don't look!
P-Principal! What's with this?
I don't want to wear this! It's embarrassing!
It suits you very well.
Now then, we'll get the party started.
W-What are you doing to my b-butt-?
N-No-!
N-Not my butt-!
Urara-sensei, is this your first time doing anal?
Even so, you took it pretty easily!
N-No way!
Why is this happening-?
Even if you say you don't like it, your butt's taking it, see?
Watching such a young teacher is good for your youth, isn't it?
Yes! Isn't it a fabulous display?
Y-You'll tear my butt-!
No-! Please don't-!
I knew this "social gathering" was a little suspicious,
but Atsuka-sensei knew about this, didn't she?
I'll release it deep inside you!
No!
Please no more!
Not in my butt-!
Stop it-! No-! Don't do it!
N-No-!
No!
Not... Not in my butt-!
It's coming out-! No!!
No... No, I can't hold it in-!
No... Please don't look!
It's... It's not stopping-!
Wetting yourself?
You should care more for your dignity as a teacher...
As punishment, please entertain the other teachers.
Not my butt again-!
No-!
This is extraordinary!
I'll use her hands...
Then I shall as well.
I'll take her mouth, then!
Hell... This academy is hell!
B-But-!
For Takayuki-san, I-!
Please, no more!
Pull it out-! Please pull it-!
No-!
So deep...
N-No more, please-! Please make it end!
Well then, everyone!
N-No!
No!!
Urara-sensei is slimy from our semen...
I haven't had such a good time in a while!
This is horrible!
Being raped by the other teachers like that...
Thanks for today.
But now for the good news.
You'll be able to meet your fiancée soon.
Eh?!
I can meet T-Takayuki-san?
That's right.
But if you do, don't take a day off, no matter what.
Y-Yes...
Takayuki-san... I'll be able to meet you soon!
Hey, you lot! Urara-sensei is giving us a private lesson in her swimsuit!
Make sure you cum plenty.
T-This is horrible!
Hurry... Hurry up and make this end!
No-!
Please don't spray it on me! No!
Please don't!
I don't want to have semen from my students poured on me anymore!
It's an order from Kijima-san.
Don't feel bad, Sensei.
C'mon, do the next one!
K-Kurose-kun! Please don't be so rough!
I'll choke! If you that, Sensei will choke!
Hey Urara-sensei, use your tongue! Go on!
This is too much-! Please hurry up and finish!
I can't do it anymore...
I see, then...
No-!
N-No! Don't-!
So deep-!
It's going in so deep-!
No!
No, no-!
Don't! You mustn't! Please stop moving-!
No-! No!
Don't hate it so much, Sensei.
Wasn't I your first? Don't be so cold towards me...
Don't say that!
No, no!
You can't-! Stop moving-!
No-!
Urara-sensei, I'm gonna cum!
No!!
C'mon, next! Go on!
Then I will.
Me too!
Please let me go...
No!!
I finally caught your fiancée.
I'll let you meet him tomorrow.
Eh... R-Really?
Come to the school gymnasium tomorrow evening. Don't be late.
Um, where is Takayuki-san right now?
W-What's the meaning of this?
Takayuki-san?
Where is Takayuki-san?
Atsuka-sensei, why are you here?
K-Kijima-san... What's the meaning of this?
You are... Kaho, aren't you?
I hear you like doing anal despite your innocent looks!
Hey Kurose, shall we make her scream from double penetration?
N-No way...
Kijima-san, please wait!
Atsuka-sensei!
Why are you...
P-Please help us!
Urara-sensei, I'm sorry...
No way... What happened to you? Atsuka-sensei!
Atsuka-chan can't go against us!
Urara-sensei, you're too kind.
You're not in the situation to care about others.
I am a teacher after all...
That's very admirable.
By the way, weren't you looking for your fiancée?
T-Takayuki-san?
Where is Takayuki-san?
T-This ring... It belongs to Takayuki-san.
Your fiancée had been seeing someone he liked for ages.
He was playing games with you.
You've been lied to all along.
N-No way...
There's no way a man can hold back without having sex before marriage these days!
But Takayuki-san agreed to that...
He became engaged to you because he wanted a cosigner.
However, when he couldn't rebuild his company, he sold you to me.
And then he ran away under his real name.
That's a lie! Takayuki-san isn't that kind of person!
I can't believe something like that!
One more thing.
All the things you've been doing since you entered this academy have been filmed.
Filmed?
From selling those videos, the debt's been being repaid.
Do you get it, Urara-sensei?
My embarrassing self is on video?
He sold me... But this is his ring...
The one we promised we'd never take off.
What have I been working for all of this time?!
Unfortunately, you won't be getting your bride costume anytime soon.
But don't worry!
You'll be our bride tonight!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Urara-sensei...
Atsuka-sensei...
The wedding dress I've been dreaming of wearing in front of Takayuki-san...
Am I going to get violated in this?
That suits you, Urara-sensei!
I'll take care of you!
No-!
No way-! N-Not so suddenly-!
I-It's reaching my deepest spots!
This is the side position! Doesn't it go in deep?
I hear you love anal, Urara-sensei.
I'm putting it in as well.
N-No, not my butt, not my butt! Not there!
If you do that so much, I'll-!
Okita-sensei! We're gonna do it too!
N-No way! Not you too, principal!
No!!
Please stop!
Stop-! Please stop moving!
It sure is tight inside when both holes are taken up!
It's like her pussy has gotten smaller!
No-! It’s too much!
This is too much! I'm going crazy! I'm gonna lose it!
Atsuka-sensei...!
I wouldn't have thought I would be able to have sex with you, Ojou-sama!
This is-!
Your cock is going in too deep-!
No! You're gonna stretch Kaho too much!
Doing both at the same time-! It's-!
It's too much!
It's quite good, isn't it?
Which hole feels best?
D-Do I have to say?
Of course! Otherwise-!
Both are! They both feel great!
Both my butt and pussy feel amazing!
T-This is too much!
It's so good!
No-! Not at the same time-!
No more! I'll go crazy, I'm gonna go crazy!
I see, then go on! Lose yourself!
Looks like you're starting to feel good...
As if-! Not from my butt-!
My butt... My butt-!
This is amazing-! N-No, I'm gonna cum!
I can't hold it in-! I'm cumming, I'm cumming-!
S-So good-!
It feels really good!
I'm gonna cum, I'm gonna cum!
N-No-!
Urara-sensei! We should enjoy it too!
I don't want him to thrust so much, yet-!
I can tell that you're feeling aroused, even if you don't like it!
You can't help but get wet from anal with your student, can you?
That's not true-!
No! Please don't say that!
Anyone would feel good from this-!
Even though I don't want it, my butt and my pussy...!
No! Don't thrust so much!
You should forget about that backstabbing fiancée of yours!
No! I don't want to forget!
I don't want to forget him, but...
I've nearly had it!
I'm gonna cum soon!
I'll make sure to let it out inside.
I'm gonna cum too!
No-! No more!
Takayuki-san! Where did you go?
Please save Urara!
No!
Don't-!
Not inside, not inside!
I'll... I'll lose it-!
Even... Even though I tried my best for Takayuki-san all along...
It can't be... I can’t have been dumped!
But, I wonder why...
I loved him so much, but I can't remember his face!
I don't want to remember anything, I don't want to think of anything!
I want to forget everything!
This is painful, but...
Urara-sensei sure is going at it! She's feeling aroused!
"Sure going at it"?
I'm... I'm just having these perverted things done to me!
She's sucking me so much! It seriously feels great!
I bet she's feeling good from the anal too, right?
No way... I'm having nasty things done to my pussy, butt, and mouth, yet...
This is wrong, I'm their teacher...
But-! I've...!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
I'm cumming in her butt!
I said you couldn't release it inside...
But you're releasing so much...
Something is coming!
I'm gonna lose it again-!
I came again...
But I don't feel bogged down...
Is it because I feel that I don't need to try hard
since I've been dumped by Takayuki-san?
Everything has...
Atsuka-sensei, you're feeling aroused from having both holes sandwiched, aren't you?
You're trying to make me say it again, aren't you?
I feel it!
It feels really great being doubled like this!
Kaho-chan's ass, it’s warm and it feels great!
Please stop doing just my butt!
No! If this keeps going, Kaho-!
Kaho won't be herself any longer!
Don't twist up my insides like that!
My butt, please don't do it so hard!
This is too much, I've really had enough-!
Please! Please stop it-!
It's coming out inside my pussy and butt...
No more, I'm gonna cum!
I-I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Kaho is at her limit too!
This feels too good, and-!
No-! I-It feels too good!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I... I don't need to think about anything anymore, do I?
All I have to do is embrace the pleasure, don't I?
Everyone's doing the same thing...
Goodbye, Takayuki-san...