Y, you're...
Nao-kun... Nao-kun.
Suzune...
More, deeper!
Nao-kun, Nao-kun!
Suzune...
Suzune!
Suzune, Suzune!
W, who is she?
Suzune!
Suzune.
Suzune, Suzune.
No, no!
That's not me!
Masakazu-san, my sister Yuiko's husband...
Killed his sister, Suzune-san, in a car accident...
She was Naoto-san's fiance...
Not there!
l can see everything, Suzune.
No, it's embarrassing!
Naoto-san, please be more gentle...
C, cuming!
Here, Naoto-san.
Thanks.
Late last night, l heard a very loud scream coming from Ayumi's room.
S, Shino-chan, would you like seconds?
No, l'm on a diet.
Anyway, how long do you plan to stay?
When l meet the achievement...
Achievement?
How can Sis welcome such a bastard.
l'm here...!?
Well, Mizuna wanted to walk with us
Hey, Ayumi.
Did you make me lunch again?
Y, yes..
l can't wait.
Ouch!
Mizuna, why did you do that?
Hey, don't pull on me Mizuna!
Ayumi or Mizuna.
l have to impregnate one of them.
l know it's cruel, but l have no choice...
After puberty, people become interested in the opposite sex.
Men, body hair begin to grow, voice becoming deeper, penis development...
Women, breast development, first menstrual period...
Feels good...
Feels good.
Cuming, cuming!
Did it feel good?
Yes, it felt...good....
Well then, want to do something that feels better?
Mizuna, is the neck your erogenous zone?
Erogenous zone, a portion of the body when stimulated helps you get sexually...aroused.
Your nipples are getting hard.
lt's a cute butt.
Feels good...
l'm sticking two in.
Cuming, cuming...
Cuming, cuming!
Well Mizuna, l'm ready.
Well?
We can stop here if you want.
l'm...fine.
Don't be so tense.
Going.
Does it hurt, Mizuna?
l, it...hurts!
Endure the pain, Mizuna..
Please...
Mizuna, Mizuna, Mizuna!
Mizuna, it's almost over.
Mizuna!
Why with me, do you...
Suzune, Suzune!
Mizuna, Mizuna!
Your tight...very tight, Mizuna!
l'm cuming Mizuna.
l'm going to unload everything in you!
l hope you find it to your liking...
Looks delicious
Time to eat!
Ayumi.
ls something wrong?
N, no, it's nothing.
Strange...
She's acting as if l'm a stranger?
Does this mean she hasn't opened up to me yet?
Naoto-san?
Ayumi.
No, please stop!
Ayumi!
That hurts, Nao-kun...
lt hurts, it hurts...
Su, Suzune...
Why do you always call me by that name?
Suzune...what's wrong Suzune?
No, that's not me...
Suzune...please forgive me!
No, why are you doing this here!?
Nao-kun, this way.
Suzune...
No, please stop, snap out of it Naoto-san!
Nao-kun, want me to use my mouth?
Suzune...
Come on Suzune, lick it!
Suck it and make me feel good!
Come on, l need it now Suzune!
Naoto-san....
Y, yes..
Suck it, suck it now Suzune!
OK...
S, Suzune, just like that!
lt feels good Suzune.
Jerk it with your hands as you suck.
Just perfect, Suzune.
Alright, l'm cuming Suzune!
Don't stop jerking, l'm not done!
Y, yes
Don't stop!
S, Suzune?
What's gotten into me?
My body craves for more.
No, ever since Naoto-san first had me, l haven't been myself...
lt feels good Suzune.
l'll stick it inside, so take off your panties.
ls this what you want?
You want this, right?
Y, yes, l want it...
What do you want?
l want your...penis.....
lnside me!
l see, you want it inside that much?
You are a pervert, Suzune.
l don't care who l am to him, l want Naoto-san....
Please, stick it inside me, Suzune...
lt's inside, your hot, throbbing member, inside me!
Suzune...
More, Naoto-san.
lnside...it's amazing Naoto-san!
Doesn't it feel good, Suzune?
Feels great!
So warm...it's driving me wild!
Cum, please cum Naoto-san, cum inside me!
Give me every drop!
Cum inside me, please cum together!
Cuming, Suzune!
Cuming!
Again, only with me, he kept calling out the name, Suzune...
So you're telling me there's no way you're kicking him out?
Shino, please understand.
Our family has been protected by his family for many years and...
l don't want to hear that same old story again!
Shino...
Well Sis, don't get our sister's involved.
They shouldn't be part of this
Destined or not, they don't deserve this...let's take care of it ourselves!
Sis, if you're not going to protect them....l'll be the one who will!
Shino...
Hey, it's the perverted monkey.
P, perverted monkey?
Well, aren't you?
You're going to their rooms to fuck, right?
See?
Here, here, what about me?
You're drunk.
Wait!
Sorry...let me hug you for a while...
S, Shino?
l get lonely...l need to drink sometimes to keep myself from loosing it.
Having sex, right?
How come you never lay your hands on me?
Your job is to get one of us pregnant, right?
l don't lay my hands on drunk girls.
Be a man!
Or are you afraid of me?
lt's not fair that you'll ignore a beautiful girl like me!
Come on, take me!
Try to get me pregnant!
You don't care who the mother is as long you have a child, right!?
H, hold on...
l, it's been a while, so...
Your tits are really big.
Probably the biggest of the sisters
...ldiot.
Here, milk this.
Milk my thing with your big tits, Shino.
S, sure...
Yes, that feels good Shino...
No, not that!
Why not, your nipples are responding to it.
But...stop!
lt hurts, stop!
Lick it, please lick it!
Naoto-san...
P, please be more gentle.
lt's been a while so it hurts, please be gentle!
Why, Naoto-san...
Now, all of us had sex with Naoto-san...
At first, l only did it because Yuiko asked us too.
But now, Naoto-san is very....