What is this?
This...toy ring?
To be honest, l dont know.
l picked it up during Masakazu-san and my sister's wedding.
Here, this ring is for you Suzu.
What, really?
Wow, thank you!
This is Suzu's.
Suzu?
Suzune-san?
l gave this to her as a present when we were kids.
l'm positive...
But l wonder why she kept this toy ring?
lt was probably a very important treasure for her.
Maybe Suzu...
Wanted me to remember her and...now shes...
l always thought it was cute ever since l picked it up.
Ayumi, what'swrong!
lt's Nao-kun!
Suzu...?
Nao-kun!
l wanted to see you!
To my surprise, my dead fiance...
is back, borrowing Ayumi's body.
P, please be more gentle!
lt's been a while so it hurts!
Please!
W, why...Naoto-san....
Naoto-san came here to impregnate one of us.
No one knows who will get pregnant...
So Naoto-san even does it with my sisters.
Cuming, l'm cuming!
Not inside, dont!
But you said you dont mind getting pregnant.
lt's in so deep...
To get her pregnant...
Suzune-san, what would you do?
You want to have Nao-kun's baby?
Seconds!
Uh, OK.
Mizuna, how many times have l told you not to read while eating!
S, Sis, l thought you were on a diet?
lt's fine.
l have to be healthy for a possible baby.
How are things looking?
Looks good.
l think Shino will be the one.
l see...
Thank you.
Dont talk to me like that...
Arent we a married couple?
Stop it, l...
l...
S, Suzune!
Suzune!
Naoto-san's fiance...
My sister...
l killed her.
So l cant...
Masakazu-san, dont pressure yourself.
lt's not your fault.
lt's useless, l cant...
My sister and Naoto-san having a baby...
it may be over...
Suzune-san, you want to see Naoto-san?
Naoto-san?
Um, this is the girl's...
What's wrong Naoto-san!
l dont know...
l cant stop thinking about you Ayumi.
Ayumi l want you...to have my baby.
Him stimulating me is making me want it again.
What am l thinking...
Ayumi, use your mouth.
B, but...
Right here?
l beg you, Ayumi.
Naoto-san...
Ayumi, hurry!
l need it!
Y, yes.
This, Naoto-san's...
Going to be inside me...
But was inside my sister yesterday.
What's wrong Ayumi?
But Naoto-san, you like Shino more than me...
Not true.
Then why do you...
l love you.
lt's because l have fallen madly in love with you.
N, Naoto-san?
ls that not good enough?
l know l'm on a mission to make a baby...
But l've fallen in love with, l can't help it!
ls that a bad thing?
No, l love you too Naoto-san.
Ayumi...
l want to have your baby, Naoto-san.
l love my sister, but...
More so, l love Naoto-san.
For Naoto-san, l can do anything.
Naoto-san, does it feel good?
Let me make your thing bigger.
Ayumi!
Naoto-san's...what a waste.
l'm sorry, Naoto-san, l m really sorry...
No, it's fine.
No, it's not.
lt's not fine, Naoto-san.
Now, please cum...please cum inside me.
Ayumi...
Naoto-san, cum inside...right here.
Please.
Alright.
Hurry.
lt's inside, Naoto-san's inside me...
lt doesnt hurt...
lt doesnt hurt, but...what is this?
This painful...lonesome feeling?
Here, look, look at me going inside.
lt's inside, inside!
ln a bit, Naoto-san's is going to ejaculated inside me and...!
lt feels good, it feels good right there.
Lift your arms.
Naoto-san, more.
Naoto-san, l love...
l love you Naoto-san.
Happy, l'm happy...
Naoto-san, Naoto-san!
Nao-kun....Nao-kun....
S, Suzune!?
Suzu, Suzu!
Naoto-san wants to see Suzune-san.
Only l can have them spend time together...
Then l shall...
l'm cuming!
Cum, please, cum everything inside me!
(Sign: Library)
Why...?
l told him not to lay his hands on them...
Why can't it be me?
Good...
Mizuna!
l wonder how this one is?
Feels good...
Good, it feels good!
Come on, stop it.
You know it suseless.
Masakazu-san, l've accomplished my tasks.
Naoto-san has chosen my sisters.
So we can finally live as a married couple.
Yu, Yuiko...
Brother, my dear brother Masaku.
S, Suzune?
l'm so happy to be your sister, Brother.
Because of it, l've fallen in love with the man you care for.
l'm sorry Suzune, please forgive me.
No, it's not your fault...
So, shower Yuiko-san with your love.
Pretty please.
Suzune!
Masakazu-san?
D, dont, l said l don't want it!
Shino-chan, dont be shy.
lt feels really good.
Just pretend you were tricked and try it out.
l changed my mind, l don't want too!
Don't say...that!
W, what are you doing Mizuna!?
H, hey, l said don't!
Stick this inside...your butt and...
lt'll help you get wet quicker.
See, doesn't it feel good?
Stop, stop!
lt's been a while, Masakazu-san...
Good.
Masakazu-san...
Yuiko...
lt feels good!
No, it's making me crazy!
Good...
Shino-chan, you're so wet...
Feels good!
Who am l?
Ayumi...
No, this is Suzu.
Bingo!
You're good at this Nao-kun.
Ayumi never called me Nao-kun.
Besides, the characteristics...
And habits...are Suzu's.
Hey, Suzu.
ls that ring what's keeping you here?
Yeah...l think so, but l m not sure.
l'll disappear soon....
What, disappear?
So this is the classroom you attend...
Hey Nao-kun...
Listen to me and don't laugh.
There's one thing l want to do for you before l go.
...What?
l want to...pleasure you with my mouth.
l know it's a weird thing to ask as a last wish...
But l always wanted to try it.
Are you sure that's it?
That last thing being that?
l've always been straight forward with Suzu, but this time l couldn't utter a word...
May...l?
So this is Nao-kun's...
lt's not the first time you've seen it.
Yeah, but we were kids then.
lt's so hard...
Can l lick it?
Yeah.
What's wrong, Suzu?
Nao-kun, l love you, l love you!
Nao-kun, l dont want to go!
Suzu...
l wanted to tie the knot with you!
l wanted to go through a wedding ceremony!
l wanted your baby...
l...love you too...
But this body within my arms isn't your's Suzu.
You taking over Ayumi's body isn't a good thing.
You cant...
Nao-kun, you love Ayumi-chan dont you?
l love her.
As my substitute?
You are you, Ayumi is Ayumi.
l fell in love with her for who she is.
l understand.
l know what l'm asking for is impossible...
Suzu...
l really do understand.
Nao-kun, l have to...go now.
Suzu?
Take care.
Ayumi-chan as well...
Suzu?
Suzu, Suzu!
Naoto-san?
My goodbye with Suzu was disappointing.
After that day...
Suzune-san has never appeared again.
Can l love Naoto-san as deeply as Suzune-san had?
And will Naoto-san love me the same?
Naoto-san?
Ayumi...
Naoto-san...
Naoto-san, does it feel good?
Yeah...
Ayumi, l'm ready.
lt's inside, it's inside.
lt's all the way inside!
Naoto-san, Naoto-san!
Ayumi.
Ayumi!
Naoto-san.
Naoto-san, Naoto-san...
Ayumi...
So, after everything, Naoto has chosen Ayumi only.
l'm positive Ayumi will give birth to a healthy baby.
Shino-chan...
l know, l...l'm not disappointed.
Come, lets go back.
OK.
Cuming, l'm about to cum Naoto-san.
Please, cum with me Naoto-san!
Cum inside!
l'm cuming Ayumi!
Six months later...
Lets see, diapers, powdered milk, a rattle...
Hey, what do you think about this bed for the baby?
Sis, you're thinking too far ahead.
As they say, better to be ready.
Both of you are thinking too far ahead...
Suzune-san, please watch over us.
Naoto-san, myself, and...
Come out healthy...
Suzune-chan.