Naoto-san...
Yuiko...
You're so tight.
Really tight, Yuiko.
lt's embarrassing...
But you're wet...
Don't lie to me.
Because...
Naoto-san, don't tease me.
lt's great Yuiko, l can see everything.
No, embarrassing...
P, push it in now.
Naoto-san...
N, Naoto-san...let me make you feel better.
There...right there!
l want it, please Naoto-san!
Give it to me inside!
So happy.
Give me your cum!
A baby...
Please make me pregnant!
Cuming.
Cuming!
You came alot, Naoto-san.
Yuiko Hizuki
l'm sorry, Naoto-san
Just because l can't get pregnant...
lt's not your fault Yuiko.
The tradition is to be at fault.
The cursed tradition...
Naoto-sama, may l?
Masakazu-san...
What is it, Masa?
Old Master has summoned you.
Not another long pep-talk.
Masakazu Hizuki
My name is Naoto Rindo
Naoto Rindo
l'm the successor of this clan.
Rindo Group is a family who became wealthy after the World War.
For every 3rd generation, there is a ceremony to be held to keep the family prosperous.
And l am the one that needs to go through the ritual known as the Hinotsukisai.
Manzo Rindo
Alright Naoto.
This is going to be your last chance.
Yes, l know....
You couldn't impregnate Masakazu's wife, Yuiko.
So instead, out of her sisters, Shino, Ayumi, Mizuna...
Any one of them...
You have to impregnate them with your successor.
But Yuiko...
Well, it's not Yuiko's fault that she can't get pregnant.
l see, so you're saying that your seeds are to blame?
O, of course not, don't say that.
Well, l do understand you are saddened by your fiance's tragic death...
But putting that aside, the curse upon the Rindo family is scarred in deep Naoto.
Don't let your guard down.
Here we go again...always about the curse.....
Hey, are you listening!?
O, of course.
Listen, if you can't get one of them pregnant by the ceremony, you are expelled from the family!
E, expelled!?
And this is how my temporary new life with Yuiko's sisters in the city begins.
Kouichi, the one who raised the sisters is sent out on a one month vacation.
Only the three sisters are at the apartment.
Naoto-sama, please seed one of them within the month.
Shino Hizuki
l object!
Please understand, Shino.
This is a decision made by Old Master.
Mizuna Hizuki
Why do ''we'' need to pleasure him!?
Ayumi Hizuki
Sis, are you trying to ruin our lives!?
Of course not...
What is it then!?
The only reason why we can live in luxury is because of the Rindo Family's support.
You already know, right?
Luxury, delicacy, conductive of sumptuous living.
Fine, l'll just leave this place!
Don't Shino!
Please calm down!
No matter how much l care about you, l don't want a baby!
How about you, Ayumi?
But...l never thought about it....
Having a baby that is...
You're right Ayumi...but listen to me.
The Hizuki family is...
Pregnant.
When the females egg is fertilized, or the state of having a child in the body.
This is going to be tough...
Not like they're going to happily and willingly get pregnant by me.
lf you can't get one of them pregnant by the ceremony, you are expelled from the family!
Fine, l'll do it, l'll do it!
Who's room shall l go to...
lt can't be her...
So that means...
Why do ''we'' need to pleasure him!
No, l don't think she'll let me...
Then...
She's my only choice.
S, so cute...
Ayumi!
W, what, what are you doing!?
S, stop, please, stop!
- W, wait!
- Stop, please!
D, don't look please...
H, how can you...
S, sorry, l jumped to quick.
l thought you were great since l saw you, and...
l need to make a baby before the ceremony and...
Or else, l'm going to get expelled from the family, so l panicked and...
Well, l wasn't thinking about your feelings...
Sorry!
U, um...
G, good morning...
M, morning...
B, breakfast is ready...
Thanks...
l'm finished.
See you later.
See you.
Here you go.
Thanks.
My best chance is definitely with Ayumi.
l need to convince her first.
l now attend the school the three sisters go to.
And at school...
Um, l don't know if you'll like it but...
U, um , was there something you didn't like?
That's not it, l'm thankful.
Wonderful.
Ayumi was kind to me all the time.
She's very kind and very devoted.
l am honestly deeply moved.
lt's so delicious.
l wonder if l can do it.
Having Naoto-san's baby...
l know it's the family fate...
But it's too sudden...
This is a kiss.
Not too hard, right?
Let me lead, there's nothing to worry about.
No...don't...
No, don't look, it's embarrassing.
N, not, there.
Ayumi, say my name.
Say Naoto.
N, Naoto-san...
Thank you, Ayumi.
Stop, don't!
Don't, Naoto-san...
Naoto-san, please stop!
Don't take it off!
Stop, please!
l can't...
No, stop!
Rub my thing.
T, this is a man's...
No!
Good...
What were you doing in Sis's room...?
Mizuna is the youngest sister.
lt appears that she was peeking while Ayumi and l were at it.
l decided to teach her some sex-ed with the study books she had.
This is?
Petting...
This?
Masturbation...
Vagina, a woman's sexual organ...
There are three erogenous zones for the vagina...
Clitoris...
The G-spot located inside...
A great orgasm can be achieved once it's developed...
The cervix, deep inside the vagina.
Erogenous zone of the uterus.
T, the penis hitting the walls, vibrating through the peritoneum gives pleasure...
V, vagina feels good!
Masturbation feels good.
Masturbation feels good!
l want to try...
Pleasing a man with my mouth and tongue...
lt moved!
lt's getting...bigger.
This is the smell of a penis?
lf you want, we can stop.
Put it deeper in your mouth and kind of stimulate it with your throat.
Just perfect...
Can't hold in much longer!
Yuiko-san swallowed that...
Smell of a Chestnut flower?
l see, so you don't want to deal with Naoto-san anymore?
lt's not that...
lt's my confidence...
A bit disappointed, l thought you would do well.
l told you it can't be done.
l don't care what the reason is, but having Ayumi take the place of his dead fiance is a joke.
Shino...
l know this isn't easy for you.
However, if you reject this, it will be the end of the Rindo family.
l beg you to rethink this for Naoto-sama.
Ayumi, you angry?
Not telling...
As expected, Ayumi was mad at me.
lt took me about a hour to convince her, but finally...
lt's wet.
lt's embarrassing...d, don't.
No, stop!
l thought you would do well.
l told you it can't be done.
l don't care what the reason is, but having Ayumi take place of his dead fiance is a joke.
Um...
Gently...please...be gentle....
Yeah, l know.
O, ouch!
lt hurts!
Na, Naoto-san!
Then it happened.
The memories l've been hiding have resurfaced.
T, this is...
Nao-kun, it feels good...
Y, you're!
Nao-kun...
Suzune...
More, deeper!
Nao-kun, Nao-kun!
Suzune...Suzune!
Suzune, Suzune!
W, who is she?
Suzune!
S, stop it Naoto-san, it hurts!
Stop it, it hurts, it hurts, Naoto-san!
Suzune.
Suzune, Suzune!
Suzune!
Stop it!
Stop!
Suzune.
No matter how much l plead...
Naoto-san wouldn't go easy on me...
He wasn't making love with me, he was making love with his lost fiance...