A small village near the edge of the mountains.
Rinin Village.
An unusual custom has been passed down here.
To subdue Iwanaga Hime's anger,
on the nights of the new moon and the full moon,
a young girl is chosen to be the priestess.
She is raped, broken, and shamed.
I, Yamazaki Suzuko, returned to this
place, my home village, as a teacher.
For the sake of my mother, who was chosen as priestess,
and still lives in depression today,
I promised myself I would put an end to this custom.
However, unable to fight back,
I was chosen as priestess
and turned into a disgraceful sex slave.
The group that carries out the ceremonies
is the Gang Rape Club.
The one in charge of arranging these ceremonies
is the student council president of Rinin High,
Tamura Motoko.
She is the one who sent me to the hell of a sex slave.
I will never forgive that woman.
Never.
Katsuragi Hospital
This is it. I've finally found it.
With this, I can send that woman to hell.
Translation: Snake | Editing: hiddenmaskl | Timing: vltouch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Chaosrains
The Gang Rape Clubru
Ep 4: Maki and Motoko
In order to save Aiko-sensei,
Shiori-sensei became the priestess.
They say that Shiori-sensei has fulfilled her
duty since a new priestess was found.
Who could the new priestess be?
Maki...
My precious Maki...
No matter what happens, I will definitely protect you!
As the child of a former priestess,
I was raised carefully to one day protect Rinin Village.
As long as I am here, at the center of this custom,
I won't let anyone get away with anything.
Those are members of the Gang Rape Club!
I'll definitely get them to talk today.
Motoko-chan!
Good morning.
Hey, Motoko-chan?
Maki... I will definitely protect you!
Thank you.
Then... let's go, Motoko-chan.
Home room is about to start.
Um, excuse me, have you seen Katsuragi-san?
Is she absent today?
You mean Maki? She's skipping.
She's been absent for a month already.
If she's tired of this, she could just quit.
It's hard to believe that Maki would...
Could it be...
That voice! Don't tell me...
Get out of the way!
Who did you make the priestess!?
My pussy feels good!
All the way inside!
Come deep inside!
Be sure to take it all in.
Squeeze your throat more!
This throat-pussy is great!
I'm gonna cum in here. Be sure to take it all!
Maki!
No, no, no!
My Maki, my Maki is...
Release Maki this instant!
I haven't given permission for this!
You can't do that, Prez.
Let go of me!
Protecting someone from becoming
the priestess for personal reasons...
Maki!
You want it? You want more semen?
Stop it! Don't you dare cum!
Don't you dare stain Maki!
I want it!
Please give lots of thick semen to Maki's womb!
Maki, you can't!
I'm... cumming!
I'm cumming!
I worked so hard to store the semen
inside my body since morning...
I'm cumming from all the overflowing semen!
Maki!
It's my turn next.
Hurry and clean it up, starting from the base.
Yes...
How is it? Can you smell it?
Yes, the fragrance is wonderful.
I know, right?
I haven't washed it in a week just for
the sake of our school idol Maki.
Thank you very much.
Maki will clean it up for you with her slutty saliva.
This is great!
There's so much!
Don't swallow it yet.
Open your mouth and show it.
Savor it with your tongue.
Gargle it in your mouth.
Make some more bubbles.
Good, now taste and enjoy.
Show us again.
Maki...
This asshole has horrible manners, doesn't it?
It's twitching and asking for cock like crazy!
No... don't stare so much...
Amazing! My pussy and my anus are
being violated at the same time!
Which one is better? C'mon, tell us!
Both! I love both!
I can't choose between them!
Wow, how horribly slutty.
Even though you were once the school idol!
Maki is still an idol!
Even if I'm feeling it from having
both my pussy and ass violated,
I'm still everyone's idol!
What's with these lame boobs?
Your sister had so much more.
I'm sorry! Maki will work hard!
I'll work hard to have huge, naughty boobs like Onee-chan!
No...
It's painful... if you spread it so much, Maki's
pussy and anus will be all loose!
They already are. Squeeze tighter!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry for having a loose pussy and anus!
You're cumming again!
Semen is flowing inside me!
My Maki is... Maki...
Well then, Maki-chan. Be sure
to say hi to your favorite prez!
Hey, Motoko-chan... Maki is so happy
from becoming everyone's sex slave...
I'm so glad... I became a priestess!
Maki!
As punishment for running away from
her responsibilities of being a priestess,
Maki went through an especially cruel month.
What did you guys do to Maki?
Let's have a look now.
The recordings of how the pure, innocent Maki-chan
became the dick-loving sex slave.
Well, Oji-san will be the one to
take Maki-chan's virgin pussy.
Don't!
It hurts!
No!
Wow, Maki-chan's screams are great! Let me hear more!
It hurts, stop!
I'll make it so your body loves cock right away.
No!
Cumming!
– I'll be giving Maki-chan's virgin pussy a creampie!
– No, no, no, no, no!
No!
C'mon Maki-chan, this is a moment
worthy of commemoration!
Smile, smile!
Ow!
You're squirting such slutty juices, you naughty child!
I'm sorry! But, it... it feels... good...
No! I'll cum! No!
Great, Maki-chan! It's your first white-eyed ahegao!
Congratulations!
What a great view. It's the school idol flashing at a park!
This is embarrassing...
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Speak up, or we'll make you do more embarrassing things.
Please let me go to the restroom.
Hey, the idol wants to go to the restroom!
Looks like we've got a show to watch!
We'll pay close attention, so go ahead and do it.
Huh? Here?
Of course!
Hurry and let it out!
If Maki-chan won't do it, we'll just get
Katsuragi-sensei to do it instead.
Don't do anything more to my mom!
Then you know what to do, don't you Maki-chan?
This kid, she's really peeing!
Looks like we'll get some good shots.
Please... don't take photos...
To think that the pure Maki-chan is actually such a slut!
I think I'm cumming just from looking at her!
No... If you're gonna cum then cum inside Maki!
Even my mouth is okay...
Maki-chan is the best!
She's wetting herself!
So much for her pure image!
You'd better lick the Prez's seat clean. She can be scary.
Motoko-chan... I'm sorry...
I've always wanted to rape Maki-chan!
Thrust more and more!
Mess up Maki's pussy!
C'mon, don't pretend you don't love it!
Cock tastes good! I love cock!
I can't... I'm cumming!
More... Give me more and more semen...
You slut! Don't get so full of yourself
just because you're popular!
You had this coming after seducing
all the guys with your slutty body!
Serves you right.
Cumming!
C'mon, look up. Smile.
Who said she's the pure school idol?
She's just a perverted bitch.
Hey bitch, turn over here!
Yes!
What's wrong? Where's your usual assertiveness?
Why are you here!?
I have a present for you.
I, Yamazaki Suzuko, announce
Tamura Motoko as the priestess!
Only the person herself or her family have the
right to recommend someone as priestess.
You don't qualify.
Take a look at this.
This is a special birth certificat for children of priestesses.
One is yours, and the other one is mine.
So what?
Look here.
The name of your father is written here.
And the name of my father...
Do you mean!?
That's right! The man who impregnated my mother
is the same as the man who impregnated yours!
N-No way!
You and me are half-sisters with the same father.
And I qualify as a person who can elect you to be priestess.
No way! You're lying! There's some kind of mistake!
Okay, you guys! Violate her as much as you want!
Make it so that Motoko can't live without cock!
S-Stand down!
I'm the president of the Gang Rape Club!
I'm the person who leads and organizes the ceremony.
If you resist me you'll die!
I've always wanted to cover Prez in semen!
I'll be sure to tear away that
perfect-student mask of yours right away!
S-Stop!
No!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I won!
Stay away from me you meat loaf! Pig!
Prez's pussy has the fragrance of rotten cheese!
Don't smell me, you moron!
No!
Stop!
Stop it!
You're loud. I'll shut you up with my dick.
I took her fellatio virginity!
How does your first cock taste, huh?
Disgusting! The dick of garbage like you is the worst!
Well, your throat-pussy is about to receive
cum from this garbage dick right now.
C'mon!
St-Stop it!
Stop it already!
I'll be the one to take Prez's virginity!
Stop!
I've become one with Motoko!
Don't call me by my name you perverted pig!
There's no way that your gross cock
will ever make me feel good!
Motoko! If you squeeze that much, I'll... I'll...
If you dare cum inside, I'll never forgive you!
I can't hold it back, I'm cumming!
No!
Great, isn't it? Getting so much cum
poured into your virgin pussy.
Oh my, oh my, what a scary face.
I'll give you a present as an apology.
What are you planning to do!?
It's an aphrodisiac that'll make you feel very good.
I'll force you to be aroused.
Stop it!
Let's give you an injection here too.
I'll make sure the hate that I feel is engraved into your body.
No!
The high and mighty Prez is sucking on my dick happily!
I won't lose to sick beasts like you!
Looks like even the Prez was just a slut after all!
I am the Rinin High School Student Council President.
The chief executive of the Gang Rape Club!
There's no way I'm feeling anything from this!
Motoko.
How miserable you look, all covered in semen.
Sis is so happy for you.
Don't you forget!
You all that harmed my precious Maki...
I will never...
You are the absolute worst.
The Student Council President, Tamura Motoko,
will leave her position today.
Tamura-san has not been feeling well recently
and fears that she cannot take care of
all the work in the student council.
So I will be temporarily substituting as the president.
Well, Tamura-san, please greet everyone.
She's not feeling well because she got knocked up!?
Even though she's got a cool face,
she does that stuff, too, huh?
Um, I sincerely apologize for the trouble...
I'm causing for everyone by leaving
my position as president...
I haven't worked with you all for long,
but I'm very thankful for all your support...
I've done as you said! Let me go to the restroom already!
Yes, you've worked very hard up until now.
By the way, what's with this stomach!?
I... can't!
I can't stop it!
It's coming out! More and more is coming out!
Excretion feels so good!
Everyone is watching and I should be embarrassed,
but it feels so good!
I'm cumming while excreting!
Enemas... feel good...
Do it again...
It's been half a year since I made
Tamura Motoko the priestess.
Now that she's become a priestess, the
Gang Rape Club will soon disappear.
And that is because
Tamura Motoko, Katsuragi Maki, Akamura Shion, and
Katsuragi Aiko have been made to be the eternal priestesses.
And no new priestesses will ever be made.
If the four are to die, the children they've given
birth to will become the new priestesses.
I have decided it to be so.
They will be violated as priestesses until they die.
It isn't that bad of a deal for them though.
My revenge is complete.
You can rest peacefully now, Mother.
This is a small village near the edge of the mountains.
Rinin Village.
The village that once had an abnormal custom
of raping their female sacrifices to God.