A small village nestled amongst the mountains.
Rinin Village.
In this village, an unusual custom is performed.
In order to subdue Iwanaga Himes anger,
on the nights of the new moon and the full moon,
a young girl is selected to be the priestess.
She is broken, raped, and shamed greatly.
With the village being my hometown,
I, Yamazaki Suzuko, returned here to be a teacher.
My mother was a former priestess.
To exact revenge for the hurt that still resides within her,
I vowed in my heart to put an end to this custom.
However, without a chance to resist,
I was selected as a priestess,
and was turned into a disgraceful sex slave.
The one controlling these ceremonies was...
the student council president of
Rinin High, Tamura Motoko.
The group that carries out this ceremony is called...
The Gang Rape Club.
The Gang Rape Club
Ep 3: Shiori and Maki
Nakamura-sensei...
Mother...
Hurry up already.
What's taking so long?
I can't hold my piss in any longer!
Hey, no budging!
Infirmary
A-Aiko-sensei... here...
If I give you this, you'll do a lot of things to me, I hear...
Well, take your clothes off.
What a stinky dick.
You haven't washed it in a while.
How dirty you are.
But the other guys say you love this smell, so I...
Who told you that?
You honestly want me to suck on this dirty, stinky dick?
Y-Yes.
The guys... said...
that if I order you to, you'll do it.
What will you order me to do?
Show me your tits, lick my dick, and drink my cum,
you fucking whore.
Since you put it that way...
H-Hurry up and suck my dick,
you hag!
Very well.
You stink.
The smell of rotten cheese is wafting up my nostrils.
But... that's what's so good.
I love it.
The dick cheese you've been keeping
on your unwashed dick...
I love it.
Let me eat it. I want to eat it all up.
All of it...
I want to eat all of your dirty, young dick cheese...
I will eat all of it for you.
Give it to me!
I want you to fill my mouth with cum.
D-Don't swallow it, you old hag!
You're not supposed to swallow it yet.
Show me the cum in your mouth.
Close your mouth and savor the taste of it.
Delicious, isn't it?
Very delicious...
Let me see.
Do you want to swallow?
Yes...
If you do, then say, "I want to swallow".
Don't spill any of it, either.
I can't understand what you're saying.
I wanna drink it.
I told you not to spill it!
Can't you hear me, you old hag?
This is what you get!
I want it...
I want the delicious...
Delicious cum...
I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm so happy...
I got so much semen... I'm so happy...
Come on, time to take a commemorative photo.
Spread your legs wider.
Smile.
Double peace signs.
Maki.
What's wrong?
You've been acting strange lately.
Please, I'm your sister. Tell me.
Could it be... about the Gang Rape Club?
Onee-chan...
Even I've heard of them.
I'm a girl who was born in this village, after all.
It couldn't be that mother was...
More!
Finger me more!
My pussy yearns to be fucked!
Dicks...
More, more...
Give me more...
Inside my pussy and inside my ass, too...
Yes, I'm cumming!
From having a load of cum shot in my
mouth while being fucked in the ass...
I'm cumming...
Mom!
You brutes!
How dare you!?
This has nothing to do with you, Nakamura-sensei.
Please leave.
Nothing to do with me?
She's my mother!
We are merely adhering to the
long-held customs of this village.
Once a girl has been turned into the priestess,
not even a teacher or her family can save her from her fate.
Besides...
Please, don't stop.
I want more semen...
It seems Aiko-sensei doesn't want to be saved.
Mom, snap out of it!
Let go of me!
It's too late.
There's no helping her.
No, I can save her.
Are you serious?
In that case, there's only one way.
Maki-chan... Dad...
Tomonoba-san... I'm sorry!
Give me the robe.
I volunteer to be the priestess.
It's been a while since Aiko-sensei
was selected as a priestess.
It must almost be time for a new priestess to be chosen.
That's strange.
Why has no one contacted me yet?
I'm the president of the Gang Rape Club.
What's going on?
Who will be the next priestess?
The old hag was nice, but...
a young wife is...
awesome!
Shut up!
Keep quiet... while you fuck me!
You say that, but...
You're feeling good too, aren't you?
I'm not... I'm not enjoying it!
Well then, let's try sticking this in you.
No! Stop it!
Your pussy is full now, but I like this hole too.
Not in there!
No!
Nakamura-sensei, your tits are really soft.
I've always lusted after you.
During class, I always tried to imagine what
your tits looked like under your clothes.
I wondered what color your nipples were, as well.
That's gross!
Nakamura-sensei... Shiori...
So this is what your nipples look like.
Shiori's nipples... they're very pretty.
Stop it.
Don't say that.
Shiori, whenever you wore tight-fitting skirts...
I could see the lines of your ass.
And... during class... I jerked off.
No!
To think that I can cum inside you now...
No.
Don't do it.
Don't cum inside me!
I'm cumming inside.
My semen... will be in your womb, Shiori.
I'll squirt it in!
No!
Take it out!
Cum outside, please!
I'm... I'm cumming...
My cum will be... inside your belly!
No, stop it...
Please, please, please, please...
No!
You don't have to hate it that much.
After all, you've already had so many guys cum inside you.
Look how much there is.
How many guys has it been?
No...
Please let me go...
I'll break...
Looks like she's starting to enjoy it.
Sensei...
No matter how good it feels, if you cry out too
loudly, the club members will overhear us.
No...
– No!
– Hey, shut her up!
Right.
Very nice. Shiori-sensei, I love your mouth-pussy.
Oh shit...
I'm... almost there...
There's still more.
I'm definitely gonna cum inside you!
I'll shoot every last drop into your womb.
Be sure to get pregnant.
N-No...
Stop it.
I've never given birth before...
I don't want my first baby... to come from gang rape...
No!
I’m cumming... into your pussy!
I'm cumming... while being raped...
I'm being fucked... there's cum going into my pussy...
While being impregnated... I'm cumming!
Onee-chan, you look pale.
Are you okay?
I-I've been really busy lately, so I think I'm just tired.
But I'll be fine.
If that's all it is...
Onee-chan?
Onee-chan!?
I-I'm okay...
Sorry for showing you this strange side of myself.
Onee-chan!
What is that?
Onee-chan! Ortee-chan!
Don't look at me...
It's nothing... really...
It can't be nothing! It can't...
Mom?
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
The doctor says I'm recovering quickly.
But... Mom, you're not smiling.
There's nothing to worry about anymore.
You're not the priestess anymore.
And this hospital is in the neighboring village to ours.
Those horrible boys won't come here.
I'm sorry.
I don't remember any of it.
I don't remember bow I became the priestess,
and I don't remember what they did to me.
I can only recall faint images.
Mom...
But... my body remembers.
What if I'm raped again?
I feel as if I could lose my mind and no longer be myself.
Don't worry.
Everything is okay now.
What's happened to Shiori?
She hasn't come to visit me lately.
It seems she's been busy with work.
But I'm sure she'll be okay.
She'll be okay...
My wife, Shiori... Did something happen to her?
Listen, there's something I need to tell you.
Shiori?
Shiori, what's happened?
What are you boys doing?
What? Let go of me!
T-Tomonobu-san... I'm sorry.
Nakamura-sensei, we're returning your wife to you.
We've chosen our new priestess, so we
told her she's free to go home now.
But she can't walk by herself.
Priestess? Are you guys from the Gang Rape Club?
Shiori-san took good care of us.
We got plenty of good use out of her.
W-What have you done to her!?
Do you really want to know?
We don't mind telling you.
Hey.
Come on. You don't need to hold back anymore.
I think that makes fifty guys inside of her for today.
What?
Though before that, hundreds of guys came inside her,
so it was hard to keep count of how many overall.
Come on, tell him like we practiced.
I've accepted semen from many
different men inside my pussy.
S-Stop it!
Every day, every day, semen from countless
men has been pumped into my pussy.
Stop it!
I've had my insides filled almost to
the point of bursting with semen.
I have come to love the feeling of
so much semen inside of me.
Because I'm a whore of a wife.
That's enough!
Let me leave!
We're not finished yet.
Come on, take a good look.
Come one, we'll help you out, so go ahead and birth it.
See? It's coming out.
I'm pissing myself!
I-I've been fucked in the ass so many times.
It always feels so good.
All month long, I've taken a countless
number of cocks up my ass every day!
In the end, the last week...
I took this long one in my butthole...
I have... I have taken it inside me...
Look, Shiori-sensei, you dirtied the school
floor and made Nakamura-sensei angry.
Come on.
I'm sorry...
Tomonobu-san...
It's the priestess.
It's our new priestess!
A new priestess has arrived at the Gang Rape Club!
It's Maki!
Katsuragi Maki!
Holy shit! She's really pretty!
I've been wanting to fuck her for a long time!
New priestess.
Tell us your name.
I am the new priestess, Katsuragi Maki.
Nice to meet you all...
I-I'm still a virgin.
P-Please, love me a lot.
Move it!
Move it, you guys!
Who...
Who did you choose as the priestess!?
Acting like you were better than us, you fucking whore.
Now that our intimidating president has
wound up like this, it's all over for her.
You will pay for this...