A small village nestled amongst the mountains,
Rinin Village.
In this village, an unusual custom is performed.
In order to subdue Iwanaga Hime's anger,
on the nights of the new moon and the full moon,
a young girl is selected to be the priestess.
She is broken, raped, and shamed greatly.
With the village being my hometown,
I, Yamazaki Suzuko, returned here as a teacher.
My mother was a former priestess.
To exact revenge for the hurt that still resides within her,
I vowed in my heart to put an end to this custom.
However, without a chance to resist,
I was selected as a priestess,
and was turned into a disgraceful sex slave.
The one controlling these ceremonies was...
the student council president of
Rinin High, Tamura Motoko.
The group that carries out this ceremony is called...
The Gang Rape Club.
The Gang Rape Club
Ep 2: The Fallen Aiko and Yamanaka Tomomi
Shit, Yamanaka sure is cute.
I heard she won the prefecture's tournament, right?
That's freaking amazing.
Dammit... The pussy underneath that leotard.
I wanna fuck it up with my dick!
Goddammit!
I'm really jealous of Tanoue, who gets to
do whatever he wants with that pussy.
Tanoue?
Tanoue-kun! Go for it!
She's dating Tanoue, the ace of the baseball team.
He's a star of the high school baseball league
and bound to go pro when he graduates.
She'd never even give us a second glance.
I'm sorry, Kenji-kun,
but this is a very important time for both of us.
I think we should wait until we graduate.
I guess you're right.
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry too.
Yamanaka Tomomi...
Tomomi...
Your brother is... your brother's dick is so...
Hard for you... for you, Tomomi...
Hey, are you sure?
That's right.
He says there's something he
wants to discuss with you alone.
Kenji-kun is in here?
Kenji-kun?
It's me, Tomomi.
Onii-chan? Where's Kenji-kun!?
Tanoue is probably playing a fun
game of baseball right now.
What's going on?
I'm leaving!
Stop it!
Let me go!
Tomomi...
Have you heard of the Gang Rape Club?
What's that?
I've never heard of it!
Let me go!
It's a custom that's been passed down
through the generations in this village.
If a relative, lover, or spouse writes
down a name on this paper,
the person whose name is written becomes the priestess.
And she is raped as a sacrifice.
Onii-chan... what are you talking about!?
Tomomi...
Your brother has been waiting for this day for a long time!
You haven't done it with Tanoue yet, right?
No!
Stop it!
The pussy that even Tanoue hasn't touched...
Onii-chan will take Tomomi's virginity!
No!
Onii-chan!
Idiot.
Your job ends here, Onii-cban.
Maki... Did something happen?
You haven't been yourself lately.
When I was at the pool the other day...
No, it's nothing.
Maki!
No matter what happens, I will protect you, Maki.
Motoko-chan...
I want you to remain pure white forever.
Motoko-chan?
Good going, Kenji. One more time!
Got it?
Don't you dare cry out.
Or your darling Tanoue will notice.
The school idol's ass is completely exposed.
Look, if you go like this...
you can see all of her asshole.
No! Don't!
Don't look at my butthole.
It's embarrassing!
Look, my finger's going in.
No!
Don't put it in!
I'm... being played with...
With Kenji-kun nearby.
There's a finger in my butthole.
Not even Kenji has touched me there.
I'll tweak the other one too.
Please, don't touch my pussy...
I told you not to cry out, or Tanoue will notice.
My voice is... coming out! No...
I can't let Kenji-kun see this...
If he does, I'll die!
She's already soaking wet!
Why? This hurts, but it feels good.
My pussy is releasing so much naughty juice.
She's getting aroused from being spanked.
That must be because of all the anal training we did.
We've turned the school idol into a bitch
who can't go on without anal stimulation.
It's about time we add this baby.
No way...
You get to lose your virginity to a bat.
I'm sure even Tanoue would approve.
No...
Please, just stop at my butthole.
Just give up.
We drew straws to see who would claim
your virginity, and Bat-kun won.
See? We'll use the thicker end as a special service.
Take it.
So she really was a virgin.
But I guess she would bleed from that even if she wasn't.
Like I care.
Here it goes.
This hurts... My mind is going blank!
What kind of face am I making right now?
I don't want Kenji to see my face like this.
But my pussy is... so wet.. and I can't... stop...
I need to pee... I need to pee!
Go ahead and piss yourself!
I'm cumming!
What's the matter?
Katsuragi-sensei.
Katsuragi Toshio-sensei is the guidance counselor here.
He's also Katsuragi Aiko's husband,
and Maki's father.
I was just checking over the DVDs that
were confiscated from the students.
Hey, are you sure this is okay?
Doing this to Suzuko-sensei after her
time as a priestess has ended?
It's fine.
After all, she's already been turned into a sex slave.
Yeah, but we'll piss off the president.
You think I'm gonna let her order us around forever?
I see...
Maybe the DVDs are porn.
And so...
Very well.
I'll watch them with you.
Fucking Katsuragi.
Try not to freak out when you watch those.
AV Room
Sorry about this.
Having to do this for my students...
Don't worry about it.
It's part of my duty as a guidance counselor.
What's this?
Look...
My butthole and my pussy are both full.
Just look.
See? You can see better at this angle, right?
I love being watched. It makes me feel good.
I get turned on!
Shit, what a fucking whore you are.
You're spreading your pussy wide and begging for it.
I've never seen a bitch this slutty.
Please, tease me!
Tease my ass a lot!
Sure, just like this!
Yes!
My pussy... My pussy feels so good!
I can't take it anymore!
Dick... I want a dick...
I want a dick in my pussy!
Put your dick in me!
Aiko...
Aiko-sensei?
Now, hurry up and fuck me!
Give me cock.
What's that? What's going on?
What a hot woman! I feel bad getting her for free.
Aiko-sensei, how much do you cost?
1000 yen. 1000 yen per person.
Hey, did ya hear?
She'll let you plow her pussy for just 1000 yen.
What a cheap pussy she's got.
I like it.
1000 per person is my price.
Just hurry up and plow me with your dicks!
Fingers just won't cut it.
I want a dick fast.
Oh, shit. I guess we don't have a choice!
I had no idea she'd change so much
just from becoming priestess.
She must've really been starving for it.
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming in broad daylight...
I'm looking so nasty in front of everyone...
Charging just 1000 per person...
To have tons of dicks thrust into rne...
I'm cumming!
I can't stand it! This bitch is too hot!
My tits... Grab my tits too!
What's with these nasty tits?
They've been squeezed so much, they're all saggy.
Squeeze them!
Squeeze my saggy tits!
I want them to be squeezed!
Squeeze my tits... Squeeze them a lot.
My nipples, my nipples feel so good...
I love it when my nipples get stretched!
I'm melting!
My tits, my tits can't stand it...
The nipples on my sagging tits are hard like rocks!
Squeeze them hard... Make them hard!
Squeeze them and pull them!
Yes, that's right.
I'm cumming from my tits!
Who cums from having their tits squeezed?
Hurry up and cum from the cock fucking your pussy!
Your cock... I love your cock...
I love having a cock in my pussy...
My insides are being stirred up by a cock!
I'm cumming!
I can't hold it anymore!
Open your mouth!
It feels good to be violated all over.
I've been violated by your cocks.
Your dicks have completely messed me up!
My pussy... Yes...
Please, fuck up my hole...
Handjobs are only 200 yen...
Mom!
Maki...
Oh, no... Mom, why?
Come on, watch carefully.
If you're a girl born in this town,
that might happen to you someday.
N-No...
I'm so aroused.
To have my daughter watch as tons
of dicks are shoved into me!
Having my daughter watch me doing such things...
I'm... feeling it!
Mom...
I'm cumming! Cumming! Cumming!
Maki, watch me.
Watch your mother cum, as tons of dicks are
shoved in her, and she becomes a sex slave!
No!
Oh, I'm going to get pregnant.
With so much semen inside of me...
I won't know whose semen it is...
I won't know whose child it is...
A baby...
I'll get pregnant!
No!
Come on!
Your daughter is watching.
Maki-chan, I need to have my pussy plowed some more.
So wait just a bit longer.
Look forward to the fourth one.
K-Katsuragi-sensei...
No matter how promising your future...
No matter how much you're in love...
If you are a girl born in this village,
there is no escaping your fate.
No matter what sort of tragedy that will result in...
Please...
Just let me go.
Stop doing such despicable things to me!
Don't be stupid.
You still haven't had a real dick in you yet.
Stop... don't do... nasty things.
Shit, you're still in high school, so why are your tits so huge?
That hurts! Stop it!
Just look. We used to only be able
to dream about doing this,
but now we're able to squeeze the school
idol's tits as much as we want!
They're so huge!
And her nipples are hard.
No!
Don't suck on my breasts!
Wow! Tomomi-chan, your tits taste like milk.
My nipples... Not my nipples...
Please, not that!
Or I'll... I'll...
Or you'll do what?
I can't say such embarrassing things out loud...
Then I guess we'll have to see what's
going on down there ourselves.
Wow, you're already soaked.
No! Don't say that!
You guys wanna see Tomomi's pussy?
Yeah!
Do you wanna thrust your dicks into it?
Tomomi-chan!
Then let's show them.
No!
Wow!
Awesome!
Do as you please.
Don't do it!
Don't suck it!
Now...
Time to thrust a dick inside.
No!
Please! Don't put it in!
My... Kenji hasn't even seen it yet.
I see. So you want Tanoue to see?
Bring him out.
Let's bring him face to face with reality.
Kenji-kun... Please, don't watch!
Don't watch!
Let's treat you to your first dick while Tanoue watches.
No!
Tanoue, it's gone in.
Don't put it in!
It feels gross...
It doesn't feel good...
Not at all...
If it's not Kenji-kun's penis,
then I won't... feel good!
How much longer will you last?
It doesn't feel... doesn't feel good...
Come on.
No...
No... Don't...
Come on, say it.
Say it feels good.
It doesn't... feel...
It's hitting me... so deep...
Cry louder.
Stop!
I'm being raped...
My pussy is... releasing naughty... juices...
No...
My pussy...
is getting fucked up...
My pussy... stop doing that to my pussy... No!
So much dick in me... makes me...
Oh no!
I can't... No!
Stop it!
Oh no...
Not inside...
My pussy is full...
I'll get... pregnant...
Does it feel good?
Not at all...
Won't you say it?
If you don't say it, we'll stop.
No... No...
Don't stop...
Well, what do you want us to do?
My pussy...
I want my pussy fucked more, please!
Did you hear that?
She's turned into a sex slave.
Yes, I'm a sex slave.
Tomomi...
Come on, let him see your naughty face.
No! Don't watch!
Kenji-kun, don't look at me!
I don't want you to see me like this!
Tanoue, are you watching?
Tomomi's pussy juice is spilling everywhere.
No...
Your dick...
This dick is so...
Thick, hard, and hot...
My pussy is being stirred up!
No... it's too good...
Being fucked is... a dick being put inside...
The dick is hitting so deep inside.
And it feels so good!
My pussy is getting fucked by a penis.
My tits... not my tits!
My nipples... are getting crushed...
Milk will... Milk will come out!
My tits are being squashed...
If you keep doing that, I'll...
I'll cum out of my tits!
I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Spray it on her.
On no...
Don't watch me like this...
Don't...
My insides... are so full... nothing more will fit...
We filled these vials full of our semen just for this day.
Be sure to fill yourself up
No...
I'll die.
No!
I can't hold back anymore!
Hold it!
I can't!
It's coming out.
It's going to come out of me!
Okay, fine.
We have to give Tanoue a better view.
God, no...
Come on. This is your toilet.
Show your boyfriend.
Kenji-kun! Don't! Don't!
It's coming out... It's coming out!
I can't hold back...
I'm pooing... I'm pooing...
The semen is going to be pooped out!
It's... It's coming!
It's coming out!
No!!
It's coming out of my butthole!
Kenji-kun, I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
I'm sorry...
If it's impossible to put an end to the old customs,
then I shall become those customs myself.
Wait for me, Tamura Motoko.