Since the age of mythology,
There's a princess who's like a flower's blossom,
who got married to the descendant of god,
Iwanaga Hime, who also married him along with her beautiful sister.
Just because she was ugly, she was the only one who got ignored.
From then on, Iwanaga cursed her beautiful sister and her descendants.
To protect ones self from the worst scenario caused by the curse,
When it's the dawn of the new moon and full moon in this town...
The maiden who's like the flower blossom princess,
is brought out for public opinion, meaning gang rape.
They've been doing this ritual to ease her rage.
The name of the town is Rin'in.
The place where I was born.
And the one who administers this ritual is called the Rinkan Club.
Rinkan Club
1st Story. Yamazaki Suzuko and Katsuragi Aiko
You're beautiful, Sensei.
You're like the reincarnation of the flower blossom princess.
You guys, ruin her more.
If it stays like this, Iwanaga Hime's rage will not ease.
This is not how it was supposed to be...
A few days ago
After I graduated from college, I became a teacher of a private school in Tokyo,
And came back to this town after 8 years.
I'm Yamazaki Suzuko, I'll be your adviser starting today, nice to meet you.
Wow... she's beautiful!
She's a beautiful teacher.
The reason I came back is to take care of my mom.
But I have another reason.
I have something important to do in this town.
Tamura Motoko-san.
You're the president of the student council, Tamura-san right?
Yes, I am.
And your other title, you're the president of Rinkan club.
I'm going to stop you from continuing what you're doing!
Remember that!
Sensei, you're from this town, right?
Why?
You're asking me why?
That's because it's a foolish thing!
Doing a ritual in this era?
Don't you think it's strange?
I'm a believer.
When I was young, my mom was raped.
No... no... no...
No!
My mom wanted to die but she couldn't.
Since then, her body has been weak.
You can't turn me into a maiden.
To be a maiden,
You must be blood related, a spouse or your lover
must write your name in the people names card.
That was the condition, right?
My blood relatives will never write my name.
I'll remember that.
I've done my effort to stop the rituals of the Rinkan club,
But no one in this town wants to help me.
Tamura-san, is she absent again today?
Calling me to such a place, what do you want from me?
What have you been doing instead of coming to school?
Sensei, I want you to watch this.
You went to Tokyo?
You're Tamura Motoko-san, right?
I'm surprised, you came here from the province where Suzuko-san lived.
I've heard a lot about you from Sensei.
So I wanted to meet you after I came to Tokyo.
I just called Sensei from her place.
How is Suzuko-san?
She's fine.
Oh no...
Sensei, you're naive.
You're telling me that you'll destroy the Rinkan club, but you have a boyfriend in Tokyo.
W-Why?
I haven't contacted him since I came here.
He's so kind.
When I said if you write your loved one's name, according to the legend of the town,
You'll have a happy life in the future...
N-No...
He gladly wrote this.
And what's wrong about that?
That has nothing to do with me.
If you're born in this town, you must obey the custom of this town.
And if you won't become a maiden while you're alive, Sensei, you'll be...
I don't understand what you're saying, let go of me!
I'll make Yamazaki Suzuko into a maiden!
I said no!
No! S-S-Stop it.
I'll report you to the police!
It's no use in this town.
N-No wa-
Wow! It's Yamazaki-sensei's boobs!
Let me touch them too!
Let them go!
I'm getting a very nice smell from this part of you, Sensei.
Stop it.
I'll smell your ass-hole too.
No!
These guys trained their bodies at Masurao falls last night.
Let me purify your body, Sensei.
Here we go!
No... Don't... Stop it!
Stop it!
Even if you do that...
You're a tough one.
I think it's better to use that one...
St... op... it...
What? My body has become hot-
It's an herb that has been used in the ritual since a long time ago.
Your mom was also a tough one but when she drank that,
She turned into such a dirty whore.
S-So you're the ones who raped my mom...
Oh your hips are already moving, Sensei.
It doesn't feel good at all-
Hey, if you move that wildly, his face will be smashed.
Isn't it time?
Now Sensei, lets start this.
No. Don't, don't!
Suzuko-san is too much for me.
She's beautiful and my inspiration.
Why don't we send her a video letter?
P-Please stop it, please!
What? A video letter?
Why don't you tell her right now?
Please... Please forgive me!
Ok, let her hear your feelings then.
Ok then...
Suzuko-san, how are you?
I'm fine here.
While you're there taking care of your mom,
I'm doing my best here to become a respectable chef.
We can't meet easily...
But as promised, I'll become a respected chef in 3 years,
And I'll come pick you up.
Now, we're far from each other but I feel that were always linked.
It's so good... I'm about to cum...
It's hard for us right now, but we must over come this.
Do... Don't let it out~!!!
Wow! That's nice.
How many kids do you want?
What?! Oh, well... uhm... I want 3.
I'm sure you two will give birth to cute babies.
Is that so? Thank you.
Then here's for the last promise.
Suzuko-san, I think I'm about to reach something,
So I promise that I'll become a great man and come pick you up.
No a baby... a baby will be made...
So do your best too Suzuko-san.
I'll write you a letter again later.
Is that all? Come on add more.
Suzuko-san, I love you.
I love you.
You're beautiful, Sensei.
You're like the reincarnation of the flower blossom princess.
Remember this...
You guys, ruin her more.
N-No!!
Take this off... Please take this off!
I'll come here again when dawn comes.
Please change your attitude by the time I come back.
Remember this, I won't lose...
Motoko-chan, have you heard what happened to Suzuko-sensei?
Maki?
Sensei is absent.
They can't contact her.
Is that so?
I hope nothing happened to her, but I'm a bit worried.
You're kind, Maki.
Eh?
I feel at ease when I see you, Maki.
Eh? Is that so?
But I'm happy to hear Motoko-chan say that.
Don't worry.
I'm sure Sensei is alright.
That's...
She's Yamanaka Tomomi-chan, a first year.
She's the gymnast representative from the prefecture.
That's why...
She is good in sports and she's cute like an idol,
And she's going out with Tagami-kun, the ace of the baseball club.
She's amazing.
She's really beautiful.
Like a flower that just bloomed.
Half a month from that day, I'm constantly getting raped by those men,
and I've became a whore who can't resist their lust.
T-Then, Katsuragi-san, read this line.
Since the age of mythology...
But I still haven't given up...
And then, the day for me to be the next maiden had come...
I'm a woman from this town,
so I understand the meaning behind you guys coming here in that attire.
Katsuragi Aiko, the only doctor in this small town,
Tamura Motoko's best friend, Katsuragi Maki's mom.
But I won't let you touch Shiori and Maki.
... They'll never become maidens...
Don't misunderstand.
You're the one we'll rape right now.
No way. Who did this?
Mamoru?!
I'm sorry mom.
This boy shoplifted and didn't want to be reported to the police so he wrote your name.
You want to make this old woman into a maiden?
Well, we can't hold it any longer...
Yeah, we can't hold it any longer.
I can't wait for the hanging boobs.
Yeah can't wait!
Shut up, keep quiet for a moment.
Motoko-chan, so now you're the president of the Rinkan club.
I understand.
I don't have any choice if Mamoru is under you.
But in exchange, don't you dare touch Shiori and Maki.
Please.
I can't change the rules, even if I'm the president of Rinkan-club.
Is this all you've got? You guys are no good.
Y-You bitch, hey let her drink the herb.
Drink this you old bitch.
H-How about this, you can't resist, eh?
Here you go, the high speed piston.
I-It's so good.
Shot it already, it hurts.
I'm cumming!
You're no good.
You're a 100 years too early to mess with me!
Y-You old bitch!
Stop it!
This Sensei is not a bitch who you guys can settle down.
No... stop...
Clip the clit using the thumb and index finger,
middle and ring finger into pussy and pinky into ass...
It's no use, I wont feel anything from anyone who rapes me...
How long can you keep saying such things?
This part, huh?
Next one is this, I'll give you my penis.
Aiko's pussy is sucking me!
Don't say such dirty things!
It feels good, right?
I-I don't feel anything good.
A lot of juice is still flowing out from Aiko's pussy.
No... stop that...
These drooping boobs, I want to suck them.
D-Don't say drooping.
No stop, I've never tried anal... no!
Don't... my ass... not my ass... I don't like anal.
I knew it, the town's head didn't do it to you.
You can't...
You have the body of slut!
No...
Take it out... stop this foolish thing!
No!!!
I'm next!
No, it's me!
Hurry, let me do it.
Ok, don't be in a rush, just wait.
No...
S-Stop...
No! I'm going to break!
Aiko-sensei, think about what happened to you,
How good you felt.
Then, Iwanaga Hime will be very happy.
I don't feel good at all.
You won't feel good when you're being raped!
You won't become a maiden if you don't accept it in your heart.
I wont feel anything like this.
Even though you say that, your nipples have gotten hard.
N-No... don't touch my nipples...
You like this, huh?
No... no not the nipples...
No... no...
My nipples and pussy feel so good...
The boobs, the nipples, the pussy... they feel... they feel so good.
Yes... harder... put it into Aiko's pussy harder.
Wow! So this is Aiko-sensei.
Tease the pussy more...
Do the pussy more...
We've done a lot.
No, we're still lacking.
Please suck this...
Hello?
Hello? Motoko-chan?
You know, my mom isn't around today,
She's gone out because of some urgent business.
Mamoru also went to his friend's house,
So how about coming over to eat dinner?
Motoko-chan?
I'll come.
Good, can you come right now?
Yes.
Alright!
Oh by the way, have you heard the weird rumor?
Motoko-chan, is she coming?
Yes, she'll come soon.
And about the rumor, have you heard about the Rinkan club?
I think it's just a rumor, but if it's true, then it's quite scary, right?
Yes, it is...
Kenji-kun, please forgive me.
Tomomi, has put so many penises inside...
M-Maki... Aiko...
M-Mom!
I've been seen, I've been seen by my daughter!
My pussy has been played with!
Rinkan club and Tamura Motoko, I will never forgive you!