Long ago,
the beautiful Konohana Sakuyahime
descended from the heavens.
Iwanaga Hime, who accompanied her beautiful younger sister,
was sent back alone merely because she was considered ugly.
Iwanaga laid a curse upon her beautiful younger sister
and all of her descendants that remains until this day.
So in order to protect their bodies and souls from this curse,
a ceremony is performed when a new or full moon occurs.
Upon this mountaintop, a beautiful maiden,
serving in the role of the priestess, is violated thoroughly.
The ceremony is conducted in order to quell Iwanaga's rage.
The name of this village is Rinin.
It is the place of my birth.
And the group responsible for carrying
out this ceremony is called...
The Gang Rape Club.
The Gang Rape Club
Ep 1: Yamazaki Suzuko and Katsuragi Aiko
You are so pretty, Sensei.
It's almost as if you're the true
reincarnation of Konohana Sakuyahime.
Boys, be sure to mess up our dear Sensei even more.
At this rate, we'll never appease Iwanaga Hime's rage.
This isn't how it was supposed to be...
Several Days Ago
After graduating from college and
teaching at a private school in Tokyo,
I returned to this village after an eight year absence.
Yamazaki Suzuko
Starting from today, I will be your homeroom teacher.
My name is Yamazaki Suzuko.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
She's so pretty.
I came home in order to care for my sick mother.
But there's also another reason for my return.
There is something that I must take care of in this village.
Tamura Motoko-san?
You're Tamura, the student council president, right?
Yes, I am.
And your other title is...
President of the Gang Rape Club.
I vow to put a stop to what you're doing!
Don't you forget it!
You were born in this village, weren't you, Sensei?
Then why?
You're asking why?
Because it's absolutely absurd!
Performing such ceremonies in this day and age!?
Don't you think it's perverse?
They are religious practices.
When I was young, my mother was chosen as a priestess.
No!
No! No!
My mother...
My mother wanted to die, but she couldn't.
Since then, her body has been weak.
You can try to make me your priestess, but you will fail.
To become a priestess, a blood relation, a spouse,
or a lover must write down your name.
That's the condition, correct?
And my only living blood relative
would never write down my name.
I'll keep that in mind.
From that point on, I made stopping
the Gang Rape Club my goal.
But not a single person in the village joined me in my cause.
Tamura-san... is she absent today?
Why did you call me out here?
What did you do while skipping school?
I wanted you to see this, Sensei.
You were in Tokyo?
You're Tamura Motoko-san, right?
I'm surprised.
To think that a student from Suzuko's
hometown would come looking for me.
Sensei has told us so much about you, so I just
had to meet you while I was here in Tokyo.
Sensei gave me your address.
Is Suzuko-san doing well?
Yes, very well!
This can't be...
Sensei, you're so naive.
You're trying to stop the Gang Rape Club, yet you
have a lover waiting for you back in Tokyo.
H-How?
I haven't contacted him at all since moving here!
He's a very nice man.
When I told him that, according to our village's legend,
writing down the name of his lover
would grant her a happy life...
No!
Well...
He was more than happy to write down your name.
And what do you intend to do with that?
This has nothing to do with me!
Those who were born in this village
must adhere to its customs.
And if you don't become a priestess
during your lifetime, you'll be...
What are you saying? I don't understand!
Let go of me!
Yamazaki Suzuko, you shall become our priestess!
I'm telling you, I don't want to!
N-No! Stop it!
I'll sue you all!
Doing so would be futile in this village.
N-No!
Yamazaki-sensei's tits!
Hey, let me have a feel too!
Let go of me!
Sensei's emitting a lovely, exotic smell from this spot!
Let me smell her asshole too.
These men cleansed their bodies at Masura Falls last night.
Now we must cleanse your body as well, Sensei.
Here we go!
No! Stop it!
Stop it!
Do you really think doing this will help the village?
What a stubborn woman.
I suppose we're going to have to use that, after all.
What?
My body has become so hot...
It's a special herbal infusion that has been
used in this ceremony since ancient times.
Your mother was also a prude at first,
but once she drank some of that...
She became a bitch in heat.
Y-You were the ones who raped my mother!?
Oh, your hips are already starting to move,
Sensei.
No...
I-I would never... enjoy this...
Hey, if you get too wet, you'll make a mess of this guy's face.
I guess it's about time.
Okay, Sensei.
Let's begin.
No, no!
Suzuko-san is too good for someone like me.
She's beautiful, virtuous...
– Sensei is really special to me too.
– Stop it! No!
– Why don't we send her a video letter?
A video letter?
Yes!
She can watch it while she's away
to stave off her longing for you.
Have mercy! Mercy!
Well, let's get started.
Please start when you're ready.
Well, then...
Suzuko-san, are you doing well?
I'm doing quite well.
With you having moved away to take care of
your mother, and me having a live-in job,
we won't be able to see much of
each other for the next few years.
But as we promised, three years from now,
once I'm a man, I'll come get you.
– I'm... I'm sorry!
– I'm sorry!
We may be apart now, but...
As long as we remain in each other's
hearts, we'll always be together.
Awesome!
– This is a trial we must overcome together.
– Unreal!
And once we've endured this separation...
Don't cum inside me!
I want you to marry me.
Aww, that's so sweet.
How many children do you plan on having with her?
Huh? Oh... good question.
Three kids, I suppose.
I'm sure the two of you will have cute babies.
You think so? Thank you.
Well, one last thing!
– Suzuko-san, I feel like I'm learning so much.
– It's coming out...
I'll make sure I mature into a reliable man,
and then I'll come take care of you.
– No, I'll get pregnant...
– I'll get pregnant.
– Good luck with your work as well
I'll write to you again soon.
Is that all? Come on, come on.
Suzuko-san...
I love you.
You are so pretty, Sensei.
It's almost as if you're the true
reincarnation of Konohana Sakuyahime.
You'll pay for this!
Ravage her harder, guys.
No!
Take this out. Take this out!
When the sun rises, well return.
Hopefully you'll have changed your attitude by then.
This isn't over yet!
I won't let you beat me!
Motoko-chan, did you hear about Suzuko-sensei?
Maki?
Sensei is absent, but she hasn't told anyone why.
No one has been able to contact her.
Oh...
I just hope nothing serious has happened to her.
I'm worried about her.
Maki, you're so sweet.
Seeing you fills me with a sense of serenity.
That's so embarrassing!
But I guess I'm happy to hear that you
feel that way about me, Motoko-chan.
There's no need for you to worry.
I'm sure Sensei is fine.
Who is that?
That's Yamanaka Tomomi from class I.
She'll be representing our prefecture at the
next rhythmic gymnastics competition!
So that's why...
She's really talented at sports and she's pretty like a idol.
And what's more, she's dating the ace
of the baseball club, Tanami-kun.
She's just so cool!
You're right.
She certainly is beautiful.
Like a blooming flower.
From that day, those men continued
to soil me for half a month.
I have become their sex slave, unable to resist their desires.
T-Then, it's Katsuragi-san's turn, right? Please read the line.
Long ago, the gods...
But I haven't given up yet!
And now...
The day when the next priestess must be chosen has arrived.
I am a woman of this village.
So I know what you coming here in that attire means.
Katsuragi Aiko.
She is the only doctor in this small village.
She is also the mother of Katsuragi
Maki, Tamura Motoko's best friend.
But I won't let you lay a finger on Shiori or Maki.
I will never allow them to be chosen as the priestess.
Well, I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't misunderstand.
The one we're here to fuck right now...
is you!
How could this be? Who did this?
Mamoru?
Mom... I'm sorry!
We caught him shoplifting, you see.
And he didn't want us to report him to the cops.
You want to make an old lady like me a priestess?
Well, it's not like we really want to fuck an old lady.
Oh, man, so gross.
Her tits are all saggy.
I don't want to touch that!
Back off for a moment, guys. Just wait.
Motoko-chan, you're the president
of the Gang Rape Club now?
Fine, I understand.
If you have Mamoru, I suppose I have no choice.
But in exchange, don't you dare touch Shiori or Maki!
Please.
Despite being the president of the Gang Rape Club, I have
no say in who is chosen to carry out the ceremony.
Is this all you've got? You guys are pathetic!
This doesn't feel good at all!
Damn you!
Hey! Give her the drug!
Damn it!! Here, drink up, you old hag!
Well? Do you like it now?
Here you go!
Super-sonic pistons!
Whoa, this is so good.
Take it out already. It hurts.
Whoa...
You guys are pathetic.
You little punks think you have
what it takes to mess with me?
You're a hundred years too early for that.
Y-You fucking old hag!
Stop it!
This doctor is too much for you guys to deal with.
S-Stop...
The thumb and index squash the bean.
The middle finger and ring finger go inside the pussy.
And the pinky goes...
It's of no use!
No matter what any of you do to me,
you'll never be able to make me feel good!
Do you think you'll be able to keep that act up for long?
How about this?
And up next...
I'll bury my dick inside you.
Your pussy is squeezing me.
Stop shouting such obscene things!
It feels good, doesn't it?
I don't think it feels good at all!
Juice is still flowing out from your pussy.
No way... it's like a flood...
S-Stop it...
Her saggy breasts are so soft.
No, don't say that!
Stop it!
I've never done that!
Not my butt! Not in my butt!
Stop it!
Not in my pussy or my butt!
I knew it! Your husband doesn't fuck you anymore, does he?
That's...
Your nasty body has been going to waste.
No! Stop teasing me...
You're spouting bullshit!
I'm up next!
No, it's my turn!
Then hurry up and get it over with!
Right, I got this.
I'll show her a good time.
No...
No! I'll break!
Aiko-sensei, please think about what is happening to you,
and how good it feels.
If you do, Iwanaga Hime will surely be pleased.
I don't feel good at all!
Being raped could never feel good!
If you can't accept it in your heart,
you'll never be a proper priestess.
I'll never feel pleasure from this! I won't!
You say that, but look at how hard
your nipples have become.
N-No!
Don't pinch them!
You like this, don't you?
N-No!
Not... Not my nipples!
No... No...
My pussy is full of...
It feels good!
My breasts, my nipples, and my pussy...
Everything...
feels good!
Yes!
My pussy loves this!
Send me to hell!
Wow, this is awesome!
So this is Aiko-sensei's true colors!
My pussy... My pussy is hungry for more!
Fill my pussy up completely!
Are you almost finished?
No, this isn't nearly enough!
Perform fellatio on me!
Hello?
Hello, Motoko-chan?
Listen, my mom's not home today.
She went out to run some errands a while ago.
And Mamoru is over at a friend's house as well.
So if you'd like, how about coming
over to have dinner with me?
Motoko-chan?
Sure, I'll come.
That's great! Can you come right now?
Sure.
Okay!
By the way, Motoko-chan, have you heard that
weird rumor that's been floating around?
Is Motoko-chan coming?
Yep! She said she'll be here soon!
Have you heard of something called the Gang Rape Club?
I think it's just a rumor, but it'd be scary
if it turned out to be true, wouldn't it?
Yeah, it would be...