Rinin is a small town within the mountains.
This is where a wicked tradition continues.
In order to appease the local deity Iwanagahime,
Young woman are appointed shrine maidens.
Every night of the new moon and full moon,
they are to be violated, in other words,
they are subjected to a gang rape.
I, Yamazaki Suzuko, came back here to my hometown to be a teacher,
and for my mother who had been living in despair,
ever since she was violated as a shrine maiden.
I vowed to put an end to this tradition.
However,
without any means of resisting,
I was made into a shrine maiden,
and became a despicable sex animal.
The group who were leading those rituals was,
the Rinkan Club.
The person actually leading the entire thing,
is Rinin High School's student council president,
Tamura Motoko.
The very person who threw me into this pit of Hell.
I will not forgive that woman.
I never will.
This is it.
I finally found it.
I can finally send that woman to hell with this.
Rinkan Club
Episode 04: Maki and Motoko
In order to save Aiko sensei,
Shiori sensei became the shrine maiden.
Though I heard that, she is no longer one,
as there is a newly appointed shrine maiden.
Just who in the world is the new shrine maiden?
Maki...
The one most precious to me.
I will protect you no matter what.
The children that were conceived through the rituals,
are treated as treasures of Rinin and are well taken care of.
As long as I am at the center of this ritual,
I will not let them do as they please.
Members of the Rinkan Club?
I'm going to get to the bottom of this.
Motoko-chan,
good morning.
Motoko-chan?
I will protect you, Maki.
Yes, thank you.
Let’s go now, Motoko-chan.
Homeroom will start soon.
Excuse me, do you know where Katsuragi-san is?
Is she absent?
Are you looking for Maki?
She just ditched classes.
She has been ditching for almost an entire month now.
She can just quit if she really wants to.
Did she really do that?
Could she be...?
That voice, could it be...?
Out of the way!
Who made her the shrine maiden?!
Yes, this is it.
Shove it in deeper!
Suck on it nicely.
And don't leave a single drop.
Her mouth pussy is just the best!
I'm going to cum now.
Swallow it all.
Maki!
No, no, no!
My Maki... My Maki is...!
Release her right now!
I never approved of this.
You can't do that president.
Let me go.
What a wonderful sentiment.
Protecting the women in this town so that none
of them would easily become a shrine maiden.
Maki!
Do you want it?
Do you want my cum?
Stop!
Do not cum inside her!
Don't you dare taint her!
I want it.
Please give me all your sticky and smelly cum!
Maki, no!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out.
All of the cum that was poured inside me this morning,
it's all pouring out while I cum!
Maki!
I'm next.
Clean it up well.
Start with the underside.
Okay.
Well, does it stink?
Yes, it's very smelly.
Of course.
I didn't wash it for one week just for the school's idol.
Thank you very much.
I will clean this big dick with my mouth.
This feels really great!
It's coming out!
Don't swallow it yet.
Open your mouth and show it to me.
Savor it well.
Show it to me again.
Mix it up in your mouth some more.
Okay, then swallow it slowly.
Show it to me again.
Maki...!
This ass hasn't learned any manners.
It's twitching as if it wants a dick inside it.
No, please don't look at it that much.
Oh wow, both of my holes are getting filled.
Which do you prefer?
Say it.
Both.
I love both of them!
I can't just choose one of them!
You're really a slut.
And you're supposed to be the pure idol!
I'm still an idol right now.
I'm currently feeling very horny with
these two dicks drilling inside me,
but I'm still everyone's idol!
What's with these rather small breasts?
It's very different from your sister's.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing my best.
I'll work hard to make my breasts as voluptuous as Onee-chan's!
No...
It hurts a bit.
If you open my ass that wide, it will become loose.
It is a bit loose already.
Try to tighten it again.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for making my holes loose.
They're cumming inside me.
Their cum is seeping into me.
My Maki is... why...?
Now Maki-chan,
why don't you greet your beloved president?
Hello Motoko-chan.
I'm here with everybody and I'm very happy.
I'm glad to be a shrine maiden.
Maki!
Because she resisted becoming a shrine maiden,
we subjected her to an entire month of hell.
What did you do to Maki?
Now, let's watch.
The miracle,
from the pure Maki-chan, to the current dick-loving sex pig.
Okay I'll be taking your virginity.
No...!
No!
I just love that scream of yours.
Let me hear more of that.
It hurts, stop!
I'm going to make you love dicks as soon as possible.
No!
I’m cumming.
I'm going to cum inside your virgin pussy.
No, no, no.
Please not inside!
Look, a moment that you'll never forget.
Smile now.
It's already getting this wet.
What a naughty girl.
I'm sorry.
But... it feels good...
No...
I'm cumming... no!
Good for you, Maki-chan!
Your cumming expression is just pure gold!
Congratulations.
Nice view here.
I can't believe that the school idol would expose herself like this.
Th-This is embarrassing.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Say it.
We're going to do something worse if you don't.
Please let me use the toilet.
Hey, the idol wants to use the toilet.
Looks like we'll get to see something good.
We're going to watch carefully so don't worry.
Eh? Here?
Of course.
Just pee already.
If you don't,
we'll just have to let Katsuragi-sensei pee for us.
Please don't involve her in this anymore!
Then you get it already, right?
She's really peeing!
Here's a nice view to take a picture of.
Please, don't take pictures.
For the pure Maki-chan to be this slutty...
I'm about to cum just by looking at her!
No, if you're cumming, then please do it inside me.
My mouth would be fine.
Maki-chan, I'm cumming!
She just peed.
You've just soiled the table!
Be sure to clean it up by licking it, okay?
That's the president's tablet, you know.
Motoko-chan, I'm sorry.
I wanted to rape you before so badly.
Thrust it in me more!
Stir up my pussy more!
Here, have a good taste.
Your dick tastes good.
I love dicks!
This is...
More, give me more of your cum.
Don't get too cheeky just because you're popular in school.
You're best it to provide sexual satisfaction to all the boys.
Serves you right.
I'm cumming!
There, raise your head,
and smile.
Where's the pure school idol now?
She now just a slutty sex pig.
Hey sex pig, face here.
Yes...
What's wrong?
You're usually more calm and composed than that.
Why are you here?
I have something to show you.
I, Yamazaki Suzuko,
hereby appoint Tamura Motoko as a shrine maiden.
The only ones who can appoint shrine maidens,
are either the headperson, or a close family member.
You are not qualified.
Look at these.
These are special birth certificates for appointees.
The first one is yours, the other is mine.
Is there something on them?
Look at this.
The name of your father is written here.
And the name of my father is...
No-No way...
That's right.
The man that impregnated my mother,
and the man that impregnated your mother,
are one and the same.
That can't be.
We we're born through different mothers,
but nevertheless are blood-related.
I have the full right to appoint you as a shrine maiden.
I am more than qualified.
That can't be.
You're lying!
This is some sort of a mistake!
Now everyone, rape her to your heart's content.
Make her body crave for dicks forever!
B-Back off!
I'm the Rinkan Club's president.
The headperson of this entire group.
Your lives are forfeited the moment you defy me!
I really wanted to bathe you in my cum for a long time.
That model student face of yours, we'll make
it into a stupefied one in no time.
St-Stop!
No!
Rock, paper, scissors!
I-I won!
You big ball of fat!
President, your pussy stinks like the smell of cheese.
Do-Don't sniff it, you beast!
No!
Stop!
Don't!
Stop that!
Shut up.
Just lick my dirty dick.
I just got her to fellate me first!
So, how's the taste of your first cock?
It tastes bad and it's the worst!
You're about to make this dirty dick cum
with your mouth pussy though.
Here!
St-Stop! Stop that!
I'm going to take your virginity!
Stop!
I'm now one with Motoko.
Don't call me by my name, you pervert pig!
Your filthy dick doesn't feel good at all!
Motoko, if you keep squeezing me like that,
I'm going to...!
D-Don't cum inside!
Don't cum.
I'm going to cum now.
No!
Isn't that good for you Motoko?
Your virgin pussy just got a big load of cum right from the start.
My, such a scary expression.
To make it up to you, here's a little gift.
Wha-What are you going to do?
An aphrodisiac that will make everything feel good.
I'm going to make you horny.
St-Stop!
I'll give you a shot here as well.
I'm going to carve all of my hatred into your body.
No!
I'm actually inside the pussy of our great president!
I-I'm not going to yield to this!
This just means that you president, are
also nothing more than a sex pig.
I'm the council president of Rinin Academy!
The headperson of the Rinkan Club!
I-I'm not getting horny from all of this!
Motoko...
You look really unsightly with that cum all over you.
Your "sister" is very proud of you.
Remember this,
I'll never forgive all of you, you who have tainted Maki and...
You truly are the worst.
Tarnura Motoko, the school's council president,
will be leaving her position as of today.
Her health has not been that well over the past few days.
If this were to continue, it might cause a negative
effect on the activities of the student council.
With that, I would like to announce that I will
temporarily take over her responsibilities,
along with all the other duties that is related
to a student council president.
Now, Tamura-san, please give everyone a greeting.
Not healthy? Why, she's pregnant already!
Under that calm and composed expression, lies
someone who'd do just what she wants, huh?
Umm, I am no longer able to perform my duties as council president,
I truly have caused trouble for everyone.
My thanks to everyone who followed me till the end.
I-I fulfilled my promise already.
Now let me go to the toilet!
Yes, you truly have worked hard till now.
Anyway, what's with this belly?
I-I can't, hold it in... anymore...
It won't stop!
It just keeps coming out!
This feels great!
Everyone's watching,
and this is embarrassing,
yet it feels great!
I'm cumming while taking a poop!
Pooping feels so good.
I want to do it again...
Half a year has passed since Tamura Motoko became a shrine maiden.
Because of her status now as a shrine maiden,
the Rinkan Club eventually fell apart.
That's because, Tamura Motoko, Katsuragi
Maki, Akamura Shiori, and Katsuragi Aiko,
are now appointed as shrine maidens for life.
There will be no other shrine maidens besides them.
If any one of them dies,
The child that they give birth to,
will be appointed as the new shrine maiden.
That's what has been decided.
From now on...
...all of them will be raped forever and ever as a shrine maiden.
For them however, that won't seem to be a bad life.
My vengeance has been exacted.
Now you can finally rest in peace, Mother.
This is a town in the middle of the mountains.
The town of Rinin.
This was formerly the town where a wicked tradition
of sacrificing maidens to be raped was practiced.
www. pixy-soft. com