There's a small town within the mountains
known as, Rinin.
They conduct a foul tradition that must be stopped.
In order to appease the anger of Iwanagahime,
each new and full moon of every month,
young women are appointed as Shrine Maidens.
They are then violated.
In other words, they're gang raped.
I, Yamazaki Suzuko,
came back here to my hometown to be a teacher
for the sake of my mother who has been living in despair.
Ever since she was violated as a Shrine Maiden,
I vowed to put an end to this tradition.
However,
with no resistance,
I've become a Shrine Maiden.
Call me a despicable sex animal.
The person leading the rituals is
Rinin High School's Student Council President:
Tamura Motoko.
The Rinkan Club is responsible for handling the rituals.
Episode 3: Shiori and Maki
Nakamura-sensei...
Mother...
Finish it quickly.
It's still not over?
Infirmary
Get in line properly!
A-Aiko-sensei...
Here...
I heard that if I give you this,
you'll do a lot of things for me...
Then take it off.
What a stinky cock.
You left it unclean for a while, didn't you?
That's filthy!
E-Everyone said that you'd like it more if I leave it like that.
That's why I...
Where did you hear that?
And you want me to suck on this stinky cock?
Yes...
Everyone said that I can just order it, so...
What are you going to make the doctor do?
E-Eat my cum while titty-fucking me...
You old hag...
If you say that...
Eat my cum quickly, you old hag.
Fine.
It stinks.
It's like the smell of bad cheese.
It's spreading out,
but I just can't get enough of this.
It's good.
The thick cum left on a dirty cock...
– It's really good...
– Old hag...
Let me eat it, all of it.
I want you to let me eat it.
This is good.
The liquid from a dirty cock...
I will take all of it.
Please pour lots of semen into my mouth...
D-Don't drink it yet, old hag.
You mustn't swallow it yet.
Show me the semen that's in your mouth.
Close it and taste it thoroughly.
Tastes good, right?
It's delicious.
Show it to me.
Do you want to drink it?
If you want to drink it, say that you want to.
Don't spill it.
I can't understand what you're saying!
I want to drink it!
I told you not to spill it!
You stubborn old hag.
Take this!
Delicious.
It's delicious!
I'm going to cum!
I'm happy.
I'm happy to get this much cum.
Here, I'm going to take a souvenir photo.
Widen up once more.
Smile!
Make a double peace sign!
Maki.
What's wrong?
You've been acting strange these past few days.
Talk to me, little sis.
Are you thinking about
the Rinkan club?
O-onee-chan...
Me, too.
I've at least heard stories about it.
Because I'm also a girl who was born and grew up in this town.
No way. Did Mom...
More!
Stir it up more.
I want my pussy to be stirred up.
Cocks...
Give me more...
In my pussy
and in my butt...
I-I'm cumming...
Semen's getting released into my mouth
while my butt's being raped!
I'm cumming!
Mom!
You...
What have you done?!
This has nothing to do with you, Nakamura-sensei.
Please leave.
Nothing to do with me?
She's my mother!
We are just doing it according to the traditions
that have been passed down.
Once chosen as a Shrine Maiden,
even if she is a teacher or a relative,
no one can save her.
Besides...
Don't stop.
Give me more cum.
It doesn't look like Aiko-sensei wants to be saved at all.
Mom, get a hold of yourself!
Let go of me!
You can't!
She can no longer be saved.
No.
I will save her.
Are you serious?
If that's what you think, then there's only one way.
Maki-chan...
Dad...
Tomonobe-san...
I'm sorry...
Give me one of those charms.
I'm going to appoint myself as a Shrine Maiden.
Nakamura Shiori
It's been a long time since Aiko-sensei
has been appointed a Shrine Maiden.
Haven't they decided on the next Shrine Maiden yet?
This is strange.
Why am I, the Rinkan Club's president, not receiving
any calls or messages from them?
Who in the world is the next Shrine Maiden?
The old hag was good,
but a young married woman isn't bad either.
Shut up.
Don't say a word!
Even if you say things like that, you like the feeling, don't you?
I don't like it at all!
Oh, then,
why don't we put this in?
No, stop!
Your pussy's now occupied, but
I also love this hole, you know.
Not that hole!
No...
Nakamura-sensei's breasts
feel really soft.
I've admired you for a very long time.
During class, I imagined the form of
your breasts under your clothes.
Like what color were your nipples...
I've been thinking about those kind of things for a long time.
You disgust me!
Nakamura-sensei...
Shiori...
So this is what your nipples look like...
Shiori's nipples are so pretty!
Stop!
Don't say that!
Whenever you wear those tight skirts,
the shape of your butt becomes very visible.
I've been... masturbating in class.
No...
I never thought I'd be able to cum inside Shiori.
I don't want this.
Stop.
Don't release it inside!
I'm going to cum inside.
I'm going to burst my semen inside your womb.
Don't...
Pull it out!
Release it outside!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to release my seed into Shiori's womb!
No, you can't!
Please! Please! Please! Please!
No!
You don't have to hate it,
because we've already released it many times inside.
What an amazing amount of cum.
How many times did we do it?
No...
No, I'm going to break.
So you're finally
realizing the good feeling?
Sensei...
Even if it feels great,
if you raise your voice,
students in the other clubs will hear you.
No.
– No!
– Hey, cover her mouth!
It's good.
It's good...
Shiori-sensei's mouth-pussy...
Oh, no.
I'm about to
cum!
It's still coming out.
I'm going to properly release it inside here.
I'm going to release it all inside and
not leave a single drop of it out
until you get pregnant!
No...
Stop.
I still haven't given birth to a child yet.
For me to have a child from the Rinkan club...
I don't want it!
I'm going to release it
inside your pussy!
No!
To be raped...
To be gang-raped...
To have my pussy get filled with cum...
while being impregnated...
I'm cumming!
Onee-chan,
you don't look well.
Are you all right?
I'm feeling a little tired,
because I have been quite busy these days.
But I'm okay.
It's all good, then.
Onee-chan?
I'm okay.
I'm sorry I have to show you something weird like this...
Onee-chan?!
What's that?
Onee-chan!
Don't look.
This is nothing...
Don't look!
You don't look fine at all!
You don't look fine...
Mom...
How are you feeling?
I'm fine now.
Don't worry.
The doctors said that I'm going to have a speedy recovery.
But...
you don't look happy.
There's nothing to worry anymore.
Mom's no longer a Shrine Maiden.
We're at a hospital in a nearby town,
so those people won't come.
I'm sorry.
I don't remember anything.
Why was I chosen as a Shrine Maiden...
What happened to me as a Shrine Maiden?
I can only remember parts of it.
Mom...
But...
My body remembers it.
If I get raped by someone again,
I might lose myself again.
Don't worry.
It's fine now.
How's Shiori?
She doesn't even come to visit anymore.
She seems to be busy with work.
But if its onee-chan, I'm sure it's okay.
It's okay...
My wife...
Did something happen to Shiori?
No...
There is something that you need to know.
Shiori?
What's wrong with her?
What are you all doing?
What?
Let me go!
Tomonabe-san,
I'm sorry.
Carnal toilet   Cum inside   100th time   Sex animal
Nakamura-sensei,
we've come to return your wife to you.
We told her there was a new Shrine Maiden,
so she can go home now, but...
She can't seem to leave.
A Shrine Maiden?
You're all from that Rinkan club?
Shiori has taken real good care of us.
We've already used her quite a lot.
What did you do to Shiori?
Do you want to know?
We're fine with that.
Hey.
Come on! No need to hold it in now.
Anyway, today we've had about fifty men cum inside her.
But we don't know how much cum
she had inside her before us.
Hey.
Tell him yourself as we instructed.
I had my pussy completely filled with cum.
Stop!
Every single day,
semen from a countless numbers of men
flowed into me.
Stop this!
Lots of cum got released inside my pussy,
and I also came all the way.
I am a lewd wife that feels joy
whenever semen fills me up.
I don't want this anymore!
Let me go home now!
It's not over yet.
Here, have a good look.
Here, I'm going to help you out.
So let it out quickly.
There, it's coming out...
I was raped so much in my butt,
and felt really good all the while.
I had my butt filled with cum for an
entire month by a lot of penises.
And finally this past week, they stopped using penises and...
And inserted this inside me...
Oh come now, Shiori-sensei,
you've soiled the school's floor. That means
Nakamura-sensei will be mad.
There.
I'm sorry...
Tomonabe-san...
It's a Shrine Maiden.
A new Shrine Maiden!
A new Shrine Maiden has come to the Rinkan club!
It's Maki!
It's Katsuragi Maki!
Damn, she's cute!
I've always wanted a chance with her.
New Shrine Maiden,
tell us your name.
I am now the new Shrine Maiden.
I am Katsuragi Maki.
Nice to meet you all.
I'm still a virgin.
G-Go ahead...
Please take good care of me.
Move it!
All of you move it!
Who is that?
Who did you appoint as a Shrine Maiden?!
You are finished, you sex pig!
Even our dear president's like this.
It's all over now.
I will remember this...