Our school utilizes the benefits of international
relationships with other schools.
We have many foreign exchange students here.
Oh, really?
But it certainly is unusual for us to have a
newly appointed teacher this time of year.
W-Well, that's...
The school's commissioner listened to my
difficult request, and I'm grateful for that.
Rinkan Gakuen
「Please stop it! Mom, don't look at me!」
Episode 1.
「Step on the chastity of the virgin and the MILF!」
Geez!
I'll be fine.
You really are a worrywart, Mom.
I'm not a child anymore.
Your Ai isn't...
Ai, you should use the phone later.
O-Oww!
Oh, you're ridiculous, Ai!
Yes, I'm doing well.
Don't worry about things on my end and
keep trying hard at your work, darling.
They were bouncy.
I guess I lose that contest.
Now, you mustn't stare at people like that!
It's poor etiquette.
When's dad coming home?
He said it won't be for a while.
Mom, are you lonely?
As long as you're here with me, Ai, I'm fine.
Huh? Daughter?
She married when she was still a student.
That's what I heard.
At school, you don't call me "mom", Ai.
I'm sorry.
Um... Thanks for helping me, Haruka-sensei.
The three-way meeting has been scheduled.
Tomorrow after school, okay?
Then I'll go tell Aihara-sensei about it.
Did you forget someth...
Do you know what tulips mean in flower language?
Aihara-sensei...
Yes, I do. That's why I like them.
They mean the same thing as my name.
In order to make flowers bloom beautifully,
we must care for them well.
Let me teach you how to care for them.
Isn't she a beautiful flower?
But we must continue to care for her like
this, otherwise she'll wither and die.
Th-This can't be!
I-It's a lie.
It must be a lie!
It has to be a lie!
Don't you think it's strange your mother
transferred jobs so suddenly?
She engaged in lewd acts with her students.
She's a model pedophile.
She must have been lonely being
apart from her husband.
But the reality of her actions at
school is not a good thing.
If the school's commissioner found out about it, the
best case scenario is she would be locked up.
I'm sure her teacher's credential will also be revoked.
Th-This can't be!
Isn't he great?
He's an exchange student from America.
He's the one in the photos.
Your mother says his dick feels particularly nice.
No!
Japanese chicks give
good head and I love it.
No...
Give head...
Just by sucking on his dick, he says he'll
keep your mother's actions a secret.
B-But I can't do that!
Aihara-sensei, where's the school
commissioner's office again?
We'd better tell your father, too.
I suppose he'll divorce her.
D-Divorce?
The commissioner's office is on the
first floor, farthest down the hall.
I'll do it!
I'll do it, I swear!
So please!
No...
I promise I'll do as you say.
I'll... I'll perform fellatio.
You need to say it in Japanese,
otherwise there's no point
in doing a foreign exchange.
Please let me suck it.
Suck what?
Your penis...
You mean his dick.
Your dick...
Let me suck your dick, please.
How dare you do this!
What are you trying to do!?
Please excuse us, we boys are going
through a curious sexual phase.
We want to learn a lot about you, Haruka.
Don't call me by my first name!
Like, we wanna know why you had to
quit working at that other school.
Prodding personal questions is poor manners!
So, we can prod your p〇ssy, but we can't
prod your personal life? That's weird.
You can't mean...
I think a nice fuck in front of an audience
would really take the edge off.
S-Stop this now!
If you squirm too much, we might
poke something too sensitive.
No!
Can you hear me, Haruka?
Yes...
Then say your name.
T-Taifuuji Haruka.
What're your measurements?
I don't know.
Come on, there's no way
you wouldn't know that.
It's been years since I measured.
When was the last time you checked?
Maybe nine or ten years ago...
That's fine.
My bust is 89.
My waist is 60.
My hips are 90.
89? I guess that means
you're at least an E-cup.
I'm an F-cup.
After I gave birth to Ai, I got bigger.
No!
When did you lose your virginity?
Wh-When I was in university.
Who was it?
M-My husband.
My current husband.
So I guess you're not really getting any.
I-I've never been with a man other than my husband.
No! Don't!
Don't do it!
Not so roughly!
Stop!
No!
So you wanted to suck it
so badly it makes you cry?
You'd better squeeze it out quickly
or else there'll be consequences!
Please, stop this.
I can't take it anymore.
There's a global standard
for ladies, you know.
International women have to have
their p〇ssies spread open.
No!
You haven't exracted enough milk.
The white bitches will take
all the men away from you.
So we're gonna give you some training
to prevent that from happening.
We told you there'd be consequences.
D-Don't do it!
N-No!
We're gonna fuck you one way or another,
so you might as well just accept it.
No! Don't!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
A while since you've spread
your legs in front of a man.
No...
Don't!
You really don't want it?
But you're soaking wet.
No!
Why is this happening?
Because you're a mother.
To protect her offspring,
a mother will do anything.
Really?
If I do exactly as you say,
you won't hurt my daughter?
You promise, right?
It all comes down to how much longer the
drugs will take to make you lethargic.
A yellow monkey bitch is a piece of cake
to seduce once she has tasted a cock
from the mighty black forest.
Then we'll have us a nice bowl of
steaming hot MILF, I guess
Not there!
No!
No! Oh, no!
As I suspected, I can go deeper in this way.
Got it? Let's have a nice DEEP relationship.
No! Not yet!
Don't! Not in there!
We'll make you forget about
your stupid husband.
No!
No...
Please, stop it.
Yes! Yes!
What was that? Say it louder.
But...
I can't... be so slutty!
Sex feels good BECAUSE it's slutty.
No! I-I can't!
Don't lie. Or I'll stop.
No...
If you want my c〇ck, then just say so.
Yes! Yes!
This is the first time...
I've felt so...
So good!
Oh yes!
This is the first...
You're so thick and so hard.
Yes!
All the way inside! All the way to my uterus!
Yes...
Yes!
Say it louder, so everyone can hear.
You're awesome!
You're so awesome!
You're so thick,
and so long,
and so hard!
It doesn't even compare to my husband.
You're so amazing.
How about we let your eggs
experience the awesomeness.
No!
Don't!
Today's my... Not inside!
You should be happy. You'll give birth
to a kid with a big, strong d〇ck.
Stop it!
Please, stop it!
Please!
No!
M-Mom?
Let's show Mommy how
much you've grown up.
No!