I'm... I'm gonna cum again!
I can't stop myself!
I'm cumming!
Come on, Sayaka-chan, you only
came about 70 times so far.
That's right! You'll have to cum at
least 30 more times.
– No, I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
– Akimiya Sayaka...
– No I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I don't think there's any other guy who
knows as much about her as I do.
Height: 159cm.
Weight: 47kg.
Shoe Size: 23cm.
Right handed.
Eyesight of 2.0.
Her three sizes are:
Bust - 95, Waist - 61, and Hip - 94.
Her bra size is a G.
Over time, I realized just how captivating her body is.
Even though I was watching from a distance,
her charm has bewitched me.
She's been the beloved subject of my fantasies.
That is Akimiya Sayaka.
I'll leave Sayaka's training to you.
I've looked into your height, weight history,
family, hobbies, grades, friends...
I've really looked into who you are.
I even know that you've been stalking her.
You're also subscribed to several adult sites.
Mostly gangbang and S&M.
What did you think of the video of her being defiled?
I wanted to be there. I wanted to break her,
and mess her up with my own hands.
Excellent. I'll grant your wish.
Do what you want. Anything at all.
Try anything that comes to mind.
I'll permit everything.
You can even torture her.
I'll grant any and all of your desires.
As long as it's within the boundaries
of this school, anything goes.
After all, it's owned by us - The Shakkoukai.
That includes the students, and the teachers too.
I'm not actually in love with her or anything.
I don't mind.
In fact, it'll be more interesting since
you'll be doing things half-heartedly.
You see, I took Sayaka in at a young age
for the sole purpose of having fun.
I've been waiting so long to see her break like this.
So, what will you do? What's your answer?
Stop it! I'm going to lose it!
Stop the shocks! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My nipples and my pussy are going to break!
I'm cumming!
I...
Addicted aphrodisiac to gang bang.
Nowhere to run! All 1428 students have sex with Reijou Sayaka ~.
Mornin'!
Good morning.
Will she obediently listen to whatever I say?
Yes, she will.
There's the fact that I threatened
to release that DVD of her.
You can also make use of the fact that
she's addicted to this aphrodisiac.
I used it a long time ago when I was training her.
She got so addicted that she can barely function without it.
I'll leave it with you.
As long as you have it, she'll be unable to disobey you.
Good morning, Akimiya-san.
Good morning.
Could I speak with you after school?
Speak about what? Something about class?
Nope, not that.
Then what?
About the Shakkoukai.
Wh-Why do you...
How do you know about that?
Well, let's talk about all that after school.
I'll tell you where we'll meet later.
Audiovisual room 2.
So what did you want to talk about?
I spoke with your father and he told me a lot of things.
Like about the Shakkoukai,
and how you've been hooked on this stuff.
Wh-Why do you have that?
This is something your father gave me,
as part of his request for me to train you.
Oh, there you are.
Wait, Akimiya-san's here.
Yeah, she is.
Sorry to call all of you out here.
It's no problem, but...
You said you'd show us something
interesting, but what is it?
– But seriously, why is Akimiya-san here?
– Oh come on, calm down.
You'll understand why I called all
of you and Sayaka here soon.
No!
No! Stop! Don't look! Stop!
Come on, Sayaka-chan, you only came about 70 times so far.
Please, stop! Don't look, this is just...
So, you guys get it?
Saitou, what is this?
Is this really Akimiya-san?
No! Th-This is...
As you can see,
this video shows her secret.
Her father said I'm free to do whatever I want to her.
He also told me that she'll do whatever I ask.
Isn't that right?
Th-That's...
I'm the only one who has the drug.
There's also the fact that they've seen who you really are.
Just look at them.
If we let them leave as they are,
don't you think they'd talk?
Would you be fine with that?
I get it. I'll do anything you say.
Anything?
Yes. I'll do anything you say.
It feels like I'm forcing you.
If you don't want to, that's fine.
Everyone will just leave, myself included,
but I won't be giving you the drug.
What are you saying I should do, then?
You should tell them this...
There's no way I can say...
You can't?
Akimiya-san?
Was that really you in that video?
And did he really mean that you'd do anything he says?
E-Everyone...
I, Sayaka, am his s-slave, and...
H-He said he wants to see me being
raped and violated by all of you.
S-So please, give me all of your dicks!
I want to be the outlet for all your sexual desires!
H-Hey, Saitou. Is this really okay?
Yeah, of course. She said it herself too.
Here you go, Akimiya-san.
Don't forget to show everyone your big tits.
Let me see!
Me too.
Hot damn!
Akimiya-san's tits!
Come on, suck my dick.
You've done this thousands of times already, haven't you?
I can't watch anymore. Akimiya-san, use your hand.
Me too!
A-Akimiya-san's holding my dick!
Sayaka, are you even trying?
Should I electrocute you like they
did in the video as punishment?
We're just getting started here.
For such a good blowjob, I'll let you have this as a reward,
but also to prepare you for what's to come.
Sayaka, I'm going to be teasing you even more, okay?
We're having sex, Sayaka.
My dick is in your pussy.
Damn, this is Akimiya-san's pussy?
Saitou's dick is spreading it apart!
Oh, man!
No, don't look!
You can't look!
What can't they look at?
You have to spell it out for them or they won't know.
My pussy!
Don't look at my pussy! My pussy!
Her juices are gushing out from how he's
sliding his dick in and out of her.
Akimiya-san's... Akimiya-san's so sexy!
Look, Sayaka. Your classmates are masturbating to you.
I... I don't want to be masturbated to!
I was finally... finally able to have a normal life here!
From now on, this will be your normal life.
No!
I'll be even rougher for you, so just let yourself go.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Let's show them some more.
They're all your fans.
Hey, someone put their dick into
her asshole. She's used to it.
Can I? Really?
Yeah, no problem. She'll love it.
O-Okay, I'm putting it in.
Akimiya-san, here I go.
Don't!
– Please! Take your dick out from my ass!
– I won't lose. I'll keep fucking your pussy hard!
Please, don't move!
Your dicks are rubbing against each other inside of me!
I'm going to cum again! I'm gonna cum!
She came again?!
Damn, is this really Akimiya-san?
Okay, time to switch.
Huh? Wh-What?
I mean, there's like 20 people here.
It's not over until you make all of them cum.
No!
I came so much yesterday, but it doesn't feel like it at all.
No! Someone... Someone please help me!
Your throbbing dicks are going to get me pregnant!
Use my pussy and my ass!
No, stop!
It's already been a week, huh?
Time to move on to the next step.
Akimiya-san!
Wh-What?
I need your help with something.
Okay...
Great. Let's get going.
What's the meaning of this?
I was thinking you could entertain the teachers today.
After all, there's going to be a lot going on from now on.
N-No! I don't want to!
I never thought that you'd be this slutty.
I had high hopes for you, you know?
Seriously.
We'll have to talk some sense into you, now that you've had
impure, sexual relationships with so many students.
You made me sad, Akimiya.
I never thought you'd be fucked
by so many of our students.
A-Aren't any of you embarrassed?
Embarrassed?
What's embarrassing about lovingly
guiding one of our students?
My classmates were one thing, but I don't
want to have sex with my teachers too!
Don't cry, Sayaka.
Here, I'll give you your favorite.
No!
Sayaka, lie down there.
Wow, this is great.
You said it. She's so lewd.
Students these days are so dirty.
Hey, Sayaka. Move your tongue like you always do.
I want it! I want to lick a dick!
Please go ahead, President.
Oh, would that be fine? Here I go, then.
What a lewd way to use a tongue!
You all must be bored just watching.
Please feel free to play with her body as you wish.
I'll be taking care of this dirty breast, then.
I can't believe you've been taunting me
with these huge breasts everyday.
I'll make sure to rub them well.
Your plump, smooth thighs are amazing.
I've never seen anything like them.
Hey, come on, your tongue's getting lazy! Move it more!
Principal, are you done with that mouth?
It's about time I use this mouth down here.
I'm cumming!
Sayaka, it's not over yet.
Look. I have a present for you.
This is great!
Shit, I'm gonna cum!
I'll make up for not having sex with you yesterday, Sayaka!
Stop! Your dick in my ass is making me tingle all over!
It's gonna make me break!
My pussy is becoming a mess!
I can keep cumming!
You're gonna cum inside my pussy again!
Stop! Take it out! Take it out!
I'm cumming!
Wake the hell up, Sayaka!
Man, you guys are still so soft.
If you don't do this much,
Sayaka won't understand that she's not allowed to faint.
W-What did you just put in my pussy!
It's my hand. I just slid my fist inside of your pussy.
Stop! Stop!
And that's basically how she is right now.
Looks like it's going well. Splendid.
Yes. Let's talk about what happens next...
translator: hikarukon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: bis | punk4real
quality control: hyakupercent