There's a small town within the mountains
known as, Rinin.
They conduct a foul tradition that must be stopped.
In order to appease the anger of Iwanagahime,
each new and full moon of every month,
young women are appointed as Shrine Maidens.
They are then violated.
In other words, they're gang raped.
I, Yamazaki Suzuko,
came back to my hometown to be a teacher
for the sake of my mother who has been living in despair.
Ever since she was violated as a Shrine Maiden,
I vowed to put an end to this tradition.
However, with no resistance,
I've become a Shrine Maiden.
Call me a despicable sex animal.
The person leading the rituals is
Rinin High School's Student Council President.
Tamura Motoko.
The Rinkan Club is responsible for handling the rituals.
Episode 2: The Fallen Aiko and Yamanaka Tomomi
Damn, Yamanaka's so cute!
Aside from being physically fit, she's also sexy, right?
Really amazing!
I really want to stir the pussy that's under her leotard with my cock.
Damn, I'm really jealous that Tanoue can
just play with that pussy anytime.
Tanoue?
Tanoue-kun!
Do your best!
The baseball club's ace player.
I heard he's currently dating her.
With him practically being a professional star player,
she won't even look at us.
I'm sorry, Kenji-kun,
but it's still not the right time.
Until we graduate from high school...
You're right.
I'm sorry.
No.
I need to apologize, too.
Yamanaka Tomomi...
Tomomi...
Onii-chan is...
With Onii-chan's cock...
Tomomi will...
Hey, are you sure?
Yep.
He said he wants to talk privately.
Kenji said to meet him here?
Kenji-kun...
Kenji-kun?
It's me, Tomomi.
Onii-chan?!
Where's Kenji-kun?
If you're looking for Tanoue,
he's probably playing baseball.
What's the meaning of this?
I'm going back now!
Stop!
Let go of me!
Tomomi,
Yamanaka Tomo
do you know about the Rinkan club?
What's that?
I don't know!
Let go!
It's a ritual that's been passed down for a long time in this town.
The person that bears the name of a relative,
lover or spouse that's written here
will become a Shrine Maiden,
sacrificed and then raped by men.
Onii-chan, what are you saying?
Tomomi...
The Onii-chan you know...
has been waiting a long time for this.
You haven't done it with Tanoue yet, right?
No!
Stop!
Tomomi's hasn't been touched by Tanoue...
Your virginity is mine.
No!
Onii-chan!
Idiot.
Your role is already over, Onii-chan.
Maki, did something happen?
You haven't been looking well lately.
When I went to the pool the other day...
No, it's nothing.
Maki!
No matter what happens,
I will protect Maki.
Motoko-chan...
Maki, please stay as pure as you are now.
That's great, Kenji!
One more time!
Do you understand?
Don't ever let your voice out.
Your beloved Tanoue will hear you.
The butt of this academy's idol is in plain sight...
There, if we do this,
we'll see the butthole perfectly.
No!
Don't!
Don't look at my butthole!
It's embarrassing!
Hey, a finger is going inside.
No!
Don't put it in!
I'm being fondled and played with...
Near Kenji-kun...
Getting a finger inserted in my butt...
Even Kenji-kun hasn't touched me there yet.
Play with the lower part, too.
Please, don't touch my pussy.
We already told you not to raise your voice, didn't we?
Tanoue will notice.
It's coming out.
My voice... I can't...
If Kenji-kun sees me here,
I'm dead.
Oh, you're already wet.
My butt...
It hurts, but it feels good.
That part of me
holds a lot of erotic fluids.
This bitch gets aroused when she gets spanked?
It's because we've trained her anally since then.
The academy idol is now
a sex animal that can't live without
an anal orgasm.
Let's insert this now, shall we?
No way...
If your first time is with a baseball bat,
even Tanoue will be proud.
No, please don't!
Not with my butthole, please!
Give it up already.
The one that will get your virginity
has already been decided. It's Tanoue.
Here now.
I'll be inserting the thick end as a special service.
So you were really a virgin?
Oh, but even if you were not a virgin,
I think it would still bleed.
What the hell do I care though?
I'll thrust it in.
It hurts.
My mind's going blank.
I wonder what my face looks like right now.
I don't want to show this face to Kenji-kun.
But my pussy is wet,
and it's getting all stirred up inside.
I'll pee.
I'm going to pee!
Just go pee swiftly!
It's coming!
What's wrong?
Katsuragi-sensei.
Katsuragi Toshio-sensei of the Educational Guidance department.
Her husband is Katsuragi Aiko, a doctor.
He's also Katsuragi Maki's father.
I was thinking about checking out the
confiscated DVD's from the students.
Hey, is this okay?
Abusing Suzuko-sensei even though she has
completed her role as a Shrine Maiden...
It's okay.
That woman's already a sex slave anyway.
But the Chairman's going to get mad at us.
I'm not going to stand around all day and hear you complain.
I see.
There's a possibility that the videos might
contain pornographic material.
So that's why...
I understand.
Let's watch the video together.
Watch Katsuragi closely.
Audiovisual Room
I'm sorry.
Because of my students' problems...
It's okay.
This is also part of my role in educational guidance.
This is...
Look.
At my butt...
At my pussy...
Look closely.
Here.
If I do this,
you can see it better, right?
I feel very good.
It's out in the open...
Geez, some crazy sex animal you are.
Exposing and widening herself like this...
I've never seen a lewd woman of this kind before.
Please, tease me!
I want my butt to be teased a lot!
Yeah, I'm really going to do that!
This is good!
My pussy...
My pussy feels really good!
I can't hold it anymore.
A cock.
I want a cock.
A cock in my pussy.
Insert a cock in my pussy!
Aiko!
Aiko-sensei?
Now, rape me quickly.
Give me a cock, please.
What's that?
What are they doing?
This great woman.
I can't leave this woman alone.
How much are you worth, Aiko-sensei?
1000 yen.
I'm okay with one person at a time for 1000 yen.
Hey, heard that?
She's willing to get a cock thrust in her for 1000 yen.
What a cheap pussy.
That's just fine.
1000 yen per person is fine.
So please, thrust a cock into me quickly!
I don't want fingers.
I want a cock right now!
Hey, hey, guess we can't help it.
For her to change like this
after getting selected as a shrine maiden,
she sure has improved a lot.
I'm cumming!
By the pool, at this time at noon...
Getting myself in a lewd form like this
with 1000 yen per person...
Getting screwed by lots of cocks...
I'm going to cum!
Man, I can't have enough of this sex animal!
My breasts.
Play with my breasts, too.
What's with these helpless breasts?
It's been sucked so much it's already dripping.
Play with them.
I want you to play with my dripping breasts!
Please fondle both of my breasts a lot!
My nipples.
My breasts and nipples are being teased.
I'm going into ecstasy.
I'm going to melt because my nipples are being teased.
Breasts.
I can't get enough of you touching my breasts.
My dripping breasts...
The nipples that are getting hard in front of a cock
are being held tightly.
It's okay to pull it tightly!
I'm about to cum with my...
Cum with my breasts!
No one cums with their breasts, you know!
Cum with the cock that's in your pussy!
This cock...
This cock feels good!
The cock that's in my pussy.
The cock that's stirring me up inside.
I'm cumming with it!
I can't wait anymore.
Open your mouth. Open!
I've gotten raped so much with these cocks.
Use your cocks to mess up every part of my body!
So good...
My body is all wet, covered with semen. This is so good...
My pussy's 1000 yen.
My butthole's 500 yen.
A handjob would be fine at 200.
Mother!
M-Maki?
Mother, why are you...
There. Watch closely.
If you're also a woman born here,
it's possible that you'll also be like that.
N-No...
I'm getting aroused
being watched by my daughter.
Getting lots of cocks in me
in this beastly fashion, while my daughter watches...
I'm getting aroused!
Mother...
I'm cumming!
Look, Maki.
Look at how I cum.
Look at how this sex animal gets stained and cums...
Look!
I don't want to!
I'm being impregnated.
Lots of semen is being released in me,
and I no longer know who released them all.
A baby formed from an unknown semen...
I'm going to... I'm going to have...
...children!
No...
There, your daughter is watching.
Maki-chan,
I'm being seeded right now.
So please wait a bit more.
Look forward to our fourth baby, okay?
Katsuragi-sensei?
No matter how pure she is,
even if there's a beloved one waiting for her,
a woman born in this town
shall never escape from the clutches of fate.
Yamanaka Totomi
No matter what kind of tragedy they may face.
Please!
Leave me alone already.
Stop abusing me!
Don't say such foolish things.
You still haven't tasted a real cock, have you?
Stop.
Please don't do lewd things!
Damn.
Having big breasts like these for a high schooler...
It hurts.
No...
Look.
This is the academy idol that we fantasize about.
Yamanaka Totomi's breasts are open for business!
They're really big!
The nipples are clearly standing out!
Don't!
Please don't suck my breasts!
Amazing. Tomomi's breasts taste like milk.
My nipples...
Not my nipples...
If you do that, I'll...
If I do this, you'll what?
No, I can't say such lewd things...
Then we'll have to directly investigate
what's truly happening.
Look at that. You're already very wet.
No!
Don't say that!
Hey guys, do you want to see Tomomi's pussy?
We want to!
Do you want to insert your cocks in it?
Yeah!
Then, we'll present it to you.
Do whatever you want.
All right!
Stop that!
Don't suck!
Now, I'm going to put my cock in.
No!
Please, don't put it in!
I planned on giving my virginity to
Kenji-kun...
Oh, I see.
You want Tanoue to see it...
Bring him over.
Let him see the reality.
Kenji-kun...
Please, don't look!
Don't look!
Shall we have your first cock inserted in front of Tanoue?
No!
Tanoue, it already went in all the way.
I don't want it inside!
This cock doesn't feel any good.
If it's not Kenji-kun's cock,
I won't feel good!
I wonder how long you are going to hold...
I-It doesn't feel good.
It doesn't feel good.
Here!
Don't!
– Please, don't!
– Come on, say it now.
Say that it feels good.
It feels...
It doesn't feel good...
All the way inside...
Deep into my womb... no!
Keep shouting!
Stop!
I'm being raped,
and there are lewd secretions coming out of my pussy.
No...
My pussy...
It's being stirred up.
I don't want...
I don't want my pussy to...
This is...
A cock's thrusting fully into me.
I'm being nailed!
This kind of...
I don't want...
I don't want this!
No way...
It's inside.
It's been released in my pussy.
I'm going to get pregnant.
Does it feel good?
No!
This is...
Not gonna tell, huh?
If you don't say it, I'm going to stop.
No. Don't stop.
Then, what do you want to do?
Please rape...
Please rape my pussy more!
Hey, heard that?
She's already become a sex slave animal.
A sex slave...
Tomo... mi...
Here now.
Look at that lewd face.
No, please don't!
Kenji-kun, don't look!
I don't want you to look at me!
Tanoue, are you looking?
Her liquids are dripping out.
Hey, this cock...
This cock is thick, hard and hot.
My pussy is being abused by it.
This is good.
I never thought that it could feel this good.
Being screwed...
Having my pussy pierced...
Getting a cock to hit deep inside me...
It really feels good!
My pussy's being stirred up by a cock...
No, not my breasts!
If you tease my nipples like that,
milk will...
Milk will come out!
My breasts are stuck here.
If my breasts get done in like this,
I'm going to cum with my breasts!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
Spread it on her.
Stinky pee...
Please don't think of me as a urinal...
No!
My tummy's already full and it can't take in anymore.
This is the semen that we had collected specially for this day.
Taste it until you get full.
No!
It's coming out.
I can't hold it in anymore!
Hold it in!
I'm already at my limit!
My insides will explode!
Okay, then.
We'll have to make sure Tanoue sees it clearly then.
No way...
Okay, this place will be your toilet.
Show it to your boyfriend.
Kenji-kun.
No!
It's going to come out. It's going to come out!
I can't hold it any longer.
Kenji...
Kenji!
It's coming out
from my butthole!
It came out!
No! It's leaking out!
It's all gushing out!
Kenji-kun!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
I'm... sorry.
If I can't break the tradition,
then I shall be the tradition.
Just you wait,
Tamura Motoko.