I'm going to break!
S-Stop it!
Stop!
D-don't cum inside me!
I think it's about time
we moved on to the next stage.
Assicted aphrodisiac to GANG BANG
~Nowhere to run! All 1428 students have sex with reijou Sayaka~
Wanna have lunch together, Akimiya-san?
What do you want this time?
I just want to have lunch with you.
That's all? That's fine then.
What are your favorite foods?
Fruits. Stuff like peaches and oranges.
Oh nice! I'm a fan of those myself.
So then what don't you like?
Meat. I hate the taste.
That's new. Never heard of anyone
not liking the taste of meat.
Couldn't you just put sauce on it?
Putting sauce on it wouldn't solve anything.
It would.
You see, trying to overcome things
is what makes us human.
Experimentation and wisdom
are how we overcome things.
Nice philosophy you got there,
but it doesn't make sense in this context.
What are you up to?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about what you're doing right now!
Did you forget? I told you.
All I want to do is eat lunch with you.
Well, I'm done eating, so I'll see you later.
Sorry if I was bothering you.
See you tomorrow, Akimiya-san.
Now that I think about it, it's been a while
since I last went went home right after school.
Now, can anyone tell me what this phrase means?
How about you, Akimiya?
What's the matter?
Nothing, I'm fine.
It means that you have
something that must be done.
Like that, it is often used to imply "everything".
Just skipping one day's dose
and she gets like this?
Later, Akimiya-san. See you tomorrow.
W-Wait!
Need something?
A-Are we not doing that today?
Doing what?
What are you saying? The thing we always do.
With everyone...
What do we do with everyone?
I-I mean...
Me and everyone else have...
You and everyone else have what?
F-Forget about it!
Looks like there's still some time
left before she's at her limit.
But that time is quickly running out.
Can't wait until tomorrow.
Come here a second!
P-P-Please! The d-drug!
I-It hurts! P-Please!
Please, just hurry!
My head's already starting to go crazy!
So please, just give it to me!
Oh, I wonder what I should do...
I'll suck your dick!
O-Or would you prefer having sex with me?
Either way's fine!
Please just give me the drug!
I'll do anything! So please, please hurry!
You'll do anything? Really?
Okay then, could you do me a little favor?
You're kidding...
I-If I do that, I'll... I'll...
No problem then.
I'm not going to force you to do anything.
Wait! Wait!
What?
Um... I...
If you're done, I'm gonna leave.
I'll do it!
So give me the drug!
Please hurry up and give it to me!
Oh, great! Thank you!
Hurry up and walk!
What's going on?
You're kidding.
Fucking move!
Bite this
Yes...
This is so... embarrassing...
Looks like we have an audience.
You can stop here, Sayaka.
Y-Yes...
Hello everyone. I, Akimiya Sayaka,
am a perverted slut who loves cocks
and I deeply apologize for
deceiving everyone to think otherwise.
I have sex with at least ten
older men for hours on a daily basis.
The number of people I've had sex with has
probably reached the thousands. I'm a huge slut!
I've been cum inside of so many times
and even gotten pregnant.
I've already had seven abortions!
But even so, I still have dicks
cumming inside of me every day!
S-So that being said, I'm hoping that from today on,
I will be the school's public cum dumpster,
in order to relieve everyone's sexual desires!
Blowjobs, creampies, anal sex...
Anything goes! Do whatever
you want to this dirty little slut!
Whether it's in my mouth, pussy, or ass,
I'll do my best to take in all the cum
you have as your personal dumpster!
Please use me however you want!
Holy shit. I need to take a picture.
They're taking pictures of me like this...
No!
What happened to her?
No clue. But if what she said was true,
she was getting money for
having sex with those older guys.
She's a slut, so maybe she's
gone crazy from having so much sex!
I need to tell my friends about this.
Hey, Sayaka-chan, I'm gonna take
a picture so pose for me!
Yeah, I wanna get a good,
dirty picture, so keep that in mind.
A pose? What should I do?
Hey, this perverted cum dumpster slut,
Sayaka, is gonna take all your cum!
Teehee.
What the fuck is that pose?
This bitch is so fucking dumb!
Yes I am!
I am an idiot who loves cum, sex, and cocks!
Be sure to make me look cute!
Akimiya's done for.
I've never seen a girl act this crazy before.
Hey, look over here, Sayaka-chari!
You're so cute, dirty, and stupid!
You're not done yet.
Did you forget that you were
going to show everyone how you cum?
W-Wait! S-Stop! D-Don't! P-Please!
No can do, Sayaka.
You gave up on any mercy
when I gave you the drug.
Come on, Sayaka. You've gotta say that
you're cumming, otherwise no one will know.
No! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! Just saying it is making me cum!
So like this, you use this formula to...
Come on, suck it harder,
you fucking cum dumpster.
Sensei, those numbers are wrong!
Oh, they are. My mistake.
Here it comes. Drink it all, okay?
Yes, please! Let it all out in my mouth!
Do me next!
Y-Yes...
Publie dumpster
And like this, everyone here becomes
a different kind of human being.
I'm going to fuck your pussy
like there's no tomorrow, Akimiya!
It's so deep!
Why the hell are you speaking like a human?
You're a dog, aren't you? Go ahead and bark!
This is fucking hilarious.
Come on, Sayaka, be a good doggy.
I will! My pussy feels so good! I'll be good!
And so, everyone in the school
treated her like a slave.
You stopped cheering!
Keep cheering for our baseball team!
E-Everyone's looking over here.
Please, don't make me do this.
Th-This is so embarrassing, I'm going to die!
Like hell you can stop!
If you don't keep going,
I won't give you your dose today.
No, for the whole week.
Go! Go! Cocks!
Fight! Fight! Cocks!
Go! Go! Let's go!
Let's go! Cock! Yay!
They're going to tear my pussy!
Take them out!
Hey, calm down, Sayaka.
I'll give you a shot
that'll make it feel all better.
My mind's going crazy!
Oh, this is just beautiful.
So fucking beautiful.
She's become the plaything
of the entire school!
My pussy is melting from the pleasure
of being fucked by this hard cock!
Shit, I'm gonna cum!
No, not inside! No, please don't!
I'm next!
A-Another dick is inside of me!
That's one more person you've had sex with today!
Isn't that great?
No, it's no...
Her pussy is so tight, it's swallowing me whole!
It feels so fucking good!
I'm cumming inside!
There's even more cum inside of me now!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum from all this semen!
Yeah, go ahead and cum!
I'll make you cum all you want!
I'm cumming! I don't want to cum!
I'm cumming! I can't stop cumming!
Sayaka, you're the best!
Show me more of your pathetic self!
I'm cumming!
Hey, morning, Sayaka!
Good morning...
Okay, take off your clothes.
Right here and now?
Yep. Right here and now.
Come on, hurry up.
That took she has of not being used to this
no matter how many times she's done it...
It's just wonderful.
Sayaka?
Y-Yes...
Hey, don't be hiding anything.
From now on, you're going to attend school like this.
What do you mean? Like this?
But, I'm naked...
Yep, stark naked.
You are forbidden from putting on clothes.
For the entire day?
Yep.
You don't need clothes anyway, do you?
Like this, you can get fucked no matter
when and where you are, isn't that right?
Yeah, exactly!
Besides, you're our school's pet,
why would you need clothes?
Yeah, seriously.
You have big tits and a good body,
so it's not like you have anything
to be embarrassed about.
So, from now on, while you're within school grounds,
you're forbidden from wearing clothes.
Okay?
If you understand, respond to me.
It's a really great idea, isn't it?
I-It is...
I understand...
From now on, I, Sayaka,
will be naked while I am in school.
So who can tell me what "Chartism" is?
Akimiya, stand up.
Something wrong? Stand up, Akimiya.
Yes...
Chartism is a movement from the latter
half of nineteenth century England,
centered around the working class
were not given any power to vote.
Through the efforts of the workers who aimed
for the realization of a normal, fair election,
for fifty years after the realization
of their ambitions in 1838,
they were able to work out The People's Charter
which gave them the basic rights that they desired.
Good job. Looks like you've been studying.
You can sit back down.
Sayaka, from now on,
you need to have sex with 150 people per day.
He's gonna cum inside me?
I'm cumming!
No...
You're a dirty little slut, as usual.
You can still drink a lot more, can't you?
No!
N-No! No more...
I'm cumming!
Stop! I'm gonna die!
I'll listen to whatever you tell me to do!
She's so cute and beautiful!
I can't get enough of this!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for putting your
great cock into my filthy pussy!
Your wide-ass pussy is so tight
now because of the electricity!
– Did your pussy always feel this great?
– I'm cumming!
This is so great!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming, Sayaka!
I'm gonna cum in your womb again!
Nothing but sex, sex, and more sex!
All year round, twenty-four hours a day!
She'll always be fucked by someone.
This girl is less than human or even
livestock – she's the lowest of the low!
She's my ideal woman, Akimiya Sayaka!
I'm cumming!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr | hybrio21
editor: fyurie