Our school takes advantage of international exchanges,
so we teach many exchange students here.
I-Is that so?
But it's strange that you'd be transferred to a new job at this time.
W-Well, that is...
The school principal listened to an impossible request of mine, so I'm very grateful to him.
Hm?
Original Creator: Lune lovesK
SubDESU-H Presents
Rinkan Gakuen
Stop! ... Mom, don't look!
SubDESU
-H
Presents
Original Animation Video
Rin
kan
Gakuen
First part: "Crush the Virgin and the Hot Wife's Fidelity!
Jeez!
It's fine, really!
You're such a worrywart, Dad! I'm not a child any more! So there!
Ai! I need to use the phone next!
Ow-w-w-w-ow!
Really, Ai.
Yes, she's doing fine. There's no need to worry, darling, keep on working hard.
They went 'boing, boing'.
I'm no match.
Really, you shouldn't stare at people.
It's poor etiquette.
Dad... When did he say he's coming back?
He said it'll just be a little while longer.
Mom, are you lonely?
Since you're here, Ai, I'm fine!
Oh? A daughter?
She had a student marriage, apparently.
That lady...
At school, I'm not 'Mom', okay, Ai?
I'm sorry!
Um... Please, Haruka-sensei?
The parent-teacher conference, right? I’ll do it.
After school tomorrow, okay?
I'll go tell Aihara-sensei about it, then.
Did you forget somethi—
Do you know what tulips stand for in the language of flowers?
Aihara-sensei.
I know, so I love them.
It's the same as my name.
TL Note: Ai means “love”
For flowers to stay in bloom, they need to be taken care of.
I'll teach you how.
Such a beautiful flower, isn't it?
But if it's not taken care of, it'll wilt.
Th-That... can't be...
It's a lie!
It has to be a lie!
It must be a lie!
When your mother changed jobs, didn't you think it was strange?
If the teachers seduce the students, it's a major sex crime.
Being separated from your father is lonely, right?
But, from the standpoint of this academy, it's an unpleasant fact.
If the principal learns of this, at the best it would result in disciplinary action.
In the worst case, she would have her teacher’s license revoked.
You can’t...
Isn't he wonderful? He's an exchange student from America.
He's the one in the pictures.
The sex with your mother was dependent on his feelings.
No!
Japanese fellatio feels really good, so I like it.
No...
”Fellatio”?...
If you just suck his penis, he says he'll keep the thing with your mother a secret.
I... I can't do something like that!
Aihara-sensei, where was the principal's office again?
We really shouldn't tell your father about this, should we?
They'd probably get a divorce.
D-Divorce?
The principal's office is at the end of the hallway on the first floor.
I'll do it! I'll do it, so please...
Please...
I'll perform fellatio, so...
I'll... perform fellatio!
If it's not said in Japanese, there's no meaning in studying abroad.
Please let me suck you.
Suck what?
P-Penis...
'Dick'.
It's a... dick.
Please let me suck your dick!
Doing something like this, what are you all planning?
We're at the age where we're full of curiosity.
We want to know various things about you, Haruka.
Don't address me without my title!
Like why you left your last school.
Prying into private matters is rude!
You let us into your pus*y, so isn't it strange that you won't let us into your private matters?
You can't mean...
We think it'll be refreshing for you to spill your guts in front of everyone.
S-Stop it!
If you move too much, it'll pierce something sensitive.
No!
Can you hear, Haruka?
Yes.
Try saying your name.
Dai...bu...chi... Haruka.
We wanna know your measurements.
I don't know.
'I don't know' isn't an answer.
I knew them years ago, but not any more.
When did you know them?
Before I had my child, more than ten years ago.
That'll do.
Bust: 89 centimeters. Waist: 60. Hips: 90.
89 centimeters is about an E-cup.
My cup size is F. After I had Ai, they got bigger.
No!
When did you lose your virginity?
In... my... college days...
Your partner?
H-Husband... My current husband...
You've never done anyone but him?
I've never had anyone except my husband.
No, no!
Don't! Not so roughly!
Don't!
No!
Didn't you want to suck it so much you cried?
If you don't squeeze it all out soon, you'll pay for it afterwards!
Please... stop...
I can't take anymore...
It's the global standard for ladies.
Opening your pu*sy for international society.
Nooo!
You didn't drink enough milk, did you?
All the white sows will steal your Japanese men away from you.
That's why you'll let us replenish your energy.
We did say you'd have to pay for it afterwards.
No, don't!
N-No!
You're going to spill everything anyways, so you might as well be honest.
No, don't!
It's been a while, hasn't it? Having your legs spread wide open in front of a man.
No!
Don't!
Whaddya mean, 'don't'? You're all wet.
No!
Why? Such a...?
Because you're a mother.
Because a mother will do anything to protect her daughter.
Honestly... Will you keep your hands off my daughter if I do as you say?
You'll make a promise?
The real hurdle is when the drugs weaken your judgment.
How would it be if we let the yellow monkey sow remember the taste of penis just once?
But the mother-daughter sandwich starts here.
That place is...
No!
Like I thought, it goes in deep here.
Good, good, let's have a deep encounter.
No, not yet...
If you... go in that far...
We'll make sure you forget about your husband.
No!
Stop!
Yes, yes!
What was that? Speak up!
But! That's vulgar...
Because it's vulgar, it won't feel good? It's sex, after all.
No! Don't!
Stop complaining or I'll stop.
No!
If you want my c*ck, be honest.
Yes, yes!
This is the first time... it's felt... so good!
The first... So good!
Pounded... and fucked...
Going... all the way in... to my uterus...
Yes... yes...
Raise your voice! So it can be heard!
Amazing!
You're amazing!
Thick...
and long...
and hard...
It's incomparable... Amazing...
Let your eggs feel that as well, then.
No!
No! Not inside today!
Be happy. A super-thick penis means you'll have a strong child.
Stop!
Please stop!
Stop! I beg you!
No!
Mom...
Show Mama how much you've grown, daughter.
No!
Nooo!