Deep beneath the mountain, there's a small town called Rin'in.
A dark story of their urban legends lie here.
To avoid the curse of Iwanaga-hime's rage,
in the dawn of a new moon and a full moon in this town...
The young maiden who's like a flower blossom,
should be brought to the depths of the cave.
In there, she will be publicity raped, we call it "gang rape".
I'm one of the women who was born in this town,
I'm back here as a teacher at my old school.
I'm Yamazaki Suzuko, the only daughter of my late mother,
who has been gang raped in that ritual before.
For the sake of my late mother, I've returned in this town
to stop everything that'll happen.
But suddenly, I've been captured as one of the maiden's descendants and was gang raped by those people.
The one who managed that gang rape ritual was,
the student council president of Rin'in Highschool, Tamura Motoko.
And then the group who managed that ritual,
is called the Rinkan Club.
Rinkan Club
2nd Story. The beautiful fallen, Aiko and Yamanaka
Damn, Yamanaka is so cute!
She won the inter-high competition, you know?
She's awesome!
Damn, I want to stir up that pussy so hard with my penis.
Damn it, I'm even jealous of Tanoue for being able to stir up her pussy.
Tanoue?
Tanoue-kun, do your best!
I heard that she's going out with Tanoue,
an ace from the baseball club.
With a baseball star like him as our opponent,
there's no way she would look at us.
I'm sorry, Kenji-kun.
Now is an important time for us.
We should wait until we graduate.
That's right, sorry.
No, I'm sorry as well.
Yamanaka Tomomi.
Tomomi.
Onii-chan is...
With Onii-chan's penis...
I want to... I want to...
Hey, is it true?
That's right, he wants to talk with Tomomi in secret.
Kenji said like that, in here?
Kenji... kun?
Kenji-kun.
It's me, Tomomi.
Onii-chan!? Where's Kenji-kun?
I'm sure he's practicing at the field like an idiot by now.
What do you mean!? I'll go back right now!
Stop it!
Let me go!
Tomomi, do you know about the Rinkan Club?
What is that? I don't know anything, just let me go!
It's the oldest ritual in this town.
Whoever's name is written in this envelope,
even if she's someone's girlfriend or even fiancee,
she'll become the maiden.
She'll became the maiden who'll be raped.
Onii-chan, what are you doing?
Tomomi, Onii-chan...
has been waiting for this day...
You haven't done it with Tanoue, right?
No!
Stop it!
This pussy which Tanoue hasn't touched.
I'll have Tomomi's first time right now.
No~!!
Onii-chan!
Idiot.
Your turn is over, Onii-chan.
Maki, what's wrong?
You've been lurking here alone and you don't look that well.
In the other day, when I was at the pool...
No, It's nothing.
Maki!
Whatever happens in the future, I'll make sure to protect Maki.
Motoko-chan.
I want to keep you clean from it.
Motoko-chan?
That's great, Kenji! Once more!
Listen well, don't you ever let your voice out
or he'll notice us here.
I can see clearly our academy idol's ass.
Hey, when I spread it like this.
We can see her asshole.
No, you can't! Don't look at my asshole.
It's embarrassing.
Hey, I can put my finger in it.
No, don't put it in!
Tomomi is being seen.
While Kenji-kun is this close to me.
His finger is inside of my ass.
Even Kenji-kun hasn't touched it.
Why don't we touch the lower one?
Please, don't touch my pussy.
Didn't I say not to let your voice out?
Tanoue will notice your voice.
No... It'll come out... not at this place...
If Kenji-kun looks over here... I can't live anymore.
She's already this drenched.
Even though it's hurts, I feel good from it.
There's juice come out from my pussy...
This bitch is feeling good from being hit on her ass.
I'm sure that she's been doing a lot with it.
I can say that this academy's idol has fallen into sex slavery.
Is it about time that we use this thing?
No way...
I'm sure that you'll be happy to know that Tanoue's bat
is going to take your first time.
No... please, don't let that thing inside of me!
Just give up.
We've voted that Tanoue's bat
would fill your pussy for the first time.
Here, I'll put in the big one as special service from us.
There!
Hm... She actually is a virgin.
Even if she's not a virgin, I'm sure that this would make her bleed.
Like I care, here you go!
It hurts.
That thing is inside of me right now.
What face am I making right now?
I don't want Kenji-kun to look at my face right now.
But, my pussy feels so wet right now.
With that thing inside of me...
It makes me want to pee...
Let your pee out!!
I'm cumming~!!!
What's wrong?
Katsuragi-sensei.
He's the social studies teacher, Katsuragi Toshio-sensei.
He's also a doctor and Katsuragi Aiko's husband,
Katsuragi Maki's father as well.
I want to check the DVD which I confiscated from my student.
Are you sure it's okay? Doing something like this after she's already lost the right to be a maiden?
It'll be alright.
I'm sure that bitch is already a sex slave by now.
But, you'll make our president angry like this.
Do you really think that we're going to listen what Motoko says all the time?
That's right.
Maybe it might be pornography.
That's why...
I understand, I'll accompany you to watch it.
Katsuragi, don't you wet yourself.
I'm sorry, it's my student after all.
No... No... I'm sure it's also the job for a social studies teacher like me.
This is!?
Look at them, look at my asshole and my pussy.
Look at them...
There, like this you can see them clearly.
It feels so good when all of you look at them so much.
I can feel it.
Geez... What kind of bitch are you?
Spreading your privates like this.
I've never met a woman as indecent as her.
Please, touch at my ass...
I want you to tease my ass so badly.
Sure.
I'll do it.
Good~!
Pussy... My pussy feels good!
I can't hold it-
Penis... I want penis...
Aiko wants penis inside of her pussy!
Please put in your penis~!!!
Aiko...
Aiko-sensei?
There... Please rape me, insert your penis.
Hey... hey... what's happen over there?
Is that...
There's no way such a fine woman is free.
How much is your price, Aiko-sensei?
1000 yen... One time for just 1000 yen.
Hey, did you hear that? For 1000 yen, she'll let your penis thrust into her pussy.
What a cheap pussy.
That's fine, 1000 yen for one person.
Please put your penis inside of Aiko's pussy.
I don't want your finger... Please let me taste your penis, quickly!
Hey... hey... What can we do with that?
I can't believe she acts like this after being a maiden.
I'm sure that this is also her nature.
Cum!
Aiko, in broad daylight at the pool like this.
Being in such an indecent pose, just 1000 yen for one person.
I'll cum from a lot of penis fucking me from behind!
I can't get enough of this bitch!
My breasts... Please tease my breasts too!
What the hell is with these strange breasts? Do they get longer from getting touch them?
Tease them, I want you to tease my elastic breasts!
I want you to tease them.
I want to stretch out... my breasts... like before...
My nipples... My nipples feels good~!!
I can feel you teasing my breasts...
Aiko is going to meltdown from this~!!
I can't hold... I can't hold my breasts.
My lactating breasts...
My breasts are lactating while my pussy getting fucked like this,
I want to feel more of it~!
More of it...more intense.
That's right... Let me cum with my breasts.
No one would cum with their breasts,
just cum with your pussy!
Penis... Your penis feels good, your penis is fucking my pussy.
Your penis is stirring up the inside of my pussy, I'm going to cum from it~!!
I can't hold it anymore, open up your mouth... mouth.
A lot of it...
I've been fucked so much...
Mess up Aiko with the release from your penis~!!!
My pussy for 1000 yen.
I would even let you fuck... my assholes for 200 yen.
Mo... Mother!?
Maki!?
No way, why would my mother do that?
Hey, watch carefully.
If you were also born in this town, you'll experience
something like that in the future.
No... No.
I can feel it, while my daughter is looking at me.
While there's so much penis inside of me,
When my daughter looks at my indecent body like this,
I can feel all of it~!!
Mother... Mother...
Cumming... cumming... cumming...
Maki, look at your mother.
Look at me while I'm being bitch and there's a lot of penis inside of me!
No, I don't want to!!
There's a lot of it... A lot of semen inside of me... I can't even tell whose semen it is.
I wouldn't know whose seed that is,
I'll bear a child from it...
I'll get pregnant with all of it~!!!
No~!!!
Hey, your daughter is looking at you!
Maki, wait for it... Let me finish this for you.
Please wait for it.
I'll make the fourth member of our family right now.
Ka... Katsuragi-sensei?
How hard are you going to escape from it?
Even your promised boyfriend.
All women who are born within this town can't escape their fate.
Even so, there might be cruelty lying ahead for us.
Please, just let me go.
Please don't use Tomomi for something like this!
What are you saying?
We haven't let you taste real penis yet, right?
Stop it, don't do such indecent things to me.
Damn, you're such a high-school girl but you have breasts like these.
It hurts... no!
Look at this, I'm touching our academy idol, Yamanaka Tomomi's breasts.
She's got such big ones, look at her nipples standing up!
No, don't suck on my nipples!
It's great, I can feel Tomomi-chan's milk like this.
My nipples... My nipples... No-
If you do something like that... Tomomi will...
What will happen then?
No, I can't say something like that!
Then, what'll happen to you after this...
Let's examine this thing down here.
No~!!!
What's this? You're already this wet.
No... Don't say that!
All of you, do you want to see Tomomi's pussy?
Yes, we want it~!!!
Do you want to put your penis in it?
Then, let us show it to you.
No~!!
Do as you'd like!
Stop it! No... No-
Then, I'll put in my penis.
No~!!!
No, don't put it in!
Don't put that thing inside of my pussy.
Is that so, you want him to look at you?
Bring him in.
I'll let you see the truth.
Kenji-kun, please don't look at it.
Don't look at it!
Why don't we let Tanoue see us thrust into this pussy?
No... You can't-
Tanoue, I'm inside of her.
No~!!!
Stop it... No-
It doesn't feel...
It doesn't feel good...
It hurts.
Without Kenji-kun's penis,
there's no way Tomomi...
would feel good!
Let me hold you up then.
There's no way...
There's no way I would...
There.
No~!!!
No... No...
You can't... You can't~!!
Why don't you say it? It feel good.
It doesn't feel...
Deep...
Deep inside of it... No~!!!
More cries!
No~!!!
I've been fucked by it, my pussy is being fucked by that penis.
No-
Tomomi's pussy...
is being stirred up.
I don't want my pussy... like this...
That penis is thrusting inside of me.
No... no... no~!!!
You can't do that~!!!
No-
No!
No way, inside of me...
Inside of my pussy-
I'll get pregnant from it.
Does it feel good?
No, this is-
You won't say it? If you won't say it then I'll stop it.
No... You can't...
You... You can't stop it!
Then, what would be good for you?
Inside of Tomomi's pussy,
please stir up my pussy~!!!
Hey, did you hear? She's already being a sex slave for us.
Tomomi is a sex slave.
Tomo... mi.
There, I'll let you see her perverted face!
No, don't look at me!
Kenji-kun, don't look at me... Please don't at Tomomi's perverted face like this.
Tanoue, can't you see Tomomi's juice?
It's flowing out right now.
No... With this penis... With this penis inside...
This hard and hot penis makes Tomomi's pussy drenched...
Good... I can't believe it's this good...
Being fucked in my pussy like this... With this penis deep inside of me-
It feels really good~!!!
My pussy being fucked while my breasts are like... No-
Tomomi nipples...
If you pinch them like that,
I'll go crazy from it~!!!
Don't pinch my breasts like that.
If you do something like that.
Tomomi... will cum with my breasts~!!!!
Cumming~!!!
Tomomi is cumming~!!!
Spread it on her body.
You can't do that.
Don't pee on my body like this...
No!
You'll make Tomomi's stomach full of it.
This our semen which we were saving for this day.
I'll make sure to taste all of it.
No~!!
I'll die.
I can't hold it~!!
I can't hold it anymore~!!!
Hold on!
Please, let me go!
Tomomi's stomach is hurting a lot!
I got it.
We have to make sure that Tanoue can see it clearly, right?
No way.
Hey, in here will be your toilet. Let your boyfriend look at it.
No... No... No...
No~!!!
It leaking out...
I can't hold it anymore!
It's... going to come out!
It's coming out... from Tomomi asshole.
Coming out~!
No~!!!
It's out!
Even what's inside of me is also coming out~!!!
Kenji-kun, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry~!!!
I'm... so... sorry.
If I couldn't destroy the tradition,
I'll be part of the tradition itself for now.
Wait for me, Tamura Motoko.