Onee-chan is continuing her career as
a top fashion model even as of today.
Anna was worried back then, that there were inadequate
work opportunities as a gravure idol.
It was the that they took advantage of her.
No...!
Stop!
Here...
It hurts.
Stop.
Don't move.
The seminar of self-enlightenment.
Believes Laboratory.
I finally won against you, Onee-chan.
Are you familiar with Kokudou Academy?
I've heard that it's a really notorious all-boys school.
I can't believe that I have a connection to such a school.
Even now.
My goodness.
When it comes to my students,
everything always has to be about brawls and violent incidents.
We're constantly receiving complaints about them.
They even brutally take on passersby that
simply exchange glances with therm.
No one really has any distinct control
of the situation here anymore.
Truly deplorable I'd say.
The teachers are also about to quit their jobs,
so regular classes and lessons will soon be out of the picture.
Though, there are really only a selected few
who actually come to school anyway.
Now, that is sad.
I empathize with your troubles.
Delicious.
This tastes delicious.
Please, give me more of your cock...
If that's the case...
How about I send one of my members there
and give the students a chance to be saved.
Oh, I really appreciate the offer.
Can I add a little suggestion while we're at it?
We have one student here that has longed
to be freed for quite some time already.
I'm going to let her be admitted into Believes Laboratory.
Yes, please give her the necessary guidance.
The tip of your cock is turning my pussy inside out.
Yes, its rubbing inside me.
Her name is Mizushima Kaho.
What comes out of the Revered lewd religious
Leader, is now in the mouth of Riko... Chapter
Don't just strongly stroke it.
A slow, gradual pace is important in stimulating it.
I understand.
Be careful not to let your teeth touch.
Try to take in a larger portion if you can.
That's right.
It would be as if you are opening your throat wide.
Concentrate properly.
No need to rush.
Keep in mind to match your pace with his penis.
Yes.
Keep it slow at first.
Edification is the essence of Believes Laboratory.
In mastering it, you also become the master of your youth.
It will bring you to greater heights.
Properly adjust the angle and deepness,
so that your clitoris also rubs against his penis.
Like this?
That's right. Keep that up.
I'm cumming!
Ichinose-sensei,
let us do it please.
Ichinose-sensei.
Sensei.
Okay then.
How does it feel?
How does the body of a former fashion model feel?
How does my pussy feel?
Your body is the best Sensei.
My mind becomes completely muddled
with your expert hand's stimulation.
Your tongue feels hot.
It feels like my cock is about to melt!
Everyone.
Please edify yourselves gradually.
Everyday edification is the key to a sound mind and body.
Now, let us all wash away the heart's stains using our bodies!
Edify!
I'm at my limit already.
I'm about to be edified!
I'm about to edify too!
How about me, can I edify myself too?
It's okay.
Completely edify yourselves.
I'm also about to...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...!
Edify!
Thank you very much.
That was the best edification that I've ever had.
You all did well.
Do your best again tomorrow.
Once you get to the advanced course,
you'll get to cum inside me as many times as you want to.
Okay?
Yes!
Good work.
The shower room's open already.
I got myself cummed in again.
Me too.
Thank you for your hard work.
The way you taught them earlier was wonderful, Ichinose-san.
Thanks, Sateki-san.
Still not done for the day yet?
Yes.
I still need to do something.
Is there something wrong?
It's nothing.
So how was it today?
How were the seminar attendees?
Well, everyone is very spirited,
and learn quite quickly.
I think they'll become splendid members of our faith.
I was thinking of letting you be the audience
to a high class corporate personality.
Thank you very much.
I will do my best.
Umm...
Was Anna absent from the seminar today?
Have you heard anything from her today?
No, I haven't.
Hey, look at that.
Anna.
Anna?
Anna...
Is she for real?
Is she a swim wear model?
Thanks!
Oh wow!
Look... at me.
Look at me!
I can't get enough of this...!
She also has a really cute face!
I can't hold myself anymore.
I'm really sorry...
You guys, what's the meaning of this?
Let me go.
Ichinose-sensei.
We can no longer hold ourselves back.
We can't wait until our ranks go up.
We want to have sex with you now.
Please!
You can't do this!
You mustn't!
Not in this place...
Stop!
Oh, but Sensei...
Are you getting wet?
S-Stop saying such foolish...
Hey, wait...
I'm going in.
Don't.
You can't do this.
Pull it out!
You are violating the rules!
Wow, so this is Ichinose-sensei's pussy.
Amazing...
He's completely dominated by his youth
and simply thrusting wildly.
Then this is...
But if I let my voice out,
someone will see us.
It's really hot and stiff.
This youthful cock...
How did this happen...
Me, in this run-down, dirty corner...
To be violated here by people younger than me...
Sensei, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
Cum?! Are you about to release it?
You're releasing it?!
Don't!
Don't release it inside me!
I'm cumming inside!
Don't...!
Wow...
Do you boys understand what you have just done?
This... This is...
Your insides are the best Sensei!
What? It's longer than the previous one,
and it reaches very deep inside me.
Oh wow...
More, thrust it into me more.
I'll... I'll be swept away by something this great.
Please cum.
Cum as I expose my embarrassing self to you all.
I'm also feeling great here.
I feel great as you all stare at me.
I love it.
I love being watched.
I love it!
Lots of it came out.
So all of you felt really good.
Everyone, thank you.
Sensei, Sensei...
It's coming out...
Sensei, I love you.
This is wonderful.
Takayuki-san.
Your big thing is thrusting in and out.
It's Okita-sensei!
Anna?
It hurts.
Oh, this is splendid.
What a nice offering I received here.
Seems that my edification with you would
instantly take me to greater heights.
It's big, and it's too deep in me.
It feels like it's going to go straight through me.
Too big.
You're feeling it already, huh?
Now that's our Anna-san.
No, not my breasts.
She is one of our best advanced members here.
I guarantee you that she can change Kokudou Academy.
Anna?
Kokudou Academy?
Because my organization has the best women around,
that gives me a tremendous preemptive advantage!
Though, in case the male members
have already grown tired of them,
they'll immediately be sent out.
It's hot.
Is it over already?
Oh wow.
It's still stiff.
Of course, even if we do send them out,
we would never completely set them free.
It is very important that I keep this
organization's secrets unknown.
And at that time, they'll probably be already
sinking to the bottom of the sea as corpses.
This is...!
The insides are sucking me in.
That can't be...
Wake up already, Anna.
You must not go.
Go back to your old cheerful self.
I swear, I'm going to save you from this hell,
with my very own hands.
It's thick, and stinky...
Delicious.
My cute Anna-chan is covered in semen.
Well then, here I go.
It tickles!
Did you bring it already?
I love you.
I love everyone.
Your cock, and my pussy...
I love feeling good.
I'm cummmg.
Oh, it suits you quite well Anna-chan.
Anna-chan's pussy!
It becomes exposed as the white skirt gets
pulled up, and it looks very tender!
Anna!
Onee-chan?
We're getting out of here.
You're just being tricked by them.
The edification ritual.
The self-enlightenment seminars.
Everything's scam!
They were just using you from the very beginning!
To them, we are simply outlets for their own carnal desires.
If we stay any longer,
everyone will get killed!
Anna?
The one who doesn't understand is you.
What I really feel.
You should already know, and yet you still don't!
No, I guess you could never have understood.
You're the one at fault.
It's all because you were too perfect.
Open your eyes Anna!
We need to get out of here.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
My, oh my, Onee-chan.
That's just messy of you to pee there.
How filthy.
Can't be helped though.
Here, let me clean that for you.
It hurts, it hurts!
Stop, stop, Anna!
Amazing!
Onee-chan just grew a cock!
It's wonderful.
That's wonderful, Onee-chan.
What are you
I'm one with Onee-chan now.
I'm happy.
Stop!
Don't move Anna!
This is...
That part... My insides are going to break!
It feels good.
Onee-chan, your thing is hitting deep inside me.
Do you feel great too, Onee-chan?
Come on, make yourself feel better!
I'm going to work hard for it.
I'm going to work hard for you, Onee-chan.
My pussy and her pussy are connected.
It's as if I'm actually inside her.
Your cock is hitting me hard inside.
I'm one with Onee-chan now.
I've loved you for a long time.
I wanted to become like you,
and now I'm having sex with you.
I... I really feel very happy right now.
I feel like going to heaven already.
Anna...
My precious younger sister.
There wasn't a single day that I forgot about you.
I thought you were just going to be cute forever.
But now, you've grown to have a really horny body.
Also, when did you learn to do all this perverted stuff?
This is...
I can't stop...
Anna...
You love me, right?
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum with your stiff thing.
Anna...!
Anna!
I'm cumming.
Oh no,
I came...
Welcome, Sensei.
Please make yourself at home.
Now Sensei, let's get started,
with our extracurricular classes.
Onee-chan...
Let's do it more.
Let's play some more.
The memories that I had after that became fuzzy.
Anna-chan, you're the best!
This is really good stuff!
Here!
Here now.
We're probably going to get stuck in this school.
Amazing, so this is the pussy of the famous Ichinose Riko?
Now it's my turn!
I don't think we'll be able to escape.
Not I, nor Anna.
I'm really loving this school now.
I'm very happy...
I'm cumming.
Everyone, you're all wonderful.
This is the best.
It seems to get really tight when you think you're about to drown.
This is great.
Let me go...
More.
Please give more of the delicious stuff.
Please thrust inside me more.
Release it!
Release it until my pussy is filled!
Cum in me more!
No, please.
No more cumming inside!
I'll be impregnated!
I don't want to get pregnant!
No...!
No butting in line!
If you want to properly do it with me, please fall in line!
I... wasn't able to save her...
But, at least we'll be together forever.
Anna, as long as you are with me...