You don't intend to quit now, do you?
You're our single guarantor.
I am Takayuki's fiancée and a teacher.
I won't quit that easily.
Please, I beg of you.
Anything but that...!
It hurts.
Stop!
Are you familiar with Kokudou Academy?
If you work there, you'll be able to repay me with
something that's worth a few days of payment.
Takayuki-san, please forgive me.
I am now stained.
Your fiancé has been seeing another woman for some time.
He just played you,
and deceived you all along.
That's a lie...
Your pussy is superb as always, Urara-sensei.
It smells great.
Smell that? It reeks of the female scent, Urara-sensei.
The sensation from these tender boobs is also fantastic.
Just like every day, in my plain old private room...
Now, take it the way you always do.
How was it, Urara-sensei?
How was the taste of my semen today?
It was delicious.
Thank you very much, Principal.
End this already!
It's already throbbing in pain.
Oh, is that so?
Then you'll have to beg a little better.
Ochita-sensei.
Please, let my pussy drink all of your semen.
Please cum inside me.
Seems that you've finally learned to love being cummed inside of.
How about you, Urara-sensei?
Can you tell me how many times we have ended this again?
Yes.
28 times while cumming in my mouth.
24 times while cumming on my face,
and 33 times while cumming in my pussy.
Now that's my Urara-sensei.
You really love my cock, don't you?
Yes, I love it.
I love your cock.
It's comin out now.
Where do you want me to cum today?
Cum wherever you like.
Then let's cum over your face.
Please let me be already...
That's enough already, Urara-sensei.
We'll be ending our session for now.
Oh, and I still won't allow you to change or take a bath.
Oh yeah, I was introduced to a rather
interesting place the other day.
There, I saw someone that looked very familiar.
Your ex-fiancé, Saijou Takayuki.
Where did you see him?
Oh? That wasted look on your face
earlier seems to have disappeared.
I see that you really want to meet him.
Where? Where is he?
You probably don't know it yet.
The place is known for their special seminars.
They say it's a place of self-enlightenment.
Please tell me!
What is the name of that place?
The Believe Laboratory.
Believe Laboratory.
I tried looking into it but,
aside from being well known, ironically, there
isn't really any other information about it.
There's also no invitations coming from the organization's leaders,
so there isn't any chance to see what it actually is.
What should I do?
You seem to be troubled about something.
We are...
Spring Urara, The seasons of betrayal and despair chapter
Welcome, Ebihara Urara.
Do you know me?
There is nothing that I do not know.
The wisdom that is granted to me by the heavens,
gives me the power to oversee everything.
Well, these people came to investigate me.
You were invited to go to Kokudou Academy,
and became victim to sexual violence caused
by the teachers and students, correct?
On top of that, you were betrayed by the only
speck of hope that you had, your fiancé.
You, who has been cast off like that, went through the
hell of having forced sex every day, did you not?
How do you know that?
Let's try to get a more precise figure
of your carnal experience, shall we?
The heavens have told me the answer.
Yes, I've been enlightened by you.
Upon going there,
I had sex with the teachers and students
every day, anywhere within the school,
sometimes even for the entire day.
As I attended school each morning,
someone would fuck me faster than I could even open my bag.
The semen that I always hated, they
forced me to learn how to drink it.
And after my body remembered the sensations,
I couldn't stop masturbating every night.
What should I do?
You should release the hidden power within you.
That is what this organization, the Believe Laboratory, stand for.
Your ex-fiancé, Saijou Takayuki,
is indeed here in the Believe Laboratory.
Please let me meet him!
need to speak with him!
He is currently in the middle of his training.
He feels ashamed of himself.
Everything started with the carnal desires
that came from within one's self.
He came here to atone for his sins,
and has immersed'himself in a harsh
and rigorous training program.
He has...?
If you want to meet your ex-fiancé.
You need to relinquish the sex life that you have lived before.
Are you capable of following my guidance?
Yes, I'll do anything.
So please, let me meet him!
Here, we'll guide you to the seminar room.
It is your first time here, correct?
We'll be starting with this basic course, before
moving on to a more advanced one.
Please change into the seminar uniform
we have prepared over there.
Right here, right now?
Is there anything wrong?
You cannot wear underwear, by the way.
You also cannot let yourself drown in
the pleasures of sexual intercourse.
Let your mind flow just like water or air.
And then, as you take control over your own sexual desires,
the path will open towards a bright future with your fiancé.
As I see it the reason why you are
intoxicated with sexual pleasure,
is because you have little control over your physical body.
T-That's...
Well then, let us begin.
What are you going to do?
No!
Don't!
Ouch...!
We can't do this among women...!
There is no escape.
No...!
Please don't lick It!
Ebihara-san, you must not feel horny.
To feel horny is to expose the weakness in your heart.
That's right, you cannot submit to your sexual desires.
You can't do this!
If you do that, I'll...
Oh no...
You have to hold on.
Even if this is done to you!
Your insides are hot, and dripping wet.
My fingers feel like they're going to melt.
can't hold on...
I'm cumming.
Oh my, she's wet all over.
No, this isn't...
Ebihara-san.
It has been decided that you will take the special treatment.
No...
Stop...
Just what kind of treament is this?
If you intend to resist, then just leave.
It hurts.
No...!
Don't!
My breasts are...
My breasts are going to be torn off!
If you can't resist this,
then you won't be able to endure the following training sessions.
You're right, Onee-chan.
Zenkou-sama's thing is even more amazing!
This body is really lewd.
Each time I thrust it in, your pussy wraps it tighter and tighter.
Please don't say that.
I'm not lewd...!
My insides are about to burst!
Please don't rub this stiff thing in me too much!
Yes...
You may not be qualified for the next training session after all.
Are you fine being unable to meet your fiancé?
I'm sorry!
But I...
I can't take it anymore!
I'm...
Oh my, how dirty of you to pee here.
It seems that she is still ill-prepared to accept our faith.
You're right.
She's a failure.
I'll have you understand our organization's devotion.
I'll introduce you to the special training session, Ebihara Urara-san.
Good morning.
Today is the long awaited day for our seminar group.
Our leader, Majima Zenkou-sensei, will provide
us with his teachings yet again.
Now, here comes Zenkou-sensei!
It's Zenkou-sama's voice!
Where is he?
It's Zenkou-sama!
He has finally arrived!
I am truly grateful!
It's as if they are welcoming some kind of savior.
Believe!
Ebihara-san.
Trouble comes to the one who passes the
chance to  participate in this gathering.
No... Well, I'm still not really.
I can see through to your very core.
You are deeply possessed with a malicious entity.
And it has perfect control over you.
That can't...
don't actually feel anything different.
I see, you don't even realize it,
but it has already invited countless misfortunes.
If we don't start the exorcising ritual soon, it may be too late.
Now then...
Let us all begin.
The ritual of edification!
Edify!
This may be a wonderful edification.
Now, enter inside me.
Thrust inside to my deepest parts.
Geez, you're rather impatient.
Hurry up.
Now, we don't have time to waste.
In order to expel the demons within you.
You must never feel horny.
The demons will devour you the moment that you do.
Don't lick there...
This is embarrassing.
Stop...
You must endure it.
The demons are corrupting you as we speak.
Lots of it is coming out...
You're really too hasty...
Wow!
Oh wow!
This is wonderful.
Oh, what's this? You can't seem to endure it.
You're even dripping wet now.
These demons are quite fierce.
It's only a matter of time before they completely devour you.
We must do whatever is necessary to stop it.
What should I do?
I shall edify the empty space within you with this!
You don't intend to...
No!
You can't do that!
I'm going to break!
To resist my will is equivalent to submitting to your pleasures.
Here I go.
Edify!
See? You already came as I entered you.
Just how much carnal desire are you withholding?
It's too thick, my breath is...
That's just half of it.
The real edi ication starts here!
Here I come!
It's inside me.
Amazing.
It's in deep as it can be, and I feel like my pussy is going to break.
But...
It's my first time feeling something like this.
It feels good.
It feels great!
Please, rub It in me more.
This is troubling.
already told you that you must never be horny.
That opening is making such an obscene sound.
Very well.
I shall accept this challenge then!
Yes..
It feels great!
My insides are getting turned inside out as it thrusts in.
It's tingling deep inside.
Thrust it! Thrust it into me more!
This feels good!
I'm cumming.
What a despicable sight!
It seems that you've been completely
overtaken by this lewd body of yours.
I don't care if I'm lewd.
I want to cum.
I want to cum more!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum again!
Oh wow!
Why don't we release it now then?
My special secretion!
I don't want to get pregnant.
Please, please release it outside.
For you to receive my power,
It has to reach deep inside you.
Please don't.
Not today.
I'll get pregnant if you cum inside me...
No!
Edify!
No way, you came inside...
What a formidable demon that is.
Everyone, let us cleanse Ebihara-san with all of our powers!
No!
That's no good.
You have to drink it all up.
The semen from these men will cleanse and exorcise it.
All these strangers are cumming inside me.
No need to hold back.
Deliver everything that you can to Ebihara-san.
Drink this.
This one too.
I'm going to cum inside.
I'm sorry.
But I can't take this anymore...
Make sure to drink it all.
I can't do this anymore.
Someone came inside me again.
Hey, still not done?
My thing here is getting tired of waiting.
That's...
This is exactly the method that is used for edification.
I expect you to savor every bit of it.
Open it.
Open your mouth.
No more.
can't take this anymore.
I'm going to drown in this.
I don't know... what's happening anymore.
My mind is going numb.
Please don't make me cum anymore.
As expected of my regular seminar attendees.
You have wonderfully edified her.
Now, for the last part.
It's not over yet?
No more please.
I can't move anymore...
There's no need to hold back.
As the ending ceremony to this gathering,
I shall pour my divine punishment into you!
No...
My insides are already full.
Edify!
My insides are... very full.
The verdict has been decided.
it is already too late for you,
and for your fiancé as well.
It is unfortunate,
but we were unable to save you from your demons.
Your ex-fiancé, Saijou Takayuki, is not his real name.
His real name is...
Kaji Tomoyuki.
As you can see, he is currently working for Believe Laboratory.
Look, that's your senior at your previous workplace, right?
She's actually a regular here.
Okita Asuka.
Do you understand now?
They already planned to betray you from the very beginning.
Oh yeah, I have some more tasty news to tell you.
She seems to be pregnant already.
Bearing his child.
They're always having sex like that.
All the while knowing that Kaji was your fiancé.
Believe...