Even now, Onee-san is still the legendary model!
Anna was very worried about not getting
enough work as a gravure idol.
They took advantage of her from that.
No!
Stop it!
It hurts! You can't!
Don't move!
The self-advancement seminar: Belief's Laboratory.
I've won against Onee-chan!
Have you heard of the Kokudou Academy?
It's a boys' school with quite a bit of problems.
At this moment, I'd never think that I'd have
such connections with this school.
No, no, when it comes to our students it's
either fighting or destruction of property.
There have been complaints every day for quite a while.
They'll attack anyone passing by just
because they made eye contact,
so right now there's no one who's willing to come near here.
It's very, very sad.
The teachers quit right away, too, so
not much of classes is happening.
Well, there are hardly any students
who show up in the first place.
Oh my. That must be lots of hard work.
It's tasty... it tastes very good...
Zenkou-sama...
I love this... I love this!
If that's the case,
shall I send a Clergy from Belief's Laboratory
to help your students?
Oh! That would be greatly helpful.
Well I also have a proposal.
There happens to be a student who wants to release herself.
I will ask her to join Belief's Laboratory...
Yes, please guide her well.
A penis is stirring up my insides...
It's rubbing... yes!
It is a student called Mizushima Kaho...
RINxSEN + Ran-Sem Cross Mix.
Presented by Erobeat | http: //www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Long Live the Religion of Lust!
Excrement can go inside Riko's mouth... Arc.
It's not just about jerking at it with force.
There's also a regulation of strength of the stimulation.
Yes...
Be careful not to let it hit your teeth.
Once you're used to it, try taking it in deep.
That's right,
like it's opening your throat.
Focus your consciousness.
There's no need to be in a hurry.
Try to pay attention to how the penis is moving.
That's right, start slowly and carefully.
"Release’’ is the essence of Belief's Laboratory.
To take “release" to its furthest extent, gives
true happiness to your mental world.
Then you can reach the a higher realm.
Adjust the angle and depth while making
sure the clitoris hits the penis.
Like this?
That's right. Keep it up.
You can't...
No!
Ichinose-Sensei, please take care of me!
Ichinose-sensei!
Sensei!
Alright.
How is it?
The body of a past model.
How is my pussy?
Sensei's body is the best!
The stimulation from your fingers is making
me go numb all the way to the head!
Ah your tongue... My dick is gonna melt!
Everyone, please release yourselves more and more!
Release every day will lead to a true healthy body and mind!
Now everyone, release the stagnations in your
heart deeply inside each other's body!
Release!
Release! Release! Release! Release!
I'm at my limit... I'm going to release!
I'm gonna release as well!
Me too!
Can I release!
It's alright. Go ahead and release yourselves!
Me too, I'm going to...
Cumming, cumming, cumming, cumming...
Release!!
Thank you very much.
I had the best release.
Well done. Please work hard tomorrow as well.
Once you qualify for the high level course, you
can cum inside me as much as you want, okay?
Yes!
Great work!
Thanks for the great work!
The shower is empty now!
I got creampied without permission again...
Me, too...
Thank you for your hard work.
Your coaching was wonderful today as well, Ichinose-san.
Thank you, Sakaki-san.
It hasn't ended for you today?
Yeah, not yet...
Is there something bothering?
No...
How were the students of the seminar today?
Yes, everyone was very eager and... learned very fast...
They will become great believers for sure...
I've been thinking of appointing you to be the
partner of the president of a large enterprise.
Thank you very much.
I'll work hard.
Um,
Anna didn't appear at today's seminar...
Have you heard anything?
I haven't heard anything.
Huh?
Hey, look at that.
Anna?
Anna...
Really?
Unbelievable.
Actually?
Amazing!
Here it comes!
Nice, nice, nice!
Good!!
Really?
Amazing...
Unbelievable...
Look... at me...
Look at me... at me!
I can't resist!
She's amazing with that cute face!
I... I can't hold back anymore!
I'm so happy...
You guys... what is this about?
Let go of me!
Ichinose-Sensei, we can't hold back anymore.
We definitely can't wait until we rank up!
We want to have sex with Sensei right now! Please!
No!
You can't! You can't do it... in somewhere like this!
No! Stop it!
Hmm? Sensei, you're wet.
Don't say such ridiculous...
Hey, wait...
I'll put it in.
No! Don't!
You can't! Pull it out!
This is against the rules...
Amazing. So this is Ichinose-Sensei's...
Amazing.
Although he has no technique, he's young and energetic.
M-My voice will leak out!
But if I let out my voice... We'll be found!
They're so hot and hard... young penises...
Unbelievable...
For someone like me to be over powered and violated by
younger boys in such a dark, dirty comer of the hallway...
Sensei... I'll cum... I'm going to cum!
By cumming you don't mean... are you going to let it out!?
No! Not inside! You can't cum inside!
Cumming! Inside... I'm cumming inside!
No!
I let out lots...
You guys... do you understand what you've done?
Something... Something like this...
Sensei's insides are the best!
What this? It's longer and reaches
deeper than the previous one...
Amazing!
More!
Rougher!
Something this amazing...
I'll get carried away...
Cum!
Cum while looking at me!
I feel good, too... I feel good from everyone watching me...
I like this!
I love being watched! I love it!
You felt so much... from watching Anna...
Thank you, everyone!
Sensei... Sensei!
I let it out... inside...
Sensei, I like you!
It's so wonderful!
Takayuki-san... a large one is going in and out of me...
It's Okida-Sensei!
Anna?
An-...
It hurts...
Oh, this is wonderful.
Oh my I have received a great offering.
With this my release will surely reach a new level!
It's too big and too large...
It'll break through my stomach...
I can't breathe...
Has she done it already? As expected from Anna-san!
My boobs... not my boobs!
She is a high level Clergy and a pride of our Laboratory.
She will definitely change Kokudou Academy!
Anna... Kokudou Academy?
After all, we have gathered the best women here.
All chosen through very rigorous selection.
In exchange, if they lose their lust or bore the male believers,
We get them to quit without mercy.
It's so hot!
Is it the end already?
Amazing!
It's still hard!
Of course, even if we make them quit, we can't just let them go.
The secret of our community must be protected by all means.
At that time...
They’ll sink into the oceans as a corpse...
This is... She's convulsing inside!
No!
No way...
Open your eyes and wake up, Anna.
You can't leave!
Please return to the bright and cheerful you back then.
I will definitely save you
from this hell with these hands!
It's so thick...
And stinky...
Tasty!
The cute Anna-chan is covered in my dirty semen!
Well, here we go.
It tickles!
Did you bring it for me?
I love it! I love everyone! Dicks and pussies too!
I love things that feel good!
Cuming! It's coming out, coming out!
Oh, it suites you very well, Anna-chan!
Anna-chan's pussy! So soft and squishy
showing from that white skirt!
Anna!
Huh?
Onee-chan?
Run away, Anna.
You're being tricked by those people!
Stuff like “release” or “self-advancement seminars" are all lies!
You've been used from the start!
We've just been use to satisfy their sexual desires!
If we keep going on,
we'll all be killed!
An-Anna...
It's Onee-chan that doesn't understand.
What feelings I had had...
Even though you should have known...
You didn't understand!
No... there was no way you could've understood!
It's your fault! It's Onee-chan's fault for being too perfect!
Wake up, Anna! You have to run away!
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up!
Shut up!
It hurts!!
Geez, Onee-chan, pissing yourself like that.
So sloppy.
Geez, so dirty.
Guess it can't be helped. Here, Let's clean you up.
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop it! Please stop it!
No!
Amazing!
A penis is inside Onee-chan!
Beautiful... the beautiful Onee-chan...
What are you...
I'm connected with Onee-chan!
I'm so happy!
Stop! Don't move, Anna!
Something like this...inside... I'll break down there!
Yes!
This feels good!
Onee-chan is reaching deep inside!
Does Onee-chan feel good as well?
More... let's feel better and better!
I'll... work hard! If it's for Onee-chan, I'll work hard!
My pussy... is connected with Anna's pussy...
It's as if... I'm violating Anna...
Onee-chan is reaching deep inside!
I've become one with Onee-chan!
I've always... always loved you!
I wanted to become Onee-chan!
To think that I could have sex with you...
I... I'm so happy... I could die!
Anna... my...irreplaceable sister...
There's no day that I've forgotten about you.
I hoped that you'd stay cute and pure forever...
You've grown into such a lewd body, haven't you?
And these erotic things... when did you learn them?
This is so... irresistible!
Anna... You are willing to love me...
I'm cumming... cumming from Onee-chan's hard thing!
Anna! Anna!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
No! Anna!
I came...
Welcome, Sensei.
Please hang around for a bit more.
Well, Sensei, let's start the extra lessons, shall we?
Onee-chan, more! Let's play more together!
My memory from then has blurred out.
Oh, Anna-chan is the best!
Amazing!
There!
C'mon!
I suppose we've been trapped in this horrible school...
Amazing, so this is the pussy of that famous Ichinose Riko!
My turn next!
It doesn't seem like well ever be able to escape from here.
I... Anna...
I've really gotten a liking into this academy!
Anna is so happy!
Cu-cumming!
Everyone is amazing!
This is the best!
The moment you think you'll drown... you squeeze real tight!
This is great!
Please forgive me...
Not yet?
Hey, don't push.
Human Toilet
More! Give me more tasty stuff!
More! Rougher!
let it out, let it out! Let it out until you fill my pussy!
Let out more!
Please! Don't let out anymore!
No!
I'll get a baby! I don't want to get pregnant!
Don't jump the queue!
If you want to do it with Anna then stay in line!
...couldn't save her...
But...
We'll always be together now.
Anna...
As long as I have you...