You're not thinking of quitting, are you?
You hold liability as well.
I'm TakayuKi-san's fiancé and a teacher.
I'm not going to quit.
Please! I beg you! Anything but that!
No!
It hurts! It hurts! Stop! Stop!
Have you heard of the Kokudou Academy?
If you work there for a month, I can help with the interest.
Please forgive me, Takayuki-san.
I've been tainted.
Your so called fiancé has been going
out with someone for quite a while.
You’re nothing but a toy for entertainment.
You've been fooled all along.
No way!
Men's Room Meat Urinal
Urara-sensei's pussy is amazing as always.
Such a good smell. Very thick.
Your whole body smells of me, Urara-sensei.
Your soft boobs are so good it feels like a dream.
It must be from all the protein I give you every day.
Well then, do it just like always.
How does my semen taste today, Urara-sensei?
Yes, it’s delicious.
Thank you very much, Principal.
Please end it, it hurts down there!
Oh really? Then you should ask Kurase-kun
properly right, Okida-sensei?
Please, please let my lewd pussy drink lots of semen.
Please let it out inside me.
Even though you hated getting creampied
so much, you’re completely into it now.
What about you, Urara-sensei?
What kind of finishes have you had up to yesterday?
Yes. I've had... Inside my mouth, 28 times.
On my face, 24 times.
And inside me, 33 times.
As expected from Urara-sensei.
Do you like my dick that much?
Yes, I love it! I love the principal's dick!
It's coming.
Where shall I let it out today?
Please cum, wherever you please!
Let’s go with the face today.
No!
Please, let me go!
That’s enough now, Urara-sensei.
I'll leave it here for today but,
you're still not allowed to change or shower, okay?
Oh by the way, I was invited to an
interesting place a few days ago.
And I saw someone who looked very alike to...
your fiancé, Saijou Takayuki.
Takayuki-san!? Where was that!?
You get energetic the moment you hear his name.
You must really love him.
Where, where is he?
You probably don't know about the place.
It's a very popular seminar that’s been going on recently.
Something about self-discovery.
Please tell me! What is the place called?
Belief's Laboratory.
I've tried looking up, but there s hardly any
information about it despite its fame.
You're not even allowed to attend without an invitation.
What should I do...
You look like you're troubled.
We are...
RINxSEN + Ran-Sem Cross Mix.
Presented by Erobeat | http: //www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: Piroko | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Spring, the Season of Betrayal and Despair Arc.
Welcome, Ebihara Urara-san.
You... You know me?
There is nothing I don't know.
The gods have given me power to see through everything.
Um, so these two came up to me...
You work at the Kokudou Academy,
and have been assaulted sexually by the teachers
and students there, haven't you?
In addition to that, your fiancé and only hope, has betrayed you.
With a destroyed soul you've been living
in depravity and sex up until today.
Am I right?
How do you know?
Shall I tell you what kind of sex you've been having as well?
Cum in Mouth: 28x |Cum on Face: 25x | Cum Inside: 33x
The skies have given the answers!
Yes, to me!
Ever since that day,
I've had sex every day at all sorts of places in
the school with the students and teachers.
Sometimes I'd have non-stop sex for the entire day.
Before I even have time to put my bag away every morning,
someone would push me down, and put his penis inside me.
I’m able to drink the semen I once hated now.
And since I remember the pleasure of cumming,
I can’t stop masturbating even after I come home.
What should I do...
Release one’s hidden strength by self-discovery,
is the purpose of the seminars at Belief's Laboratory.
Your fiancé's name is Saijou Takayuki, right?
He has indeed been here.
Please let me see him! I need to talk to him!
He is in training at the moment.
He feels very ashamed of what he’s done.
And the misfortune you’re going through
because of his uncontrolled lust.
He is working and going through tough
training in order to redeem himself.
He is...
Huh?
In order to see your fiancé, are you willing
to quite the life of sex you had.
And follow my guidance?
Yes! I’ll do anything, so please let me see him!
Well please go ahead into the seminar room.
It is your first time here, right?
Well then...
Please attend this basic lecture that will prepare
you for the special lecture coming up.
Please change into the seminar clothing on the chair.
Right here right now?
Did you have any questions?
Please take off your underwear as well.
You cannot let yourself fall into the pleasures of sex.
Please think of it as air or water.
Once you have overcome the pleasures sex brings,
you'll be facing a bright future with your fiancé.
From what I can tell, the reason you can't
overcome the pleasures of sex,
is because you have yet controlled your lustful body.
T-Th t’s not true...
Well, let's begin.
What, what are you going to do?
No!
No! You can't! It hurts!
But we're both girls!
I won't let you get away.
No! Don't lick down there!
Ebihara-san, you shouldn't be feeling it.
Feeling pleasure is the signs of a weak heart.
That's right, if you lost yourself in pleasure, you'll fall again.
No! If you suck that much...
That"s right, you have to bear it.
Even if I do this!
It’s so hot and slippery inside!
My fingers feel like they're gonna melt!
No more... I'll cum! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!!
Wow, it's so sticky.
No... this is...
Ebihara-san. I've decided that you need special treatment.
That's...
No! What kind of treatment is this!?
If you're going to refuse, I guess you'd have to leave.
It hurts! It hurts it hurts! No!
No! My boobs, not my boobs!
If you can't even withstand this, you won't be
able to keep up with the training afterwards.
You're right, Onee-chan. Zenkou-sama's is much more amazing.
What a slutty body, your pussy gets
tighter and tighter as I move.
No way! Don't say that! I'm not slutty or anything...
You'll break me! The hard thing is hitting my womb!
It's good!
Looks like you might not be qualified for the special lecture.
Is it okay to not see your fiancé?
I'm sorry! But I'm, I'm at my limit!
How disgraceful, wetting yourself like that.
She doesn't have enough faith in the beliefs.
I guess she's failing.
Looks like we need you to deepen your understandings.
I shall invite you to the special lecture, Ebihara Urara-san.
RINxSEN + Ran-Sem Cross Mix
Good morning everyone.
Finally, today you will meet the organizer
for our seminar, Majima Zenkou-sensei.
Well, let us welcome Zenkou-sensei.
It's the voice of Zenkou-sama!
Where is he?
It’s Zenkou-sama!
Zenkou-sama has come to us!
Thank goodness!
It's like they’re meeting some kind of saviour...
Believe!
Ebihara-san.
It's a very consequential problem not to join me chant.
That's... I'm still...
I can understand the reason.
You are possessed by a very powerful evil spirit.
It is controlling you.
That's... I don't feel anything...
That right! The evil spirits will bring you
misfortune without anyone noticing!
Oh my!
We must start the extermination ritual
right away or it will be too late!
Well!
Everyone should start as well! The ritual of release!
Yes yes!
Looks like this will become a great release.
Come. Shove it hard into me.
My, you're in a hurry, aren't you?
Hurry!
Come on. We are running out of time.
For the sake of exterminating the demon inside you!
You mustn't feel it.
If you feel it the demon will possess you
to the extent where there is no help.
Not there! It's embarrassing!
Stop...
You must withstand it.
We are racing against the demon inside eroding you.
So much...
You're in too much of a hurry!
Wow! Amazing! You’re hard again!
Oho, never mind with standing, even more
of your love juices are flowing out.
This demon is very strong!
If this goes on you will be completed taken by it.
There's only one way.
What are you doing to do?
I shall release your body with this!
You don't mean...
No! That's won't fit inside!
I'll be torn apart!
Refusing me right now means that you can neither meet him.
The release has arrived!
To climax just from inserting, how much
have your drowned yourself in lust?
It's so thick, I can't breathe...
I'm only half inside, you know?
The real release shall now begin!
It’s inside... amazing...
It's stretching me to the very limits... I think I'll break...
But... It's the first time with something this thick...
It’s good! It feels good!
Please! Please move!
More! It’s rubbing! It feels good!
This is trouble. You've been told so many
times that you shouldn't feel it.
My pussy is making slutty sounds!
Well then. Receive all of it!
It's good, it feels good!
A hard cock is stirring me up inside.
My whole body is going numb!
More! Rub my pussy! My pussy feels good!
I'm cumming! Cumming!
How shameful! You are possessed
by your unbelievably slutty body!
I don't care if I'm slutty!
I want to cum more! I want to cum!
Cumming!
Cumming again! Cumming!
Amazing!
Well it's about time I release myself.
I don't want to get pregnant!
Outside, please let it out outside.
For my powers to work, I must do it deep inside your body.
No! I’m not safe today! I’ll get a baby!
No!
Release!
No! Not inside...
What a powerful evil spirit.
Well! Why don't we all help cleanse Ebihara-san!
No!
My turn!
No no, you have to drink it all.
It is the sex fluids of males that will help clean you.
Someone I don't know poured his semen inside me...
Don't hold back.
Let out all your releases inside Ebihara-san!
Please drink it!
Mine too!
I'll cum inside you!
No! I’m going to come again!
Don't spill any out.
I can't drink an more!
Please stop cumming!
Inside again...
Why aren't you done yet?
Everyone's waiting!
Not there!
That’s the highest technique for the release.
Take your time to savour it.
Open your mouth!
I can't... drink anymore...
I’ll drown in semen...
I can't think straight anymore.
I’m going to become retarded!
Don't make me cum anymore!
As expected from the students of the seminar.
What a well done release.
Well, time to finish up.
More? I can't take it anymore.
I can't even move...
You don't have to hold back.
Well, for the finale, I shall release my power inside you!
No! My stomach can't fit anymore!
Release!!
My stomach is... so full...
I'll announce the results:
It was too late.
Both for you and your fiancé.
It's a shame, but I wasn't able to save you from the demon.
Saijou Takayuki was a fake name for your fiancé.
His real name is...
Kaji Tomoyuki.
Right now, he's working at Belief’s Lab like this.
See? That's your senpai at your workplace, right?
She works here, too.
Okida Asuka-san.
Do you get it now?
They both planned to betray you from the very beginning.
Oh by the way, one more thing.
Apparently she's pregnant.
With his baby.
They having sex like that every day.
Knowing that you're his fiancé.
Be...
Believe...
love love hiramekanai
Love, love. Without shine.
ase wa mune no hire
Sweat decorates my chest.
aa utsurona shisen no saki m wa
Ah, what lies beyond that hollow gaze?
down down tometai
Down, down, I want to stop it,
shinobiko myuuwaku
the temptation appearing silently.
ara shiteruka mata tokete iku
Ah, did you know? It’s still going to melt away,
ochite iku
and fall down.
kokoro ka kazoete
My heart is counting,
kogoeru sadameyo
the destinies being frozen.
konoyode hitotsu
The one thing in this world,
nakusenaiyo nakusenai
I'll never let go, never gonna lose.
watashi no kimochi
Are my feeling,
todoiteru kana
reaching you like I hope?
anata no hitomi
If your eyes can,
kashi no youni harete lku nara
Shine like they once did.
Kieteiku sekiamo
Then the world vanishing is nothing
amai yuuwaku
but a sweet temptation.