I'm Rune.
I work at a pharmacy here in the island of Tiara.
One day, a debt collector named
Shalban came to meet me.
I learned that my father owed
a ridiculous sum of money.
I got caught by an orc on my way home from finding an Yggdrasil flower...
I got soiled with his semen as well.
When I was lost on how to earn money,
I got tricked and recklessly raped.
A lot of terrible things were done to me.
However, I've already decided
to become a fully fledged
pharmacist like dad and mom.
I still have a lot of debt to pay,
but I will do my best!
The Pharmacist of Tiara Island
W-Wow...
A lady living in such a mansion
went out of her way to request for me.
Come in.
I already saw several doctors,
but never someone as cute as you.
P-Pleased to meet you.
I'm Erunelle Odette, an apprentice pharmacist.
My name is May Roseline.
You don't have to be so tense.
May I perhaps call you Rune-chan?
Yes!
I am so glad to meet you.
Huh? W-Wait...
Forgive me for startling you.
This is the condition I am in.
Whenever it becomes like this,
it won't just settle down.
I-I am hopeless!
Being seen like this is very embarrassing for me,
but I can't help myself throbbing down here.
M-Mei-san...
P-Please, will you lend me a hand?
Unless I vent enough of my lust out,
my dick stays hot and won't get well!
I-I understand! If it's something
within my capacity...
Rune-chan, you're cute! You are so cute!
Both of your lewd ass, and tits which look really soft...
Oh, no!
My cock feels so good!
P-Please don't stare too much.
I-It's embarrassing...
I'm sorry for dragging you into this.
No way... If she keeps being this gentle with me,
I'll end up feeling weird even when both of us are girls!
Rune-chan, your skin is silky smooth and fair.
Your nipples are pink too,
and they became hard already.
I don't have such a pleasing body.
Monsters and humans alike already had
my body defiled lots and lots of times.
That's not true at all.
Rune-chan, you're not defiled at all!
No way, that's my... Not down there!
Your pussy feels hot and it's now dripping wet.
So, you're feeling it.
N-No, don't say that!
No way! D-Don't!
It's alright, I am the same as you right now.
Doing naughty things to you
makes me feel very very excited!
M-May-san, me too...
I want to do it to you as well.
N-No, Rune-chan!
If you... If you do it that hard...
I'll immediately...
It's alright, shoot it out. Don't hold back.
Shoot it out to relieve yourself!
You too, Rune-chan...
Let's feel good together!
No way...
Mei-san's tongue feels warm
and it makes me feel so good!
I-I'm slowly getting naughtier as well...
I can't stop myself!
I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
Rune-chan, forgive me! I'm sorry!
It's coming out!
Th-This is not good, It won't settle
down after coming only once!
Rune-chan, I can't hold myself back anymore!
It's alright.
Please use my body in any way you want.
Your pussy is wonderful!
It keeps on clenching and sucking my cock inside!
It feels so good, it feels like I'll drown in pleasure!
Your puffy tits are hitting mine and
they're rubbing against each other.
I-It makes me feel so good!
Hey... Rune-chan...
Do you love my cock?
Say it! Say that you love it!
Mei-san, your cock is hard, thick and huge...
...and I love it!
Your pussy is squeezing me tightly!
I'm deep... I'm reaching deep inside you!
Please, keep doing it more!
You can be reckless on my pussy!
Mess it up! Stir it up into a soppy mess!
Rune-chan, I'm gonna come!
I will come lots and lots
inside your pussy, okay?
I never knew about it before.
I never thought that intercourse...
That sex can feel this good!
It's... It's the first time that I felt
like this... I feel so heavenly!
R-Rune-chan...
You're shaking your hips so much on your own...
You're naughty... You are so lewd!
I'll work hard...
I'll work hard to ease the pain of your cock!
I'm coming already, I'm coming again!
My cock is, it's going to ejaculate!
Come... I'm about to as well!
We'll be coming together!
R-Rune-chan!
I can't take it anymore! I can't!
My body is burning and I'm about to go crazy!
I'm coming... I'm coming... I'm coming!
No! No!
Let's do it together, the two of us...
Here is a medicine that I brewed.
If you drink this when your body is throbbing,
it will alleviate that feeling.
Rune-chan... I truly am grateful to you.
I already am feeling alright, and it's all thanks to you.
No... If I only had more herbs,
I could've made an even better medicine
for you, Mei-san. That's why...
Are you going there, after all? To the Glow Pass...
Yeah, that place has a lot of medicinal herbs.
It also seems that a magical item called
"Blue Rose Wand" is hidden out there somewhere.
But aren't there plenty of
dangerous monsters in that place?
Try not to put yourself in danger, alright?
O-Okay...
But I have to do this, right?
If I can just stroll around and have people say
"Aren't you cute, I'll give you money." to me,
that will be such a great life.
W-Wow...
This is amazing!
I wonder if the wand is somewhere in here.
Wh-What's that?
A-A female human!
A-A cyclops?
A woman... A woman!
N-No!
No, don't lick me!
I'm sticky... I'm sticky all over!
Yummy... It's yummy!
A woman's body is...
N-No... No!
I-It feels gross!
I-I'm begging you, stop licking my body!
Don't! Let me go already!
No way! No!
I can't wait any longer...
N-No way, stop... I can't take
something that huge!
Ouch!
No, don't! Stop...
You can't!
No... D-Don't move...
Ouch... It hurts!
Pussy! Pussy!
No way!
His huge thing is mashing up my insides!
I-If this goes on, I'll end up dead... I'm gonna die!
I am... I am about to plant my seeds in you!
No way! No, I don't want that!
Stop! I-I'm begging you...
Don't shoot inside! No!
No—!
Th-There's so much of your hot stuff inside me!
I'm begging you! Let me go already!
Y-You'll break me... I'll break!
No—!
Pussy... I love human pussies!
They're so tight! They're the best!
N-No! Stop thrashing your dick around!
Any more... Any more than this and my body will...
Plant my seeds... I will plant my seeds!
Again... I'll get creampied again!
He'll ejaculate inside me!
I'm already at my limit!
Somebody, somebody help me—!
Your pussy is squeezing me!
You and me, we're highly compatible!
That's not true! You're wrong! There's no way...
You! Don't lie!
The truth is, your pussy is feeling it!
You're feeling good!
I-I'm getting more and more indecent.
It's because I'm getting raped a lot all of the time...
I'm coming!
I will come together with you!
Stop...
I'm coming!
I can't, I can't!
I'm starting to feel good...
I can't!
No! I-I don't want to come!
I don't want to come, but...
Rune-chan...
I-I still want to do more...
I still want to do more!
No—!
N-No—!
There it is!
With this, I'm sure that...
Magic wand, please...
Lend me your power!
I see...
It seems that you went through so much.
And this is what you got afterwards?
Yes... I'm sorry.
I only barely escaped so that's the only one I got...
Whatever, ten thousand...
No, I'll take this at the price
of twenty thousand gold.
Thank you!
Erunelle Odette, huh...
Someday, this girl will...
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization