This is the tranquil island of Tiara.
I lived a happy and fulfilling life
on this island lush with bountiful flora.
That was the case, until yesterday...
Dad, mom...
I am now alone.
I can't just keep on crying like this, right?
I have to get a hold of myself!
The Pharmacist of Tiara Island
That's weird...
Mom always said that you can pick them up one after another around here.
My name is Erunelle.
Everyone just calls me "Rune".
I'm still in the middle on my studies
as an apprentice pharmacist.
Oh, there it is!
The flower of Yggdrasil...
If I manage to brew this using magic, then...
Just a little more!
I wonder why I always couldn't do it...
Hey, young lady.
What are you doing in a place like this, oink?
It's a tiny female critter, oink.
You'll make such a nice plaything, oink!
No... Don't come any closer!
Oink!
No—!
Enough of your futile resistance, oink.
I'll give you lots of love using this thing, oink!
N-No way...
Stop!
It stinks!
No—!
I knew it! Human mouth-pussies are the best, oink!
Th-This is suffocating me!
I can't... I can't breathe!
Stop, stop!
First, I'm gonna shoot one out, oink!
What? What is he planning to do?
What is this thing?
It's hot and gooey... It tastes bitter!
Hey, hey... We're not done with just this much, oink.
It can't be... No way!
I-It's not over yet?
My cock juice is special, oink.
You'll be in heat and unable to endure it
when you take it in into your body, oink!
No way! My body is on fire!
Wh-What did just happen to me?
There, there! Swallow my cock juice,
and you'll gradually feel lewder, oink!
N-No, stop!
Don't come anymore! No—!
We're far from done! We're just
about to get on the good part, oink!
No... Stop!
No... No!
And after that,
I've been forced to swallow an
orc's semen over and over again.
More! More, oink!
Stroke my cock with your tits, oink!
I'm begging you, let me go already!
You're saying that
but look at how slushy your pussy has become, oink.
You're feeling good from this, oink!
No, no! Don't stir me up there!
Y-You're wrong!
There's no way that I'm feeling good!
Look at these, your nipples are stiff, oink!
No, don't say that!
Even though I shouldn't feel good
from this... I shouldn't get aroused!
I can't get enough of rubbing against your stiff
nipple, oink! I'll spray it on you again, oink!
No, don't rub it against me anymore!
Something's coming... from deep in my belly...
I feel something coming!
Oh... I can't take it anymore, oink!
I'll shove this into your pussy, oink!
No way, I'm begging you...
Anything... Anything but that!
Don't do this!
Wh-What was that?
So you are here.
You gave me a hard time looking for you.
U-Umm... Who are you?
I am Shalban of the Balfolle Company.
Shalban-san, umm...
Thank you for saving me.
Erunelle Odette,
I came to collect the debt that your father owed.
What on earth is happening here?
Dad, mom... I'm scared!
The remaining debt your father has
is one million gold.
Now that both of your parents are gone,
I have no choice but to collect it from you.
I-I have no way to pay that huge amount!
It's the first time that I heard about this!
Your parents...
I heard that they were experts in brewing magic.
B-But, I'm still an apprentice.
I still can't properly use brewing magic.
It can't be helped, then.
Selling this run-down shop
won't even cover the interest.
Would you rather sell your internal organs?
O-Organs?!
Nah...
Though, aren't you quite a beauty?
If you'll sell your body in the slums,
you'll earn a million gold in no time.
P-Please stop! I can't do such a thing...
Oh well, I'll let you off for today.
However, I'll make sure that you'll settle the debt.
Is that clear?
Wh-What should I do?
I can't do this, after all.
Earning money from doing this kind of thing...
I definitely can't do it!
Hey you, your face tells me that
you're not from around here...
What are you doing here, peeping?
Or do you want to sell your body as well, huh?
Y-You're wrong. I'm, you see...
But since you went here, doesn't that
mean that you have some money issues?
Th-That's, umm...
Alright then, we'll play with you.
Why... Why did I end up in this situation?
Come on, don't hide them.
Let us have a good look!
O-Okay...
Yes, that's good!
You're just a brat but you got some huge racks!
E-Everyone is looking at my naked body.
My embarrassing parts are all exposed!
Okay, shall I have you suck my cock first?
I-I understand.
You have to beg for it.
I told you how earlier, right?
Y-Yes!
I-I'll lick your dick, please let me suck it!
Call it a cock, it's a cock!
I want to suck your cock, I-I'm begging you.
Please let me suck your cock!
I'm being forced to do such things.
Just how miserable have I become?
But I have to endure this.
It's all for the sake of money, so I have to bear this!
Yes, yes, that's the way.
Make sure to take my whole cock deep into you.
No way, it keeps on getting bigger inside my mouth!
It's pulsating and getting hotter!
I can't get enough of this!
I'll use that hole then. Her pussy, I mean.
N-No way...
What's the problem? Isn't that fine?
Don't you want to feel good as well?
I-I, umm... never did that before.
S-So, anything but that.
Hey, hey, hey! Are you for real? I'm so lucky!
Hey, you hoodlums! Hold her still.
No, no!
Let me go! Please let me go!
No, I don't want to!
Idiot... Of course, we can't stop now
that we've already gone this far!
Wow, this is crazy! Her pussy
is squeezing me so tightly!
Ouch!
I-I'm begging you! Pull it out, pull it out!
Don't be so rough on me!
Virgins all talk like that right off the bat.
It's alright, you'll start feeling good in no time!
Come on, keep your mouth working!
Th-They're so cruel!
Even though this is my first time...
This... This is way too cruel!
Okay, it's about time for me to shoot it inside you!
No, he can't!
If he does that, I'll get a baby!
No way, I don't want that!
No, no, no...
You can't!
Hey, no slacking!
It won't be over until you satisfy everyone.
I'm begging you, please let me go already!
I-If this goes on,
you'll break me down... I'll break down!
Shut up, like hell we care about that!
Somebody... Somebody help me!
Dad, mom... Help me, help me!
No one will come to your rescue
even if you weep and cry!
Look, I'm gonna shoot one down here as well!
Stop, don't come inside me anymore!
No, this is turning me crazy!
I don't want this! No, no...
No—!
This girl's pussy is squeezing me tightly like crazy!
Is she about to come?
Here, take a look!
You told us that you're a virgin,
yet your pussy is nothing but slutty!
Stop kidding me!
Why is my body feeling hot again?
They're making a mess of me despite
knowing that I'm inexperienced!
And even though I shouldn't feel good...
I'll give this lewd pussy another creampie,
so you should come together with me!
No, I don't want to! I don't want to come!
I shouldn't even feel good from being forcibly raped!
No, I can't!
I'm feeling lewder and lewder!
I can't hold it in!
Oh, that felt refreshing!
See ya! We're just playing around so it's free!
U-Umm...
Huh?
Don't tell me that you're
seriously whoring yourself out?
You're kidding me, right?
N-No way, that's cruel!
Don't mess around with me, you're just a brat!
If you want money, go around
and whore yourself out more!
I don't want to experience that horrible thing again.
I am clueless about how the outside world works.
Dad and mom have always been
taking care of me up until now.
I want to become a fully fledged
pharmacist like them.
And then, I'm sure that even the debt...
Focus...
Just a little longer...
This time, for sure!
I-I did it! A brewing magic!
Alright!
I think I'll be able to work things out now with this!
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization