Last time, I met the lady in the mansion named May-san.
And, umm...
May-san has a lot in her hands since she has such a body.
That's why I helped by comforting her...
I'm sure that it's also a way of helping others...
Or at least that's my intention.
And after that, I went to search for medicinal herbs.
But I got caught by a cyclops in the cavern.
And yet again...
What should I do?
I feel that I'm getting more and more indecent.
He's forcing himself upon me,
but in the end, he brought me to climax.
H-However, I got a rare item from the enemy.
I still have a huge debt,
but I will work hard!
The Pharmacist of Tiara Island
However, I'm in the same spot yet again today.
It's just as I imagined...
You look very good in those!
U-Umm, my lord...
I am but of lowly birth.
I am not worthy of the honor to tend you, my lord...
Yes, yes, that's right.
You know, seeing pitiful girls
like you worries me so much...
So much that I can't help it!
You have such nice hips.
Your well-filled plump bulges out
when I squeeze them hard.
They bounce right up!
U-Umm... Please... Please stop!
Aren't you in huge debt?
You lost both of your parents. You know that
you have to come up with something, right?
I'm sure that I can be of some help to you.
H-His lordship sits at the highest position on this island.
I might end up being driven out
of our town if I refuse him!
It gently takes the shape of my hand.
This bouncy butt is top-notch!
Yes, that's good!
I love that so much!
If you'll listen for a bit to what I'll say,
I'll pay you plenty.
So, how will it be?
Y-Yes...
Thank you.
I-I'll be glad to...
This is for the sake of repaying the money,
so I need to endure it! I have to!
These round puffs seem to be
brimming with youthfulness and filled with vigor!
I can't get enough of this!
My lord, it's embarrassing here.
People outside might see me.
You might say that, however...
No! No way!
Look, you're already mushy
and soaking wet down here!
No way, I'm...
I'm starting to feel horny again.
If his lordship will put his thing in me right now...
You're a bit tight... That's good as well!
No, I can't!
I'll moan out loud if I lose my focus!
P-People out the window
will notice me! I have to hold it in!
What do you think of my cock, huh?
Yes, it feels good...
It's so splendid...
What about it is splendid?
Come on, say it!
Y-Your dick...
My lord's splendid dick...
...is sturdy and it feels so good!
Yes, yes...
Good girl, that's great!
Thank you...
Please use my body...
...in any way you please!
Make them see how you look from out there.
Come on, wave your hand at them!
No... No!
Don't, no! Don't look!
Please don't look at me!
Yes, that's lovely! Oh, you suddenly got tighter.
It seems that you're quite fond of being watched.
H-He's wrong! This is only embarrassing for me.
I hate being seen by others in such a state, and yet...
No, I can't take this anymore...
I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come already!
I'm coming... I'm coming!
My, oh my...
You're just a maid but you dare
come before your master does.
This calls for some punishment.
My lord!
Please... Please forgive me!
Shall I enjoy myself using this one next?
Th-That's the wrong spot.
That's my assho—
This tightness is incredible!
Is this your first time having anal sex?
Don't move...
My ass... My asshole will split open...
You'll tear it up!
Don't worry.
I'll be making you feel good soon.
This is awful... It feels strange as
he presses inside my belly!
Why? Even though what he's doing hurts...
...my body is gradually feeling hotter!
How is it?
You're amazing down here as well!
N-No... I can't... I can't do this.
F-Feeling good from the ass shouldn't be normal...
Such a thing is...
Do you prefer getting pleasure from the front?
If that's the case...
No way! That's...
Stop!
Here, here, here you go!
No, no!
No way, both of them at the same time...
W-Wow!
Your body is trembling!
Inside me... They're rubbing
against each other inside me!
They're stirring me into a sloppy mess!
I'm begging you! Pull them out! Pull them out!
Then hurry up and satisfy me.
Make me come!
No way! I can't do that! I can't!
I'm about to go crazy!
Coming... I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
Alright, do it.
I'll pour my semen into this filthy asshole!
No, no! No way!
I can't hold it in anymore! It's coming...
Coming... It's coming! I'll again...
Wow... There's so much of it pouring in...
I-It's filling my asshole up...
Oh...
You did a great job.
How did you earn this much?
I-I'd rather not talk about it...
I only have to do work
that'll help other people...
...or that's what I thought to myself.
And yet, I always...
Won't you be able to brew
new medicine using this money?
Huh?
Upon accepting this money from you,
I will lend it back as an investment to a pharmacist.
Gather your materials. Work hard and find
a way to get them for your brewing.
You don't intend to keep wearing
yourself out up until now, right?
I-I see...
Have you heard about a drug
called "Chrono Syrup"?
Y-Yes.
If I'm right, it's an arcane regression
drug that can reverse time.
It is rumored that this so-called
Chrono Syrup is fancied by botanists.
How about it, Erunelle? Can you brew it?
A-Alright!
I'm not sure if I can, but I'll give it a try!
Do your best! Do your best!
I'm sure that I can do this.
Even I have at least improved a little,
and I studied a lot!
This is the arcane regression
drug named Chrono Syrup...
Y-Yes. If you'll use it on plants,
I think that it'll be most effective when diluted with 10 parts of water.
Alright, then. Shall we try it on you first?
Huh? M-Me?
Aren't you the one who brewed this drug?
That's how adults take responsibility.
I-I understand. I'll try it for a bit, then.
H-How is it, Rune-chan?
H-Huh? I'm...
It can't be... Can Chrono Syrup
really do such a thing?
Who are you?
I-I'm York! You are...
Ah, this is bad! Your clothes...
Wear some clothes!
I feel weird.
I feel dizzy, and my groin...
My groin kinda feels tingly.
O-Onii-chan, help me!
O-Onii-chan?
That's right, I have to fix your body.
We'll use this to fix your body, Rune-chan.
Okay, give it a lick.
O-Okay.
Yes, yes... Just like that.
Lick it more like it's ice cream.
Onii-chan, what is this called?
It moves and twitches.
It's a cock.
You see, this is called a cock.
This is a cock...
Onii-chan, I wonder why...
I'm just licking this cock but I feel wobbly.
It's alright. That's good.
More, keep licking it.
Suck it, suck it!
Your cock is getting hotter.
What's happening to it?
Just wait for it.
I have a lot of the medicine stored in it.
I'll give it all to you, Rune-chan!
Okay, Onii-chan.
Give me lots of your cock medicine!
My groin is aching.
I can't bear it any longer!
You're so naughty, Rune-chan!
I'm sorry, my medicine spilled out.
W-Wow...
It's hot and sticky.
This is the medicine from onii-chan's cock.
Just wait for it.
This time, we'll have the medicine
injected inside your body.
Okay...
O-Onii-chan...
This pose is embarrassing!
Bear with it, Rune-chan.
This is a medical treatment as well!
N-No!
It's so big... I can't do this!
It's gonna tear apart!
I'll slowly push it deeper, Rune-chan.
You're a good girl, aren't you?
Bear with it a little more!
Stop...
No!
Alright, the whole thing went in.
I'll start pounding your loli pussy, alright?
Onii-chan, I don't want this.
Don't move... No!
Th-This is amazing...
Such a tiny hole can be stretched wide...
Th-This feels good!
No, don't! This is bad!
If you keep doing that, you'll drive me crazy!
R-Rune-chan, I'm gonna come too!
It's about to come out!
I'll shoot the medicine inside you!
Onii-chan, onii-chan!
Rune-chan, you're incredible.
You're already mushy down here.
It feels like my whole body is tingling.
O-Onii-chan... It feels good, it feels good!
Deep inside me... It keeps on
hitting me deep inside!
It feels good!
Me too... I feel the same!
Your loli pussy is so tight
that I feel like coming again!
It's gonna come out again!
Yes, it's okay... Shoot it out!
Shoot it out! Shoot it out!
Splash lots of it from your cock, please!
Rune-chan, do you like my cock that much?
I like it! I like your cock! I love it!
I want more! Mess me up with your cock!
Yeah, I can't hold it in anymore!
I'll shoot it out!
Me too... I'm gonna come too!
I'm coming, I'm coming...
Your cock... Your cock is making me come!
I'm coming—!
I don't clearly remember it,
but it seems that I ended up having sex again.
My groin... My groin is aching...
Whoa! Wh-What's that?
A-An earthquake? No way...
It looks like quite a huge one!
The truth is that at this night
when the earthquake happened,
I yet again got myself involved
in another strange event.
The story will be continued next time.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization