Darling!
Ikumi!
Darling...
I was just thinking if now is the right time...
For what?
L-Like having a child...
Don't you want to yet?
Of course I want to.
You do? Then...
But aren't you gonna work
on school starting tomorrow?
It's would be bad to already be in
maternity leave right after you start.
Won't us having children
be better at a later time?
I see... You are right.
Ryoujoku Rinne
The Endless Cycle of Humiliation
Ikumi Arc
Here's your packed lunch, darling.
Okay, thanks.
Listen, Ikumi.
We work at the same place starting
today. Wanna go together?
Darling... There's the fact that my
little sister Shizuka goes there.
Also, didn't we already talk
about keeping our relationship
a secret from the students?
Oh, that's right.
I'll be going first then, okay?
Okay.
Don't forget to bring your lunch.
I had put an effort to make you one.
I understand.
I'll be on my way, then. See you later.
Have a safe trip.
She's Sunohara Ikumi-sensei,
who'll be teaching P.E. class.
In her college days, Sunohara-sensei was a schoolmate
of the now retired Kanou Makoto-sensei.
They were both in the swimming team
and was said to be good rivals of each other.
And she became a national candidate
on swimming with her breaststrokes.
She is a woman of great achievements.
I'm looking forward on what
our schools sports education
will become with her as a great addition in it.
Well then, Sunohara-sensei. Now it's your
turn to greet all of our students, please.
I am Sunohara Ikumi that
was just introduced.
I already talked with Vice-principal Oomine
about my teaching portfolio
and I'll only say one thing.
I'll work persistently on everyone of you!
Wow! You're amazing, sensei!
Jeez, onee-chan...
Alright, we're going to practice the "sprint starts".
The meeting for the autumn fest is coming,
so memorize our theme for the ceremony.
Hey, Shizuka. Make yourself busy as well.
Onee-chan...
Call me Sunohara-san when
we're inside the campus.
Sorry.
Sensei, don't be the swimming
team's adviser 'coz they're weak!
Isn't the resistance stronger
when you are moving in the water?
Hey, you shouldn't make fun of adults!
That new P.E. teacher....
Nice body, as expected from a candidate
to fight on swimming competitions.
A schoolmate of Makoto in college...
Please stop this! I'll get angry even if it's you
who do this to me, Yasuno-sensei!
Wait! That... is...
No—!
Yes... Yes... I'll have your child.
With your baby seeds...
With master's copulating semen...
Please impregnate my pussy-womb!
I had a great time with her,
but she's just another sow after she fell from grace.
It's about time for me to start on a new game.
Good work for today, Yasuno-sensei.
May I take my break with you?
Akagi-sensei, haven't you got
yourself such a beautiful wife?
I'm a little jealous.
I never thought that my wife would get
assigned in this school of all places.
Oh, we're keeping it a secret from the students.
That's the reason she is using her maiden name.
I understand.
Oh yeah, here's a new release.
Yasuno-sensei... Where on earth
have you been getting all these?
Well... I have several connections here and there...
However, it's kind of a waste
of time to indulge yourself
with that stuff when you already
have such an adorable wife.
Yasuno-sensei, you're just saying
that since you're a bachelor.
Masturbation and couple sex
are two separate things.
She's a diligent and assertive
woman as you see, right?
At one time, she got so mad on me
when I nonchalantly licked her asshole.
Of course there's no way I can
ask her for some bondage play.
She's going to divorce me!
If I were you, I'd teach her
the pleasures of bondage
even if I end up getting hated.
That's impossible! That's just a
pipe dream of single men!
You'll understand when
you get married as well.
We have the same kinky inclinations after all.
It would be a big scandal if a clergyman gets caught with his kind of hobby!
Well, let me hear about your
comments on that one later.
Okay. It helps to have a comrade of
similar interest in the campus.
It's time for my reward!
I have a good harvest today as well!
Let's see... Oh! This is from
that third year beauty!
Despite having a pretty face,
her shorts has such an erotic scent!
It's moist and has a sour smell,
I can't get enough of these!
That was close...
But who could that be at a time this late?
That's...
Hello, master...
That new P.E. teacher that
you said you're gonna smut...
She's wandering in the campus this late.
I knew it!
Sneakily browsing on people's desk
in the staffroom in the dead of the night,
What do you think you're doing, Sunohara-sensei?
If you're planning to call the cops, then do so!
Your crime will be exposed as well!
What are you talking about?
Quit playing dumb!
Makoto's divorce and sudden disappearance...
I thought it's strange so I investigated it.
You're the one that deceived Makoto!
The evidence for everything are now out!
She seems to be a woman that can be dominated.
We got ourselves a troublesome one, master!
I don't care! This actually saved us some effort!
You're a beast!
You'll only be acting tough now.
Lowly scum! I will never yield
no matter what you do to me!
I know you won't even
have the guts to kill me!
You'll be in jail when the sun rises!
Will it really go that way?
This is amazing!
I have a good view of your beautiful pussy!
No! Stop looking!
Where did your guts from before go?
You have a nice body just as I thought!
I've always been wondering
how P.E. teachers are down here.
I'm going to take a good time finding out.
No—!
Your crotch stinks from just working out!
It smells like a pickled seaweed!
No, stop!
Woah... Such a wonderful clitoris you got!
As I expected, It got a dignified
look fit for a P.E. teacher.
I'll take my time savoring this!
No!
It's encroaching deep inside!
What? What's this?
What's happening? No!
Your tongue... It's jumbling up my insides!
Not there! No!
Stop it! Stop!
Not there!
No... Don't!
No... Not that deep!
You're spreading it open!
Ouch! It hurts!
Sunohara-sensei...
Aren't his tongue skills great?
Sunohara-sensei, did your nipples get hard?
Th-That's not true at all!
Sensei, you're reeking off such a lewd scent!
No!
Let go of me already!
You're starting to make
even more moans, sensei!
No—!
Sunohara-sensei just came.
She's responding well with such sensitivity!
It's too early to get worn out!
The master is saying that he's
gonna give you a lot of loving!
Sensei...
Please stop!
I-I already have a husband!
You already knew that, don't you?
I'm telling you it's fine!
Makoto said the same in the beginning,
but it didn't take long and she can't
come without my penis anymore!
I'm gonna put this inside!
Accept my thing properly, sensei!
No...
So thick...
No—!
Your inside are already drenched!
Your asshole is in plain sight,
isn't that embarrassing?
I'll give that asshole lots of love, but before that...
I'll be caressing you here first, Sunohara-sensei!
You can't!
I said that you're now just a bitch.
From now on, I'll be fucking this body of yours!
Y-You're tearing me apart!
What's wrong? Does it feel good?
You are making such good moans!
No! That's not true!
She's sucking master's fat cock like it's delicious!
Stop watching!
No!
N-No way...
I don't want this, but why...
What's the matter? You started
to squeeze me down there!
Why... why am I... with this...
Forgive me, darling.
I'm sorry... I'm...
I'm... coming—!
You climaxed?
Ikumi, from now on I'll be
teaching that body of yours
all about the pleasures of having men.
Yasuno-sensei, may I have a word with you?
What's with that face? Something wrong?
The truth is, my wife seems yet
to come home since last night.
Might you have any idea?
Huh? As far as I know, she participated
on the newcomer training since yesterday.
Haven't you heard anything
from the School Director?
Huh... Oh, so that was it!
My wife have never spent the night out
without letting me know first before.
Don't worry, they'll be back by tomorrow.
Oh... I was worried and got lost in thought.
But thanks to that, didn't you have
a great chance to watch that DVD?
Ah! That one was excellent!
It got me so riled up!
Yasuno-sensei, I'm looking
forward on the next one!
Now that's something!
Sensei, isn't it about time
for you to give in already?
If you don't, this important place of yours
would end up looking like
something unusable soon!
Who would want to become
your obedient plaything?!
Is that so, then I won't hold back!
Is Ikumi not conceding yet?
Yeah... She's such a stubborn woman!
I see.
Ikumi, how about this then?
He has this hobby of voyeurism
and this is something he caught by chance.
Shizuka!
It looks like your little sister has a boy he likes.
I don't know how she got it.
While sniffing his shorts,
she's doing something like this!
Stop this already! Please delete that!
If this goes out in public,
I wonder what will happen
to your cute little sister.
Is my sister safe?
Worry not, we haven't done anything yet, but...
I'm begging you, don't lay
your hands on my sister!
That depends on how you feel.
You're a demon!
Are you in a position to talk that way back on him?
I understand! I'll just have
to do as you say, right?
Huh, is that the right attitude
when you ask for a favor?
Hey, untie the rope.
I want her to kowtow on me stark naked.
What's wrong? Can't you do it?
I-I'm begging you...
Please spare my sister at least.
That's my—
Who said that you can move?
Don't you care about what
happens to your sister?
Just how miserable do I look now?
But this is for my sister's sake. I must endure this!
D-Don't put your fingers in there!
Is this your first time to have
a finger stuck inside here?
O-Of course it is! Please pull
your finger out already!
Try squeezing my finger
inside your asshole!
That's it... Hmm, you're doing great!
Nice reaction.
Not that!
How is it, Ikumi? How does having a cock
inserted in here for the first time feel like?
You're tearing my asshole apart!
Relax your asshole and accept my thing inside!
Hey, you sow! Make an oath
while I'm ravaging your asshole!
That you'll become Shirou-sama's
slave for all your life!
No... No!
You don't care what happens on your sister?
I'll say it... I'll say it so
spare my little sister!
Then do it! Make a pledge!
Yes! I am Shirou-sama's sow slave!
I'm a female slave for Shirou-sama to fuck for life!
Okay! This should be good enough for a slave!
I'll pour it inside so take everything in!
No... No—!
I-I'm getting peed
inside my ass?!
From now on, you are going to
follow everything that we say.
Is that clear?
Ikumi, are you done with the club activities?
I'm about to get done as well.
No one else's around so how
about we go home together?
I-I'm sorry.
I still have to work for the
upcoming sports festival.
I see...
And also, I'll be home late tonight as well...
Bye, sensei!
Take care on your way home.
Hey, I've been waiting for you, sensei!
Doesn't this clubroom reek of masculine stench.
This is a perfect place for your training!
I'm gonna be training you a lot.
Let me have a look.
You're craving for it a lot,
you're ass is drenched!
So much for a P.E. teacher!
I can't get tired of this! Stinky!
Good job not getting found out by the students.
You can't take it anymore that
you want to get it on, right?
I'm going to tie you up with the
rope that you love immediately.
S-Stop!
Your mouth says that, but this
mouth is rather being honest.
Just from imagining yourself being teased,
your pussy starts to overflow with juice!
Did having this inside you for
a whole day make you feel good?
I'll be taking it out slowly now, okay?
No...
Wow, your asshole is gaping wide open!
And this putrid odor that makes me want
to sneeze is spreading all over the room!
Stop sniffing it!
You can't go back from being
an ordinary woman anymore.
I used that underwear that I wore
for a whole day to gag your mouth.
Now you're looking good!
Next, we'll use that piss-stinky supporter
pants down the floor of some rascal.
We'll be wrapping it around this toy
and let you have a feel of it deep inside!
Here you go, it's going inside your ass!
While sniffing my underwear, help yourself and have a good taste
of this stink-shrouded vibrator!
Here you go!
Are you gonna come from that stench?
Take this! Come by your asshole!
How does my cock covered with
your own filth from anal sex taste?
I'm coming!
It's about time for Ikumi's body to be ready.
Yes!
Master, should I start making some preparations?
Yeah, make all the necessary preparations.
Several Days Later
And we'll now proceed to everyone's
most-awaited main event!
Today will be a stage debut of a new slave!
This slave is still an ordinary housewife,
so we can't reveal her name or show her face.
But her body has been properly
trained and a totally indecent one!
Rather than her husband's cock which often couldn't make her come, she wants a gangbang
and wants being bound and teased.
And just for today, she got a piercing on her clitoris.
She even have undergone surgical
sterilization even to my surprise!
Without further ado, we present her to you!
The new face of our shop!
It's the arrival of a female slave's passion!
You won't get knocked up anymore
no matter how many men do you, ma'am.
Go out there and enjoy as much as you can!
Hey, don't keep the audience waiting!
Wow! Isn't she sexy?
I want to see the face of her husband!
I have to endure this.
This is all to protect my sister, and my whole family!
Well then, everyone who bought the
special tickets, please come up on the stage.
Oh, there are 30 of them for today.
Then, take your turns in numerical order,
and five people at a time.
Hey, aren't you making such amazing moans!
Come one, at least show us your face!
Woah! Sir, that's not—
More... Give me more!
I-Ikumi...
More... It feels good!
Incredible! I'm going crazy!
I wonder what my young protégé will
think after seeing that lewd face of hers?
Filthy cocks are delicious!
Please shove them more to me!
I-It feels great in my ass too! Thrust it in there!
I-It's hitting deep! It reaches my womb!
I love this! This is what I wanted!
There's a lot of stiffies coming after me!
It's scraping me inside, it feels good!
Both of the cocks are grinding
against my womb and ass!
I can't stop myself! Fuck me more and more!
I want it! This is what I wanted!
Grind your dick more against my womb!
Mix up and mess my insides!
I love dicks! Give me lots and lots of them!
My asshole is being penetrated too, amazing!
I want it!
I'm gonna come again from my ass!
Dicks, there's a lot of dicks!
Keep them coming in!
Please make a mess of my pussy!
It's okay! You can break me! Break me down!
Good, good, good!
I'm coming! I'm coming already!
Coming, coming, coming, coming!
There's a lot of it flowing out...
More, more... Fuck me a lot!
Please... tease me...
lots and lots more...
Use your raw, long and fat dick...
and make my pussy...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Support the group by sharing the releases
and and giving it proper credits.
http://sakuracircle.animeholics.org