Presented by Erobeat j httpV/www.erobeat.net | erobeat@ircrizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: vltouch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Ryou Seibai!
The Secret Punishment Records of Pretty School Girls
Wakana, Saki, the End of Judgement and.. Arc
Ouch...
What's going on?
You're finally awake, aren't you.
If you don't stay still I'll shout.
What do you want with me?
I was planning to never forgive you...
But I'm a kind person, so I might forgive
you depending on your attitude.
My attitude?
I want you to help Urumi.
To become my cock in the place of Mogi.
Since there are still lots of girls out there that I don't like.
So you're telling me to rape someone?
That's right. You're pretty good at it anyways.
What will you do? Are you willing to help Urumi?
Or?
Stop joking around!
As if I'd ever help someone like you!
Well said, Kyouichiro.
What is this!?
If you make such loud noises, you'll excite the snakes.
Someone so self-centered and
obsessed about cleanliness,
Could never stand such unpredictable
and unsanitary animals.
Looks like she's really afraid of snakes.
Of course! They're stinky, and they bite at you randomly...
Go somewhere else!
No!!
No!
Stop this! I'll die...
Y-Yamiko-san? What is this?
Don't worry. Right now in addition to fear and disgust,
she's also lost her mind in the pleasures of sex.
More... violate me more!
Give Urumi more deep inside!
It hurts, but.. It feels good!
It's moving... inside Urumi...
My stomach will break!
It's filling me up!
It's going in and out, and filling up my uterus!
No... It's stirring up my insides...
No, I'll break, no!
I want cock... It's so lonely... as if my pussy is crying...
Kyouichiro, seems like it's your turn now.
Hey, I'll put it in. Relax.
Yes, this is what I wanted! Please, move around lots!
Stir around and mess up my insides!
Kyouichiro, don't hold back and give
a good respond to her expectations.
I know.
Amazing, feeling it so much she's become like this...
More! Move around! Tease my uterus lots!
Amazing... Urumi is dirty right now...
I'm covered in bacteria, and yet I'm doing such things!
Yeah, such a horrible smell.
Urumi stinks! I don't want this! But my body won't stop!
Amazing... If you do it that much...
No... I'll die...
No more... I'm going crazy...
If you do it so much... I'll...
Cumming!
No, my uterus will break!
Cock feels so good! Urumi's becoming no good!
Let it out! Fill my insides with semen!
I'm being filled... White, stinky semen
in Urumi’s precious place...
It's flowing out... from inside Urumi...
It's coming out... no... it won't stop...
You can't even take care of your own
urination, it's like you're some animal.
No... don't look... It feels... good...
Oh dear, you're trouble. Letting out all you
want and then just fainting like that.
To have her pride destroyed and allow
what she hated to go near her,
She probably can't take it if she
didn't do something like this.
My hands won't stop... No... not this...
I'm cumming soon...
Cumming, I'm cumming!
This... It belongs to Kakui-sensei!
Oh, such an amazing coincidence to meet you here.
What's up?
I'm just out here to breathe some fresh air.
What about you, Manabe-san?
This is my favourite spot I come here
to get a change in mood and stuff.
By the way, Mukuchi-san's been a little
troubled and it's apparently about you.
You have any idea?
Eh?
I suppose not. Mukuchi-san's been
looking down on you and all...
Sorry, did that hurt you?
N-no, I don't mind.
And also, a few days ago I lent the key to the tea
room to Mukuchi-san and never got it back.
It's never happened before, I wonder what's wrong?
Sorry for calling you here suddenly. Actually...
Where could it be...
Um... Uh... here it is!
Why?
If we don't do something quickly...
so...
In addition to losing the key to the tea room,
you also didn't find what you lost?
I'm sorry, Sensei. But this time I'll definitely...
Enough.
Sensei... I'm really sorry, Sensei. Um, I...
I'll definitely find the key and find what I lost and...
Wouldn't you please let go of me!
Kakui-sensei!
- Several weeks after Mukuchi's Accident -
Long time no see. It must have been tough.
Yeah... After such things happened
to Kakui-sensei and Mukuchi-san...
Kobishima-san quit the student council suddenly as well.
All their work came right to me, and it was so busy...
Although I'm doing this because I want to, as might
be expected workload of three is intense...
If it s not anything too hard, shall I help you?
Sound good. It's a deal then.
That was fast.
Just kidding. You're awfully friendly though, aren't you!
Did Shiraishi-sensei ask you to do this?
It's fine. It'd help me a lot if you
could lend a hand anyways.
I approve your joining of the student council.
It might be sudden,
but this is the spare key to the tea room.
Please clean it every day from now.
Hey!
But you said you'd help me with my work, right?
So I thought I'd make it easier for you to come in.
Well then, Mr. Helper, please take
good care of the tea room.
It's a trap.
I see.
Things are going way too smoothly.
It's as if she's helping us open the
path that we re trying to go.
It's said that lights are usually followed by shadows.
Let's act very carefully from now on.
But it's also a chance. The situation often
moves much faster than expected, right?
True, that's also a way to think about it, yet...
Listen, be careful to not make any mistakes.
I get it.
Hey Saki-chan...
Mogi-kun...
You know too much!
No!!
Huh? It's not this one...
Not this one either...
There should be some kind of clue somewhere...
Damn it...
I don't see it anywhere. Huh?
What's this?
Please dis-band the student council and work
on it along with us teachers, Manabe-san!
Didn't Sensei approve of my plan?
More importantly, it is better for yourself not to interfere.
Manabe-san! What you are thinking is wrong!
I guess you saw it all.
Is this the truth?
Yup, it s all true.
Hinase-sensei is really earnest It's very admirable.
But that seriousness became trouble for me.
If she had followed my warning,
she wouldn't have had that happen to her.
It's such a pity.
Ah! Ouch...
You! You won't be forgiven for something like...
Wait... that's...
It's what's about to penetrate you right now.
What are you talking about?
There's no way something that
thick can fit... stop, stop it!
What’s this? Bloods coming out.
How does your first dick taste!?
It should have hurt more for my sister!
Hurry up and let go of me! Or I'll... I'll break!
No... it hurts! It hurts!
What? Are you starting to feel it from getting raped?
The student council president
is making such slutty noises!
That’s... that’s not true...
The slutty president has love juices
dripping from her pussy!
No! My breasts!
If you hit so deep...
I'm letting it out.
No! Stop! Not inside! I said stop!
You can't let your semen out! No! Not inside!
Don't!
No...
You really let it out inside...
It's coming... it's coming... so much of the hot stuff... No...
It's not the end of it.
Ryou Seibai!
The Secret Punishment Records of Pretty School Girls.
No! No more! If this goes on...
My stomach is being stretched out...
Not there... no!
It has just started! It’ll get much more rough than this.
If you do it so hard... my insides...
No! I'll...
I'm about to be at my limit.
I'm letting it out.
Letting it out? You don't mean...
Inside again? Not that! Stop!
Not semen!
It won't all fit in...
It's flowing back...
Inside again...
Not so much! My pussy... will break!
It's pulsing inside...
I'll insert it in even deeper.
No! If you do it any harder... I'll...
It's still too early for you to cum.
I can't hold back anymore...
No! No!
It's coming out!
I'm letting something out as well!
I'll let it out again. I'll pour lots
inside of you this last time!
Semen... bursting open inside... Don't let any more out!
I'm going to...
I tasted so much of semen...
It's flowing out..
So much flowing inside... to my uterus...
Huh...
Now I've done it..
I'm sorry. I ignored your warning
and went to the tea room.
I was found out by her, and more over I got
caught in my emotions and raped her!
I'm very sorry! I've lost my qualifications
as a Dark Auditor!
I'm prepared for any punishment.
It's enough. We figured something out
from how she's behaved so far.
Her true nature is masochism.
Eh? So she's an M?
That's right. In both the case of the student council,
arid the case of what happened yesterday,
she's unconsciously satisfying
her desires from self-sacrifice.
However, Manabe Wakana's grades, athletic
ability and her role in the student council...
She makes sure that she is perfect at all of them.
She believes that there's no one she can surrender to.
In other words, she wants to surrender to someone.
So that's why she's a masochist..
However, a commoner won't be
enough to make her surrender.
Isn't there no solution to this problem then?
There's you.
Me?
Don't be so modest You have a sadist
mind that you've been holding back.
I thought so after watched the past judgments you done.
You seem to achieve sexual excitement
by abusing others.
A sadist that tries to force intercourse
is the best partner for a masochist.
If we can unleash your full potential, there would
be no time for Manabe Wakana to feel bored.
After knowing the pleasures of a woman,
no one can escape from it.
Manabe Wakana will definitely return to you, Kyouichiro.
What... about me?
No... I'll break...
It'll break there...
Your body doesn't have enough
resistance against pleasure.
So from now, enjoy as much as you want.
Please, take it out...
I can't take... take this...
Take it out?
Sticking out your ass like that, do you really want it out!?
No... It'll break... I'll cum... Cumming!
My boobs... No... Not there!
You seemed okay with your virginity taken.
What about the virginity here?
You can't! It won't fit in my butt!
No! Stop it! Not anymore!
It's painful!
Hey, I'm gonna move.
No... Stop it..
This is wrong... You're too cruel!
No matter how beautiful you are,
your shit will still be dirty!
Don't say such vulgar things!
My butt is having cramps... and I can't move...
You perverted woman.
Kyouichiro! Send this girl to heaven!
Alright The president so bored and empty
from all the student council work,
I'll satisfy you!
It's filling up inside my butt!
There no way I'll find another woman so slutty!
My butt... it being pulled in and out...
Cumming... I'm... from my butt! From my butt!
I'm cumming from my butt!
It's coming out! I'll let out a lot inside your dirty asshole!
There's still more!
This... I'm going to die...
Go ahead and let out all the darkness
inside you, along with this pleasure!
Coming... It's coming!
Looks like it's over.
The desires she's been seeking,
and all the boredom she was in.
All filled by Kyouichiro.
Finally, her judgment has been completed.
My mission here has been completed.
There's nothing left to do here.
Your connection with the darkness should also end.
From now on, please walk on a bright path!
Well, take care.
Yamiko-san...
When Nee-san left, Yamiko-san was there for me.
If Yamiko-san leaves, then I would
have no one around me...
What I've done until now...
Kyou-chan!
Nee-san!
I'm back! Did you want to see me, Kyou-chan?
Why? Did you run away from the hospital?
No, I didn't. Did you hear nothing from Shiraishi-sensei?
I've left the hospital.
So, I ended up scaring you, didn't I?
She kept quiet so it would be a surprise, I think.
I heard about what happened from Shiraishi-sensei.
Sensei was really sorry about dragging you into her job.
There really isn't anything to apologize about.
I did it as the revenge for Nee-san.
But it was thanks to Yamiko-san that
I didn't turn into a demon of revenge.
I didn't want you to do something like revenge for me...
I'm happy that you worked hard to protect me,
but I can't stand Kyou-chan getting
hurt or hurting anyone for my sake.
I get it I'll never do anything that
makes you sad, ever again.
If it's a request from Nee-chan, I'll do it no matter what!
Then, can you do me a favor right now?
So a penis looks like this...
Um, Nee-san?
What are you...
I'm sorry. I haven't seen it since when we took
a bath together when you were small.
You've really become an adult,
so I'm a little shocked.
She's probably remembering what happened...
I can't take this...
I know what happened to you...
You're afraid of men, right?
Then you don't have to push yourself.
I can just live as your brother...
It's true that I'm afraid of boys now.
Kyou-chan is my brother, but...
You're special.
Kyou-chan... I've always...
Me too, I've always been thinking of Nee-san!
Yeah, I knew...
I'll never let go of Kyou-chan again.
So, well, um...