Dear!
Ikumi!
Dear?
Yeah?
I think it's about time.
Time for what?
For a baby...
Do you still not want one?
No, I do, but...
I knew you did! So, let's...
But you have school tomorrow, don't you?
Can't have the new teacher already
be taking maternity leave.
How about we hold off on kids for a little longer?
Oh, yeah, I guess so.
Rape Reincarnation
Ikumi Arc
Dear? Here's your lunch.
Oh, thanks!
You know what, Ikumi?
It looks like we'll be working at the same place today.
Wanna leave together?
Dear, I thought we said that we would keep the
fact that we're married a secret from everyone
including my little sister, Shizuka?
Oh, right.
I'm going to leave now.
Okay.
Don't forget your lunch!
I went through the trouble of making it.
I won't.
Okay, I'm off.
I'll see you later.
Yeah, have a good day.
This is your new PE teacher, Sunohara Ikumi.
She's a fellow college classmate of Kanou
Makoto who recently resigned.
I hear that they were in the same swimming
club as well and were strong rivals.
She's an extremely gifted individual who was even
a candidate for the National Athletic Meet.
We believe that she will be crucial in helping to
develop our school's athletic departments.
Now please introduce yourself to
the students, Sunohara-sensei.
As the principal so graciously said, I'm Sunohara Ikumi.
I think you've heard enough about my
background, so I'll keep it short.
Don't expect this to be easy!
You're the best!
Geez, sis...
Let's start practice!
We're getting close to the fall tournament,
so let's make sure we practice enough.
Come on, Shizuka, hurry up.
Onee-chan, call me Sunohara-san when we're at school.
Sorry.
Sensei, it sucks that you're not the swim club's coach!
I think you'd get everyone really motivated
if you were in a swimsuit.
Hey, don't tease adults!
That new PE teacher...
She really has the body of a former potential
national swim meet representative.
And she's a classmate of Makoto from college?
Please stop! I may respect you, Yasuno-sensei,
but I'm not going to forgive you for this!
Wait! Don't...
I'll bear your child!
Please give me your seed master!
Please impregnate me with your seed!
She was fun, but after I broke her,
she was just a sex craved whore.
I think it's about time to start a new game.
Hello, Yasuno-sensei.
Mind if I join you?
Oh, Akagi-sensei? You have quite the beautiful wife.
Makes me jealous.
I never thought that my wife would be
transferred to the school I worked at.
Oh, but please keep it a secret from the students.
We had her keep her maiden name for that purpose.
I know.
MASK MARRIED WOMAN
Amateur Mask Series
Story of Training a Married Woman
Oh, right, this is the new volume.
Yasuno-sensei, where do you get these things?
Well, I have a lot of connections, you see.
I can't believe you're jacking off to this
stuff when you have such a hot wife.
You only say that because you're single.
Masturbating and sex with your
wife are two separate affairs.
Take a look. She's diligent and spirited, right?
But she gets really mad when I lick her asshole.
I can't even think of asking her if I could tie her up.
She'd probably divorce me.
I'd probably have her experience being tied
up with a rope even if she didn't want to.
That's not happening. You're just spouting
the delusions of a bachelor.
You'll understand once you're married.
I guess we all have our own fetishes.
I'd be ruined if anyone found out that
I have this fetish as an educator.
Well tell me what you think of the video later.
I'm just glad that I have a guy like you in the school.
Let's get started.
Oh looks like I've hit the motherload!
What do we have here?
This must be that beautiful third-year's.
She has a beautiful face, but the
smell from her spats is nasty!
I love this sour smell!
Shit, that was close.
Who the hell's here at this time of night?
Wait, that's...
Hey, boss?
That new PE teacher you told me to watch
is walking around the school by herself.
I knew it!
What are you doing snooping through someone
else's desk in the dead of night?
Mind telling me what you're doing, Sunohara-sensei?
If you want to call the cops, do it.
But I'm going to expose everything you've done here.
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
Makoto's divorce and her sudden disappearance...
They didn't add up, so I started digging around.
Ybu're the one who tricked Makoto, aren't you?
I'm going to get all this evidence out in the open!
I'm gonna have fun breaking her.
Boss, you've really picked a tough one.
Whatever.
It'll just make it more fun.
You monster!
Act tough while you still can.
You sleazy bastard!
I won't break no matter what you do to me!
You won't kill me.
When morning comes, you're going straight to jail!
You think that's how it's going to play out?
This is great! I can see every last bit of her beautiful pussy!
No! Don't look!
What happened to that fire you just had?
You really have a good body.
I'm gonna get a good look at what
a PE teacher like you is packing.
No!
You smell pretty bad. Must be from the exercise.
It smells like sour seaweed!
No, stop!
What a lovely clitoris!
You definitely have a body fit for a PE teacher.
Let me get a good taste!
Something's coming inside me!
What? What?!
What is this?!
Stop!
Your tongue... Your tongue's stirring up my insides!
No! Not there!
No! Stop!
Stop!!
No!
No! Stop!
Stop... Stop going so deep!
You're going to rip it apart!
It hurts! It hurts!!
Isn't his tongue amazing, Sunohara-sensei?
Your nipples have gotten hard, Sunohara-sensei.
N-No they haven't!
Sensei, the smell down here is really getting nice and dirty!
No!
Get away from me!
But we're just getting started, sensei!
No!!
You just came, Sunohara-sensei.
Very sensitive. Perfect reactions.
It's too early for you to be tired out.
The boss is saying he'll take good care of you, sensei!
Please, stop!
I have a husband!
You know that, don't you?!
That's what makes this good!
Makoto said the same thing at first, but she quickly
became unable to live without my penis.
I'm gonna put it in.
Make sure you give it a warm welcome, sensei!
No!
It's so thick!
Your insides are already soaking wet!
Must be embarrassing having your
asshole out for the world to see.
I'm gonna take good care of you.
But first...
Let's make some good love, Sunohara-sensei!
Stop!
I'm gonna make your body understand
that you're nothing but a whore!
It's gonna rip!
What's the matter? Feel good?
You're moaning.
I-I'm not!
It looks like she's happily gobbling up your dick, boss!
Stop looking!
No!
I... I shouldn't like this, but...
Why?!
What's the matter? You're gripping my dick really tight.
Why? Why am I...
Dear, please forgive me!
I'm sorry!
But, I...
I'm cumming!!
You came, huh?
Ikumi, I'm gonna pound the pleasure
of a man into your body.
Yasuno-sensei, you have a minute?
What's the matter? You don't look good.
My wife hasn't been home since yesterday.
Have you heard anything?
Oh, I'm having Sunohara-sensei participate
in the new teacher training.
Didn't the headmaster tell you about that?
Oh, so that's what's going on?
My wife's never gone off somewhere without telling me.
Don't worry, she'll be back by tomorrow.
I worried for nothing.
But didn't that give you plenty of time to watch that DVD?
Yeah! That was great! It really turned me on!
I can't wait for the next one!
It's gonna be a lot of work.
Sensei, how about you give in already?
If you don't, you're not gonna be able
to use your privates anymore.
I'm not giving in to the likes of you two!
Oh, is that right? Then I'm gonna keep going!
So she still hasn't broken yet?
Yeah, she's a tough one.
I see.
Then how about this, Ikumi?
This is just something that a hidden
camera happened to take.
Shizuka!
Apparently there's a boy she likes and when
she thought nobody was looking,
she took his spats and decided to do this with them.
Stop!
Please erase that!
What do you think will happen to your
dear little sister if this gets out?
Y-You haven't done anything to her, have you?
Rest assured, I haven't done anything to her yet.
But...
Please leave my sister out of this.
That's up to you.
You monster!
You think you're in a position to act like that?
F-Fine!
I'll listen to what you tell me to do.
Is that how you ask someone for a favor?
Loosen the rope.
Let's have her get on her hands and knees and beg.
What's the matter? Can't do it?
Please...
Please don't do anything to my sister.
Th-That's...
Who said you could move?
Don't you care about what happens to your sister?
This is pathetic.
But this is for my sister! I have to endure!
D-Don't put your finger in there!
Is this your first time having a finger in here?
O-Of course it is!
Please hurry and take your finger out of there!
Try tightening around my finger.
That's good.
Yeah, not too bad.
You react well.
No not that!
How's your asshole feel having its first dick inside it, Ikumi?
I-It's going to tear!
Loosen up your asshole by yourself!
Take it in!
Come on, you whore, vow while
you're being fucked in the ass!
Vow that you'll be my slave forever!
No! No!!
So you don't care about what happens to your sister?
I-I'll say it!
I'll say it, so please don't do anything to her!
Then swear it!
Do it!
Yes, I'm your dirty whore, Shiro-sama!
I'm the dirty whore that will be fucked
by you for the rest of her life!
Good. That's enough for a slave.
I'm gonna piss in you, so take it all in!
No!!
There's urine streaming out inside my butt!
From now on, whatever we say, you obey.
Got it?
Ikumi, club over for the day?
I just finished up too and everyone else has
already left. Wanna go home together?
Sorry, I have to help prepare for the athletic festival.
Oh.
Um, I'm going to be back late tonight too.
Bye sensei!
Get home safe.
Was waitin' for you, sensei.
Reeks of guy, doesn't it?
It's the perfect place to break you in.
I'm gonna make sure I pound it into you.
Let's take a look.
Your ass is already this wet? Couldn't hold
it in? You're such a dirty PE teacher!
Perfect!
It stinks!
Can't believe none of the students noticed.
You wanted to be fucked so badly, didn't you?
I'll tie you up with that rope you like so much.
S-Stop!
Your mouth up there might say that,
but your mouth down here is honest.
Just imagining getting fucked is already
making it overflow with juices!
You were getting off from having
this in you all day, weren't you?
I'll take it out of you real slow.
Wow, your asshole is still wide open!
The pungent smell from this is filling up the room!
No! Stop smelling it!
There's no going back to being a normal woman anymore!
You look great with the underwear I was
wearing today stuffed in your mouth.
Next I'm gonna stick this piss-smelling underwear
onto this and shove it deep inside your body!
Look, it's going into your ass!
Get a good taste of the stench from
my underwear with your mouth
and the stench from the underwear
down here with your asshole!
Come on! Come on!
Are you gonna cum from the smell?
Come on! Cum with your ass!
How's the taste of a dick soaked
with the stench of your shit?!
I'm cumming!
Looks like her body's about ready.
Yeah! So how about it boss, we ready to do the thing now?
Yeah, we're good to go.
Several days later
Up next is the main event!
Appearing for the first time on stage is a new slave.
She's still somebody's wife,
so we can't reveal her face or name,
but her body is perfectly dirty.
She herself asked to be fucked by different
dicks, not just by her husband's!
She's even gone through the trouble of enlarging
her clitoris and having a tubectomy.
Now then everyone, please watch.
Raise the curtains!
Time for her to take the stage!
Don't worry. You can't get pregnant anymore.
Have fun out there!
Don't keep them waiting!
That's a nice body!
I wanna see what she looks like!
Endure it.
This is to protect my sister and my family!
Now I'd like to invite the customers who bought
the special tickets to come onto the stage.
What's this? Thirty people today?
Well then, let's do this in groups of fives,
starting with the lowest numbers.
Hey, you moan nice.
Show me what you look like!
S-Sir! You can't!
More... More...
I-Ikumi?!
More! Make me feel good!
So good! I'm losing my mind!
Wonder what he'll think when he sees her face like that.
Your dick tastes so good!
More! Please fuck me more with them!
My ass... My ass feels so good!
It's hitting! It feels so good!
Good! So good!
There are so many hard things coming inside me!
They feel so good rubbing against me!
They're rubbing around inside my ass and pussy!
More! Please shove them in me more!
I want them!
I love this!
You can shove them in me even more!
Mess me up with your dicks!
I love dicks!
Please give me more!
You're stretching out my ass so much! It's so good!
I'm gonna cum with my ass!
Give me more... Pound me with your dicks!
Please make a mess of my pussy!
Break me! Break me!
It's good! It's so good!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
There's so much cum...
More... Give me more...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Please play with me more... much more...
Shove that raw dick of yours into my pussy!