Kibitsu Academy, a school where only
the top students are admitted.
It is a well-known theological school, most
known for its open school tradition.
Within it, there is an independent group
of three popular female students,
known as the student council.
They are the elite of the elite,
and no one ever goes against them.
Not even the school's instructors.
Hey you...
You've learned more than you should.
P-Please stop this foolishness!
This is really something!
Shut up!
No, someone
Someone, please help me.
Help me, Kyou-chan!
Nee.-san?
She's been coming home late these past few days.
Could she have...
A boyfriend already?
No, I mustn't think like this!
So it's been 10 years since that time, huh?
Nee-san and I are not really related by blood.
She is actually my step sister.
But, when both our parents died in an accident,
she decided to work and raise me while still being a student.
Why did she have to be my type?
In time, Nee-san became more and more beautiful.
I became helplessly attracted to her.
I could even say that I love her!
For a young and beautiful teacher to actually be my older sister...!
How in the world am I supposed deal
with these out-of-control feelings?!
My patience is at its utmost limit!
Oh yeah...
If I study well, get hired in a company and get a good salary,
then I could....
It's really getting late now.
No, please stop this!
Wow, what great tits you have, Hinase-sensei!
T-That's not...
You're really getting aroused from it, right?
Your boobs are sure looking tasty.
P-Please stop right this moment!
I don't want to treat my students as criminals!
You've sure got an annoying mouth there.
I wonder how long that spirit will last?
Please...
Stop...
Don't do it...
Oh no...
Please, Kyou-chan!
Kyou-chan, save me!
Here, I'll keep this as long as possible.
Oh, it's dripping blood!
Sacchan, so you were a virgin, eh?
Is this for real?
This is humiliating...
Wow, that looks painful, so this is what a virgin's blood looks like.
I sure would like to have a taste of this!
I'm going to make you feel better, Sacchan!
I can't think properly anymore!
Oh no...!
Kyou-chan! Kyou-chan! Kyou-chan!!
Oh crap...
How about I cum inside for a finish?
Cum inside?
Anywhere but inside... !
Here I go!
No...!
I'm...
Hey, Nee-san!
Hey, where are you?!
You, did you...?!
Endurance punishment!
So, the student council are behind this?
There are many things in the world
that are better left unknown.
If you don't want to end up like Instructor Hinase,
it's best for you to not look further into it.
Please just wait!
I want to expose the hidden side of the student
council that did this to Nee-san!
Please, I'll do anything!
I can't let those kinds of people get away with this.
Hmm, do you know what an undercover judge officer is?
Hey look, its Manabe-san...
She looks wonderful...
Manabe Wakana...
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't just sit there.
Since when did you get here?
The student council is something like
an out of control supervisory body,
and is centered on three primary representatives.
It's said that they hold more power and
influence than the instructors and PTA,
however, it is rumored that behind the curtain,
they are involved in violent acts and illegal financial transactions.
This is Manabe Wakana, the first of the three representatives.
She's the president of the student council,
as well as the president of the Tea ceremony club.
She's also the granddaughter of the school director.
She's very charismatic and is idolized by
everyone as a dependable role model.
Aside from Manabe Wakana,
we have Kobishima Urumi.
She's the head of the 3rd year disciplinary committee,
and during breaks she's treated as the newest idol on campus.
She only comes to school occasionally,
but she's very popular,
and there is a very strong bond between her fans.
Lastly, we,have Mukuchi Kuu.
Though still a 1 st year student, she's already
captain of the Athletics Club.
She holds multiple running records in track and field,
has a prodigious aptitude for physical activity
and a cute, small animal-like charm,
making her very popular as well.
After studying everything about your enemies,
you'll first need to establish contact with them.
Ouch, ouch!
Yamimaru-san!
It hurts, could you please get this thing off me?
This ferret is magnificently named Yamimaru.
It's usually quietly perched on top of Yamiko's head,
but when agitated, it just loses control and bites.
Yamimaru-san is getting angrily impatient.
No way!
Just go out there and greet the gal!
Pure white...
No!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...!
Geez, I can't even get angry if you apologize like that.
Anyway, I'll ask you directly.
What do you think of Manabe?
can't think of her as someone who ordered
for Nee-san to be assaulted.
That kind of sweet student council president is quite rare.
Exactly.
Manabe Wakana is an outstanding student,
a woman that possesses strong leadership qualities.
T-That's right...
But humans are never limited to just one side.
If you are unable to peer through that side,
then you are of no use as an undercover judge officer.
Understood!
Everyone, as always, thank you for everything.
What a hottie.
Kobishima-senpai...
Is that understood?
As for the vector,
in order for point P to pass through lines A and B...
Our math instructor, Kakuin Mikado.
A man who is on relatively good terms with Nee-san.
In the eyes of men, he is nothing but
an annoying middle-aged man,
but it seems that he's very popular among the girls.
Could it be that Nee-san also likes that guy....?
No, no!
Excuse me...
That appearance, could it be the one from earlier this morning...?
Well then,
I'll be taking my duties into consideration and
concentrate on my studies for a while.
Yes, that would be better for you.
Thank you for providing me with such guidance.
Now then, if you'll excuse me.
Ah, we met earlier this morning, right?
Yes, that's right.
You see, my eyesight isn't that good.
That's why I take off my glasses whenever
I look at something up close.
Hey, what's your name?
Um, I'm Kyouichirou.
Nice to meet you, Kyouichirou-kun!
N-N-Nice to meet you too.
See you then.
See you...
Tsk.
Didn't  you know?
Hinase-sensei is currently off due to the shock
of her experience of being assaulted.
Really?
Mogi has been talking about her quite proudly, you know.
He declared that he had made Hinase-sensei his woman.
So it was him?
That must be really bad for Sensei if he was the one who did it
But you know what?
She was immediately admitted into hospital just because of that!
You guys...
Hey...
It's dangerous for a weak and dainty instructor to
be out here alone at a time like this, you know?
How dumb.
So, what do you need from me?
I need to talk to you about Instructor Hinase.
When did you last meet her?
That was really erotic.
She was taking down my big thing, in tears.
It was really thrilling and satisfying.
But you know, it was quite careless of
you to call me to a place like this.
Do you want to be raped by me that badly?
Have you no shame?
The likes of you are even lower than bugs!
Do it!
Save me!
Now then,
I'll have you spew out every single bit of information you know.
We just followed the orders Kobishima gave us.
There's not a single person that can defy her...
Now it's decided who we will investigate first.
So it's Kobishima-senpai...
Okay, I'll try asking around.
I'm sure there are many of her fans on campus.
Give up on that idea.
We can't learn the truth by asking those people.
You must try to establish direct contact with her.
Well, it's alright, isn't it?
I've really thought that you're perfect for some time now.
Stop saying such foolish things!
I'm an instructor!
On top of that, you're...
Sensei, you really are a worrywart.
It's okay.
Nobody will know, if we just play around a bit.
I'm also afraid of the mass media, you know?
So it's a secret, all of it will be kept secret.
You really are too attractive and that makes it all too suspicious.
So, what's in it for you?
Need to erase a few red marks?
Actually...
I want you to do something terrible to a
female student that I've just targeted.
Something terrible?
That's right!
You know the story about how Hinase-sensei was raped, right?
Could it be... that you were the one behind that?
Correct!
I tried to ask someone else to do it,
but lately I've been having trouble with some people.
indictment Note
to Kobishima urumi
I have something on you.
if you don't want the whole academy finding out what it is
come to gymnasium this evening alone!!
Why are you...!
So it was you, huh?
How foul of you to have written this kind of note.
So what do you want to do?
I want to ask you something about Nee-san, Hinase Saki.
Could you be...!
Why did you use Mogi to assault Nee-san?
Answer me!
Well... because she's an eyesore?
What?!
That person was really standing out you see.
It was really troublesome for me when she was around.
I don't want anyone stealing my thunder for any reason.
You seemed to be the type to move according to my plans,
so I thought of making you my pawn.
Well, things are like this now so that's too bad for you.
Ah, forget it.
In any case, you really are a sister-loving pervert.
You just humiliated a family member!
What do you understand about me?!
Eeek!
Please save me!
Huh? Was my voice not loud enough?
Anyone, please!
Geez, that was such an irritatingly shrill voice...
You're the one from the infirmary!
You're also in on this?
Yep, and it seems I met a few weak bodyguards.
Kobishima Urumi,
you need to learn what pain is.
Endurance Punishment.
Academy Girls Secret Penalty Records.
What are you going to do?
Your voice is getting shaky.
You already know what will happen to you, don't you?
No!
Let me go!
This position is...!
Stop struggling!
No...
Wow, it's gotten wet.
It's twitching and shaking.
Please don't look!
You're an instructor, right?
Please stop him!
My, my, what an increasingly annoying woman.
Now, I wonder what this will taste like.
No, you can't...!
You won't easily get away with this!
You say that, but you're already overflowing
with erotic juices down here.
No...
I feel weak...
Seems it's already loosened up a bit.
Then I guess it'll be me with this.
Huh? What?
No! Anything but that!
Too late for you to struggle now!
Look closely while I put it in!
Wow, it's so tight, it feels like I'm going to get totally squeezed!
It's going in...
Here I go.
Take it all the way in, okay?
It's in.
It hurts!
It hurts.
Pull it out!
Blood's coming out.
So you're a virgin.
No...
Please... let me be...
What are you blabbering about?
We're just getting started!
It's making such cute sounds...
It looks like your pussy is starting to like cocks.
That's not... true...
Then I'll just make it like them!
Then III just make it like them!
Oh no, my body's getting horny...
I'm about to cum.
I want you to take it all.
No, don't cum inside!
Do it outside!
I don't want it inside!
No way...
He's really cumming inside...
This is terrible...
I'm definitely going to get pregnant with this...
We're not done yet.
Noway, we're still...!
No...
I don't want to be impregnated!
Oh no, it's getting big again!
I'm cumming again!
No, don't cum inside anymore please!
I'll get pregnant!
You came inside again....
What am I supposed to do now?
I can't be an idol anymore!
You can still stay as a student, you know?
The victims that you harmed are the ones
that are out of this school already.
If you didn't attend this school,
that wouldn't have happened!
That's nonsense!
Even if I were to disappear from this school,
it would still stay the same with Kuu-chan!
Are you referring to Mukuchi Kuu?
Who else would I call that?!
I don't like this anymore...
Sensei, don't...!
She's masturbating...!
My pussy feels hot.
I want to do it more.
Please, do it more intensely!
It's deep inside...
Penetrating, and stretching my pussy...
Oh no, my hips are moving...
Sensei's good smell is, oh no...!
Not the fingers!
Since when have you been here, Yamiko-san?!
Please don't surprise me like that!
Keep quiet. What would you do if she finds us?
Anyway, this isn't the time for you to get an erection, you know.
My pussy is overflowing with all these juices...
It feels good, Sensei!
It's good... do it more...
Do it... Yes!
Drill all the way in!
I just can't stop!
Oh no...
No...
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, Sensei!
I can't control it anymore!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Who the hell are you?!
What were you doing out there?
Do you think you can easily get away with this?
I just happened to pass by the club room
when I heard someone moaning inside.
I can see through right through your lies,
you just wanted to see my naked body.
I'm really sorry.
I apologize.
"I apologize" my ass.
I'm definitely not going to forgive you for this!
It's going to be your turn now, so prepare yourself.
S-So this is a cock...
What's this? And how can it grow this big?
Oh, so it becomes like this.
Turning into a really horny form like this.
And the smell is...
Horny as well.
If I do this,
will it grow bigger?
It's already big but we'll see.
Something is slowly coming out.
This smell is really something else.
My nose is starting to feel numb.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming already!
If you're cumming then hurry up and cum!
Release it all in front of me!
Let it all out!
What a huge load,
So this is what semen smells like.
So this is what semen tastes like.
Now we're even, okay?
Oh no, it's time already!
If I don't hurry to the tearoom,
my appointment with Sensei will...!
Tearoom?
She clearly said tearoom.
Okay, we'll go after her.
Okay!
Hey, that hurts!
You're a teacher, why do you have handcuffs?
Let me go, you idiot!
Hey, what were you doing in the tearoom?
What are doing to me?
Let me go this instant you idiot!
Who would say anything to the likes of you?
Oh, so Kuu's pussy looks like this.
Why are you looking so closely at it?
The smell is... a bit sour and sweaty.
Stop that... not there...! That's...!
If you want me to stop, then are you
willing to answer my questions?
What is you real reason for going to the tearoom?
What are you doing there?
I just went to get something I'd forgotten.
Then why were you trying to escape?
Wait up!
Because you two were being too insistent!
We've got you cornered now, Mukuchi Kuu!
Give up already!
Just who are you two?
What's wrong?
Still don't feel like speaking up?
I-I told you, I just went to retrieve the printed
homework notes that I'd forgotten.
Let's properly interrogate her then.
Okay, understood.
No, no...!
Stop!
No!
Something squiggly is entering me!
No, no...
Stop...
Even my butthole...?!
No, stop!
Even my butthole...
Why did it turn out like this?
Please don't put your tongue in.
Not the fingers too!
No... stop...
I feel twitchy deep inside.
Hey, stop it already.
We won't get any answers from her in this state.
Stop...
That's, no...
My body feel like it's melting...
What was with that crappy interrogation?
Eh? Well, but...
I did try my best earlier.
We didn't really get a single bit of information out of her.
Even if you say that,
I'm not that experienced yet and that
was the only thing I could do.
How pathetic.
If I were the one who interrogated Mukuchi Kuu,
I would have definitely been able to make
her spill out some information.
Though I can't execute it anymore even if I think of it now.
Come!
Huh? Where to?
I plan on giving one thick-headed student
here a few supplementary lessons,
be grateful.
Hey, wait!
What in the world is this?
Wait Yamiko-san, why are we...?
It would seem as if I'm some pervert here.
Hey, Yamiko-san.
Stay still now.
Keep your face straight up.
What are you doing Yamiko-sa...
Please move away.
Don't just slack off there.
Start licking it.
What?!
Do as I say, you have no other choice.
There, that's right.
See, it's already wet, right?
It's slowly starting to overflow.
Just a little more...
We need to bind that thick thing just a little more,
as if we are trying to dig and extract it.
You're not reaching into the lower part!
Just keep moving.
Suck it up... suck it up properly.
More and more secretions are coming out.
Your part here is also getting wet.
How is it?
Feels delicate and sweet, right?
Just keep on licking.
That's good.
Quite good at your level.
A passable mark I'd say.
You just went with the flow of your own
desires on the last part though.
Do you understand, Kyouichirou?
Don't forget this sensation.
I harassed you simply out of hatred and desire.
It looks like that felt great for you.
It felt really different.
That's right.
You became lost in yourself and just
went violently against Mukuchi Kuu.
Not a punishment, but a mere act of violence.
A simple sex crime done out of revenge.
You sure are right about that...
I don't really need to repeat this,
but you must constantly remember,
what you are really doing, and what you really need to do.
Without going out of control, and leaving it to your emotions.
I understand.
So punishment is different from revenge then.
Correct.
Thank you, Yamiko-san.
I don't need to be thanked.
Just give me results.
That'd be the best form of gratitude for me.