So the day is almost here.
Just a little bit longer.
No need to worry.
You’ll be fine, Elena.
After all, I have trustworthy friends.
Elena, are you ready yet?
Oh, you’re still not ready?
Hold on, Giselle, I told you to always knock before entering my room!
How many times must I remind you?
Oh, Elena, stop being so uptight.
We’re gonna have to say goodbye to the Victoire before you know it.
That doesn’t logically follow what I said earlier.
I really wish you’d change that about yourself.
It’s rude.
What may seem trivial to you is important to me.
Sheesh, Elena, you just worry too much.
Giselle, listen to me.
Unless you understand simple issues like this,
you won’t last long in battle.
Don’t worry.
I won’t falter so easily.
What about you?
I think a ship’s captain should be a little more calm and patient with her underlings.
I promise I won’t trouble you too much, Elena.
Yes, I suppose.
I do appreciate that you all are working so hard.
But listen,
it’s because you are our captain that we try so hard in the first place.
Thanks to you being on this ship, we’ve come so far.
Giselle…
But I only wish you’d wear cuter underwear…
What are you doing?
Stop that, Giselle!
Aren’t you ashamed?
Why should I be?
We’re both women.
Don’t tell me you…
Hey, Giselle, what are you doing?
St-Stop it!
I knew it.
You really are adorable, Elena.
I am your superior officer, don’t be so impertinent!
We’re soldiers, don’t forget that.
We shouldn’t have those sort of thoughts in our minds while we’re in uniform.
We’ll have plenty of time to fraternize after the war is over.
But while I’m wearing this uniform,
I am Captain Elena Gregor of the International Federation Fleet vessel Victoire.
If that’s the way you feel, I guess I’ll have to wait a while.
TS: Original Video Animation
Guerrilla Hunting 3
1st episode: The Hesitant White Military Uniform
Oh… oh no.
This is too intense.
Yes!
Awesome!
Your cock… is filling my pussy so much.
Your cock is tickling me.
More! More, deeper!
Wow! This feels so great!
I can't take it anymore!
I’m cumming…
Oh no…
I just came, so my pussy is really sensitive right now…
If you’re so violent with me, I’ll…
I’ll… cum too fast!
I’m cumming!
I'm cumming again!
Unbelievable…
It’s all the way in my uterus…
What is it?
It seems like your hatred of the opposite sex has vanished completely, Elena.
Just… Just take these ropes off immediately!
What are you doing?
U-Untie me now!
Don’t you understand me?
I ordered you to untie these ropes!
What are you going to do to me?
Don’t come any closer.
In a place like this…
If you think I’ll just bend to your will, you’re sadly mistaken!
That line would have had much more impact if you weren’t spread-eagle with your tits exposed.
What a nice view.
I… If you continue with these indecent acts, I will inform the council at—
What?
My lips are being stolen by such a fiend!
Well, the lips of the annoying Colonel are surprisingly soft.
No! Gross!
His tongue is inside my mouth.
No!
This is my first kiss!
Eew!
For someone who protests, you sure seem swollen.
No!
Don’t touch me down there!
It seems as though you still fail to understand the position you’re in.
No matter what you do to me, I will not surrender to you!
You sure have some huge tits, Colonel.
That tight uniform must be awfully uncomfortable.
I’ll give you a better uniform after we finish.
How disgusting!
You’d better stop that immediately!
That may be what your mouth says…
But your body says it’s enjoying it.
That’s a lie!
That’s definitely… not true at all!
If you’re going to say that much,
let me see some proof.
What are you doing?
Hey, st-stop it!
Stop it, please!
Don’t resist me, Colonel.
I can’t… how cruel!
He’s degrading me so…
Your actions are rude and degrading. You must stop immediately or else—
Ohhh? Why are you wet, Colonel?
Is it sweat?
Or else, could it be…
You’re sure sensitive down here, Colonel.
No!
Stop it!
Don’t do this!
I’m still in my uniform…
In this place…
And this man…
Is licking me down there…
No… This doesn’t feel… right…
This is just…
How dare you… try to have your way with me.
Just cut it out!
You can STILL speak to me in that manner?
Just what I'd expect from you, Colonel.
First, let me shut that mouth of yours.
What?
That’s… a man’s…
How grotesque!
That expression means… this is your first time, isn’t it?
It's your first time seeing one of these things.
Put that disgusting thing away!
Disgusting?
I’ll make it so you’ll never be able to forget it.
Wh-What is this?
It stinks!
No!
Stop it!
Come on.
Don’t hold back, Colonel.
Go.
Come on.
Eew!
This is… This is so dirty.
And I have to put it in my mouth?
I absolutely refuse!
Come on, suck on it.
I can’t breathe…
My mouth is… so full.
I can’t… keep this up!
Colonel, the inside of your mouth felt pretty good.
And what’s more, what huge tits you have.
Just the sight of them makes me want to use them.
So hot… The hot thing is between my breasts…
So this is… a man…
Wh… What is this?
Eew!
It’s getting bigger inside of my mouth!
Drink it well, Colonel.
Very nice.
Your mouth feels excellent.
N… No!
Stop it!
Don’t ejaculate into my mouth!
That’s gross!
Eew… no!
The inside of my mouth is…
It’s hitting my throat…
Now, drink it all, Colonel.
Don’t leave a drop behind.
Impossible!
Drink something this gross?
It’s… bitter.
So this is… semen?
It’s so bitter.
Very nice, Colonel.
I love that glare.
It’s revived me for a third time.
No way!
That made him erect?
Colonel, stay in that position and let’s go for the second act.
I’ll never allow it!
No!
Stop it!
Oh no!
Don't, I'll cum!
He’s going inside of me… little by little.
How does your first time with a man feel?
It… hurts!
It hurts!
In this place… dressed like this…
And it’s my first time!
No… no!
Stop it!
Stop it at once!
You may be a woman, but you're still a Colonel, I guess.
I think I’ll enjoy you nice and slow.
That hurts!
It’s so hot… and thick. Violating my insides.
In a place like this…!
Oh no… I can’t breathe.
How much longer will this continue?
How much bigger can it get?
It hurts, but… it’s starting to feel… good.
How strange.
I’m scared.
I feel the juices flowing inside of you, Colonel.
You’ll be crying much more later.
You say such stupid things!
But… why is my body not listening to me?
I feel so hot.
Oh no.
It’s rougher.
And it’s getting bigger.
I’m gonna go all the way inside.
I'll fuck your uterus too, Colonel.
No!
Not that!
Not anymore… you can’t…
No!
No! No!
Inside of me… it hit so deep.
It’s throbbing.
More semen is coming in…
The real fun begins now, Colonel.
The sensation… won’t go away.
You… made me wear the republic uniform to do this…
You have a gross fetish!
Seeing as how you’re neither a national nor a part of the republic,
I figured this would make things easier on you.
What the hell are you saying!
I’m the Colonel of the International Federation!
I am Elena Gregor!
You were sold to the republic.
You and the Victoire.
You honestly expect me to believe that?
In other words, your position has been severely lowered.
You might as well be my pet.
Whether you believe it or not is up to you.
But this is the truth.
Th… This can’t be true!
We were all sold?
This is all a big farce?
Well, in time you’ll become my cock warmer.
And there will be no more problems.
Stop the disgusting jokes!
I can’t believe that!
I want proof!
And that is why you’re only the Colonel of Victoire.
Again… he’s opening the insides of me. He's going inside.
Spreading it… spreading my insides.
No.
I feel it sliding against my walls as it’s coming in.
Colonel.
Your tightness is perfect.
So perfect I can’t stand it.
No!
It’s going deeper inside.
Gliding against me.
Something so big… is inside… of me…
It’s about time for you to be honest with me, Colonel.
Honest? I am being honest!
This doesn’t… feel good… in the slightest!
Good acting, dear.
And you’re so wet.
It’s… getting rougher…
I can’t take it…
If this keeps up, I’ll…
What a surprise.
You want to resist me that hard?
You certainly are a Colonel.
I am a Colonel.
And protecting everyone is my duty.
Not this!
Oh, Colonel. You sure are beautiful.
I feel like it’d be a waste to break you.
No!
What?
He’s into it?
He’s getting bigger inside of me again?
I’ll make it so you won’t be able to live without my cock.
No!
Just think of me and forget about everything else.
Why?
Why were we abandoned by the federation?
My friends…
Your place no longer belongs with the feds.
That can’t be.
You must be mistaken.
Please let me contact the federation at once!
Look at this proof.
You cannot argue with the decision.
But rest at ease.
You and your team will be housed here.
I won’t lay a hand on the others, either.
As long as you follow all the rules.
The federation genuinely abandoned us…
Now’s no time to wallow in self pity.
I must endure this no matter what!
For everyone’s sake!
So this is your hideout?
I told you time and time again.
Your methods will not break me.
That is why I adore you, Elena.
But I think your prideful posture should end today.
A strange liquid is spreading inside of me.
It’s slowly pulsating…
What’s… this?
No!
My insides are…
I will teach you a new ecstasy, Colonel.
N… no!
What’s…
It’s in my butt!
Hey, Colonel.
Cry with a nicer face, will you?
What is this?
What’s happening?
No!
I'm going to leak.
W… Wait!
Don’t move!
It hurts!
This isn’t right…
This is…
I feel like I’m going to let it out.
This can’t… this can’t be…
Oh no!
If he comes in any deeper, I’ll… It's going to come out.
Stop… I’m going to leak.
If you just let it out, you’ll feel better.
Stop saying stupid things!
Let me go!
Just be more honest with yourself.
I can’t!
No!
I can’t keep this… I really will… I really will…!
In that case, there’s a special way of asking.
How dare you suggest that!
I can’t say it… I really can’t.
It’s too much…
I… You can’t do this, Elena.
I can’t let him win.
I can’t let this bastard do this… I can’t!
I can’t… I can’t lose hope just because of this…
I must endure it!
Endure it, Elena!
B-But
I… I must endure it.
I can’t lose hope.
B… But!
I… I… I can’t hold… I can’t hold back!
Please…
Please, what?
I can't hold it.
So please… let me… please…
I can’t hear ya.
What did you say?
Just your cock…
Say it louder!
Louder and clearer!
I will think only about your cock.
So please…
Oh no!
I… I…
I’m at my limit!
Think about your friends, too.
Just my cock.
Yes!
Only your cock.
I don’t care about everyone else.
So please!
E… Elena…
Wh-Why…
Gi… Giselle…
Just fall!
No!