Endurance Punishment!
Ryou    Sei  bai
Ouch...
What's this?
So you're finally awake.
Stop that or I'll scream.
What are you going to do with me?
I'll never forgive you,
but I'm a nice person,
so I'm just going to bind you mentally.
What do you mean by binding me mentally!
I want you to help me.
I want you to be my cock, as a replacement for Mogi.
As there are still lots of eyesores around me.
You mean you want me to rape somebody?
Correct.
You're already good at it, right?
What are you going to do?
Are you going to help me?
Or maybe...
Stop fucking around!
I'm not going to help the likes of you!
Well said, Kyouichirou.
What's this?
Scream more like that,
and you'll just arouse the snakes more.
A clean freak like her wouldn't possibly be able to
resist the likes of these kinds of filthy animals.
Seems you really hate snakes, don't you?
Of course!
It stinks, it bites a lot...
Go away!
Stop.
I'm going to die.
Yamiko-san, what's the meaning of this?
Don't worry.
She's just that scared and disgusted, that
she's has become immersed in sex.
Violate me more.
Please caress my good spots more!
This is terrible, but it feels good.
It's slithering inside me.
My insides...
I feel like I'm giving birth!
It's moving back and forth inside, and I feel like
my womb's going to be completely filled!
Oh no, my insides are getting totally stirred up.
No, I'm going to break.
I want a cock.
It's itching to do it.
My pussy is crying for it.
Kyouichirou, it's your turn now.
Come now, I'm going to insert it for you.
Just relax.
Yes, I've wanted this one.
Please, thrust it into me a lot.
Rub it in, and stir my insides!
Kouichirou, listen to her request.
No need to hold back.
Okay, I got it.
This is amazing, she has become totally horny.
Rub it in me more.
Tease my womb more!
Wow, I'm being sullied right now.
I always want it clean, and yet I'm doing this.
Yeah, it sure stinks terribly.
I'm all stinky now.
I don't want this!
My body won't stop!
Amazing, if you keep that up, I'll...
Oh no...
I'm going to die.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to lose it.
If you keep that up...
I'm going to...
My womb is going to break.
This cock feels great.
I can't hold it anymore.
Release it.
Fill me with your cum.
He's cumming inside me.
This white sticky thing is filling that part of mine...
It's dripping.
Dripping from my insides.
It's coming out.
Oh no, it won't stop.
You don't even have control over your excretions?
You're like an animal.
No, don't look.
It feels... good...
My, oh my, what a light-headed person.
She came, released what she could,
and then just passed out.
She had her pride crushed,
and was violated by the thing that she hates.
If I don't try to expose her now,
I probably won't be able to pull her out from the darkness.
My fingers won't stop.
Oh no.
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming.
This is... Kakuin-sensei-s!
My, what a coincidence to see you here.
What's up?
I just came here to feel the breeze.
How about you, Manabe-san?
This is my favorite spot.
I usually come here for a change of mood.
Oh yes, Mukuchi-san seems to be minding you a lot.
Any idea why?
Eh?!
Of course you don't know I guess.
Because she doesn't really like you.
Oh, have I hurt your feelings?
No, it's nothing really.
Also yesterday,
she never came back after I lent her the key to the tea room.
That hasn't happened before,
so I wonder what went wrong.
Sorry for calling you suddenly.
Actually...
Huh? Where is it?
Oh, here it is!
Why are you...? ?
It'll be really troublesome if we don't do something about it.
So, not only have you lost the tearoom key,
but you also failed to find what you needed to look for, is that it?
I'm sorry Sensei.
But I promise to find it this time.
Enough.
Sensei...
I'm sorry Sensei...
I will definitely return the key,
Let go of me!
I mean, I will find it Sensei!
A -few weeks after the Mukuchi incident-
Hey, long time no see.
It's been hard for you, eh?
Yes.
I never thought that would happen
to Kakuin-sensei and Mukuchi-san.
Kobishima-san also suddenly quit.
I now have to do the jobs of both girls, so really busy.
I know it's bad to say it at a time like this,
but it's really tough for me to do everything.
If there are a few easy-to-do jobs, maybe I could help?
Okay, I approve of it.
That was fast.
No, just kidding, but you seem be really kind today.
Did Shiraishi-sensei ask you to do it?
I guess it's okay.
It'll really help if you can lend a hand.
You have my approval to participate in the student council.
We're starting right away, so here's the spare key to the tearoom.
From now on you'll be in charge of cleaning it every day.
Hey!
You said you would help me with my job, right?
Then you need easy access to the room.
Well then, Mr. Assistant, see you later!
It's a trap.
Is that so?
It just went too smoothly.
It's as if she herself opened the path that we would take.
Like a light that's followed by a shadow.
We should tread carefully from here on.
But this is our chance.
We just have to move forward faster than she's expecting.
True, that may also be possible, but...
Listen up, I don't want you to make a single mistake.
Okay, I understand.
Saki-chan, you see...
Mogi-kun...
You already know too much.
Huh? This isn't it.
No, not this either.
There should be a clue here somewhere.
Crap, I can't find it anywhere.
What's this?
Disband the student council and cooperate with us, Manami-san.
You do not agree with our plan, Sensei?
In any case, I would like to warn you to just forget about this.
Manabe-san!
What you are trying to do is wrong!
So it's already exposed, huh?
Is this the truth?
Yes, every single thing.
Hinase-sensei is such a devoted teacher.
I'm actually impressed.
But that diligence of hers led to her downfall.
If she had just heeded my warning...
Then that would never have happened.
It's really too bad for her!
That hurts.
Hey, you won't easily get away with thi-
Wait, what are you...?
This thing will penetrate you shortly.
W-What is it that....?
That just won't fit in.
Stop.
Stop it...
Hey, blood is coming out.
How does your first cock feel?
Nee-san felt something more painful than that, you know?
Get off me right now!
If you don't...
It's going to break!
No, ouch...!
It hurts...
What?
Are you getting horny from being raped?
The council president's pussy sure makes very erotic sounds.
That's a lie... That can't be...
What a horny president you are!
Lots of your horny juices are dripping out from your pussy!
No, please...
If you keep on hitting deep inside me, I'll...
I'm about to cum.
No, don't.
Not inside.
Stop.
I said stop.
Don't cum.
No...
I don't want...
I don't want you to cum inside!
No...
You really came inside me...
The hot stuff is flowing out of me.
Oh no...
It's not over yet.
Endurance Punishment.
Girls Academy Secret Penalty Records.
No don't, anymore of this and...
My deepest parts are being penetrated.
No, no, not there...!
We're just getting started!
It's going to get a lot more intense!
If you keep on thrusting intensely...
My insides will...
No, don't fill it in!
I'm nearly there.
I'm going to let it out.
Let it out? Don't tell me...
You're cumming inside again? I don't want...
Please no!
Don't cum!
It's already full inside...!
It's going to flow out!
I can't believe that someone like you just...
My pussy is going to break already!
It's getting filled up again.
I'm going to go even deeper!
Oh no...
If you keep up that intensity, I'll...!
Hey, it's still too early for you to cum.
I can't hold it in anymore.
No, no...!
It's going to come out!
I'm going to cum too!
Oh no!
I'm going to let it out.
I'm going to burst out every drop that I have.
Don't cum and pour your semen inside me.
Or I will...
will definitely....
Your semen is pouring into me.
It's overflowing from the sides...
It's dripping out, and it's also filling my womb.
Oh crap!
I'm sorry.
I ignored your warning,
barged into the tea room,
got swept up by her,
and even though a plan had already been
set, I still ended up violating her.
I'm very sorry.
I'm a failure as an undercover judge officer.
I'm prepared to take whatever punishment is necessary.
Just forget it.
I now understand one thing based
on your interaction with her so far.
Deep inside, she is a masochist.
Huh? She's a masochist?!
Correct.
Taking her current work within the student council,
and the recent incident into account,
we can say that she is actually unconsciously trying to hurt herself,
using these unfortunate circumstances.
However, Manabe Wakana demonstrates excellence in
her studies, physical capabilities, and roles at school.
She is unable to feel fulfillment due to this status, and
thinks that she won't be able to submit to anyone.
In other words, she wants to submit to someone.
Isn't that what you call a masochist?
Of course, she will not yield to just anybody.
Then we can't finish what we started then!
We have you.
Me?
Don't be too modest of yourself.
Within you lies the long-developed spirit of sadism.
I thought of this while watching your
progress with our punishment.
That you seem to be capable of punishing your targets
to the point that they become sexually aroused by It.
By forcibly having sex with your target, you learn more about her.
From the viewpoint of a masochist you're the perfect sadist.
If you can unleash 100/o of that potential,
perhaps even Manabe Wakana would no longer feel unfulfilled.
As soon as one learns sexual feminine pleasure,
there would be no turning back from it.
Manabe Wakana would inevitably keep
coming back to you, Kyouichirou.
You said, I'm what?
No...
I'm going to break.
That part is going to break,
When it comes to sexual pleasure, you
body is still completely unprepared.
That's why, from here on, you can enjoy
sexual pleasure however you want to.
Please, pull these out of me.
I can't do this!
It's impossible...
Pull them out?
Your holes are already like that are you
really asking me to pull them out?
Oh no... I'm really going to break.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
My breasts...!
I said stop!
Stop!
You seem to be fine after losing your virginity, just a little earlier.
But, how about your virginity of this hole?
You can't...!
It won't fit in.
Please don't!
Stop!
I don't want any more of this.
It hurts...
Here, I'm going to move now.
It's going to tear apart.
It'll tear apart!
I-it'll bleed...
This is terrible.
No matter how popular you are at school, you'll just stink here.
Please don't say such disgusting things.
Please leave my asshole be.
Please don't move, it really hurts.
You're such a perverted girl.
Kyouichirou, send this foxy lady to her heaven!
Okay, you're already very bored of your
normal life as a council president,
so I'm going to take you and fully satisfy you!
No, it's getting squeezed in, and it hurts!
There s no other girl as horny as you!
My asshole is being rubbed inside.
I'm going to cum.
My butt is... my butt is...
I'm going to cum...
I'm going to cum from my butt!
I'm going to let it out.
I'm going to pour a lot into your stinking asshole!
It's still pouring out.
I'm going to die from this...
All the darkness that is within you,
shall be released along with your sexual pleasure!
It's coming.
It seems it's over now.
The thing that she deeply desires,
and the boredom that she experiences,
have all been taken care of now by Kyouichirou.
Now the punishment is truly complete.
My mission is now complete.
no longer require anything from you.
Darkness is no longer with you.
From now on, you must take the clear and honest path.
Well then, Godspeed.
Yamiko-san.
During Nee-san's absence, Yamiko-san was there.
Now that Yamiko-san's gone, there's no one around me.
What's the meaning of all that I've done?
Kyou-chan!
Nee-san!
I'm home, Kyou-chan.
I missed you.
Why?
Did you sneak out of the hospital?
No, didn't Shiraishi-sensei say anything to you?
I've been properly discharged from the hospital.
Then I've surprised you.
She probably kept her mouth shut about
it to really make it a surprise.
I think.
I've heard lots of things from Shiraishi-sensei.
Sensei was apologetic about it.
The fact that you had to be involved in such a work.
There isn't really any need for apologies.
I exacted revenge for my Nee-san.
But, It's all thanks to Yamiko-san that
did not go out of control because of it.
I never wanted you to take revenge.
I know that you worked hard just for my sake,
but I wouldn't be able to watch you hurt
somebody just because I was hurt.
I understand.
From now on, I'll never do anything that will make you sad.
I'll listen to any request that you may have.
Then, could I request something of you right now?
So this is what your cock now looks like.
Umm, Nee-san?
Just what are you...?
I'm sorry, the last time I saw it was when you were little,
when we started taking baths together.
I'm just a little shocked with it, now that you're all grown up.
Lots of things are probably going to come back to you now.
I can't stand seeing it anymore.
I know what happened to you.
You're still afraid of men, right?
So you don't have to force yourself to do it.
I'm okay with you simply treating me as your normal brother.
It's true that I'm still afraid of men right now.
You're my little brother, but you're special to me.
Because I've always been...
Me too, I've always thought about you that way, Nee-san.
Yes, I know.
I'm never going to let go of you again.
So... let's, umm...
The continuation of this...
Licky licky paradise.
Blowjob Hell?!
Binaural.
All in the special sex story ASMR CD!