Presented by Erobeat | http7/www.erobeat.net | erobeat @ ircrizon net
Translation: Micchan | Timing: Anon | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Kiritsu high school, a school where only academically ﻿outstanding students are allowed to enroll.
An academically intensive high school where students ﻿are free to choose what they want to do.
In Kiritsu high school, there's a governing body called ﻿the student council which consists of three women.
They're the elite of the elites.
Nobody can resist them.
Even if they're a teacher...
You know too much.
Stop acting like a fool.
This is fun!
No!!
Shut the fuck up!
No, someone help Me!
Help me, Kyou-chan!
Nee-san!
She's been coming home late these past few days.
Don't tell me she got herself a boyfriend and...
No, I shouldn't think that.
It's already been 10 years...
Nee-san is actually not my real sister,
she's my step-sister by marriage.
But when our parents died in an accident, she worked
to raise me even though she was still a student.
Why are you my exact type, Nee-san?
Nee-san’s getting sexier day by day.
She really is my type.
To say it bluntly, I love her.
A young beautiful female teacher...
I can't believe she's my sister!
How can I get rid of these horny
feelings I'm feeling all the time!?
Man, I can't hold it anymore!
Oh, right.
If I study hard, get into a good company, and get
a good salary, maybe my sister and I could...
She's way too late.
No! Stop it.
You have amazing tits, Hina-Sensei.
Don't say that...
You're actually feeling good right?
No wonder you have such hot tits.
Stop doing this right now.
I don't want my students to be criminals.
You have such a loud mouth.
When are you gonna stop acting all high and mighty?
Please stop. Anything but that...
No! Kyou-chan, Kyou-chan, please help me!
I'm gonna enjoy myself!
Oh, isn't that blood?
So you were a virgin?
Seriously!?
This is mortifying.
Looks like it hurts.
I seriously can't get enough of this.
I'll make you feel even better, Saki-chan.
I can't think straight.
I can t stand this anymore.
Kyou-chan, Kyou-chan, Kyou-chan!
Oh shit, I'm almost there.
Should I end this with me cumming inside of you?
Please don't! Anything but that!
I'm... I'm cumming!
I'm ruined...
Hey, Nee-san!
Hey! Where are you?
You! You're...
Ryou Seibai!
~The Secret Punishment Records of Pretty School Girls~
The Fallen Idol and Frozen A
So, you're saying the student
council did that to Nee-san?
There are many things in this world ﻿that you'd better not know.
If you don't wanna become all messed up like her, ﻿you shouldn't poke your nose in this anymore.
W-Wait!
I wanna expose the dark side of the student
council that did that to my sister.
I'll do anything, I swear!
I definitely can't leave those fucking bastards alone.
Do you know what a dark auditor is?
Isn't that Wakane-san? She’s so pretty.
Manabe Wakana...
Hey, what are you doing? Move already.
Where the hell did you come from!?
The student council is an organization that
governs and manages Kiritsu high school.
Three student representatives are the ﻿central members of the council.
It is said that they have more ﻿power than teachers and PTA
Although, there have been disturbing rumors about violence and illegal donations concerning them.
Manabe Wakana, one of the three student representatives.
She's the president of the council as ﻿well as the presidents the tea club.
She's also the granddaughter of the school principal.
She's charismatic, has great expectations, ﻿and is a very reliable student.
Apart from Manabe Wakana, there is Kobishima Urumi.
As the head of the office of public morals for three
years, she's been a very popular idol in the school.
She doesn't come to school often,
but she's very popular within the school,
and the fans cooperate well with each other.
Lastly, there is Mukuchi Kuu.
Even though she's a first year student, she has been
elected as the president of P E, association.
She beat numerous people's track and field records.
She's popular for being a super athlete
and cute like a little animal.
So in order for us to get to know our
enemy, we need to approach them.
Ouch!
Yamimaru-san, it hurts so please get off my head.
This ferret has the splendid name of Yamimaru-san.
Ouch!
Hey, if you keep doing that...
It always stays on top of my head and stays quiet,
but when it gets angry it goes on
rage, and the person can't handle it.
Yamimaru-san is angry cuz you’re not getting to the point.
No way...
Just go greet her already!
White...
No!
Sorry! I didn't mean to.
If you apologize this much, I won't ﻿be able to get angry at you right?
By the way, let me ask you frankly, what ﻿kind of impression did you get from her?
I can't believe that she ordered people to rape my sister.
There isn't many good school council presidents like her...
Right?
Not only is Manabe Wakana an outstanding student,
but she is also a young lady that holds great leadership.
I see.
However, every human has two sides.
If you don't look at both sides,
you can’t be a dark auditor.
I understand!
Everyone, thank you as always.
Wow she's hot.
Kobishima-sempai...
Alright guys, in order for the P-point to get on the
AB line, as far as the vectors are concerned...
Kakuin Mikado, the math teacher,
is on good terms with Nee-san.
From a man's point of view, he's a narcissistic old ﻿man, but he's popular among the female students.
Oh god... I hope Nee-san isn't...
I shouldn't think about this!
Excuse me...
Hey that's the girl from this morning!
I'm thinking of quitting work for a
while to concentrate on school.
Oh yeah, that would be better.
Thank you for your help.
Well then, I'll excuse myself.
Ah, we met this morning, didn't we?
Yes.
I'm nearsighted, so I have to take off my glasses
when I look at something close to me.
Hey you, what's your name?
Um, it's Kyou Ichiro.
Nice to meet you, Kyou Ichiro-kun.
Nice to meet you.
See you later!
Tsk.
Didn't you know?
Hinase-sensei is absent because
of the shock she received.
Seriously!?
Mogi was boasting about it.
Mogi said he made her a woman.
Was that him!?
Man I feel sorry for her. She was raped by that guy.
What's she doing in the hospital, anyway? It's just rape...
You bastards!
Hey...
It's dangerous for a female teacher like
you to be alone at school after dark.
Exactly!
So, what do you want with me?
I need to talk to you about Hinase-sensei.
When was the last time you saw her?
It was so dirty!
When I was putting Mr. Gigantic Cock in
her mouth, she was crying like a baby.
But you know, you’re pretty careless
to call me to such a place.
You want me to fuck you that badly?
Shame on you!
I'm so disgusted with garbage like you.
Fuck her up!
Help me!!
Alright then, tell me everything you know!
We were only following Kobishima's orders.
There's no one who can resist her.
Now we know the target.
So it's Kobishima-senpai...
Alright, let's ask people about her.
She has a lot of fans in the school, so
we should be able to get some info.
Forget it.
Even if we get information we're not
gonna be able to fond the truth.
Approach her head on.
Hey come on. It's fine, isn't it?
I've always had a crush on you.
Don't be ridiculous! I'm a teacher, and you're...
You worry too much.
It's fine, they're not gonna find
out if we only play around.
I'm afraid of the paparazzi too, so it'll be our secret.
You're too attractive and suspicious.
So, what's your purpose?
You want a better grade?
I want you to punish a girl I'm keeping an eye on.
Punish, you say?
That's right. You heard about Hinase-sensei right?
No way, that was your doing?
Yeah it was!
I had asked someone else to do
it, but he's no longer available.
Letter of Indictment
Kobishima Urumi-sama,
I know your weakness If you don't want to be exposed
school, come to the gym alone at night.
Why are you here!?
I see, it was you all along.
You’re such a coward to write a letter like this.
So what do you want?
I want you to tell me about my sister, Hinase Saki.
No way... Don't tell me you're...
Why did you order Mogi to rape my sister!?
Tell me!
Umm... Because she was standing out?
What'?
You see, she stands out.
It would be troublesome if she were around.
I want her out of my sight.
You looked useful so I was thinking ﻿of making you my slave.
Too bad it ended up this way.
Oh well, it's fine.
You're a pervert that likes his own sister.
You embarrassed my family!
What do you know about me?
Help!!
Hmm? Maybe I should've screamed louder.
Someone help me!
Oh my... It's hurting my ears.
You are the school doctor!
You were in with him all along?
Yeah. Looks like your bodyguards will
need to get looked after of by me.
Kobishima Urumi,
You will experience the people's pain firsthand.
Ryou Seibai!
The Secret Punishment Records of Pretty School Girls.
What the hell are you doing!?
Your voice is shaking.
You know what's gonna happen right?
No! Let me go!
I can't stand this.
Stop moving!
No...
Wow. It's so wet.
Your lips are trembling.
No! Don't look!
You're a teacher, aren't you? Stop him!
Sigh. Why don't you shut up already?
Alright Let's see how you taste.
Not there! No!
I m going to make you pay for this!
You're saying that but your pussy speaks the truth.
No... I'm feeling so weak...
It's loosened enough... for this.
What?
Please don't! Anything but that!
It's too late. Resistance is futile.
Watch me put it in.
Wow.
It's so tight, it feels like my cock is gonna tear it apart.
It's inside...
Be ready for this.
I'm gonna put my cock deep inside you.
It got in...
It hurts!
It hurts! No!
Take it out!! Take it out please...
Huh? It's bleeding.
So you were a virgin.
That's...
Please...
Forgive me.
What the hell are you saying?
This is only the beginning!
It's making dirty noises.
Looks like your pussy is enjoying my cock huh?
No... No way!
Well then, I'll make your pussy want more of my cock
Oh, no...
My body is feeling everything on its own.
I'm cumming.
Be ready for that.
No! Don't cum inside!
Cum outside! Outside!
Not inside!
No way... You came inside.
How dare you...
You're gonna get me pregnant.
It's not over yet.
Are you serious!?
No!
Why do I have to get raped like this!?
No way... It's getting bigger again...
I'm cumming again!
No! Don't cum inside anymore!
You're gonna get me pregnant!
He came inside again...
I don't know what to do.
I can't be an idol anymore.
You can still be a student.
All of your victims had left the school.
If you had left as well, things
wouldn't have been like this.
What are you saying!?
Even if I leave, things will still be the
same as long as Kuu-chan is here.
Kuu-chan... You mean Mukuchi Kuu?
Who else could it be!?
I'm sick of this now!
Girl's Track Club
Sensei... No...
What!?
She s masturbating?
My pussy is getting hot...
I want it more...
Harder!
It's going deep inside of me.
It’s touching inside...
Oh, no... I can't stop moving my hands.
Sensei, you smell good.
No! Your fingers are going inside.
How long have you been here, Yamiko-san?
Don't surprise me like that.
Be quiet.
If she finds us out, what are you gonna do?
More importantly, this isn't the
time for you to get a boner.
Fill my pussy with your love juice.
Good. It feels good! Sensei!
I want it! Do it harder! Harder!
My pussy's on fire!
I can't stop it!
Oh, no... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming, Sensei!
Oh, no!
I'm cumming! Cumming!!
Who are you!?
What were you doing?
You think you're going to get away with what you did?
I was just walking by when I heard some noises.
You just wanted to see my naked body, you stupid liar.
Sorry, my bad.
What kind of apology was that?
I'm never ever ever gonna forgive you.
This time it's you turn, so be ready for this.
So this is a penis...
What? Why is it getting so big?
So it gets like this, huh?
You're being so dirty.
The smell is...
*Sniff* *Sniff*
It smells dirty.
If I go like this...
Will it get bigger?
It's pretty big.
It doesn't fit in my mouth.
Hot juice keeps coming out.
It smells so strong.
It’s burning my nose.
I'm cumming...
I'm... I'm gonna cum!
Hurry up and cum if you want.
It's getting so hard all of sudden!
There's so much, and it smells great!
So this is what cum smells like.
his is what cum tastes like.
So we're even now, okay?
Oh crap, I have to go!
I need to hurry to the tea room.
I have a meeting with the teacher.
The tea room?
That's what she said.
Alright, let's follow her!
Okay.
What the hell are you doing!? It hurts!
Why do you have handcuffs if you're a teacher!?
Let me go! Idiot!
So why were you in the tea room?
What are you doing?
Just let me go already, idiot!
Who the hell would do something like this?
So your pussy looks like this, huh?
Why are you looking so closely?
Your pussy kinda smells strong and it's pretty sweaty.
Stop it! That place is...
If you want me to stop, are you
gonna answer my questions?
What's the real reason why you were in the tea room?
What are you doing there?
I just went to get something I forgot.
So why did you run away from us?
Wait!
Because you're freaking persistent.
We've got you, Mukuchi Kuu. Give yourself up!
What the hell's up with you guys!?
What's wrong? You still not willing to answer?
I went to get stuff I forgot.
It was a handout for my homework.
Well then, make sure you interrogate her real well.
Got it!
No! No...
Stop it! No!
Your tongue is getting inside.
No... No... Stop it!
What? You're even gonna do my asshole?
No! Stop it!
Even my asshole...
Why is this happening to me?
Don't put your tongue inside!
Or your fingers...
No! Stop it!
My pussy's on fire.
No...
Hey, stop it!
It's useless if she gets like that.
No...﻿
That place... No...
I can’t move my body.
No!!
What the hell was that crappy interrogation method?
Well, uh...
I really gave it my best...
We couldn't even get one single piece of information.
Even if you tell me that, that's about all
I can do since I have no experience.
That’s so pitiful.
If it was me, I would have been
able to get a lot out of her.
This is just too much.
Come.
Where?
I'm going to give an extra lesson to a bad student.
You should appreciate it.
Wait a minute!
What is this?
Wait, Yamiko-san...
Why am I like this?
This makes me look like such a pervert.
Wait, Yamiko-san.
Just stay still, and keep looking up.
What are you doing, Yamiko-san?
Get off me.
Hey don't stop, keep licking.
Just do what I say.
You've got no other choice.
See? It's getting all wet right?
It keeps coming out.
A bit more.
Stick your tongue further into my
pussy, and lick the shit out of it.
Your tongue is not moving. Don't stop.
Suck it. Suck it more.
More juice is coming out.
You're getting pretty wet too.
It taste strong and sweet, right?
Just slurp all you want.
You're pretty good.
That was average.
In the end, you were just giving in to your lust.
Did you get it Kyou Ichiro?
Don't forget this feeling.
Did you feel me fucking you for hatred or for lust?
Looks like it felt really good, huh?
Looks like I was wrong.
Yeah. You were.
You just raped Mukuchi Kuu to fulfill your desires.
That wasn't a punishment, but a rape.
Just for the sake of revenge,
you were committing sexual crimes.
You're right...
It's not my place to say this, but...
What are you doing? And what should you do?
Those are questions you should not forget.
Don't do things just because you’re feeling like crap.
I get it.
You're telling me punishment and
revenge are two different things.
That's right.
Thanks, Yamiko-san.
I don’t need thanks, just give me good results.
That's the best thanks you could give me.