Sir, you called out Koizumi last Thursday, right?
Nooo…!
Since then, she has been acting weird.
What in the world happened?!
Sir, you know, right?
Humiliation Girls Academy
presented by OppaiSubs
visit us @ hentaicloud.com/oppaisubs
TL: pinkunicorn123 I Edit, Type: Bl4Cc4t
Time: Mr.Mew I TLC: Applepiee I Encode: Galan_rus
Humiliation Girls Academy
After getting through this darkness...
kono yami wo kirinukete
kuroi kumo wo haide
Let’s go as far as we can,
blowing out black clouds.
doko mademo susumou
mirai no housoku wo
The law of the future,
kirisutete shimattemo
I can cut it away for this love.
kono ai no tame nara
nagasugiru meiro
Never-ending labyrinth,
kodoku na kage
lonely shadow.
Give us the courage to believe.
shinjiru yuuki wo ataeteyo
mada kiesarenai tachikire fade out
Indomitable fever that hasn’t faded away,
because it has something to protect.
mamoru beki mono ga aru kara
anatano yubisaki
Your finger tips...
hotobashiru kandou
Outpouring emotions...
When you touch my skin, I feel so sexy...
Unstoppable impulse!
tomaranai shakin’
Why are you not answering me?
Sir.
You are so annoying...
I already told you I don’t know.
She’s probably just sick.
With that said, let’s stop this conversation.
Sir, I’m not giving up on this.
Fujihira, wait a moment.
I have something I want to ask you.
What is it?
There’ve been some thefts going on in the school.
It seems like the culprit snuck into the classrooms after school, when everyone was already gone.
What’s that got to do with me?
Nothing, I just thought I’d tell you since you are fixating on me.
Maybe it’s because you are hiding something yourself.
What?
Are you saying that I’m the thief?
I’m not saying that…
But it’s a good opportunity
to check your belongings, I guess.
If you’re not the thief,
that shouldn’t be a problem.
This is an important job
for me as a disciplinary teacher.
Have you found anything special?
Yes. Something unbelievable.
Wha—
This.
As you can see, it’s a condom.
From a love hotel.
I don’t know such thing.
I’ve never been to these hotels before!
Even though you’re not the thief, this is another big problem, Fujihira.
B-But that’s not mine!
Why would something that doesn’t belong to you be inside your bag?
What are you saying?
I think I need to check thoroughly.
What on earth—
Take off your clothes.
As a disciplinary teacher,
I have to check your underwear.
What?! Are your serious, sir?
“School Regulation Number 14.2a”
It’s a rule about your underwear.
You are not allowed to wear too bright colored underwear.
I’ll check it, so just take off your clothes!
No way in hell!
If you really need to,
please call a female teacher!
You want to be expelled, Fujihira?
Hurry up!
Or is your underwear too sexual that you don’t want to show?
No!
Hurry up and take it off, you failed child!
Show me your dirty underwear!
This is too horrible…
Did you also do this to Koizumi?
W-What, how dare you?!
I understand how you treat students now.
Making students do these dirty things…
What’s with that rebellious attitude?
You don’t mind me
telling the principal about your condom?
Sure, go ahead!
I also have things to tell the principal!
And I will show him the audio file I just recorded!
Wait, Fujihira!
Wait!
Stop looking down on teachers!
L-Let me go please!
Or I scream out loud!
Let’s have a deal.
What? A deal?
Let’s talk calmly.
I’ll listen to what you have to say.
Sorry, but I have nothing to say to you.
Goodbye.
Fu-Fujihira…!
Shit!
That brat Fujihira.
What happened, mate?
Seems like you’re having a bad time.
Oh, it’s you Hanyuu.
You seem like you’re living a good life.
Well yeah, I do.
Oh yes, I wanted to contact you.
I got a girl that you might like.
What kind of girl is she?
You sure she’s suited for me?
Well, wanna see her picture?
What do you think?
She looks good, doesn’t she?
Her name is…
…Fujihira.
Fujihira Junko…
You know her?
Oh you have no idea.
This is an interesting coincidence.
It’s her fault that I’m drinking shitty alcohol here.
Now I’ve lost my job as disciplinary teacher.
So you do have some problem.
But you see, this woman…
Nah, this is a good one, Hanyuu!
It’s getting interesting.
You thought of something, huh?
I’ll use this woman for something “fun”.
I’m sure you know what kind of fun I’m thinking of.
Guess we share the same thoughts.
Good, Chisato.
It seems you have improved a lot.
Why of course, while you were away I trained her after all.
Last time, she went fully right after I started playing with her.
You don’t have to tell him that…
Geez, because of the Fujihira family I wasn’t able to train her myself.
She would’ve been able to take in my dick with her ass by now if it wasn’t for them.
This is the best!
This kept throbbing
every night since I’ve let you do this.
No!
You’re much cuter now, Chisato, when you’re longing for more.
No, don’t say these things…
You’re such a good girl, Chisato.
From now on you’ll be helping men to release their pleasure.
You’re perfectly suited for this task!
Yes, if it’s for you, teacher!
First, I’ll smash that mother with a prim expression!
I’m cumming!
So am I!
Small Conference Room
How is the follow-up with Mr. Naganuma going?
My daughter said she’s heard from a friend…
…that there are graduates who had something with him before…
and work as prostitutes now.
Well, it seems like there are a lot of rumors going on…
I’ve heard this rumor before, too.
About this issue, the school has already started its research,
but we haven’t found out whether it is true yet.
Currently, he doesn’t seem like he is with any person.
How relieving…
He doesn’t seem to show his tail that easily.
I can’t believe there is such a teacher at this famous school.
If only we could do something…
That’s what happened, huh?
I don’t know what the school is thinking.
I can’t believe the school would take in such teacher,
even though he is a relative of the principal…
I guess it can’t be helped.
It’s a private school after all, and it’s probably hard for the principal to go hard on his relative.
Dear…
That’s the sad thing about society.
Tomomi was mad at me the other day.
She said I’m acting too cold towards her.
“Even Mom would leave you if you are like this”…
“and find someone else that she loves.”
It would be too late for me if that were to happen.
How can she say such things to you?
Well, I’ve been too busy lately.
I really had very little time
to be with the family. I’m sorry.
Dear…
—apparently, don’t you think this is hilarious?
Bye, then! Don’t be late tomorrow!
Of course I won’t!
All right, good night!
Good night, Tomomi.
I love you.
Idiot!
Seeya!
Okay.
Hey madam, is it really already over?
I’m sorry.
I still love you, Hanyuu, but…
I found that I need to value my family more!
I really can’t keep this relationship with you!
I understand.
But, you will still join me for tonight, right?
This will be our last...
Or I might end up visiting your home…
All right.
Phew…
Seems like it went well.
Scary, the pills took longer than expected…
Have more faith in me.
But then, I did get scared for a bit too.
So what now?
You wanna do it immediately?
Of course, I’ve been wanting
to do it for a while now.
Okay, I’ll be watching you guys
from the room next door.
Nice…
If you’d like to, please use it!
Mate, yours is pretty big.
She might wake up in the middle.
Thanks for thinking ahead.
I’m back.
Hey!
Is anyone there?
Hey, Junko!
I’m home!
Oh, Dad!
Where is Junko?
No idea, maybe out shopping?
This late?
And you too, why are you so late?
I had meetings and stuff.
I see.
Finally awake, madam?
W-What is it? Hanyuu?
What are you doing? Stop…!
Sorry, but I’m not Hanyuu, madam.
Please stop! Who are you?
I’m sure that if you stay calm,
we can both have fun together.
What are you doing?
Who the hell are you?!
Please stop!!
If you want to know that badly, I’ll tell you!
You…
Long time no see, madam.
Noooo!
Please stop it, I beg you!
Forgive me!
No! Why are you doing such things?!
Stop it!
I’m about to cum, madam!
Stop… Not that, please. No!
Nooo!
So, your mom didn’t come home?
No… This has never happened before...
Have you told the police?
Not yet…
Father said we should wait another day first.
I see…
Sorry to bother you with such a problem…
I’m sure it’s also troubling for you…
You’re probably mad at me.
No way I am.
Thanks for listening to me though, Naoki.
Bye!
Goodbye, dear...
It was a pleasure
being with you.
Why? Why is this?!
Junko!
Dad, are you back?
Sorry I’m late again.
What have you been up to until this late hour?
I was studying at my friends home.
Oh studying.
That’s nice. With who, I wonder?
Tell me the name!
I’ll call and tell them thank you.
What happened, Dad?
You’re not yourself, you drank too much!
Oh, so you can’t tell me?
Are you making fun of me
that your mother is cheating on me?
I’m also very shocked that mom is missing!
Act normal, Dad!
What? You were home late and now you are scolding your dear father?
Such a “good” daughter!
Dad…
Even you!
Eh?
So you are leaving me too?
Dad…
Tomomi!
Open up!
I’m sorry!
Please!
Tomomi!
Tomomi!!
Hello, this is Akiyama.
I can’t answer your call at the moment.
Please leave your message after the—
Hey, Tomo.
I got something I want to ask you…
What is it?
Sorry…
for asking you to meet my boyfriend.
And asking for other weird things.
It’s okay!
I’m relieved that it’s nothing serious!
I thought Mr. Naganuma
molested you or something.
Did I say something weird?
No, that’s not it.
I just think you are amazing.
Why?
You always fight for justice, and you’re so bright and active.
We’re just completely different.
No, not at all!
Tomo.
Are you not going to change?
Even since cruel things happened…
Will you stay strong,
no matter what happens?
Hey, Chisato, is it gonna take longer to your boyfriend’s place?
Oh look, you can see it from here.
It’s that mansion right there!
Oooh!
Will you be able to take it?
Through the hell you will be put in?
Hey, can you tell me?
How do you plan to go against this?
Chisato, you did well.
I’m proud of you.
Almost awake, huh?
Eh?
What?
Yoshimura!
W-What is this?!
W-What is happening?!
Mr. N-Naganuma!
Why?
Awake now? Our school’s princess…
I’ll let you “apologize” to me plenty.
No! Untie me! Please!
This attitude doesn’t suit you.
How despicable!
Using such dirty methods!
How are you even a teacher?!
Oh, it’s been only us females “playing” with you until now.
The real excitement will come later.
Stop it! Don’t touch me!
You really love masterbation, don’t you?
You’re very wet.
Precocious child.
You are so dirty.
So much moist coming from your pussy.
No, stop! Help me! Untie me!
No!
About to cum, huh?
You don’t have to hold it.
Come on, come on!
What’s with you?
The foreplay hasn’t even ended!
The main part has yet to start.
Good girl.
I’ll make you a female with my specially big dick.
If you want to rape me, then go ahead!
I’ll fight with you.
And get you arrested!
Oh really?
But I wonder what your mother would say.
If I get caught,
she’d be so sad that she loses my dick.
What are you saying?
You want to know?
Here…
That’s a magic mirror.
Isn’t it funny.
I don’t want to see!
Good girl, go ahead and look clearly.
It’s the woman you’ve been seeing everyday at home.
That can’t be true!
You can’t just...
It’s not her!
I’m about to cum!
I can’t hold it anymore!
You really like it in the butt, huh, Junko?
Mom!
Why is she in such...
Finally understood the situation, huh?
Now it’s your turn.
Stop it you pervert!
Get away from me!
Let me get a return from what you did last time.
Wow, you sure are wet.
You were waiting for me that long?
No! Don’t! Stop it!
Both Yasuko and Chisato,
I have taken their virginity.
No…! Stop it!
You’re overreacting!
It’s only the tip!
You really hate me, huh?
Looks like it’s all in!
Looks painful!
How is it?
How tight! You sure are like your mother!
N-No…! Stop already!
Please don’t! No!
Let me give it to you inside!
Let me fill your vigin pussy with my cum!
No way!
Stop it! Stop, stop…
Sir, it’s so wonderful!
Give her lots more!
Give her the biggest present you have!
There’s more to cum!
Let’s get started with the mother-child meal.
I guess so, yeah.
Mom!
I will not forgive you!
For messing up my family…
These men…
I’ll have my revenge.
kirameku genseki
Gemstones that shine...
menomae no hotaru
The firefly in front of me...
yasashii hikari ni
My heart is taken away
kokoro ubaware
from its calming lights...
kikoete kuru nowa
I can hear
chiisana futatsu no kodou
the small heartbeats of two.
Feel my heart!
moshimo kono yoni
If in this world,
densetsu aru nara
there is a legend,
shinjite miyou
let me believe
ikitsuku sono ai wo
in that love I end up with!