Stupid men...!
Onii-chan...
Original Animation Video
W
Guerrilla Hunting
2nd: The Shameful Red Uniform
Elena... why?
Why did you do that?
At this rate, I’ll...
Elena... her face looked like she was charmed.
And she wasn’t... resisting.
That can’t be true!
Especially not with Elena!
But, Elena was wearing a different uniform.
Why?
Why is it?
I don’t understand.
Why?
Why did you do that, Elena?
Let me tell you.
What?
Since the feds betrayed you girls, from this day on, you'll be my pets.
Starting today, I’ll become your new big brother, Red.
Wh-What are you saying?
You pervert!
Barging in here like that...
And taking out something so filthy...
And what’s more!
Elena...!
Resistance is not an option.
So just give up, sweetie.
I want your body to learn firsthand what a man is.
Get out of here fast!
Hurry!
Please, I’m begging you...
I... I can’t take it...
Ew! I can’t...
Please, stop...
No!
Hey, Red.
No time to slack off on the job.
Come on.
This is... a man’s thing...?
How grotesque... why?
Now.
Stop spacing out and suck on it.
No way! It stinks!
Get that dirty thing away from me!
No... oh no.
What?
It’s twitching.
It’s getting bigger.
Unless you hurry, your Colonel will break.
If you suck on it and make me feel good, I’ll release her.
Fine, I’ll do it.
I’ll suck on it, okay?
Unless you take it seriously, you’ll suffer too.
It’s hard.
And also... hot.
My mouth is so full now...
Oh no!
It’s flinching again.
It stinks.
Ew.
I don’t... want this in my mouth...
Not this gross thing.
What’re you trying to do?
No technique at all.
You suck, in the wrong way.
Shit, that’s awful.
You do it like this.
Come on.
So big!
My jaw is coming unhinged.
Come on, move your tongue now.
I’m going to throw up.
I can’t take it!
Oh well, you’re so hopeless.
It’s your punishment.
Drink it all up.
Swallow!
What is this?
There's... so... much...
No! Stop it!
If you do this... you’ll break your promise!
You said if I sucked you off, you’d release me!
But you got so wet just sucking me off.
Like this, you’re not a victim, you’re just a slut.
No! I’m not a slut!
If you’re so lewd, you'll make your brother sad.
How do you know that?
The feds sent me all your personal data.
All your private information and everything.
Wh-What are you trying to do?
S-Stop it!
Your beloved brother never did this to you, did he?
It hurts...
How pure you are.
Did you pleasure yourself all this time so as not to bother Elena?
Shut up!
No!
It’s inside of me
The hot thing is inside of me.
It’s your first time, but I can still tell you’re really wet.
It hurts...
Stop...
Please...
It’s... inside.
That gross thing... is inside of me.
It hurts!
No!
I hate this!
Help me!
Onii-chan!
It hurts!
Even though you say it hurts, your nipples sure are firm.
No... Don’t... Not...
No... No!
It’s all the way inside.
I can’t... get it out.
No... Stop it!
It hurts, but... my body is... so hot!
So the pain feels that good to you, eh?
That’s not...
Oh? But you’re so wet inside.
That’s a lie!
You’re lying!
You idiot.
You’re starting to thrust your hips too – you’re lying.
No!
No...
I... I’m not...
You’ve reached the limit of your restraint?
Please... not anymore.
I don’t want it.
Don’t you realize the situation you’re in right now?
You’re in great condition.
What a slutty body you have.
No!
Oh no!
I can’t... I can’t take it!
Just take it.
I’m gonna cum plenty inside you.
You idiot!
Don’t cum inside me!
You can’t do that!
No!
D-Don’t...
Don’t!
I’m cumming.
Giselle... I’m so sorry.
So gross.
It’s all inside me...
Flooding me.
What’s wrong with the federation?
I’ve never felt so bitter!
That gross guy stole my first time from me!
Don’t think that!
It’s not ending this way!
I’m going back to normal!
No...
Don’t...
Your mouth may say no, but your pussy is soaking wet.
Don’t say...
I don’t like this... but...
It’s tickling me... all the way inside.
I'm cumming... No... I don’t like this...
It’s filling me up...
No!
It looks like you’ve gotten used to it.
Has your boyfriend’s face been replaced by my cock?
It’s not relevant anymore!
I’m a soldier!
Your cock is flinching... and...
I hate it.
Your cock is filling me up... hitting my uterus...
So full... my uterus is so full... cum inside me!
I... can’t go back to the way things were.
Things will have to stay... like this.
Giselle... I’m sorry.
You got hurt because of me.
Giselle.
Elena...
If we get past this spot, we’ll be in the Admiral’s room.
I got it, Elena.
Giselle... I...
Elena.
That face doesn’t suit you.
I mean, you’re our captain!
You’re the girl my brother chose.
Giselle!
Let’s escape this place. With everyone.
And then, you’ll be back with the one you love.
Giselle...
We’re going, Giselle.
Elena.
Thank you, Giselle.
Huh? No one’s here.
There’s no mistaking it.
Admiral Claus is supposed to be in here.
And I was planning on kidnapping the Admiral to bargain.
It looks like you were too late.
Give everyone back to us!
Captain Logel, release our friends at once!
Do you seriously think you stand a chance against me?
What are you talking about?
Stop stalling and do it!
Huh? No way!
You sure are stupid.
E-Everyone else is here, right?
Let’s free them before he can do more to us!
I... I can’t!
Elena...?
Your friends, eh?
You two might be the only ones who feel that way.
Wh-What are you talking about?
What?
I’ll set your companions free.
If you insist.
Then release them now!
Just take a peek in that room behind me.
Well, brace yourself first.
Wh-What’s this?
This is a place where we punish people like you.
This is Admiral Claus... isn’t it?
YOU did this?
All of your friends are about to break.
Thanks to the Shither drug.
At this rate...
Where did you put them all?!
They’d better be okay!
Don’t worry.
They’re still okay.
But... what happens to them now is in your hands.
What exactly are you suggesting I do?
Your bodies will be perfect bargaining chips.
And if we help, you’ll release our friends, right?
If you want me to release your friends, just stop talking and start sucking.
I’m taking care of them.
So you girls will make perfect bargaining chips.
I never thought this would happen to me.
You're one to talk.
With that slutty face of yours.
You don’t look worried to me.
Well, I’d better teach you a little more.
You're really squeezing me nicely.
I guess you’re used to it now.
N-No...
That's...
It’s way too deep!
You’ve got spunk.
You’re sluttier than Elena.
I’ve got a charmed face just like Elena.
Let’s show your beloved brother just how slutty his little sister is.
You’re wrong... I’m not slutty.
No... My face... I don’t want my brother to see it.
Unless you get even sluttier, your friends won’t be saved.
If he does much more to me... I’ll break.
Every time I slap you, you squeeze me tighter.
That’s the reaction I want.
You can’t... do that.
I’ll break...
I... I’ll break!
So your proud face is finally melting.
No!
I don’t look like...
No...
You don’t want your brother to see you like this?
Your brother belongs to Elena anyway.
I... I don’t really... care... as long as they’re happy together.
You liar.
Your slutty body won’t change anything.
That’s not true at all!
I...
Well, no matter what happens, it doesn’t concern me.
I’ll just teach him the same way I taught you.
No... Don’t!
It’s coming...
No... No...
If this keeps up, I’ll... I’ll... I’ll break!
Then don’t think about anything.
Just feel good.
Welcome.
Milano speaking.
Sorry to be so sudden, but I still can't forget the tight feeling inside of me.
Yes.
Though my husband forced me to wear...
The military uniform...
It was thick and the fabric smothered my body.
And a hot sensation boiled up from deep inside me.
All the way to my special places.
Putting this on my body...
Makes it feel like I’m being embraced by my husband.
Oh no, when did I start doing this?
I’m rubbing my own nipples.
And I’m twirling my fingers around inside my pussy.
Oh, what if someone sees me being so slutty?
It’s flowing out...
Mi-Milano... is cumming!