What's happened to me? I can't see anything.
I can't hear anyone. I can't feel anything either!
Urara, I've been waiting for over
10 years for this moment.
Sensei?
Sensei, it's you right?
It's you who's doing this to me right?
I'll endure it then!
If it's you, then I'll endure whatever you do to me.
I've been lonely ever since
your mother passed away.
The only person who can accept
our feelings now is only you, Urara!
No...
This isn't sensei! These aren't sensei's hands! Stop!
Sensei, save me!
Urara! Urara!
We can only love masochistic
woman like your mother
who accepted everything we have to
offer with their voluptuous body.
It's not him. This isn't sensei.
Sensei, where in the world did you go?
Come back, hurry and come back!
Your mother was the same. I paid to get her out of
prostitution and made my son have sex with her.
We would fuck her silly all day
whenever we had days off.
Agh, I can't hold it anymore!
I'm going to cum right in your pussy!!
Urara, it's me. Can you tell?
Sensei?
Yes, it's Ryoudouji Shimon.
Sensei's penis feels so good.
How slutty. She's wriggling her body
trying to feel his penis more.
She's riding that big penis with such vigor...
Sex slaves aren't sex dolls
that have no life to them.
If you treat them nicely like this, they will
give their body and mind to their master.
Master, I'm sorry. I can't be satisfied
anymore without a penis inside me.
Please, please forgive me.
Urara, Grandpa and Dad really love you too as well.
Why not have fun having sex?
Just like your mother.
Yes. Please have fun as well, you two...
with my slutty ass body.
Please love me, please love me.
Oh yeah, here we go then. I'm
about to blow. Cum with me.
Yes, yes, I'm cumming.
I'll cum with you as much as you want.
Penis, penis...
This tightness is too...
So much...
Sensei, sensei... I'm cumming.
I'm cumming in you!!!
I'm cumming...
Just how slutty was her body raised to be.
We were wrong. Who knew you would be
so receptive if we just gave you love.
You are not just a replacement for your
mother. You're the best, Urara!
I'm cu... cumming!
Alright, time for the real show now.
Let's satisfy her even more.
I'm so happy right now.
Let's have more sex.
Ah, it's so good. In my asshole and my pussy...
I'm fucking your pussy so deeply and yet you still...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming again.
Cum in me.
I'm cumming... Swallow it all!
Very nice Urara. We'll make
you cum more and more.
Let's show the two of them your real ecstasy.
Wait, sensei. It's too embarrassing.
Show us Urara. Show us your real ecstasy.
Grandpa's and Dad's semen, so much of it...
Cum on me even more...
I just have to...
So rough, you're so rough...
Very good Urara.
Show them your cumming face even more.
Her cleavage is like peaches...
It feels so good...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
Urara, Urara...
Excellent Urara. Show them everything.
Show them the real you.
Ahh, it's coming out. All of it is coming out.
Agh, I'm cumming.
Look at yourself in the mirror. The
you who used to be so pure.
Look at how much you have changed.
Sensei, don't say that please. It's embarrassing.
You've become my sex slave.
Your vagina, mouth, and your asshole...
You're now a sex slave, that's all... Embrace
the joy as you take in cock.
But you said that I was cute, and
that you like me very much...
You said that you love me...
I did, and I wasn't lying. The pervert and
slut you are is so cute and I love you.
Why do I feel so good
even though I'm being treated so horribly.
It feels so good.
It's all right, I'm here for you.
Only I know the real you.
Sensei, sensei... Please love me, the sex slave
who has become so perverted and slutty.
Of course, Akane.
– Suzuka-sensei, what is this...?
– Just be quiet and watch.
Akane, Shuuichi-kun was your boyfriend right?
In that case, you have to properly
give him an explanation.
No... Sensei... Please, please forgive me.
Please forgive me.
Akane, do you really think you can make
an excuse after being caught like this.
It's all right Akane. I'm here for you.
So go ahead and tell him your true feelings.
Sorry Shuuichi-kun. I...
I've already become Shimon-sensei's sex slave.
What... the fuck are you saying...
Shimon-sensei's cock is insane. That's why I had sex
with him over and over with my pussy and asshole.
I kept cumming.
Shuuichi-kun, you reap what you sow.
You didn't cherish Akane.
She had no choice but to come to me.
I, I... Even though, Shuuichi
and everyone is looking...
My pussy wants to cum again.
I don't mind. Today is the marvelous day
that you've been reborn as a sex slave.
I'll give you my cum as many times as you want.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy sensei.
Cum, cum with me.
Ah, it feels so good.
Sensei, sensei...
Wow...
Fuck this... She's just a slut who will
sleep with anyone at this point.
She looks so pure on the outside too...
She's just another pervert slut!
Shuuichi-kun, you're wrong.
I may have become a pervert sex slave,
but I'm not a slut.
What...?
I mean... I'll never let you fuck me.
I'll only ever have sex with sensei.
Isn't that right, sensei?
Yes,
Akane is a very good girl.
She says that she only wants to
have sex with who she loves.
That's probably why she didn't
let you fuck her isn't it?
That's... No, Akane is my girlfriend,
and gave me her first kiss...
Let's go. Lets show Shuuichi-kun
and everyone our love.
Of course.
Wow, your penis is getting larger...
My hole is so full...
Akane feels so good that I can
get hard over and ever.
Thank you very much.
Please cum until you feel satisfied.
Use my pussy in any way you like.
I can't help myself watching this...
Please, let me do you as well.
No can do. The only person who
can have sex with me is sensei.
Akane, if it's not penetration...
What...?
I want them to help improve your sex skills.
Leaving him so devastated like that is too pitiful.
To be honest, that was the real reason
I called them here today.
Of course, it's up to how you feel.
Okay, if you put it that way.
A... Akane.
In return, you have to listen to whatever
sensei and I say, okay?
How lucky you two are.
Akane...
I can't stop myself anymore...
Kei-kun's cock is twitching so much.
It feels so weird doing it with the
three of you at the same time.
Akane... Akane... I'm cumming...
Ah, so much...
Very nice Akane, just like that. Show me you
getting more and more sticky with cum.
Gotcha.
Shuuichi-kun, you can cum as well.
It's alright to cum on my face.
Ahh... Let it out.
Do my makeup with your cum.
No, sensei...
I'll cum if you fuck me so roughly.
I'm cumming in front of everyone...
It's like a pussy, right?
Fuck it harder.
Make my armpit pussy cum with your penis!
You came again...
My armpit pussy came from getting
ravaged by Kei-kun...
I'll become a cum-addict if you
guys cum on me so much.
Let out even more...
Ah, you came again.
Did you get aroused by my pig nose?
Ah, Akane.
Ah, I can't hold it any...
I feel it... so gooey in the back of my
throat, throbbing... So much cum...
I'm cumming while swallowing cum!
I'm cumming while swallowing cum...
Look at me...
Look at how much you came inside my mouth...
Cleanup, cleanup.
Ah, I'm going to cum again...
Cumming...
Akane, you're amazing.
That's right. I'm doing this for sensei. I'm doing
my best at fellatio and sex for sensei.
Sensei...
Very good, very good...
You're very slutty Akane.
So much tasty cum...
So tasty...
Ah, they're cumming again.
Shuuichi-kun, more cum. I'm not going to
let you go untill you cum in my breasts.
Cum, cum please!
I'm being so turned on.
My pussy is tightening so much.
I want to cum. I want to cum!
I'm going to cum again!
You did so well Akane.
Let me reward you even more.
It's your first time being double-penetrated right?
How does it feel, Akane?
Ah, cumming!
It feels so good.
Ahh, the sight of Akane getting more
and more slutty, bathed in cum...
Sensei, look at me. Please look at me more!
The only person who gets to
fuck me roughly is you...
I'm yours, I'm only yours...
I'm yours and only yours so take me!
I'm... cumming!!!
I don't even know how many
times I've cum at this point...
Ah, wait, Akane, I'm going to cum...!
Gosh Kei-kun, it's so sticky...
This is real sex...
Sensei, Shimon-sensei...
Cumming... cumming!
Cunt on this hole as well...
Ah, so much...
Alright Akane, this will be the last round for now.
Sensei...
I'm going to shoot the rest
of my cum in your womb.
So slutty!
Sensei... Please cum, please cum!
I'm going to cum. It feels so good...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too...
How marvelous. Akane you are fantastic.
Sensei...
So beautiful...
This is the most ideal you.
You are the best sex slave.
It looks like the slave training
of the female students is going well.
Directors office
I expected nothing less of you.
Well, at the moment it is anyways.
At this rate, I might even take into consideration
what you proposed last time.
Really?!
Tonight would be convenient.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes... I've done it.
The time has finally come...
This time around, I'll finally get to
actually have sex with Sayaka.
Hey...
Can we not do it like this?
You want to enjoy having sex
with me too, don't you.
No can do. If you won't put
that on, you get no reward.
I'm going to leave you here like this,
and just go home.
Getting so erect already...
Do you really want my body that much?
Sister, I want it too...
I want Shimon-sama's penis...
Didn't you already have fun
with him enough already?
This is a reward,
and a punishment for the both of you.
Pu-punishment?
I'm letting you fuck my pussy,
so no complaints...!
This is it, this feeling...
I don't want this vibrator...
Please let me have his penis!
I wanted to taste this pussy so much.
What are you saying?
Pussies are the same all around.
Do you really not realize it?
Your pussy is a one in a million rare pussy.
What do you mean rare pussy?
You dream too much.
This suction and this texture...
It's so smooth and bouncy...
How funny that such a slave trainer as yourself
is feeling so much from my pussy.
Agh, I'm going to cum if you do it like that...
Your penis is already throbbing.
My pussy,
you can cum in my pussy if you want.
Shoot as much as you want inside.
I can't believe Shimon-sama
is cumming so quickly...
I want to cum with sister and
Shimon-sama as well...!
No Suzuka.
You can just stay there and play with your toy.
I'm going to cum at this rate too!
I'm cumming too...
What's wrong? You wanted to have sex
with me right? Then do as you please.
Why don't you just fuck my brains
out like the students?
No, that wasn't my intention...
You can fuck my mouth harder if you want.
Here, it feels so good right.
I'm going to cum instantly again...
How pitiful...
You can cum if you want,
but make sure you leave enough
to cum in my pussy!
Did you save up...?
You came so much...
Sister, please save some for me as well...
Getting your penis so hard again... I'm going
to squeeze out all your cum with my pussy.
I'm at my limit...
Sister, I'm, I can't...
I'm going to go insane...!
You can feel it can't you? You can feel
my pussy squeezing you right?
Shoot everything you have into me!
I'm going to cum together with you...
Are you okay, Shimon-sama?
Uh... uh...
It's been a while since I've had such fun.
If you want a reward again,
keep on working hard at slave training.
God dammit!
I'm not going to give up!
I'm going to get the you from
back then no matter what!
Student and teacher candidates for
enslavement are still plentiful.
I'm looking forward to your work
in the future, Shimon-kun.
Translation: Elton
Timing: Elton
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч