Do you... like flowers?
Yes.
These are verbena flowers.
They're known as "Sakura of Beautiful Women", in Japanese.
These flowers have such lovely insides.
I bet this girl's insides are just as lovely.
I'm sure she'll make a great specimen for me.
Ryuudouji Shimon's
Obscene Plot
Part 1 Traning of the Sex Slaves
And, Shimon-kun?
How goes the training of the female students?
Smoothly so far.
Directors Office
There haven't been any huge problems.
A customer's been inquiring about them.
He is the buyer and...
He wants to get a taste of what he's buying.
I have several students that I'm just putting
the finishing touches on now.
They'll be in perfect shape.
That's what I'm hoping for, Shinon-kun.
After all, my body knows just how
good you are at training women.
It's inside!
Take that! And that!
It's inside me!
Master, please!
More! More!!
Please mess up my dirty pussy more!
No problem, Sayaka, I'll shoot it in your pussy again!
Thank you very much!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna get cummed in again too!
You fucking whore. Beg me more!
No... It's going so deep inside me!
I'm gonna cum again!
It's getting so tight inside!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming again!
Drink it up!
I never thought that we'd reunite like this.
Do you...
Still hold a grudge against me?
Oh, look at the time.
Afternoon classes are about to begin, Ryuudouji-sensei.
Sayaka, don't forget. If I train your sex slaves...
I know.
When you do, I'll play with you.
Just wait, Sayaka.
I'll definitely capture you again.
Your dick is so... wonderful, Shimon-sama!
Listen, Sofuka.
I'm starting Tonegawa Urara's sex slave training tomorrow.
Y-Yes!
I understand, Shimon-sama!
Starting tomorrow, your dick will be inside Urarara-san...
This will be the final push for her.
I'm counting on you for the preparations.
Yes! Yes! I understand.
Please, I beg of you, give me...
Please give your... magnificent cum to me, Shimon-sama!
Yeah, I'll shoot it deep in you right now.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Look, it's a cum shot straight down your throat.
Yes! Yes, please!
I'm cumming!
Good, here's your reward.
I'll fuck you from behind.
I'm nothing but your dirty pet.
Please mess me up... Mess me up however
you'd like, Shimon-sama!
Really? You're really okay with
me doing you however I want?
No takebacks.
Here! Take that!
N-No!
I'm gonna cum!
You can cum, but don't do it too much.
It's easier to enjoy this slippery, but tight pussy that way!
Please retrain my pussy!
That's good.
You're not just a slut.
You're going to become my cute sex slave, right?
Y-Yes. Yes!
I will be your sex slave, Shimon-sama.
I'll do it, so please take care of me deep inside!
Good girl, Suzuka. I'll give you your reward milk soon.
I want it!
I want your reward milk!
Please shoot it out inside me!
You just came, but you're...
Your insides are wriggling around me, I'm gonna cum again!
I'll give you tomorrow's reward in advance.
I'm counting on you, Suzuka.
Y-Yes...
I understand, Shimon-sama...
Um, sensei?
Is today this kind of play?
Urara, you can hate me.
But even if I break your body, please don't lose your mind.
What are you going to do to me? I'm scared!
Sensei? Why are you...
Sensei? I'll do whatever you tell me to do.
I will! So please...
Just hold on for a little bit, okay?
Urara's arms aren't bound.
She could take off the restraints on
her legs and run away if she'd like.
So the question is, how long will she be able to endure this?
It'll be okay.
I'm sure sensei just wants to have some fun by teasing me.
I'm sure that after this is over, he'll be nice
and apologize for this, so I can't be scared!
I want to hurry up and make love not
to these toys but to sensei's dick!
Sensei! Please make love to my dirty body!
Urara, do you really trust me that much?
I'm cumming! Both from my nipples and my clitoris!
I'm being played with in my embarrassing places!
No... If you keep hitting me like that, I'm gonna...
Why? Why?!
This is nothing but embarrassing and
painful to go through with, but...
But why am I getting so wet from it?!
Why does it feel so good?!
To be a good sex slave, you must be
able to endure any Master's training.
That's what this is all for.
We're just getting started, Urara.
Stop! Stop!!
If you keep going that deep inside me...
My insides are being messed up!
Sensei, stop! I can't breathe!
Please stop! My mouth, my pussy,
and my ass are all about to break.
I'm going to break!
Urara, you're able to accept any kind of pleasure.
You've become a complete dirty slut.
You've been reborn.
Here! Take this!
That's right! Take it deeper!
Accept all of me!
Can you tell how deep I'm hitting your throat?
This is your reward. I'm cumming on your face!
Urara, can you hear it?
It's me... Shimon!
Sensei? Let's have sex, sensei!
Sure.
Please hurry and shove your dick inside me!
My ass, my pussy...
I don't care where you put it!
Please just give it to me.
That's good. Do it the way you want it.
Your dick! Your dick feels so good!
Wow! It's hitting me so deep!
It feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
Your dick's in between my boobs!
It feels so good between my boobs!
There's so much cum from you, sensei...
It feels so good!
My ass feels so good!
More! Do me harder!
No! It feels so good!
I'm cumming!
Wow, there's still so much...
Sensei! Love me harder!
This is great, Urara!
You're sucking me in!
Cum...
More!
Please give me more of your cum, sensei!
I'm cumming again!
Cum!
Please fill me with your cum, sensei!
I'm cumming inside!
I'm being sucked in!
This is good. This is good, Urara.
I'll make love to you anytime.
S-Sensei...
Shimon-sama...
Me... Me too...
I want you to train me again too!
Oh, Shimon-kun?
What are you doing here so late at night?
Sayaka?
Don't play dumb! What happened to my reward?
Oh, that's what this is about?
I haven't forgotten.
But I'm not just going to hand out your reward that easily.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Are you serious? I'm not really happy about
the way you're going about this.
But if I don't do it this way, you'd keep
going until you broke my mind, right?
Just like you did back then.
Well...
You're an animal after all.
If I don't do it like this, I won't be able to give you a reward.
Shit! But you're not going to satisfy me like this!
Did you really think you'd be able to have sex with me
just after sending one completed product to me?
I'm your employer now.
In other words, I'm your master.
Master?! We're business partners!
Fine, I get it. I'll have to give you a little bit of service.
You've gotten better. You must've been practicing
by yourself without me, right?
I can tell you're just putting on a brave
face. It feels too good, doesn't it?
Your dick's getting incredibly hot.
And I know that you want to have more
fun with my huge dick, don't you?
I bet you want to put it inside your pussy.
How many times have I cummed in this mouth-pussy?
It hasn't changed one bit from back then.
But it's even more obscene and passionate than before.
You're going to make me cum again if you keep doing that!
That's fine.
In exchange, this'll be the end to your reward for now, okay?
Y-You can't be serious!
You have no say in this.
All you get to do is just shut up, sit there, and cum.
Your dick is starting to twitch!
You want to cum, don't you?
You just can't wait, can you?
Just cum already!
Shoot your dirty, lascivious desires
out in between my breasts!
Wow, there's so much!
Just as I thought... this woman really is special.
She has something to her that none of the other girls have.
Your reward is now over.
If you want more, you'll have to try harder with work.
Mark my words, Sayaka.
I'm going to mess your body up next time
and I'm going to make you my slave.
Oh? But the next target. Sumitani Akane
is basically the idol of the school.
I don't think even you'll be able to
make her succumb that easily.
Leave it to me.
I already have preparations made.
Strong willed types like that might
be brave and resilient, but...
When you break the things that they rely on for
support, everything comes crashing down.
Hey, Shuichi, are you sure about this?
If your girlfriend finds you here with me...
Shut up, it's fine.
She says she's my girlfriend but she never lets me fuck her.
Huh?
I bet she's saying shit like, "let's have a pure
relationship until we graduate", right?
Yeah, something's up. Every guy in this school has her
eye on her for some reason, right? She's a fake virgin.
That's fine. I'll just do everything
you wanted from her for you.
Holy shit, seriously, your pussy's the best!
Hey, Shuichi, your dick is too hard!
Ah, geez!
This is too cruel...
It's tea with a little liqueur in it. Try drlinking
something warm to calm yourself down.
Thank you.
It's very good.
Its flavor really calms me down.
Why haven't you let him have sex with you, Akane-kun?
You're his girlfriend. I bet he wanted to do you
so badly, he could barely control himself.
If you just weren't so selfish...
Th-That's not...
It's my fault?
Huh? All of a sudden, I'm...
Akane, you've finally come over to my place.
Exquisite!
You're such a sinful woman.
Your boobs have the perfect feel to
them. Rubbing them feels so great.
And then here we have the treasure of every virgin!
I never get tired of its scent no matter
how many times I smell it.
You're finally going to become one with me!
Right now, I'm going to...
This is the best!
This is the best pussy ever!
The sensation, the tightness... I have no complaints!
This is wonderful! So wonderful!
I'm starting to feel... strange...
– Take my love and my genes! I'm gonna fill you up with them!
– Sensei, please! Not inside!
– No! No!!
– Take my love and my genes! I'm gonna fill you up with them!
That was great. So good.
– Let's do this rough, intense dance one more time, huh?
– Stop... Please...
– I'm sure it'll feel even better than before.
– The tea you drank had a special ingredient in it!
– Wait... Please wait!
– Because of it, you won't be satisfied with doing it once or twice!
– Stop! This isn't right!
Real sex, you see, isn't anything like this.
– But don't worry I'll thoroughly teach you everything about sex.
– No... I'm losing my mind!
I'm cumming again!
Looks like your body has already gotten the hang of this.
I bet it can't resist my fat dick anymore, can it?
Th-That's not true... I'm not a dirty girl like that...
It keeps just sliding in so easily!
Please, stop!
Please leave me alone!
I'm getting hot... so hot!
Why am I getting so hot from something this rough?
– I want to hurry up and expose your real self... your dirty self!
– It feels so good!
– If you had done that sooner, I bet Shuichi-kun
wouldn't have abandoned you.
The only person who understands you, is me.
I love you.
– So become mine, Akane!
– Sensei, please...
– I'll never let go of you!
Love me!
I'll have sex with you as much as you want!
See? Doesn't it feel good?!
My dick feels good, doesn't it?!
Yes... Yes...
Sensei, your dick...
It feels so good!
– Then it's time to brand you to mark you as my woman!
– Sensei, please let's do it together!
– Here's my cum!
– I'm cumming!
– I'm cumming!!
– I'm gonna cover you with my cum!
I'm cumming!
Oh, are you finally awake?
How do you feel?
You were passed out in front of
the nurse's office at lunchtime.
Huh?
You don't remember?
I...
I think it was just a small case of anemia.
Just take it easy tonight, okay?
Um, where's Ryuudouji-sensei?
Shimon-sensei?
I haven't seen him around here today.
Why do you ask?
O-Oh, no reason...
It's nothing.
What's going on?
Was that all... just a dream?
That can't be. I can still feel those sensations in my body.
I can feel them...
I don't get it...
Take your time to think about it.
Think about what's happened to your
body and what you're becoming.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч