Wh-What's happening to me?
I can't see anything! I don't hear anyone either!
I can't even speak!
I've waited for this day for over twelve years, Urara!
Sensei?
That's him, isn't it?!
I'll endure this punishment!
Doing this with sensei makes me so happy!
I've been lonely ever since your mother passed away.
You're the only one left who
can take in my emotions, Urara!
Wait, no, this isn't sensei!
These aren't sensei's hands!
No! Stop!
Sensei, save me!
Urara! Urara!
Ryuudouji Shimon's
Obscene Plot
Part 2
The joy from Ryuudouji as he partakes in women!
We love masochists like your mother who
can take everything that we throw at them.
This... This isn't sensei!
Sensei, where did you go?!
Please! Come back!
Your mother was just like you.
I bought her and I gave her to my son.
Then when the weekends came, I'd fuck her day in, day out.
Like this!
This is too good!
I'm going to cum inside you, raw!
Urara, it's me. Can you tell?
Sensei?!
That's right.
It's me, Ryuudouji Shimon.
– Sensei, your dick is so good! It's so good!
– How erotic! Her body's bent around him so lovingly!
She's taking that huge dick in so happily!
A sex slave is different from those weak,
human sex dolls that you know.
They put their body and soul into pleasuring their master.
Master, I'm sorry for doubting you!
I can't live without your dick anymore!
It's like I can't even breathe without it!
Please... Please forgive me.
Urara, listen. Your father and grandfather
truly love you very much.
Wouldn't it be best to enjoy sex with them?
Just like your mother did.
Y-Yes!
Please enjoy yourselves, Father, Grandfather.
Please enjoy my erotic body!
Make love to me! Ravish me!
Good. Very good.
I'm about ready to cum.
Let's cum to ether, okay?
Y-Yes! Yes!
I'll cum!
I'll go anywhere if it's with you, Shimon-sensei!
I'm cumming!
I-I'm cumming!
Dick... Dick...
Amazing! It's so tight!
Wow!
Oh, no! Sensei! Sensei! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I-I'm gonna cum again!
I'm cumming inside!
I'm cumming!
Your body's grown to be so erotic!
We were wrong! All we had to do was love
you to get you to respond to us like this!
You're no longer just a replacement for your mother!
You're amazing in your own right, Urara!
I-I'm gonna cum!
All right, it's time for the main event.
Let's satisfy her even more.
I'm so happy.
Let's have more sex!
It feels so good in my pussy and my mouth-pussy!
It makes me feel so good!
Even though I'm pounding inside you so hard, you're...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
I'm going to cum again too!
I'm cumming! Drink it down!
Very good, Urara.
Let them make you cum as much as they want.
Let's show them your best orgasm ever!
Sensei! Sensei!
This is so embarrassing! So embarrassing!
Show me, Urara.
Show us... Let us see your true orgasm!
Show it to us!
Grandfather, I'm filled to the brim
with your cum and Father's cum.
Oh no, there's so much, it's overflowing!
It-It's so rough! So rough!
That's good. Show them every last bit of your orgasm!
I can't believe how good you're feeling from me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Urara! Urara!
That was wonderful, Urara.
You really bared all.
You showed us every last bit of your true self.
I-I'm gonna cum!
All of it's going to come out of me!
– It's coming... All of it's coming out...
– I'm cumming!
We're going to put the finishing touches
on Akane's training today,
Suzuka.
Yes, Shimon-sama.
All the preparations are in place.
Take a good look.
Look at yourself in the mirror.
You used to have such an innocent face!
Take a look at how that's changed.
Sensei... please don't tell me that.
It's too embarrassing.
You've become my sex slave.
You're a dirty sex slave who gets pleasure from
having dicks shoved in her pussy, asshole, and mouth.
That's not why! You said I was cute...
and that you liked me a lot...
that you loved me!
Oh, I wasn't lying about that.
I love you as my cute sex slave! You're so dirty and cute!
I love that side of you!
Why does this feel good?
Horrible things are being done to me, but I...
I feel good!
It's okay. I'm right here!
I'm the only one who knows who you really are!
Sensei! Sensei!
I've become a totally filthy sex slave!
Please love me!
Of course I will, Akane.
Akane...
What the hell are you doing?!
S-Suzuka-sensei?
What's going on he...
Just shut up and watch, Kei-kun.
What the hell's wrong with all of you?!
What the hell's going on?!
Akane? Shuichi-kun was your boyfriend, wasn't he?
He deserves a proper explanation.
I-I can't, sensei.
Please, sensei. Forgive me! Forgive me!
A-Akane, you really think you can get out of this?!
Do you?!
It's all right, Akane. I'm right beside you.
So tell him how you truly feel.
S-Sorry, Shuichi-kun.
I'm...
I'm Shimon-sensei's sex slave now!
Wh-What are you saying?!
Sh-Shimon-sensei's dick is absolutely incredible.
I've had sex with him lots of times,
with both my ass and pussy, and he makes me cum!
Shuichi-kun, you reap what you sow.
If you treated her better...
She wouldn't have felt it necessary to come to me.
I... Even though they're here, I'm...
I want to cum so bad right now!
I don't mind.
This is a celebration of your first day
being reborn as my sex slave.
I'll pour my semen inside you over and over again.
That makes me so happy!
That makes me so happy, sensei!
Together... Together again!
It's so good! It feels so good!
Sensei! Sensei!
Holy crap...
What the fuck?! You're just a slut now!
You always looked so innocent!
But now you're just some dirty slut!
N-No, I'm not, Shuichi-kun.
I might have become a perverted sex slave,
but I'm not a slut.
After all, I'd never let you put it in me.
I won't have sex with anyone but sensei.
Isn't that right, sensei?
Yes. Right you are.
Akane's a very good girl.
She says that she doesn't want
to have sex with anyone but me.
Maybe that's why she never
let you have sex with her.
B-But Akane was my first love and first kiss...
Okay, let's go again.
Let's give Shuichi-kun and the others a great show!
Yes! Wow! Your dick's getting even bigger!
Even though you came so much, it's still...
Your pussy just feels too good, Akane.
It makes me instantly hard again.
Thank you very much!
Please keep cumming!
Please use my pussy however you'd like, sensei!
I can't hold back with this going on
in front of me! Please, let me in too!
Nope. The only person who
can have sex with me is sensei.
Akane, I'd like them to participate in improving your sexual
techniques. They just won't get to put it inside you.
I'd feel bad if they just had to stand there
and watch while not being able to do anything.
To be honest, it's part of the reason
why I had them come here.
But that's only if you're okay with this.
Okay. If that's that you want, sensei.
A-Akane!
In return, you have to listen to everything
we tell you without question, okay?
Aren't you happy, you two?
Akane... I can't hold it in!
Please!
Kei-kun, your dick's really twitching.
It feels weird doing it with three people at once.
Akane... Akane!
I-I'm cumming!
Wow, there's so much!
That's good. Keep it up, Akane.
Show me more of yourself covered in their sticky cum!
Yes!
You can cum too, Shuichi-kun!
Cum all over my face.
It's okay.
It's on me! Your dirty cum is all over my face!
No! Sensei, no! You're going to make me cum like this!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum in front of everyone!
It feels like my pussy, doesn't it?
Thrust it in me hard!
Make me cum from my armpit, Kei-kun!
You came!
I came from you raping my armpit-pussy, Kei-kun!
I'm going to become a total perverted woman who's
addicted to cum from all this cum being splattered on me!
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum with you watching!
You came again!
Did you really get that turned on from me?
A-Akane! I-I'm gonna cum!
It's dribbling into my throat.
With each pulse there's more and more!
I'm going to cum while drinking semen!
I came while drinking semen!
Look! Look at how much came out in my mouth!
Clean! I gotta clean it!
Sh-Shit!
Akane! You're so good!
Of course I am. I worked really hard.
I worked really hard to get my fellatio
and sex techniques right for sensei!
Sensei...
That's good! You're so dirty, Akane!
You can give me more if you want.
Oh wow, you came even more!
Wow!
Shuichi-kun, give it to me!
Cum in my boobs!
I'm not going to let you go until you get me pregnant!
Give me it! Give me your semen!
I'm even more turned on than usual!
My pussy's getting so tight!
I want to cum!
I'm cumming again!
You did very well, Akane.
I'll give you another reward!
This is your first time doing it in your ass
and pussy at the same time, isn't it?
How is it, Akane?
It... It feels really good.
I'm cumming!
So good!
I want to see you become even
crazier from being bathed in cum!
Sensei! Watch me! Please watch me lose myself!
I love how rough this is!
It feels so good! I love how good it feels!
Sensei... Why? I can't...
I... I'm cumming!
I don't know how many times I've cum now.
This is...
Wa-Wait! Akane, I'm gonna cum!
Ew, you made me all sticky, Kei-kun.
This is what real sex is, huh?
Sensei! Shimon-sensei!
I'm cumming!
Cum in this hole too!
Oh, wow!
All right, Akane, this is it.
Sensei!
I'm going to flood your womb with the last of my cum!
So sexy!
Sensei! Cum! Please cum!
I-I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
Wonderful. You're so wonderful, Akane.
Sensei...
You are truly beautiful.
This is how I want you to be.
You are the ultimate sex slave!
It looks like your training of the sex slaves went well.
Directors office
I never doubted you, Shimon-kun.
Everything's good for now.
Like this, I'm willing to consider that reward of yours.
Really?!
Tonight should work.
I'm looking forward to it.
Y-Yes! Finally!
The time has finally come!
I'll finally get to have sex with Sayaka!
Hey!
Could we do it without these restraints?
Don't you want to enjoy sex with me?
If you don't wear that, you won't get your reward.
I'll just leave you like this and go home.
You're already this hard?
Did you really want my body that badly?
Onee-sama...
I... I want it too!
I want Shimon-sama's dick too!
You've already had your share of fun with him, haven't you?
That should be enough of a reward for you.
N-No!
As well as enough of a punishment for you.
P-Punishment?!
If I'm letting you have sex with me,
you don't have any right to refuse anything I say!
This! This sensation!
Please! I want his dick! Not this vibrator!
This is the pussy I wanted to taste!
What are you saying?
All pussies are the same.
You really never noticed?
Your pussy is a beautiful mystery... a complete work of art!
Work of art?
I think you're making it out to be more than it is!
This sensation of being sucked in while
being caressed by your smooth, fleshy insides!
How funny. A sex slave trainer such
as yourself is so infatuated with my pussy!
No! If you do it like that, I'm gonna...
Your dick's already starting to twitch.
You can cum inside my pussy.
Just pump it inside me!
I can't believe Shimon-sama is cumming so easily!
I'm going to cum with Shimon-sama and onee-sama!
No, Suzuka.
Just stay back and keep playing with that toy.
But I'm going to cum if this keeps up!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming too!
What's the matter? You wanted to do me, didn't you?
Just move as you'd like.
Just mess me up like you do with the students!
No! That's not what I want to do with you!
You can go as hard with my mouth as you want.
Come on!
It feels so good that you can't hold back, doesn't it?
I'm going to cum again!
How unseemly.
Stop focusing on yourself and make me cum more!
Shit!
You had this much saved up inside?
Look at how much came out.
Onee-sama, me too...
It's getting hot inside my pussy again!
I'll squeeze all that cum out from you!
I hate to admit it, but I'm at my limit!
Shimon-sama, I... I'm gonna... I can't keep it together!
My mind's going crazy! I'm gonna lose it!
You can tell, can't you? You can tell how
my insides are gripping you tightly, can't you?
Shoot every last drop inside me!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming too!
Are you all right, Shimon-sama?
I haven't had this much fun in quite some time.
If you want to be rewarded again,
keep up the sex slave training.
Shit! I'm not going to give up!
I'm going to revive your past self!
There are still many candidates who
have the potential to become sex slaves.
I look forward to what the future brings.
Shimon-kun.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч