Okay, I'm going to put on the oil now.
Mio-chan, is this really your last day here?
You've been my favorite girl here for so long.
Thank you for the compliment.
What, you don't believe me?
I'm being serious.
It's been a year since I started working here,
but now I'm finally going to get married, so
I'm going to move in with my husband.
It's a shame, but hey, since it's your last day, let me do you.
That again? I've told you before, we can't do that here.
We're not a brothel.
Then how about you suck me off...
Nope.
Then how about just a picture of your
huge tits to remember you by.
A picture?
Yeah, just a picture.
I'll be sure to tip you for it. Okay?
A tip? Now that I think about it, I think my fiancee
had his eyes on a bag that he wanted.
And I promise to keep it a secret from the shop.
I'll make sure that no one ever sees it either.
Just a little, okay?
I'm not going to show you all of them, okay?
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
You're so cute!
This is pretty embarrassing.
Just like that.
That's good, Mio-chan!
Yeah, good. Look at the camera a little more.
Are you taking more pictures?
Hey, Mio-chan, give me a little more service.
He-Hey!
I promise this will be the last thing!
No! You can't!
Okay, time's up!
Oh, come on.
That should be enough for you, you
already took so many pictures.
Yeah, I guess this will do.
I'll have fun with these pictures later, Mio-chan.
At the time, I had no idea what was to come.
I quit the job in preparation for living
together with my future husband.
You keep focusing on my boobs.
Stop.
I'm so wet right now.
I can tell that it's already starting to overflow.
Why does it feel so... Oh, I get it.
This is the first time we've done it since
we've moved in together, isn't it?
Wow, you're so wet, Yuzuki.
Oh, no.
I want his fingers so bad!
Oh, h-hold on a second.
Seriously? I was so close too. Is he serious right now? Geez!
Oh, crap.
What? Something wrong?
The systems at work are malfunctioning.
They need me to come in right now.
Sorry, I'll be right back!
Huh? Wai...
I love you!
Seriously? What am I supposed to do now
with my aroused body right now?
We're getting married soon,
but his company's been keeping him pretty busy recently,
so it's hard for us to get some quality alone time.
Huh? Right now?!
Yeah, I've been drinking with one of my coworkers
and he just keeps insisting on coming over.
But we don't have anything to offer.
Oh, it's fine, we'll just bring some drinks over.
But anyway, we'll be over in like ten minutes.
Hey, wait...
Geez!
I'm home!
Coming!
Yuzuki!
This is my coworker, Horii-san.
Thanks for looking after...
Oh, hi, sorry for coming over so late...
Sorry about this.
It's fine. Nice to make your acquaintance.
Why?
Please come in. I'm going to go to the bathroom real quick.
Mio-chan.
It's been a while.
Um, customers from the store...
It's fine, it's fine.
My lips are sealed.
But what happens next is up to you, Mio... No, Yuzuki-chan.
Please stop.
Please!
How about you get me a drink for now, Ms. Bride to be.
You're really a life saver at work!
Yuzuki, pour him a drink.
H-Here.
Oh.
But man, I'm surprised.
You have such a cute bride to be here.
Yeah, I'm really lucky. Doesn't that make you happy, Yuzuki?
O-Oh, me? I'm not that...
When did you two register for marriage?
Just a little while ago.
We're the newest of newlyweds.
Oh, you guys must not have a lot of
time to fool around together then
because our company's been so demanding recently.
Oh, no, we're...
I need to endure this.
If you leave a cute girl like this by herself for too long,
some guy might come and snatch her up from you.
Please don't joke around like that, senpai.
If you really think that then help
me not have to work so much!
But seriously, you must feel lonely a lot, Mio-chan.
I...
Huh?
I'm going to make some more snacks.
No, if this keeps going on, I'm...
Ma'am?
Let me help you out.
You were nice enough to have me over after all.
I-I'm fine.
All I have to do is warm this up.
Stop!
You got really wet back there, didn't you?
Yuzuki-chan, your pussy twitched when I went in it.
It didn't... It didn't feel...
Yoshikawa-kun's got it good.
He has such a nice wife to make him food.
And the food looks so delicious! You must be so skilled.
Please stop! This isn't the place!
What was that? Are you starting to moan?
Are the fingers of another man really that good?
No, there's no way that's true!
I'm promised to another man. There's no way that I'll...
I need to satisfy him quickly and get him to go home!
Horii-san, aren't you tired from standing all day?
You told me at the store that you
wanted me to suck you off, right?
You're being pretty aggressive now, huh, Yuzuki-chan?
It's not like I'm doing this because I like it...
But for now, I have to endure this!
Deeper! Take it in all the way!
W-Wait!
Oh, your tongue is sticking to my dick!
I knew you'd be really good at this, Yuzuki-chan!
I can't breathe!
Having this guy's dick in my mouth
makes me want to throw up!
No! I got to make him finish quickly!
I need to finish this before he notices.
That's it!
No!
If you place such a cute newlywed in front of
me, I just can't help but want to eat her up!
No! Please! Anything but that!
Please don't!
I feel bad for Yoshikawa-kun, but I'm
going to have you before he does!
Holy crap, it's tight!
He's inside me!
He really came inside me! I'm really doing
it here... with this guy... I'm being raped!
Looks like it wasn't a lie that you haven't been
doing it recently since he's been so busy.
I can tell by how tight you are!
P-Please, take it out of me!
Making me have sex with you here
is too cruel! It's too cruel!
Sorry, but you really think I can stop right now?!
Please stop being so rough!
If you keep being rough like that, I... I...
I don't want this at all, but my body
is getting hotter and hotter!
What a good girl. You're trying your
best to hold yourself back.
Please, stop. He can see us through this door!
Huh? So I guess I can be a little rougher then!
No! If you do it like that, I won't
be able to hold my voice back!
He's really going to find out!
It looks like you're really curious about
what's going on in there. Let's...
Let's take a look!
No!
No! Don't open it! Please! Don't! Don't! Don't!!
Don't!!
Surprised?
Well, he was pretty drunk.
He passed out almost immediately.
Th-Thank god.
It's too early to be relieved, Yuzuki-chan!
No way! This still isn't over yet?
If you're really feeling this good,
you gotta show your husband.
Stop! Don't show him!
My pussy... Don't show him my embarrassing
side! Please! Please!!
Hey, say it.
What kind of girl are you?
I won't say it! I won't!
Hurry up!
I'm a dirty girl who is having sex in front
of her husband with a different man!
Yeah, that's good!
I'm about to cum from being raped! I'm a perverted wife!
Even if you don't want to be, you're
that kind of woman, Yuzuki-chan.
Even if you're getting played with in
front of someone, you get this wet!
Don't you feel bad for your husband?!
I'm sorry. I wanted to start a new life with you, but...
I'm such a perverted woman.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
If we don't finish up soon, Yoshikawa-kun might wake up.
Not there...
Come on, loosen up and take all of my dick inside you!
No!
It's so deep! It's going so deep!
Your pussy's getting even tighter than before, Yuzuki-chan!
Forgive me! It feels so good! I'm being raped in
front of you, but I'm getting so turned on!
No! If this keeps up, I'm going to cum!
He's going to make me cum!
It's so hot!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!!
It's already so late. Maybe I should stay over tonight.
Y-You're kidding!
Oh, crap I messed up!
I just completely passed out!
U-Uh...
This isn't good!
I haven't even begun to prepare the
materials for the meeting today!
Sorry, I'm gonna borrow your shower.
I'll be right behind you though.
Got it! Then I'll see you at work!
Um...
Yuzuki, take good care of him, will you?
I'll see you later!
Have a good day...
Um, Horii-san!
I'm just so hard right now, Yuzuki-chan.
Take care of me a little more.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
I can't believe he's making me do this!
Yeah, that's good! You're really good at this, Yuzuki-chan!
It slid in easier than it did yesterday.
You're such a horrible woman for betraying
your husband with another man like this.
I'm only like this because we did it so many times last night.
Huh? Did I just hear something?
I wonder if Yoshikawa-kun forgot something.
What do you think, Yuzuki-chan?
No! Stop!
He's going to see! No! No!
No!!
Woah! Your pussy's starting to twitch
and it's getting so much tighter!
He's really going to find out!
I was just lying before. Don't worry.
Really?
Thank god.
Now, let me thank you for all the fun you let
me have yesterday by cumming inside you!
It's starting to twitch inside me!
Please stop. Please!
If you go any farther, I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
My nightmare of a marriage was just starting.