SubDESU-H Presents
Sailor Fuku Shinryou Tsumaka
Part Two
Ok then, let’s start.
Ok.
Hey Koui-san.
Kyouka-san.
This thing…
You’re unfair.
To say that now..
But..
Koui-san is a special person for me.
But…
You’re the first special person I chose.
Ok? Koui-san.
More… harder..
Me too.
I want Koui-san to feel good.
It's warm.
Koui-san’s body temperature…
Kyouka-san..
No… It's alright.
You don’t have to overdo it..
It's alright.
Kyoka-san, I’m cumming!
Kyouka-san… Sorry.
I’m alright.
So Koui-san.
Let's do it until the end today.
Ok?
Here I come.
Ok then, let's start mom.
Ok, Nozomu-chan.
I’m going to put it in, Mirai.
Ok then, let's start.
Ok.
Izumi-nee.
I’m alright.
I’m really alright.
Are you sure?
What? Do you have something want to say?
If you have, say it.
It's nothing.
If you say you’re alright.
Why are you making such face?
So… so what?
I’ll say it clearly to you.
If you’re alright, why are you making such face?
Don’t make fun of me..
Brat..
Is it not ok if it's me?
Izumi-nee.
You don’t have to look around me.
Aside from looking, you’re doing it with me.
Yes I am but..
You know.
I’m embarrassed too.
Sorry.
You don’t have to apologize.
I want to face you honestly..
Izumi-nee.
You don’t have to say that.
I’ll accept all of Izumi-nee.
It's beautiful, Izumi-nee.
Dummy..
I’m going to put it in, Izumi-nee.
Kouichi-san.
Hajime-san.
Nozomu…
Nozomu!
I love you.
Nozomu-kun.
Hajime-san.
I’m cumming.
It seems.
kyouka-san settle down recently.
Thanks to Nozomu-kun’s counseling.
No it's not.
The receiver gained the self control of their self that’s why.
Taking control of oneself is important part of Internal Medical Treatment.
And it's part of my method I aimed for.
That’s…
In short, it’s treating by Kyouk-san’s own power.
Is that so?
You don’t have to think it seriously.
To think is the work of the doctor.
For kyouka-san, feeling is better for you than thinking.
Then… for today.
Let’s not do it for today.
We don’t have to push our self.
Nozomu-kun’s lips are not bad.
Its something brings back memories.
And something it’s not your first time.
Kyouka-san..
I remember something in the past.
In the past?
Yes.
It’s about when I was still in high school.
There was a person so close to me.
But I was innocent at that time.
I can’t understand his feelings.
I haven’t able to accept him.
And I became like this.
Nozomu-kun.
It seems I’m already alright.
To tell you the truth..  the insomnia has already gone at around 2nd and 3rd time.
But I had fun spending the time with you.
I got a hard time to say that.
Kyouka-san.
The one that Nozomu-kun talked about taking control of oneself.
Eh? Yes..
It's already clear to me the cause and effect in that way.
So I’m alright.
I see.
I was a bit worried when Kyouka-san started talking about it but.
But it seems you’re ok when I hear your story.
The one that got closed to me in the high school was…
He has similarities with Nozomu-kun.
Eh? Me?
Yes.
With Nozomu-kun.
Nozomu-kun, I love you.
So… let’s do it.
Kyouka-san..
It's alright.
Some say that if the married life is in collapsed state,
There’s no surprise to having an affair.
It came in.
Kyouka-san’s inside..
Kyouka-san’s inside is…
Nozomu-kun,
Nozomu-kun’s penis is also good.
Kyouka-san…..
I…
Love Kyouka-san..
Me too.
I love you Nozomu-kun.
Good!
It's good.
To
my
dear
Please submit this..
I’ll leave it to you.
I’ll never come back to this house.
What’s the matter?
Are you alright Mom?
Yes, I’m already alright.
So there’s no need for counseling.
Are you pushing yourself?
No I’m not, I’m alright.
Its not that Mom’s being fancy just started now but..
Eh? Hey Nozomu-chan,
You’re saying something rude to Mom.
No I’m not.
Is that so?
Nozomu-chan got tall and big.
Yes..
You’re already in a good height to be able to be kissed.
So I think I need to move forward.
It's hard to go around between you and Hajime-san.
Mom..
We need to be like this right Hajime-san?
Mom?
Mama thinks she needs to work.
Or maybe she needs to go learn something?
Do as what Mom wants.
I’m worried about Izumi-nee.
You’re unfair to letting me say it.
You know that I love Izumi-nee since before.
It's because I’m horny,
It can’t be helped.
What the things turned like this.
I…
Nozomu looks at me and
He comforted me when I’m hurt.
Nozomu was with me that’s why I was able to move on.
I didn’t accept it that’s why something like now happened…
Nozomu…
This…
Why are you here?
The door was not locked.
There’s should be a limit in not being careful.
Nozomu, you….
I think it doesn’t matter who I am.
Nozomu…
I’m worried about Izumi-nee.
It's about Izumi-nee you know.
I know that you’re just being strong.
Yes, you’re right.
Izumi-nee.
I knew.
That this is bad if I’m staying like this.
But..
I’m confused.
It's alright.
It's alright so.
Let's release it.
That’s why I’m here.
Nozomu…  thank you.
For being with me.
And also at that time..
That time..?
Yes, that time…
The same as that time..
Are you ready?
Nozomu..
Not only the boobs but also the..
Stop it after all…
No…
No….
Noooooo!!
Don’t look that much.
It's embarrassing.
It's beautiful.
Dummy.
Nozomu..
I’ve been…
Watched by Nozomu…
Nozomu is..
he’s even Nozomu..
How regrettable…
I said…
I feel Nozomu’s penis.
Izumi-nee’s boobs and tongue is so good.
It's good.
Izumi-nee.
Ok then.
Here I come.
Nozomu..
What?
I…
Wanted to be like this with Nozomu again.
Me too.
Nozomu’s…
Penis is so good.
It's so good.
I’m with Nozomu that’s why,
I’m with Nozomu that’s why…
I…
Good!
Izumi-nee.
Nozomu!!!
Soeta Masao
Izumi
Renjou Mirai
Kibou
Shibasaki Kyouka
Soeta Izumi
Mom?
Nozomu-chan.
Nozomu.
Nozomu-kun.
Welcome home.
Huh? Yes???