I-Izumi-nee...
Nozomu, don't move.
It would come out, won't it?
Izumi-nee...
Let's stay like this for a little more.
Ok?
Yeah
I love you Nozomu.
Izumi-nee.
Nozomu-kun.
Hm? What is it?
Y-You can be more rough...
But...
I know you care of me but,
I want it harder.
Kyouka-san.
I want yours to carve inside me.
N-Nozomu-chan...
N-No... you shouldn't... do such a thing...
Your comment contradicts with your mouth and that part of yours says, Mom.
Mom, does it feel good?
Hey, mom...
I feel so good.
Yes, I think its ok....
This kind of relationship.
Is it really ok?
It's ok, right?
This is... this is ok, right?
Nozomu, I’m going to cum!
Nozomu-kun, I’m going to cum!
Nozomu-chan, mom is going to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming... I’m cumming~
SubDESU-H Presents
Sailor Fuku Shinryou Tsumaka
Part One
Ahh Mom.
W-What?
How old are you already?
18 years old.
18 years old forever.
I-I feel dizzy.
A fever?
Want to put some spring onion in your butt?
I’m going to University.
Lately, Nozomu-chan had been cold towards mama.
That's because I'm already at a good age.
I can’t be the same as before.
Ok then, I’m going.
Yes, I understand.
You're saying that, but are you sure?
Mother...
You sigh on purpose and feel down?
You young ones are...!
It's not like that.
Don’t talk haughtily.
I’m sorry.
You should show the face of that man in front of my husband.
Then the day of making a grandson will come near.
Umm... I’m going to prepare for dinner...
You’re always good at cutting off in the middle of a discussion.
I’m not doing it on purpose.
Well whatever.
Anyway, do what I tell you early on, starting tonight.
So that you will give birth to our grandson after a year.
And we can prove that if you didn’t do that in that way.
I don’t need dinner tonight.
Hmph. Even how it will end, we both know it, right?
You should have said clearly that you're going to another girl.
Nozomu's counseling, eh?
Mirai-san recommended this, right?
D-Darling...
What... What should I do?
Please tell me, Hajime-san.
Hajime-san.
Nozomu-chan!
It’s a problem when a parent can’t be apart from their son.
Maybe I should also go to the counseling.
If I do it, maybe I can overcome being apart from him.
W-Wait, why is Mom also here?
I’m a girl who has worries.
It's alright with Izumi-nee, but why is Kyouka-san wearing that?
Ouch...
What do you mean by it's alright with me?
And what's the meaning of this?
T-That’s...
Maybe you...
W-What?
You've got a sailor fetish?
N-No... I don't.
This is just something I developed from Dad's suggestion.
Nozomu-chan, you liked sailor uniform?
I didn’t know that.
I would have worn this sailor uniform to wake you up every day if you had told me.
W-Wait mom...
Don't say such a thing that will cause a misunderstanding.
Oh if it's like that then...
I’ll... right?
Izumi-nee and mom too, don’t make this misunderstanding get any bigger.
I... This is my first time in counseling, but...
It's just counseling, don't think too much of it.
I’ll get into trouble if you get stressed out from this counseling.
Ok.
How should I say this...
A mental problem already means stress, so you should accept it if you're a patient.
So don't take it hard, just relax and talk about your problems and that will be enough.
Is it like that?
Well, it depends on situation.
This is not for a first timer but this is a method used after you know the symptoms.
Is it dangerous?
Its not dangerous, but...
It’s the problem of trusting each other.
I use some hypnotism sometimes.
How about the effects?
For that I'm confident of it.
It's my theme in my doctorate thesis too.
Ok then, I’ll leave this to you.
It's...
You mean the method is too analog?
I’m sorry.
It's just that I thought there was some sort of special machine.
No, I don’t mind.
I also thought it myself that this is old too.
Huh?
So from Renjou-sensei's opinion, what would be the cause of my sleeplessness?
Hmm, I can't tell with the information I've got.
But...
But?
Shibasaki-san, why are you not friendly with your classmates?
That's true... I'm not friendly with them, aren't I?
I'm sorry.
I don’t mind.
But, I think you don't have enough time.
You think so too?
Yes in my opinion.
If I’m going to say the reason, then...
They don’t treat me like I'm a special person to them.
It's only that we’re just in the same class.
So you’re saying that you don’t have any reason to be friendly with them?
Yes
You’re looking down on people around you, Shibasaki-san.
I just think that way.
I think you should be friendlier.
That’s what human relation is...
Then I’ll learn about the human relation while having sex with you.
S-Shibasaki-san.
This is not good.
Kyouka... please call me Kyouka.
It's because Koi-san is special.
K-Kyouka-san, this is bad.
It's not bad, because we're going to be in a special relation.
Kyouka-san!
Wow, so men's are like this.
Kyouka-san...
S-Stop...
I will not.
It's getting bigger.
The first semen came out.
Sensei, it feels good with my hand, doesn't it?
K-Kyouka-san...
We can still stop this...
I won't.
You’re so cute, Sensei.
Kyouka-san.
Nozomu-kun? Did I fall asleep?
Ah... umm...
I-I’m sorry.
You even prepared this place.
Don’t mind it
I see, I relaxed too much because Nozomu-kun was with me.
Hajime-san?
Because Hajime-san doesn't pay any attention to me.
I-It's because of Mirai-san...
I don’t want that.
I want to be one with Hajime-san, that's why...
I kissed you.
Mi-Mirai-san.
No, don't Mirai-san...
We’re not married yet...
I want to walk into the future with Hajime-san.
When I lost my family and was down, you were the one who lightened me up.
That’s why I want to be with Hajime-san...
Mirai-san...
You’re going to cum right, Hajime-san?
N-No, Mirai-san...
No you should not, Mirai-san.
No, I decided to do this today.
That was dangerous.
I slept while wearing this.
Somehow this morning seems better today than before.
I’m sorry for calling you.
I don’t mind it.
I must entertain you if Izumi-nee needs counseling.
I think there's no need.
It was Mirai-san...
You’re not the one who decides if you need it or not.
What’s with that? You’re just Nozomu.
No matter who I am, if it's needed then it's needed.
Izumi-nee
What? Are you having fun with one's broken heart?
It's not fun.
I’m worried about you, your crying...
You’re like from above.
No it's not.
What’s the difference?
You’re mean for letting me say that.
See? Hurry up and tell me.
Y-You know that I've been in love with you for a long time.
Well then...
Please comfort me.
Hey Nozomu, you’re breathing is rough.
T-That's because I’m nervous, it can't be helped.
Doing this thing with Izumi-nee...
I've imagined this so many times but...
I-Idiot...
You dummy, you’re always touching the nipples.
Then, I’ll touch the bottom too...
It's wet.
D-Don’t say such things.
Eh?
I-Izumi-nee...
Here I come...
Are you sure?
You wanted it, right?
I want... Izumi-nee...
Then it's ok, right?
Nozomu's dick went all the way inside me.
I’ll praise it for it's size.
Izumi-nee, I want to kiss you.
That's another matter.
N-No way...
T-Then...
You want it to move, right?
Ok, you can.
You can move some more.
What a dirty Nozomu.
Nozomu.
Don't thrust that hard-
I’m... going to cum...
I-It's ok, it's my safe day today, so...