Conceited Blonde Lady: Aiba Ruka
She's a daughter from a well-off household,
both a beauty and of academic excellence.
As a girl with a candid and fastidious disposition,
males find her difficult to approach, seeing her
as a "beauty out of anyone's league".
Possessing a great pride of her heritage, she strives be someone
that will live up to it's name and not bring embarrassment on it.
This is even apparent with all the fame and clout she has in school.
She shows contempt on Yukimasa, who lacks both dignity
and ambition despite being a son of a wealthy landlord.
And as a result, everyone around Yukimasa
followed suit and shunned him as well.
Socially Adept Childhood Friend: Isurugi Suzune
Both of their parents were old friends, and as a result she and Yukimasa
became friends that got along together since their childhood.
But now with Yukimasa being shunned and isolated, she quickly followed suit
and abandoned him like a stranger to become one of Ruka's lackeys.
And to imitate Ruka, she turned a blind eye
to Yukimasa, who was hoping for her help.
Each of Yukimasa's friends followed suit
as well and started shunning him.
Introvert Son of a Great Landlord: Doumyouji Yukimasa
Despite his grandiose lineage, Yukimasa is asocial
and is someone who doesn't stand out much.
That social standing brings stress on him and to deal with it,
he started to hang out out with his classmates.
These 'friends' treat him more of a 'walking purse'
taking advantage of him, but he just ended up getting
dragged along since he couldn't upfront refuse them.
It is because of that personality of his that Yukimasa got quite harsh words and treatment from Ruka.
The beautiful girl who works hard to perfectly become someone
who won't bring shame to her family's name: Aiba Ruka
The heir of the landlord that's even more powerful
than the Aiba household: Doumyouji Yukimasa
Aggravated on how Yukimasa just lets himself be mistreated
like a 'walking purse' and is willfully going along with it,
Ruka harshly gives him a piece of her mind every time......
Suzune, the childhood friend of his and the only person
who he can turn to, left him to join together with Ruka
and ignored him being in need of help......
While spending each day full of misery, Yukimasa received a strange mail
telling that he's been picked up as a winner of some sort of raffle.
Inside the mail is an app which seemed dubious,
but he downloaded it anyway.
It was a omnipotent app that can make people's deepest,
darkest and wicked desires in their hearts into a reality......
Original Animation
sai
min
gaku
en
Hypnosis Academy
~Humiliated and Bulging, Onset of Incontinence~
Move out of the way!
For someone who's an heir of a great landowning family,
you look nothing close on how a Doumyouji should be.
Are you not ashamed of yourself
looking all like that? Jeez...
You look miserable.
It must be hard for you, Suzune-san,
considering how you have been
childhood friends with such a guy.
It's okay for me to ignore him, right?
S-Suzune-chan...
Ah... What's up?
W-Want to go home together?
Okay.
Isn't it hot today?
Are you not sweating, Suzune-chan?
It will feel cooler if you'll take your panties off.
Yeah, you're right.
Is this alright?
[Follow Yukimasa without question.]
I want to go to the restroom.
I think you can just do it here.
Oh, you're right.
I'm getting watch while peeing...
How was it?
It felt like having some sort
of freedom, it's not that bad.
Well then. I have somewhere else I need to go.
H-Huh?
What am I doing here?
[...forget everything we did.]
What is happening?
Are you not going inside, Ruka-sama?
Is that you, Aiba-san?
S-Suzune-san, what is the meaning of this...
Suzune-san?
I think she's shocked to find
her friend with a bulging belly.
Y-You—
Wait, you can see it?
Of course, we did. It's like you are a different person.
Rio, you too?
So you were actually a slut.
There's no way that I'm indulging myself
with such acts of debauchery!
Moreover, this is—
You...
Have you noticed it?
Rio.
Rio, what on earth are you doing?!
I'm playing with my pussy in front of Ruka-sama...
This is so embarrassing, yet it feels amazing!
Masturbating while fantasizing about
Ruka-sama makes me feel so horny!
Watch me, Ruka-sama!
My pussy is dripping wet!
Ruka-sama!
This feels great! I love you, Ruka-sama...
I can't move my own body!
Incredible!
Rio is making such a face...
It really is true!
Hypnosis? Why?!
An easily swayed childhood friend, and then
a nosy lady mistreating someone unrelated to her...
Doesn't that ring a bell in you?
Why not just speak up back then if that's
the case? Doing something like this...
I'll teach you how being the one oppressed feels like.
What are you planning to do, pervert!
Move!
Don't get too worked out.
Doumyouji-kun, your cock is so huge... It's incredible!
Making us watch Rio in such a state...
It's okay. Use my mouth...
Shoot your sperm in it as my reward!
She's drinking it...
Rio is making such a lewd face
and sucking that man's thing...
Reward...
This position is—!
I don't want this, but my body won't listen to me!
No! please don't do this, Yukimasa-kun!
I apologize for everything that happened, so forgive me!
The easily swayed Suzune-chan
is thinking only of herself as usual.
You want to be first before Aiba-san?
No, I didn't mean that...
Tell me the truth.
I'm not thinking about getting raped ahead of
that bitchy lady who uses
her parents' authority for herself!
Huh? Did I just... No! Why?
That's Suzune-chan for you.
That huge thing... is going inside!
I-It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun, it hurts! It hurts!
You're gonna be next, Aiba-san.
No... No, no!
Stop it, please! It hurts!
There's nothing I can do
since you're not wet.
Right?
It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun is inside me!
Stop...
It hurts...
Are you crying tears of joy?
That enormous thing is... wildly...
No way...
Will this happen to me to me as well?
It hurts!
No! If I lose my will to fight,
I'll just end up being abused by this man!
No... No!
No... No... It hurts!
Please stop it already!
I understand, I'll end this with a creampie.
So, you want it that badly.
No!
I don't want it!
I'll get pregnant... I don't want to have a baby!
No...
Is he really gonna come inside?
Even if she might get pregnant?
This guy...
No!
No, no—!
No way!
This can't be happening!
It's pouring... inside me!
No—!
Wait, Stop this! I won't forgive you for doing this!
I can't see down there!
You'll be watching it too, Suzune-chan.
Yukimasa-kun's thing is...
So, Aiba-san is a virgin as well. What an honor!
Is it... This guy's—
I-It hurts! What is this? His thing is—!
That thick thing slid inside Aiba-san.
It's bleeding as well.
What is this? It hurts, it hurts!
It's too big!
You're tearing me apart!
It hurts, it hurts!
Stop moving!
This lowly man's thing is intruding inside me!
Is this too much even for you, Aiba-san?
Even if you do something like this,
I'll never ever break down!
Just as I expected from you, Aiba-san. Do your best.
Hurry up and make this end!
Just come already!
You're body says otherwise though.
What are you talking about?
I'm... Why am I...
What is this?
No way! Is this...
But that's... My breasts are...
The truth is you're getting excited, right?
Stop fooling around!
This is nothing but painful to me!
This feeling is something you did—
Your body is just being honest.
No way! Stop!
Not inside! I don't want to have a baby!
Stop!
No! No—!
No, no!
Stop!
No way, no way!
The semen of the worst man is pouring inside me!
I'll really get a baby from these!
Inside Aiba-san is... just like what happened to me...
N-No...
No... No—! No!
Nice job, Suzune-chan.
For sure... I'll make someone
as lowly as you regret this for sure!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next on "Saimin Gakuen"......
Inside again...
Stop this! Stop!
Lick it
No...
What a closet pervert.
You're good for a first-timer.
Good. Just drink it like that.
I don't want to lick such a filthy thing, and yet...
Stop!
Use those unreasonably
large tits of yours as well.
You quickly got the hang of it.
You're a blowjob princess.
S-Shut up!
S-Such a disgusting thing...
Lowly pervert! I'll never ever forgive you!
Here's a reward for the princess.
This... Don't tell me I have to...
My hips are moving on their own. No—!
Are you planning to come inside me again?
You started to crave for me now. Right Aiba-san?
This... thing...
Just a little more... Just like this!