Hey wait!
Thanks for your hard work, president.
And you too, Kurihara-senpai.
You're early, Serizawa-san.
Hello there!
You're cute today too as always, Yumeko-chan!
Please don't tease me senpai.
How are you feeling today?
I'm fine today.
Don't overwork yourself, okay?
I'm sorry I'm causing all sorts of
trouble due to my weak body.
Don't worry about it.
The vice president's absence record
is a whole lot longer than yours.
Manami's such an unassertive girl.
She can't refuse once she is asked to do something.
She just can't push herself onto others that much.
But she's really good at pushing
her physical capabilities though.
Let's call it a day for now.
Thanks for your hard work senpai.
Let's go home then.
I'm sorry but I still have to drop by the infirmary today.
The infirmary?
Yes.
Murakoshi-sensei is known to give personal
advice when it comes to body health.
Don't you find him rather strange?
No, not really.
That's good then.
Murakoshi-sensei is a nice person!
My body's been quite well lately.
Really now...
Well then, I'll take the lead.
See you tomorrow.
See you Yumeko-chan!
Bye...
Excuse me.
Hey there, Serizawa-san.
How are you feeling today?
Thanks to you sensei,
I feel that the number of anemic
attacks have lessened greatly.
So my special treatment worked.
That's great then.
So then, umm...
It was recommended that I take it periodically so.
Is that so now...?
Now shall we begin?
Yes, please continue.
When a woman receives a man's fluids
their bodies becomes active.
Does your body feel hot now?
Yes, my heart is throbbing right now.
How about your pussy?
I-It's wet, but how did you...?
That's the mark that tells that your body is now active.
Is that so?
I want more of sensei's fluids.
Today, instead of mere fluids, I'm going
to give you some strong fluids.
What is that?
My semen.
S-Semen? You mean the fluids that
come out of a man's penis?
That's right.
It's the most potent fluid a man could give.
It works very well.
I never knew that semen held that kind of secret.
There's a place where semen can be absorbed
better than in a woman's mouth.
Why don't we use that?
Where is that?
In one's pussy.
I'm going to insert my cock into your
pussy to directly inject semen into it.
But, isn't that sex...?
No, no.
Sex is done for reproduction right?
But this is a medical treatment so it's not sex.
I see.
That's good then.
I'm not experienced in sex yet so
I wouldn't know what to do.
It's okay.
This is not sex so even if a penis is inserted into your vagina,
you'll still be a virgin.
I'm relieved.
Then please, pour lots of semen into my pussy sensei.
Okay.
It's my first time presenting myself like this to a man, so I feel embarrassing.
No need to mind that.
Now, can you widen your thighs so that
my cock can be easily inserted?
Okay.
Oh, so your body is active already?
I feel somewhat nervous,
and somewhere around here feels
like it's itching to do something.
Is the feeling similar to that of when you are masturbating?
Oh, yes that's right.
I feel the same way when I want to masturbate.
Masturbation has a certain effect in activating your body,
so make sure you do it every day from now on.
I understand, I'm going to masturbate every day.
Good girl.
Here we go then.
S-Sensei, it really hurts there!
It's the first time that a penis has been
inserted inside so it can't be helped.
This is part of the treatment so try to hold out.
Just getting the penis inside already hurts this much.
How much more painful will it be
when my virginity is taken away?
No need to worry about that.
It really isn't that painful to do it with someone
that you love for the first time.
You really know a lot of things sensei.
I'm glad that Marukoshi-sensei was
able to come to this school.
It's still too early for you to thank me.
I'm going to move so that semen will come out, okay?
How do you feel?
It hurts so much, my mind's about to go blank.
It hurts.
Even if it hurts, we're still doing this for your health.
Yes, I'm just fine.
Here I go, make sure that your vagina takes it all.
Can you feel my semen flowing into you?
I can feel it.
Deep inside my vagina,
something hot is pouring out.
So were we able to inject enough semen?
Well, your vagina was a bit stiff so,
we were only able to inject a small amount.
Let's continue this a bit more.
If your vagina opens wider,
we could get to the entrance of your
womb and let it absorb more semen.
I understand.
Next one please.
You have a healthy reflex.
No problems here.
Thank you very much.
Wait a second.
Sorry for not showing up for a while.
That's okay.
It's considered normal already.
Anyway Yumeko-chan sure is late.
That girl has been frequenting the
infirmary these past few days.
I feel it's not good to go to that
man's place too much though.
Yumeko-chan.
So everyone's here.
That's great.
Can you all go to the gym at once?
Huh?
Welcome.
Did you call us sensei?
What do you need from us?
I just thought of playing a game, you see.
A game?
Yes, I call it, the ''Murakoshi Game"!
We don't have the time to play games.
This is idiotic.
That's too bad.
But none of you can escape from here.
Someone please sa...!
I've also set it up so you can't shout for help.
No way, how did he...?
Via hypnotism.
In order to make everyone unable to refuse, I've
placed a mental suggestion on all of you.
Hypnotism? Since when did you...?
There is one specific time where I had a chance
to meet you all one by one you see.
During that time?
In addition to that, I've also had
the rest of these girls examined.
So, what do you want us to do?
I've already said that we're going to play a game.
A "Murakoshi Game"!
I'm asking you what kind of game it is!
A fairly easy game.
All you have to do is answer a quiz question.
Get the correct answer, and you're free to go.
However, if you give the wrong answer...
If we give the wrong answer...?
You'll receive a penalty game!
A penalty like this!
Yumeko-chan!
My pussy's itching to do something.
Stop that!
Murakoshi-sama,
please give my virgin pussy your semen like you always do.
Only if you are able to do well as a quiz game assistant, okay?
Okay!
I'm going to do my best!
Yumeko-chan...
So this is also the work of your hypnotism?
Correct.
Now do you see how powerful I am?
I understand now that you're the worst scum.
But isn't it humiliating to simply
be toyed with by some "scum"?
Now, shall we begin?
M-Me?
Yes, Murakoshi-sama.
There are over 200,000 camels currently inhabiting Australia.
True or False?
A two-choice question?
No coaching and no sharing answers!
The answer is true.
Please, answer "true"!
Now, the answer is?
F-False?
Wrong.
It's penalty time!
I'm sorry sensei...
My, it feels hot in here.
What's happening?
She seems to have a hated childhood
friend in her neighborhood.
The rest of the details will be kept secret
though, to protect her dignity.
No way, don't go...!
Each of you will be receiving a different
penalty, so just look forward to it.
Please, stop this already!
Now, who will answer next?
The probability that Manami-chan will be able to answer
any question correctly in this quiz is very low.
I have to protect Manami-chan at all costs.
I'll stay here and do whatever you want,
so let the others go already.
Hmm, what should we do then?
Then how about we make you
Sayuri-chan, a representative?
If you answer the question correctly I'll release all of you.
How about it?
Is everyone okay with this?
Then we'll give you a special question.
Tada!
Question.
Two plus three equals?
What's with that question?
It's good that the question is easy right Sayuri-chan?
What does this mean?
Is it a trick question?
If you don't answer quickly I'll consider your answer wrong.
The answer is eight!
Wrong.
The answer is five.
Why?
Two plus three equals eight, right?
Stop fooling around!
That's terrible. How terrible of you president!
Was I forced to answer incorrectly using hypnotism?
That's too bad, your answer was incorrect!
Now it's penalty time!
Hmm, why don't we go for Manami-chan?
Wait!
I'm going to take whatever penalty Manami-chan is given,
so please leave her out of this!
Sayuri-chan...
I'll do anything, please.
That can't be helped then.
Now then, can you arouse me so
that I can get my cock erect?
Arouse? How should I... ?
How about doing a president strip show?
What's wrong? You won't do it?
I-I'll do it.
It's a strip show, so try to be more erotic.
As expected of the student council president,
very good!
Now my "sponge" is getting filled with blood.
Next, can you suck on my cock?
That's...
Weren't you ready to do anything for your Onee-san?
Sayuri-chan, don't worry about me anymore.
Stop forcing yourself.
No, I'm alright.
Now, go ahead and taste it.
It tastes sour.
Is this the taste of urine?
How half-assed.
Don't just lick the tip.
You must erotically suck on it whole.
Erotically?
You were sucking it like a totally aroused
bitch so it suddenly made me come.
Sayuri-chan...
There is just nothing more emotionally moving than
having the most popular student on campus,
the beautiful student council president
personally fellate you.
Besides, just thinking about what will happen next...
So we're really going to have sex?
Of course.
Turn around, show your butt to me and then plead.
Say these exact same lines okay?
"I may be a simple virgin but I want Murakoshi-sama
to take away my virginity,
so please make me into an adult."
Why should I say such embarrassing things?!
Because this is your penalty!
Have you forgotten that you're also
taking Manami-chan's share?
I-I may be a simple virgin but...
...I want Murakoshi-sama...
...t-to take away...
so please...
...make me...
Well said.
That's the top model student for you.
No...!
Oh, it's already wet.
Did you get aroused from sucking my cock?
That's... impossible...
Now then, I'm going to take your virginity now.
It's entering me!
It hurts!
A cock is penetrating inside me.
My virginity has been taken away!
It hurts!
Your cock is moving inside me.
It's going in and out,
and it's rubbing me from the inside.
It hurts, sensei stop this already.
Pull it out!
But if I do that,
I would have to take Manami-chans virginity instead.
How terrible!
A woman's cries are the best spices.
Sensei, no...
If you keep on doing this,
my pussy is going to break!
My vagina...
My vagina's going to burst!
No more...
I'm going to break apart.
Save me!
Manami-chan!
Okay I'm going to pour lots inside, Sayuri-chan.
No, I'll get pregnant!
Stop!
It's coming out.
Semen is being poured inside me.
Wow, now I'm really touched.
Now, I've protected Manami-chan...
A cock, a cock!
I want a real cock, please!
Sensei!
Manami-chan...?
That's too bad.
I've actually already finished taming Manami-chan.
No way...
It s good that you were able to give sensei your virginity.
The virginity of your older sister that you were desperately
trying to protect, is long gone already!
How terrible...
And all of the fun things are just getting started...!