Aunt's sex education.
Cousin's first sexual experience.
Mother's secret.
Young-Lady next-door, Virgin.
Childhood friend next-door, Virgin
The next prey, will it be the next-door beautiful sisters?
Well? Will you keep me entertained?
X-FAP Presents:
Hypnosis Technique
~In the domain of Illusions and Lust~
Welcome, Susumu-kun.
Onee-chan, did someone come?
Eeew, Susumu!
Susumu-kun, your cock is delicious.
It's so delicious, I would have done this sooner if I knew..
I wouldn't have kept my virginity until marriage I think..
Although bitter it's very tasty.
Onee-chan, stop it.
Susumu-kun.. This time, give this mouth some delicious cum.
Rie, make sure you take a good look at the scene of my deflowering too.
Well, Susumu-kun.. go ahead, I can't wait anymore..
Susumu-kun, thank you for taking my virginity..
Rie, the moment your sister became an adult woman, did you see it?
My pussy is getting spread..
Your big thing is fitting tightly inside me..
So this is what it feels like having a cock inside..
It hurts a lot..
It hurts but it's also good~♪
What is this?
It's completely different from when I do it myself..
The sensation is completely different..
It's good, very good..
Sex is the best~♪
Fill me up more with your cock!
It's amazing, Susumu-kun.
Tease my tits more!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Coming!
Now, watch as I give service with my tits.. okay?
This is my first tit-fuck, make you sure you savor it..
It may be a bit meagre, but I'll try my best so pardon me..
It's the first time I have fingers pushed in, but enjoy it plenty.
But I'm sensitive, be gently, okay~?
This a lie, right? Onee-chan stop!
It's alright, Rie.. Susumu-kun is loosening them properly..
I'm getting soaked, see..
Here, stick your fingers in Susumu-kun..
Onee-chan!
No way..
Onee-chan's tits..
Susumu's fingers are going in them..
Susumu-kun, you don't have to hold back~
Move your fingers and play with my tits..
This is great too!
Susumu-kun, you're great.
More.. get my tits soaked wet..
My tits are getting spread!
Susumu-kun, your fingers feel good..
Here too, it's in!
It feels great!
Onee-chan.. getting off in such a way..
It's too perverted!
I can't bear it, I'm gonna come from having my tits violated..
Susumu-kun, you too.. Give me your cum, come together with me.
It's coming out! My milk is being held back by your fingers!
Onee-chan..
Walking Onee-chan like a dog..
If someone sees us like this..
Onee-chan, is in such a state..
She who's always tidy, gentle, beautiful and stylish..
Onee-chan, seeing her in such an appearance..
It's too much..
This is bad!
Kana Onee-chan!
Good evening!
Taking a walk?
Onee-chan, stop!
Could it be you wanna pee?
Eh!? You too!?
No way! Onee-chan!
This is..
Today's lesson will be a small test in health and physical education..
Well then, first off.. Rie-san..
Come to the front and masturbate.
Y-Yes..
This is a joke.. Someone help me..
Make sure everyone can see..
Yes..
My, what a pretty pussy..
No, don't look!
Rie-san's still a virgin however..
Is that so?
Eh, still? That means I have more experience..
Rie-san, raise your face and begin..
N-No.. it's starting to get good..
It's masturbation, of course you'll feel good..
Don't hold back..
Everyone's waiting for your moment of satisfaction..
No, I'm being watched..
I'm really being watched while masturbating.
Why am I feeling it so much?
I've never felt like this from masturbating.. ever..
Seems like you're close to climaxing..
Well then, let's have Susumu-kun help.. let's solve this problem..
..You don't mean!?
Susumu-kun's cock is about to pop your cherry.
You're finally giving up your virginity, isn't it wonderful?
No way!
Come, Susumu..
Don't!
Stick it in me..
No! Such a thing is gonna take.. My Virginity!
That was a splendid tearing of the virginal membrane.. Congratulations, Rie-san.
Congratulations~!
Well then, next.. If you can have sex you'll pass the test..
Such pain... and you're saying I'll come.. it's impossible..
It's getting to feel good..
Susumu's cock is starting to feel better..
Having sex with a guy like him..
My virginity stolen and now getting fucked, this can't be happening..
P-Painful.. it's painful yet..
I'm coming!
It's great~
My son's grown up so splendidly, Mommy's so happy~
Here I come, Rie..
Come, Onee-chan..
Rie, your pussy's so tight it feels like it might pull off the strap-on..
As expected from an athletic girl.
Onee-chan, got for it.. I feel it better when it's in deep..
I know..
It's amazing, Mom! My hand really went in!
Because your hand is small.. try spreading it..
Let's make wide enough for Susumu-kun..
Yeah~ let's do our best for Susumu-chan..
How's that, Mom? Is it good?
It's.. g-great!
Susumu! Susumu! Let me come!
Susumu, you're too harsh!
The best.. this is the best feeling!
Give me that highest climax!
I'm coming!
Susumu.. that was fantastic..
I'm next, Susumu-kun..
I'm next, right~?
My, my Susumu-kun.. you're so popular..
Won't you let me have my turn first?
Susumu.. what's he so arrogant about..
Susumu.. once more.. okay?
Nee-san, stop hogging it all to yourself..
Yeah~ I haven't had his cock in me today, yet..
If we have two of Susumu's cock..
No.. five, then we won't have to fight at all..
Onee-chan, as expected that's a bit..
Susumu-kun, accept us!
Translator:
BlessedR
Raw Provider:
Mydoom
Timer:
SatsujinShinzou
Typesetting:
Fukkii
Encoder:
TLC/Editor:
Alist1
Don't be in a hurry, the real party begins now..
The night will be long..
At any rate, you're all already bound.. Just like.. Susumu-kun..
www.Xfap-Fansubs.co.cc
irc.rizon.net #xfap