So you want to help your sister
get over her trouble with men.
Is that correct?
Yes, that's right.
She hates that men only think about obscene things.
Obscene things, eh?
But that's not always the case, right Fujimi-sensei?
That's true.
If things stay this way, I'm afraid
she'll never have a boyfriend.
Well then, Futaba-san.
Just "Yuna" is fine.
Yuna-chan...
As long as you can get your sister to recognize
a man's charm, you don't have to worry.
A man's charm?
Yes, there are ways for a man to make a woman feel good.
Feel good?
Yes.
But to achieve such a relationship, a woman
must also learn how to please a man.
It's called "Give and Take".
In order to help your sister, you should
study how to please a man.
Sound good?
Yes.
This is for your sister.
For my... sister...
That's right.
You know what this is, don't you?
It's a... penis...
Co ahead and lick it.
Lick the penis...
Like this?
Move your head more, and lick it like ice cream.
Lick it like ice cream...
It seems to have gotten larger...
Yes, this is proof that a man is feeling good.
So this feels good?
This is a man's semen...
It tastes weird.
That's right, you should remember this taste.
Sensei, did that feel good?
Yes, you did a good job, Yuna-chan.
Then Yuna-chan is next.
Umm, Fujimi-sensei...
Now, we'll use a woman's special place to
show a man hospitality. It's practice.
It kind of itches, but it feels good.
You must be sure to remember how good this feels.
This is for your sister, right?
Huh?
You fell asleep. I couldn't bear to wake you.
Sorry...
You seemed very relaxed just now.
Ah, for some reason I just felt really comfortable.
That's very good.
Then all that's left is to bring your sister here.
Yes, I'll talk to her tonight and try to convince her to come.
That's right, why don't you talk to your sister's friends too?
It may help us find a way to fix this problem.
Okay!
Saimin Ryoujoku Cakuen
False Experience Technique
First
Story
Hey Aoi, is something wrong?
Yeah, Yuna and I had a fight last night.
A fight? Why?
She was bugging me to go get counseling.
Ah, could it be...
Yeah, because of my distaste foremen.
Saying that I needed to be cured.
As if I were actually sick.
Counseling, eh?
Yeah, but you understand, don't you Yurine?
Those stinking men!
They're really just walking disasters.
Although some may seem innocent, they're all the same.
You cannot be deceived by them!
Although I understand how you feel...
Huh, you've started liking other men?
You have a brother complex, right?
As long as you have your older brother, you'll be fine.
Yes, but you saying that is a little embarrassing.
So shy...
Though its true that your brother is cool...
What are you looking at!?
You bastards shouldn't stare at peoples chests!
Fighting with the male students again, eh?
Sis, you should really talk to Fujimi-.sensei...
You have a mental illness, and you need to see a specialist.
Why do you think its an illness?
Because it's not normal.
Yuna-chan, is such counseling really effective?
Yes.
Geez, why did this school have to have a counseling room?
There's nothing that talking will help with.
What a miserable condition.
What are you doing?
I don't recall ever seeing you on campus before.
I'm merely doing my duty to patrol the grounds.
Also, I'm a member of this school's faculty.
I heard there's a new school counselor. Could that be you?
I'm Fujimi Toshikazu, pleased to meet you. And you are?
I'm Shirogane Reika, the student council president.
I didn't think there was anyone who didn't know it.
Haha, being student council president
must cause a lot of stress.
I'm always willing to listen to your concerns.
I was already accustomed to this kind of stress.
From an early age I've prepared for this position.
And as the principals daughter, this kind
of psychological strength is natural.
Ah, I see.
Although this may sound rude,
I don't think there's anything here for you to do.
After all, everyone's tells the student council their problems
and we come up with a solution for their problems.
If that were true, it'd be very good.
However, there are some problems that people aren't
aware of, and these pose the most difficulty.
For example, facing the stress caused by someone
you have no choice but to obey?
What are you implying?
Well, if you'd like to find out, please
stop by the counseling room.
There's no need.
The Futaba sisters are friends with Miyauchi Yurine.
The younger sister, Yuna, also said
Yurine-chan worships her brother.
I'll go after her first.
The girl's love for her brother will
be the focus of her training.
First off, I'll have to create the right atmosphere.
Arimine, have you paid attention to
who is using the counsel room?
Yes, it seems to be gaining quite a good reputation.
So that means the students may actually
have troubles that they aren't telling us.
That's how it seems.
Yes, that does seem to be the case.
Is there an oversight in the student
council regarding the students?
No, that's not the case.
You haven't made any mistakes as council president.
It's not acceptable, using odd methods
to invade people's privacy.
Can they really be trusted?
N-No...
Arimine, find out more by the end of the day, don't let up.
Y-Yes...
Big brother, please look at this embarrassing
appearance of mine.
Ah, I'll appreciate it well.
I love big brother the most.
I always thinks of big brother when doing dirty things.
I'm such a dirty woman.
No, my pussy...
You make such cute noises.
Please don't say such things.
I just want you to, be yourself, okay?
I'm so happy...
That feels good, Yurine.
Your technique is really good.
Big brothers tongue... is in my...
Yurine, I want to put it in you.
I want to become one, okay?
Big brother, please put it in me.
Big brother... big brother!
Here, here!
Those guys again...
What are you looking at? Stop staring!
Don't try to deny it, you were staring at my chest!
Geez, what's up with that?
I only made a mistake because they stare at me so often!
Sis, I saw what happened just now.
It's really too bad.
Though everyone makes mistakes, the timing was just...
You know, Aoi, I think I know what the real problem is.
Even though you hate men, deep down
you have feelings for them.
I think that your heart must be contradicting itself.
No idea what you're talking about.
Aoi, you really should try counseling.
It can help relieve your inner contradictions.
Even you're advising such a thing?
Yes, its for your sake, you cant go on like this.
See, Yurine-chan agrees, Sis!
Well, will you give it a try?
That's right, you have nothing to lose.
I get it, I'll give counseling a chance.
So, how do you like this rare spice?
It has a kind of strange scent.
It has a relaxing effect, so it helps ease tensions.
It seems your aversion to men is cured, but
the impression you give off is still bad.
Yes, I hate men that are always acting disgusting.
Such words don't apply to everyone.
Try looking at it from another angle.
Your little sister worries about your problem.
How do you feel about that?
How... it's annoying that she worries about me.
You don't hate your, little sister, do you?
Of course I don't, she my only little sister.
Overcome your problem with men for your
little sister, who is trying to help you.
What do you think of that?
For... Yuna?
Yes, if you could overcome this little problem,
your little sister would be very happy.
Yes...
For Yuna-chan, you must get along with men better.
For... Yuna...
That's right.
Through mutual contact like this, men and women
come to understand each other better.
No, I don't want this from a man.
This is for your little sister, remember?
As the older sister, you cant let your
younger sister worry about you.
Don't worry, nothing bad will happen to you.
No way, all they think about are dirty things.
No, by making another feel good,
they're able to feel good too.
Do you hate this? Does it not feel good?
It feels good, but...
So it's good. Anything else unpleasant?
I hate the smell of men.
Smell?
It's got a strange scent to it...
No... I hate this smell...
Then you need to learn to love this scent first.
Aoi, how'd counseling go yesterday?
Well, it was...
It was?
Eh, don't you understand your problem
with men a little better now?
That's not the problem.
It's impossible to change so suddenly...
That's true...
I suppose...
Don't worry, Fujimi-sensei's words can
definitely help turn Sis into a woman!
Why are you saying such things?
Let's go.
What is this... what am I so concerned about?
Perhaps this has caused you to become
alienated from your male classmates.
This can be easily fixed.
This isn't helping.
Fight!
Fight, fight, fight!
Why... is the scent of a man so strong?
No... for some reason, my body's acting strange today.
Such a strong smell...
It's really dirty.
Smelly... it's so smelly.
How did I end up like this?
I can't do this...
My nipple is so hard...
Feels good...
It's so good, I cant stop...
So you couldn't calm down?
Right, for some reason I couldn't suppress the feeling...
Were you concerned about the men seeing?
No, it's not like that...
In order to calm down, you should study
the tea ceremonies like your friend.
Yurine is doing that?
Yes, there's a certain appeal to it.
I think that occasionally experiencing it would be good.
Is that so? Then it may be good.
Then go give it a try.
I wonder if Yurine is here yet?
Big brothers... please give it your best.
To be able to drink big brothers tea... I'm so happy.
Big brothers, please use Yurine for your masturbation.
Big brothers are almost there.
Please...
Ah, big brothers are amazing.
There's so much of big brothers' tea...
Yurine is so happy.
Delicious...
What are you doing, Yurine?
Sensei!
Please keep what you saw in here a secret.
Right...
Sis! What's wrong. Sis?
You don't seem very energetic...
Nothing at all.
Then, will you come help me with my drama practice?
Yeah, sure.
"How can you care about me, when
I'm such a lustful woman?"
"It does not matter, for your heart is..."
Sis, put more feeling into it.
Ah, yeah...
Ah, don't worry, these people are just visiting.
The scent of a man...
"Although I know this rotten matter may trouble
you, because of me there's no alternative."
"Sorry, if I can respond to your feelings, then...
I'd be so happy."
Sis, what's wrong?
Someone... please!
Aoi-kun, it seems you're finally honest with yourself.
Fujimi-sensei...
Isn't this a good chance?
Yuna-chan is also here, and now you're
fully cured of your hatred for men.
Well, everyone is here to help.
This smell... the scent of a man, I can't wait anymore...
Sis, you're too impatient.
I want more of this smell.
Cum on my body more!
Yuna wants it too...
I'd like you to attend to something.
Fujimi-sensei...
Sensei, hurry...
Please cum...
You two really like my dick, don't you?
I also want big brother's dick.
Yurine-chan too?
How is it, big brother?
It's good, Yurine.
Now, everyone line up.
Big brother's semen...
Ah, this smell...
More, do me harder, do me harder!
Please make love to your lewd little sister... big brother!
Yuna's perverted area is soaked... so happy
No, shoot it inside!
It's so hot...
Now, everyone spread your legs.
What a great view
Sensei's cock is so hot.
Big brother, I want it too.
So happy, big brother's techniques make me so happy...
Moving back and forth... Sensei!
Everyone's juices, such an amazing smell!
All over, it's all over Yuna...
Big brother shot so much... Yurine is so happy!
The use of hypnosis for the training
experiment was a huge success.
However, what to do afterwards is proving to be a headache.
Hey, don't you think that boy is good?
Yeah, but that one is more handsome.
Aoi talking favorably about boys, it's kind of weird.
Really? I think its better this way.
Yes, I'll remember it clearly.