Conceited Blonde Lady: Aiba Ruka
She's a daughter from a well-off household,
both a beauty and of academic excellence.
As a girl with a candid and fastidious disposition,
males find her difficult to approach, seeing her
as a "beauty out of anyone's league".
Possessing a great pride of her heritage, she strives be someone
that will live up to its name and not bring embarrassment on it.
This is even apparent with all the fame and clout she has in school.
She shows contempt for Yukimasa, who lacks both dignity
and ambition despite being a son of a wealthy landlord.
And as a result, everyone around Yukimasa
followed suit and shunned him as well.
Socially Adept Childhood Friend: Isurugi Suzune
Both of their parents were old friends and as a result she and Yukimasa
became friends that got along together since their childhood.
But now with Yukimasa being shunned and isolated, she quickly followed suit
and abandoned him like a stranger to become one of Ruka's lackeys.
And to imitate Ruka, she turned a blind eye
to Yukimasa, who was hoping for her help.
Each of Yukimasa's friends followed suit
as well and started shunning him.
Female Teacher who Advocates Self-Reliance: Asama Miyako
She is a female teacher who works under the philosophy that people
should always prioritize their own well-being and that they should
try to solve their own problems to the utmost of their abilities.
For Miyako's standpoint, Yukimasa's existence is a quite a headache.
She turns a blind eye every time she sees him getting teased at a mild
level. But when things escalate, she calls and gives him an earful.
"It's a hassle for me whenever you get in trouble. Get yourself together."
She was an unreachable goal as a role model teacher.
Introvert Son of a Great Landlord: Doumyouji Yukimasa
Despite his grandiose lineage, Yukimasa is asocial
and is someone who doesn't stand out much.
That social standing brings stress on him and to deal with it,
he started to hang out with his classmates.
These 'friends' treat him more of a 'walking purse'
taking advantage of him, but he just ended up getting
dragged along since he couldn't upfront refuse them.
It is because of that personality of his that Yukimasa
got quite harsh words and treatment from Ruka.
Furthermore, there's also their homeroom teacher Miyako
who nags him to change his attitude which easily attracts trouble.
The beautiful girl who works hard to perfectly become someone who won't bring shame to her family's name (Aiba Ruka), was attacked without
any chance to react by the heir of a landlord that gets on her nerves
due to his sorry state which she talks down to as well (Doumyouji Yukimasa).
He took control of Ruka's body as he publicly
humiliated her in front of their own classmates.
Yukimasa made her give him a blowjob while straddling with her clothes unbuttoned. Despite her effort to resist him, she was powerless in front of his meat stick.
However, Ruka started to suspect on some peculiarities of his actions.
And thanks to that faint glimmer of hope that she held in her heart,
she managed to break free from Yukimasa's control over her body. She took Suzune with her and they escaped out of their classroom.
Meanwhile, the teacher who advocates
self-reliance (Asama Miyako) is lost in thought.
Enrolled in her class are a boy and girl from families of landlords.
Although the girl is an excellent student overall
including academics, the boy is a problem.
He is timid, introverted and has no friends. He only gets to interact
with others whenever they need him as their walking purse.
It can't be helped that Miyako had to leave him alone to stand on his own,
but there are times that she needs to interfere as his homeroom
teacher so it can't be helped as well despite her annoyance.
The boy she is teaching is Yukimasa.
"Get yourself together. That attitude of yours will only
make people take advantage of you. I will be held responsible if something bad happens, so fix that attitude of yours."
Despite what Miyako says about teaching him a lesson, she just wants
to avoid any trouble for herself so Yukimasa isn't taking her seriously.
Original Animation
sai
min
gaku
en
Hypnosis Academy
~A Scrutinizing Female Teacher's
Over The Desk Virginity Compensation~
They should just get married already.
Last Time On Saimin O Gakuen......
You heard them.
Didn't you make them be like that?
What a pitiful recluse you are.
You don't look proud for being a pissing lady.
This much is nothing for me!
It's Suzune-chan's turn for today.
N-No... No.
I'm begging you, Yukimasa-kun!
I can't take any more of this... No!
Our lesson for today is about blowjobs.
Lick it.
Yukimasa-kun, spare me!
I'm begging you, any more of these...
No way... I don't want to...
Yukimasa-kun, I'm begging you!
That's most likely what he uses...
No...
Alright then, pee.
Huh?!
I'm sorry, forgive me!
Please, Yukimasa-kun! Relieving myself here is...
Unthinkable?
I'm sorry! I'll do it now, so...
No!
No! It's coming... out...
You're even dripping wet now.
No!
No, don't!
You can't do this!
Use sexual terms when you speak.
Okay!
No... your dick is stirring my pussy up!
No, let me go!
...not with this filthy thing!
Aiba-san, you're giving me a clean-up blowjob.
No! Why? Even though I never want to!
Use those needlessly large tits of yours as well.
It has an unsightly shape as always!
He's making me suck this thing
while sliding between my tits!
You won't be able
to dominate me from just doing something like this!
His smartphone is broken now
so we should be able to move again.
And if he finds us, we have things we can use here.
We should somehow be able to make an escape.
Yeah, that's right. I think so as well.
Aiba-san, where are you?
You're ignoring me... It can't be helped.
Suzune-chan, answer me.
Yes!
What are you doing?
Classes are ongoing. Hurry up
and go back to your class.
Did someone do something to you again?
It's a hassle for me whenever you get in trouble.
Get yourself together.
Okay...
We already know how he does it, so let's
escape for now and devise a countermeasure.
What's the meaning of this, Doumyouji?
Can't you see what this is?
I'm telling you to explain yourself!
Doumyouji!
Quit messing around, onii-chan!
That's not... Onii-chan... Why?
Then, I'm gonna call you "Miyako" as well.
Since you're here today, show us how
a mature woman's body looks like.
Miyako, take your clothes off and
sit right here while spreading your legs.
What are you saying, onii—!
Why is my body—!
You're quite a bold one, Miyako.
Stop!
Why can't I move?!
All of you, what are you
doing there? Make him stop!
You're bashful as well.
That's enough of you...
Stop! Don't touch me!
Do you think that you'll easily get away with this?
Why can't I move my body?
You... I won't forgive you
for doing this, onii-chan!
So you look slimmer in clothes.
They're unexpectedly huge and firm.
They don't easily sag down or spread out.
Shut up!
Don't do this! This nonsense
have gone far enough...
You started getting wet...
There's no way...
Stop! Any more than this and you'll
face consequences, onii-chan!
Stop! Don't look!
Stop looking!
You hate this yet you got wet.
This means that your mind
and body aren't in sync.
Stop saying stuff! Enough of this already!
Give us a live demonstration next.
S-Stop!
You're indecent.
I'll never ever forgive you for doing this!
Just as I expected from you, Miyako. Then...
Bend yourself down and stick your ass out.
Stop this absurdity! Any more of this
shameful acts and I'll absolutely...
No way... No!
Are you not ashamed of yourself
for laying your hands on a woman?!
What's so fun about doing such a thing as this?
Are you asking that now after all this time?
Miyako the female teacher was unkind to her student.
Wait, I'm scared!
I'll use this opportunity to teach you
how being oppressed feels like.
I thought you're loose down
here since you're an adult.
So, I am your first man.
Stop—!
I'll never forgive you!
This is unforgivable!
I'll absolutely...
I think this is a joyful turn of events for a
leftover woman beyond the age of marriage.
Shut up! What leftover woman are you saying?
You lowly beast!
You're being rough! Damn you!
Stop this, you jerk!
Make sure to get yourself pregnant.
Hey, are you crazy?!
I absolutely won't let you do
such an outrageous thing!
Stop! Stop!
We're teacher and student! That's...
No, stop!
It's inside me... This can't be happening!
No way!
We shouldn't just give up here right now.
We have to fight against him somehow.
Aiba-san, thank you for saving me all the time.
It's the same for me.
I never lost sight of myself
all thanks to you, Suzune-san.
Huh? What's the matter, Suzune-san?
Your skin... and everything else
about you is so beautiful...
Thank you.
Nevertheless, the reason
why he ended up like that is...
S-Suzune-san?
They're beautiful...
Wait!
Nothing but naughty things
have been done to me lately.
Could it be that my body turned weird?
You are right. Your body is hot.
Principal's Office
O-Onii-chan, stop!
Are you serious about doing it here?
We can't go any further!
There's a staff meeting right now.
Yet you're having a sibling roleplay
with a student in principal's office.
Stop. We can just do this
somewhere else, right?
Hey, do you enjoy doing this to me?!
Of course, I do. I enjoy seeing
that face of yours, Miyako.
I enjoy it as much as doing this.
This is abnormal! You're crazy, onii-chan!
That's a compliment, right?
Stop that!
Any more of this and...
You were a virgin despite your age,
so everything we do will be your first.
Mock me if you want.
There's no way that I'll forgive you for doing this...
Were you hoping for it?
I'll do it if you'll beg for it.
Don't mess with me! There's no way
I'll beg for something like that!
You don't appreciate how good sex is
yet since you just lost your virginity.
You...
Hey!
Stop that!
Hey, please...
Not here... I'll let you do it somewhere
else as much as you want!
It hurts!
You still feel pain?
I already did it with all the girls,
but each one is really different.
You mean the whole class?
You already saw it, right? No matter what I did to you,
no one cared and they only watched me.
Just what the hell did you
do on them, onii-chan?
Why are you doing all of this?!
Just ask everyone.
Stop this now, onii-chan!
Are you planning to come inside me again?
As much as I can. Until I get you pregnant.
So deep!
Don't come inside me while we're here!
That's absolutely...
Your repulsive stuff! It's going inside me!
Onii-chan... You lowly scum!
Alright then. I'll bring it to you afterwards, principal.
Understood. I'll be waiting for it.
Huh—?
Aiba-san!
Suzune-san...
You can just call me Ruka.
Ruka-san...
No, Suzune-san! That's my...
It's alright, Ruka-san. Just relax your body.
It feels good down here as well!
You're got here early. Please excuse us, principal.
I'm just cuddling Miyako.
You sure have it hard, having to
cuddle a woman of right age.
This is yet another duty of mine.
I'll clean this up immediately.
Suzune-san!
I'm feeling strange down there! Am I weird?
Ruka-san!
No! This is bad, Ruka-san...
Me too, if you keep doing that...
Me too, Suzune-san...
No way, even though it's
my ass! What's happening?!
Ruka-san!
Even though it's my ass, I'm...
Suzune-san!
No!
No, don't!
No—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next on "Saimin O Gakuen"......
This feels disgusting!
Stop this already!
It's reaching deep inside you. Does it feel good?
That can't be possible!
Absolutely not with a degenerate like you!
This is... Don't tell me that
you're gonna come inside!
This won't knock you up, isn't that great?
Y-You're right.
You can come as much as you want in there.
Both Aiba-san and sensei are good.
He's only been doing it with me in the past few days.
You should come in no time since
you have such a lewd body.
Again?! My body can't take this!
Doesn't it feel good?
It's reverberating deep inside!
I'll never accept this!
That I'm feeling good from this...
You have such a slutty body.
Say whatever you want!
I'll bet that this is yet one of your doing!
I can understand if you can't accept it.
This isn't my own fault!
It's his fault that my body feels so hot!
What are you doing? Classes are ongoing.
Hurry up and go back to your class.
S-Sensei!