I, Tanaka Hajime, have basically placed
three suggestions to everyone at school.
First and foremost... I, Tanaka Hajime,
am a Sex Counselor appointed by the government.
Next... Before a couple engages in
things like kissing and having sex,
they'll have to undergo counseling
from the sex counselor first.
And lastly...
Everything that the sex counselor says is correct.
For these men, what I'm doing
should seem like a physical exam
and a wholesome extension of P.E. class.
These men want to be able to have sex,
so they gladly offer their girlfriends' chastity to me.
And for the sake of their boyfriends,
these girls do their best and bear with
the embarrassment with no complaints.
These men pop a boner from
watching their miserable lovers.
And as I look at these men from above,
I aim at their girlfriends' womb
and unload my gooey semen!
I plant my seeds into these girls
as I irresponsibly fuck them right
in front of their boyfriends!
That is such a wonderful thing!
Saimin Seishidou
Hypnosis Sex Guidance
#2    The Case of Kurashiki Reina
However,
Sex Guidance Office
there are unruly girls among them as well.
Huh? Sexual guidance?
2nd Year / Class A
No Club Affiliation
Kurashiki Reina
2nd Year / Class A
No Club Affiliation
Kurashiki Reina
Isn't it too late for that?
I already am experienced.
Yeah... But giving proper guidance
has been neglected for several years now.
Well, I'm fine with that.
But are you saying that someone
like you is qualified for this?
You reek so much of a virgin's stench!
Sorry, did I piss you off?
I'm a girl who says whatever
is on my mind, after all.
You seem to prefer a one-on-one
session from the start.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah, yeah! I told you that's fine.
I don't want to bother my boyfriend to come.
Just get this thing over, okay?
For that defiance,
I'll maximize your sensitivity using hypnosis
and rape you into submission!
How is it, Kurashiki-san?
My guidance might be inadequate,
but I will do my best to fulfill my duty!
Wait! Tanaka, wait!
I'm coming! I'm already coming!
I-I've been coming all this time since earlier!
Huh? Are you perhaps already
giving up just from this much?
W-Why?
This is way different from when
I do it with my boyfriend!
N-No way... Just from the cock
of someone like him...
S-Stop... Stop it!
Stop for a moment! I said stop!
What's the matter, Kurashiki-san?
Weren't you so aloof earlier?
I-I'm starting to feel weird!
My body, especially down there is acting weird!
I never felt like this before!
I'm coming too much!
It's messing with my head!
Your huge mouth is just
as obscene as it is disrespectful!
We still have a long way to go, don't we?
No way, you're kidding!
I'm begging you, give me even a little break!
No, no... Am I not reeking off a virgin's stench?
I have to show you that I am capable
of giving proper guidance!
I'll apologize! I'll apologize, so please...
I'm sorry for saying rude things to you!
Forgive me already... Please forgive me!
Nope!
Look...
You'll get more and more sensitive
for each time I thrust my cock into you!
He kept on violating me afterwards.
He made me come over and over
that I already lost count of it.
Hey, you shouldn't be goofing around! Our counseling is ongoing!
Shake your hips and match my thrusts!
Jeez... You're way so bad at this, Kurashiki-san.
This is bad... I can't think of anything else anymore!
G-Good... It feels good...
Your cock feels good!
Your pussy is all but sloppy now!
Your inner flesh is coiling
around me and it feels good!
No...
My hips won't stop itself from moving!
My body...
My pussy is throbbing and
it gets hotter by the second...
I am about to ejaculate!
I'll aim for your cheeky womb
and shoot my thick stuff in it!
He's coming... He's coming inside me!
He'll make me come by giving me a creampie!
Coming, I'm coming!
You couldn't handle this level
of counseling, you poor thing.
Looks like you haven't had sex
as satisfying as this one before.
I'll train you strictly from now on,
so make sure to follow my orders.
Alright, then. Next will be...
Take a good look, all three of you.
Akeno-chan, who has experience in counseling,
will give you all a demonstration.
Akeno is sucking that thing like it's delicious!
1st Year / Class B
Tea Ceremony Club
Komori Hitomi
1st Year / Class B
Tea Ceremony Club
Komori Hitomi
S-So that's the way to suck it...
1st Year / Class E
Track and Field Club
Hasegawa Akane
1st Year / Class E
Track and Field Club
Hasegawa Akane
Wow...
Akeno-chan, who's usually well-behaved,
1st Year / Class B
Girls Tennis Club
Kawashima Yuuko
1st Year / Class B
Girls Tennis Club
Kawashima Yuuko
is now acting so lewd like that...
Your cock! It feels good!
It's so thick and hard!
More, I want it more in my pussy!
Harder... Please shove it harder inside me!
This will be a tryout counseling.
This will let girls without boyfriends
get accustomed to how a cock feels.
How am I doing, senpai?
Does my pussy...
Does my onahole pussy make you feel good?
Uh-huh!
You're doing it just how I taught you!
Good girl! Good girl!
No... No way...
Just from watching, I somehow...
Please give your milk to a slut like me, senpai!
I want it, I want your hot stuff!
I-It looked like she felt so good...
He'll be doing that to me too...
Alright, then. How about you three?
Want to have a tryout?
What is this? I'm scared! No!
It's gonna be alright, Hitomi-chan.
Just leave everything to senpai.
You'll be getting lots of pleasure in the end!
Even though this is supposed
to be my first time...
This is... This is wonderful! It feels good!
It feels good!
How about you, Yuuko-chan?
Doesn't my slippery cock feel good?
Just wait... Wait for a second, senpai!
You're going so hard on me all of a sudden!
I-I'm not mentally prepared for this yet!
Your pussy keeps sucking me in!
Weren't you actually waiting
for my cock all along?
Th-That's not true... I wasn't!
Wait... Wait... Wait!
My body is giving in!
It feels so great!
You have such an amazing pussy!
It's such a shame that you don't
have a boyfriend, Akane-chan!
No... No way!
Stop saying such things! It's embarrassing!
I-I feel like I'm about to lose my mind!
S-senpai!
Are we only allowed to have the tryout once?
We'd like to ask for one
more round if possible.
Did this pique your interests?
I'll call you over whenever
I have some spare time.
It feels hot! It's coming!
I feel something coming!
I want to have a counseling session again.
Sex Guidance Office
If I'm not mistaken,
isn't your schedule supposed to be next week?
Hey... I can't wait that long!
Hey, isn't it alright?
I've been feeling weird.
Ever since then, just thinking of you
makes my pussy feel like it's burning...
I'm begging you, give me some counseling!
I'll do anything... I'll do
whatever it takes, alright?
I see...
This might be a good opportunity...
Huh?
Whoa... What are you two doing?!
Oopsie... My bad, my bad!
We're using this place in our
sex counseling for a bit.
S-So, it was sex counseling.
Don't scare us like that!
Wh-Why do we have to do this in such a place?
We'll get this over with as soon as possible,
so don't mind us and feel free to use the urinals.
O-Okay...
Huh? N-No way!
That was surprising!
Well, I thought for a second that a couple
was romping here in the restroom.
This is nothing but sexual guidance.
I know that I shouldn't see it as obscene, but...
When I think about the fact that there's a girl
right next to me practicing blowjobs...
Hey, what's up with all of you?
Stop gawking with those rotten virgin eyes!
Will you cut that out?
I can't focus on my training!
I-It's not like that, we're just...
We weren't looking, right?
Huh?!
What are you saying when your
dicks are as hard as rocks?
Hey, come on! Just finish
your business and scram!
Hey there!
We're the one intruding here in the male restroom,
but you dare run your mouth like that!
No...
But their filthy eyes are...
No buts!
There won't be any more sex guidance
for you if you won't reflect on your actions!
No way! Don't do that!
If that's so...
Then, apologize properly!
I-I'm sorry for making fools out of you!
I'm sorry!
I-I didn't want you disrupting our counseling...
Being watched was embarrassing for me...
That's why I lashed my tongue
out in front of everyone!
F-Forgive me!
W-Wow...
That girl, Kurashiki Reina,
is being unusually submissive!
B-But it really is embarrassing!
P-Please...
Don't stare at me so much!
Th-This is Kurashiki's womanly face!
Sh-She's so cute!
Why not help us by becoming the spectators
for Kurashiki-san's live show
training while you're here?
Huh? W-Wait... What are you talking about?
Well, it can't be helped
if you don't want to do this.
Should we end this here right now?
No way! No way! No way!
Don't pull your cock out!
I get it already!
I'll let them watch as much as they want!
Come on, Kurashiki-san.
You have to give commentary for everyone.
When my tits are being fondled like this...
It makes me feel good in no time!
No way, more people are gathering around us...
Your nipples became like these as well...
Yes, my nipples... They're now standing erect...
And also... At the same time...
I-I'm shaking my hips...
And... I'm intensely being scraped inside!
I-I can't take it anymore!
My hips are loosening up
and losing their strength!
Hey, come on!
Everyone won't see you properly
in that pose, will they!
No—!
Whoa... That's incredible!
I have nothing else to hide in this position!
A-All of my embarrassing spots... All of them...
They are fully exposed!
The folds in your pussy are coiling around me!
Your pussy is a sloppy mess!
N-No way... I'm so horny right now!
Your cock is making a mess out
of me in front of all these men!
I am about to come!
I'm going for the final spurt!
I'll shoot it inside just like this!
A creampie?
H-He's just giving sex guidance,
so won't it be alright?
I-I am a kitty who's in heat all year round!
I'm about to come now!
I'm gonna come while everyone's watching!
Shoot it out! Shoot it out! Shoot it out!
I want you to fill the pussy of this kitty cat
with lots and lots of your fertile seeds!
Oh... It's coming out!
You did a great job, Kurashiki-san.
Everyone learned a lot!
Maybe we should call
the girls over next time...
That might be nice too.
What do you think?
W-We'll be having another counseling...
Saimin Seishidou
Hypnosis Sex Guidance
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization