Conceited Blonde Lady: Aiba Ruka
She's a daughter from a well-off household,
both a beauty and of academic excellence.
As a girl with a candid and fastidious disposition,
males find her difficult to approach, seeing her
as a "beauty out of anyone's league".
Possessing a great pride of her heritage, she strives be someone
that will live up to its name and not bring embarrassment on it.
This is even apparent with all the fame and clout she has in school.
She shows contempt for Yukimasa, who lacks both dignity
and ambition despite being a son of a wealthy landlord.
And as a result, everyone around Yukimasa
followed suit and shunned him as well.
Socially Adept Childhood Friend: Isurugi Suzune
Both of their parents were old friends and as a result she and Yukimasa
became friends that got along together since their childhood.
But now with Yukimasa being shunned and isolated, she quickly followed suit
and abandoned him like a stranger to become one of Ruka's lackeys.
And to imitate Ruka, she turned a blind eye
to Yukimasa, who was hoping for her help.
Each of Yukimasa's friends followed suit
as well and started shunning him.
Female Teacher who Advocates Self-Reliance: Asama Miyako
She is a female teacher who works under the philosophy that people
should always prioritize their own well-being and that they should
try to solve their own problems to the utmost of their abilities.
For Miyako's standpoint, Yukimasa's existence is a quite a headache.
She turns a blind eye every time she sees him getting teased at a mild
level. But when things escalate, she calls and gives him an earful.
"It's a hassle for me whenever you get in trouble. Get yourself together."
She was an unreachable goal as a role model teacher.
Introvert Son of a Great Landlord: Doumyouji Yukimasa
Despite his grandiose lineage, Yukimasa is asocial
and is someone who doesn't stand out much.
That social standing brings stress on him and to deal with it,
he started to hang out with his classmates.
These 'friends' treat him more of a 'walking purse'
taking advantage of him, but he just ended up getting
dragged along since he couldn't upfront refuse them.
It is because of that personality of his that Yukimasa
got quite harsh words and treatment from Ruka.
Furthermore, there's also their homeroom teacher Miyako
who nags him to change his attitude which easily attracts trouble.
The beautiful girl who works hard to perfectly become someone
who won't bring shame to her family's name (Aiba Ruka),
had her body taken control with a smartphone app
by the heir of a landlord that gets on her nerves due to his sorry state
which she talks down to as well (Doumyouji Yukimasa).
After being publicly humiliated in front of their own classmates,
Ruka and Suzune barely managed to escape. The two then had
their sullied and worn out bodies get some rest in a huge bathtub.
Meanwhile, their homeroom teacher Miyako, who acts coldly
towards Yukimasa for his own good and unsparingly gives him
an earful as well, had her first time taken by him as a new sacrifice.
He had his way playing with her seemingly plump and well-stacked body.
Yukimasa watched in delight at her miserably begging for mercy as he
indulged in their sibling incest roleplay inside the principal's office.
Suzune started to develop feelings way
beyond friendship towards Ruka who saved her.
She ran her fingers through Ruka's sullied
yet dignified and beautiful body.
Suzune's body throbbed as it easily became aroused
from constantly getting violated. It was the same for Ruka, willingly taking Suzune's finger inside her.
Despite them being both women,
Ruka indulged in intense sexual acts with Suzune.
As Ruka's pleasured and exhausted body lies on top of Suzune
from climaxing many times, what appears before her eyes
is the erect meat stick she highly despised.
O
R
sai
min
gaku
en
Hypnosis Academy
Re
Ori
Rel
Rele
Origi
Relea
Releas
Origina
Release
Released
Original
Released,
Released, C
Original A
Released, Co
Released, Cor
Original Ani
Released, Corr
Released, Corru
Original Anim
Released, Corrup
Released, Corrupt
Original Anima
Released, Corrupte
Released, Corrupted
Original Animati
Released, Corrupted a
Released, Corrupted an
Original Animatio
Released, Corrupted and
Released, Corrupted and I
Original Animation
Released, Corrupted and Im
Released, Corrupted and Imp
Released, Corrupted and Impu
Released, Corrupted and Impud
Released, Corrupted and Impude
Released, Corrupted and Impuden
Released, Corrupted and Impudent
L
La
Last
Last Ti
Last Time
What's the meaning of this, Doumyouji?
Last Time On
Last Time On Sa
Last Time On Sai
Last Time On Saimi
Last Time On Saimin
Last Time On Saimin O
Last Time On Saimin O Ga
Last Time On Saimin O Gaku
Can't you see what this is?
Last Time On Saimin O Gakuen
Last Time On Saimin O Gakuen...
I'm telling you to explain yourself!
Doumyouji!
Quit messing around, onii-chan!
That's not... Onii-chan... Why?
Then, I'm gonna call you "Miyako" as well.
You're quite a bold one, Miyako.
Stop!
Why can't I move?!
You started getting wet...
There's no way...
S-Stop!
Wait, I'm scared!
I'll use this opportunity to teach you
how being oppressed feels like.
Stop—!
I'll never forgive you!
Stop! Stop!
We're teacher and student! That's...
No, stop!
We shouldn't just give up here right now.
We have to fight against him somehow.
Your skin... and everything else
about you is so beautiful...
S-Suzune-san?
They're beautiful...
Stop. We can just do this
somewhere else, right?
Hey, do you enjoy doing this to me?!
Of course, I do. I enjoy seeing
that face of yours, Miyako.
I enjoy it as much as doing this.
You already saw it, right? No matter what I did to you,
no one cared and they only watched me.
Just what the hell did you do to them, onii-chan?
Why are you doing all of this?!
This is yet another duty of mine.
I'll clean this up immediately.
Ruka-san!
Even though it's my ass, I'm...
Suzune-san!
No!
No, don't!
No—!
Why are you...
That's so mean... I even came here for you.
Suzune-san?
Yukimasa-kun, it looks like Ruka-san is feeling good!
Suzune-san, why...
I can't move...
That's because Suzune-chan already gave in to lust.
Strong-minded people like you
are actually rare, Aiba-san.
You're glad and craving for Yukimasa-kun
that you got sopping wet down here, Ruka-san!
You're beyond my expectations
to do each other even here.
It looks like you're all prepared
and even peed yourself.
Shall we do it, Aiba-san?
I'm posing again just like before
even when I don't want to!
I'm about to make you feel good right now.
That won't be happening no
matter what you do to me!
Wh-What are you doing? That's...
...the wrong hole!
I already said that's the wrong hole!
It's so tight! Looks like I'll get
to enjoy a different sensation.
This feels disgusting!
Stop this already!
You loosened up down here. Does it feel good?
That can't be possible!
Absolutely not with a degenerate like you!
Your body is completely being honest, though.
You're talking nonsense!
It's also your fault that my body turned strange!
There's no way that I'm...
This is... Don't tell me that
you're gonna come inside!
This won't knock you up, isn't that great?
Y-You're right.
You can come as much as you want in there.
I'll need to work on both you and sensei...
Hurry up and come!
Sensei hasn't given in yet...
This is so intense!
We're not done yet.
You're being rough on me!
So intense!
Your tits are oozing.
Your body already gave in to lust, unlike your mind.
Wh-Why? This can't be real!
I'm not actually pregnant!
Your body has reached its limit
unlike your reasoning.
Say whatever you want!
But you'll never ever bend me to your will!
You're Aiba-san, alright.
Remember that things will never
keep going as you please!
Come as many times as you want!
I'll do just as you said.
He's really doing as I said?!
Make sure to clean it up, Aiba-san.
We're having a practical lesson on squirting.
He's only been doing it with me in the past few days.
You should come in no time since
you have such a lewd body.
He's humiliating me anywhere he wants.
But everyone is making a face filled
with envy, just like Suzune-san!
What if sensei catches us here?
Nobody will mind us.
I'll need to work on both you and sensei...
People like you are...
I'm sure that Asama-sensei will
put up a fight until the end!
You have such an indecent body.
Say whatever you want!
I'll bet that this is yet one of your doing!
I can understand that you don't want to admit it...
This isn't my own fault!
It's his fault that my body feels so hot!
What are you doing? Classes are ongoing.
Hurry up and go back to your class.
S-Sensei!
I thought that I heard a strange voice. Was that Aiba?
What do you think you're doing here?
Sensei, please help me!
Are you planning to have onii-chan
all by yourself by having sex here?
S-Sensei...
You're being mean too, onii-chan!
I told you to do me, but you're only
making love with Aiba all the time!
Did you get your hopes up?
Even sensei has already...
I'm...
Hurry up and let me have your cock!
Shove it in your little sister's pussy!
Jeez... You sure are a snappy girl, Miyako.
Am I not doing you a lot more than the other girls?
It's inside! My big brother's cock...
I'm entitled to have it as a teacher!
It feels good! My brother's cock is ramming deep into my pussy!
It feels good!
Sensei is making such an indecent
face like she's feeling good...
Onii-chan, your cock is scraping me deep inside!
It's digging into me and it feels good!
This is...
Will it make things easier for me to just
let the pleasure take me over like that?
Onii-chan, right there!
Keep thrusting your cock a lot more!
I want it hard!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
You look like you're wanting some.
Again?! My body can't take this!
Doesn't it feel good?
It's reverberating deep inside!
I'll never accept this!
That I'm feeling good from this...
Even when you're dripping wet like this?
It's because of you controlling me!
Otherwise, who will ever get
this way from the likes of you?
Nobody wondered about how you are until this day.
Have you not wondered why "everyone" around you is hypnotized?
Wh-What are you trying to say?
The one who made that possible
is nobody else but you, Aiba-san.
What do you mean?
I can't hypnotize every person around you,
so isn't it best to make you do it instead?
I erased your memory of that, though.
N-No way! That's a lie!
There's no way for such nonsense...
It's up to you to believe it or not,
but everything will feel easier if you submit to me.
N-No!
Not with this man! It's so frustrating!
I don't want to accept this!
No, you're throbbing inside me!
Anyone out there, anyone!
No—!
That's it! I've been wanting to see you make such a face!
No, don't!
I don't want this—!
I'll never accept this!
Here's a reward for not giving up until the end.
I haven't given you any order
since I first did it with Miyako,
so why didn't you try to escape?
Your dick is amazing!
Hey, Isurugi! Hurry up!
Making onii-chan feel good is my job!
Just a little longer... He's about to come...
You'll have your turn later, sensei.
H-Hey! We're in the middle of class!
You have to go back to your seat!
Sensei...
Yukimasa-kun's first shot is mine!
Yukimasa-kun, give it to me!
Fill my mouth with your thick semen!
Amazing!
It's so thick in the morning!
Alright, It's my turn now.
I want my big brother's cock inside me.
No, sensei. You'll have your turn later.
It's my turn to have his morning dick right now.
What, isn't that unfair to me?
Stop right there!
Both of you,
having an unsightly argument only
causes trouble for the master.
R-Ruka-san...
Aiba, you... What do you mean "master"?
Master, this sow offers herself
to pleasure your sturdy morning cock!
You finally became honest with yourself, Aiba-san.
To think that I kept myself away
from something that feels this good...
I was a fool!
Please use this great cock of yours...
and give me... I mean...
give this sow your semen!
I will forever be at your disposal, master!
I will be willing to make you feel good at all times!
Master, your cock is...
...driving me crazy
More! More! Please make yourself feel...
...even better—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization