The haughty blonde haired rich girl: Aiba Ruka
A beautiful girl with amazing grades and the luck of being the daughter of a wealthy family. She has a very straight forward and fastidious persoality which makes it hard for guys to even approach her. She carries a strong pride for her family and does her utmost to not bring any shame to it. Her family's influence and fame are especially known within the school. She begins to look down on Yukimasa, who despite being the son of the family who owns the land, exerts no authority and carries no ambition. Because of the way she treats him, the other people in the school naturally begin to treat him poorly as well.
The childhood friend, drifting through life: Ishidou Suzune
Because both her parents and Yukimasa's parents are friends, they've been together since a young age. However, because of the sour attitude that Ruka takes towards Yukimasa, she begins to follow Ruka's orders and ignore all of Yukimasa's glances towards her, looking for help. She turns the other way and looks down on Yukimasa together with her other friends.
The insular son of a large land owner: Domyouji Yukimasa
The insular son of a big family, though he makes it a point to not stand out. But that attitude of his becomes an outlet for stress relief. Ultimately, his so-called classmates and friends just end up using him as their own personal wallet. But it's not as if he didn't draw the line and refuse outright. He was being strung along. Ruka, who saw this all unfold became incredibly annoyed seeing him just take this and had some strong words for him.
Ruka was a beautiful girl who had worked hard to make sure that she would cause no shame to her family name.
As a daughter of the Aiba family, seeing the son of the Domyouji family, a family even more prestigious than hers, being passed around and used as everyone's wallet, struck a nerve with her. She then gave him a piece of her mind...
"Wh-What's going on..." Even if she wanted to run away, her body wouldn't allow her to. She had no choice but to endure his instruction. Ruka's pure and innocent body was defiled. Similarly, Suzune was also made to show everyone her genitals and be fucked on all fours.
And them came a voice that ridiculed them for the obscene acts they were participating in... "Now understand what it's like for those without power." And the things that pounded that into their heads with pain and by forcibly widening the small, narrow crevices in their bodies, was Yukimasa's meat stick...
Deflowering the people who disparaged him and verbally abused him... Being able to manipulate Ruka and Suzune as he wished... Yukimasa began his plan to expose them to even more humiliating experiences...
Hypnosis Academy
The cheeky, strong willed rich girl
Out of my way.
I'm the daughter of the well-renowned Aiba family
and you're just a defective product of the Domyouji family.
Are you not embarrassed with that face of yours?
Good grief, you're pathetic.
You have it rough, Suzune-san.
My deepest condolences that
you have him as a childhood friend.
Sure is hot.
You're not too sweaty, are you?
I think you'd cool down a bit if you took off your panties.
This good?
Listen to every order I give without question.
He's watching me pee...
Rio, what are you doing?!
It's embarrassing playing with my pussy
in front of you, Ruka-sama, but... it feels so good!
This position...
My body's not listening to me! I can't stop!
That huge thing is going in her!
It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun, it hurts! It hurts!
You're next, Aiba-san.
No! No!
Stop! Please, it hurts!
Yeah, you're not wet, so I guess it does.
Right?
It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun's coming inside me!
His thing, it's... It hurts!
What is this thing?!
What's going on?! It hurts! It hurt so much!
It's too big!
It's gonna tear!
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop moving!
No! No!
Please, no!
Stop!
No! This can't be happening!
The most vile man on the planet's
semen is pouring inside me!
I'm really going to get pregnant!
Aiba-san's getting filled up inside just like I was!
N-No!
No! No!
Not bad, Suzune-chan.
I am going to make you pay for this, you lowlife!
Out of all the places...
You're having your way with me here?!
He's a perfect match for Ruka-sama.
They should just get married!
Hear that?
You're just making them say that.
You're so pathetic.
That's not what your body's saying.
Nonsense!
My body's only like this because of you!
Whatever you say.
You're going to cum inside me again?!
Stop it!
Stop! I...
I can't...
You came in me so much again!
I'm really going to get pregnant!
Wait! Stop!
Stop! Please!
No... You're kidding me!
No! This can't be happening!
Why?! Stop!
No!
I guess there's not much dignity
in a rich girl who peed herself.
In your dreams!
Let's have health class now.
I'll use a live demonstration to teach all of you.
Hmph. You just want to do the same thing as yesterday.
You're really doing something this stupid right here?!
Now listen closely, she is what we call a "tsundere".
We'll have another great, comprehensive class.
We'll have Suzune-chan help out today.
N-No! No!
Please, Yukimasa-kun. I can't do this anymore!
Today we'll be studying fellatio.
Why is my body moving on its own?!
N-No!
Lick it.
Yukimasa-kun, please, no.
Please don't make me do anything
more embarrassing! I really...
Wha... N-No!
R-Please, Yukimasa-kun...
There's no way that huge thing can fit in her mouth!
But her body is moving on its own!
It's not perfect, but this is called a "titfuck".
That... That has to be how he...
You're so into it.
Pretty good for your first time.
Keep going. Drink it all up.
N-No! I'm sorry!
Please, not this, Yukimasa-kun!
Spread wider so everyone can see.
No! This is so embarrassing!
If I could just get his phone!
Now, pee.
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
Yukimasa-kun, I can't do that here!
Didn't you hear me?
I'm sorry! I'll do it!
I'll do it now!
No!
No! I'm peeing!
And this is what we call an exhibitionist.
No! Don't move, Yukimasa-kun!
As an exhibitionist, you feel best when
you're in front of everyone, don't you?
I'm not like that!
I feel so relieved now. It wasn't that bad at all.
What is that?
I... That's not me!
You don't feel good when being watched by others?
But look how wet you are.
No!
Stop! Stop!
Please stop!
Aren't you forgetting some words?
Your dick is stirring up my pussy!
He's using his power again to make
her say those indecent things!
You're next, Aiba-san, so make sure you're taking notes.
It must be great to be you.
But neither me or Suzune-san will break.
Aiba-san...
I can't wait to do her next.
It hurts.
It's so deep...
Yep, looks like you're gonna get pregnant this time.
No!
No! Yukimasa-kun, don't!
Stop! No!
No!
Pregnant... baby...
This can't be happening!
I'm not going to do that! In your dreams!
I'm not going to suck tha...
My body's moving on its own!
No! Why?!
Not here! No!
I...
No! Let me go!
This disgusting thing...
You're going to give me a clean-up fellatio, Aiba-san.
No! Why?!
I don't want to!
I have to kiss this thing?!
But it was just in her! It's not clean!
I don't want to lick this disgusting thing!
But I can't stop!
Use those needlessly big tits of yours.
No! My breasts...
No!
I'm moving them!
Use your mouth too.
I need to get the phone!
This thing is such a disgusting shape.
But he's making me take it in between
my breasts and in my mouth!
You got good at this real quick.
You're the princess of blowjobs.
Shut your mouth!
This is so disgusting! You pervert! Scum!
I will never forgive you!
Let me give you a reward, princess.
Wait, is he going to...
No!
Don't!
Let go of me!
His disgusting stuff is filling my throat!
I can't breathe!
It's so sticky and smelly... it's gross!
It's so gross!
You can do whatever you want to me, but I will never break!
I wouldn't have it any other way.
You're still this hard after cumming?!
Seeing your beautiful face wrought with anger turns me on.
This is so humiliating!
You're making me move?!
It feels good for you, doesn't it?
You're making me feel that way!
This isn't me!
You think so?
All the pain is gone and he's spreading me out inside,
but my body's getting used to it!
This isn't enough to break me!
Soon enough, you won't be able to resist.
That's never going to happen.
Someone like you will never be able to break me!
Don't get ahead of yourself!
My hips are moving on their own!
Are you going to cum inside me again?!
Yeah, it feels like you want me to, Aiba-san.
That's not...
Just a little more!
Just keep going...
You're really going to cum inside me again!
There's so much inside me!
It's pouring out inside me!
I definitely won't forgive you for this!
Ow!
Aiba-san, that was so intense.
Suzune-san!
Are you all right, Suzune-san?
Thank you, Aiba-san.
His phone's broken, so we should be free now.
And if he comes after us, we have weapons.
We should be able to get away.
Yeah, I think so too.
Aiba-san, where are you?
Seriously? Fine, then.
Suzune-san, answer me.
Yes!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч