Eri-chan... and Satsuki-chan too?
Kanae.
Are you well?
We were hoping Kawai-sensei would
et us rejoin the fine arts club.
According to Fujimi-sensei...
Kawai-sensei thinks were having
a bad influence on you, Kanae.
However, there's no excuse for what we did.
You two didn't do anything wrong.
No, we shouldn't have reacted the way we did.
We probably overreacted.
Yes, that's the correct.
If three people were to go through the same experience,
they would come to understand each
others hearts more deeply.
This feels weird, Sensei.
First, you must warm-up so that you can feel relaxed.
Now, you can practice with this.
Everyone will be serviced together, okay?
Yes...
First up...
With this, the three of you are now truly friends.
Saimin Ryoujoku Cakuen
Second                   Story
Substitution Technique
Umm, Fujimi-sensei...
I'm sorry, but I'm embarrassed to get counseling.
Ah, you are... umm, Uehara Miyuki-san, right?
Yes.
Were you about to leave?
No, it's alright.
Since it doesn't have anything to do with school,
I hesitated on whether to come to you.
Don't worry, it makes no difference what the problem is.
So you were unable to accept your mother's
second marriage, is that right?
I've finally learned to accept my Father's death.
But it's only been a few-years since then.
So, you feel that your mother's feelings towards
your late father are slowly disappearing?
Yes.
Uehara-san... do you love your father?
Yes, of course.
Then please, close your eyes.
Okay.
This is a form of psychological therapy.
What I say will become reality.
When you once again open your eyes,
your father will appear in front of you.
Father will?
When you are ready, please close your hands.
Okay.
Now, open your eyes.
You will see your father before your eyes.
Father...
You've grown, Miyuki.
Daddy!
You're the student council president, Shirogane-san, right?
We saw Uehara Miyuki-san going into your office earlier.
Ah, she was just asking for some counseling for her problem.
A class representative seeking counseling,
this is somewhat worrisome.
Even members of the student council
have private matters to deal with.
That's true, in a manner of speaking.
Hm, still resting.
Oh, this feels like it'd be quite the suitable experiment.
After all, parent-child communication is also very important.
Umm, Fujimi-sensei.
Yes?
A moment ago, the mother of one of
my students, Uehara Miyuki, called.
Uehara-san?
Yes.
She said her daughter's counselor wanted to do a home visit.
In order to get the other side of the story.
Ah, so that's it.
Though I told her that, as a counselor,
you aren't a qualified teacher.
What's the meaning of this?
Meaning of what?
Doing what you wish without my permission,
involving yourself with my students.
It's a required aspect for this situation.
That's why I agreed to it.
But all things have a precedence.
If her own teacher doesn't know the
situation, how can I permit it?
Is that all?
Such sarcastic words!
Fine then, but let me remind you of something.
Your job is to provide psychological counseling
for school related problems.
Please do not intervene in the personal
lives of students on a whim.
Understood. I was merely providing other options.
I'm sorry, because of me, Akiko-sensei...
It's okay, it doesn't matter.
More importantly, how are things with your father?
My Father? Sensei, what are you talking about?
So you've already forgotten it, the
secret bond with your father.
With my Father? Secret?
Ah, Daddy!
Today, I'll teach you things that are important at your age.
A woman's pleasures.
A woman's?
First, take off your clothes.
Take them off?
Yes.
This is our father's cock.
Examine it closely.
Okay.
It feels kind of warm.
Ah, it jumped!
Because Miyuki made it feel good.
Now, begin to slowly stroke it.
Like this?
Ah, amazing. It keeps getting bigger.
You're such a good girl, Miyuki.
You're my favorite.
Really?
Yes. With this, we can feel good together.
Yes, I want to feel good with you.
That's right, be careful of your teeth.
Your tongue's movement is good.
Miyuki.
Ah, this is Daddy's...
That's right, it's semen.
It tastes kind of weird.
I've only just started touching your breasts and pussy,
but you're already feeling it.
Because this is the first time someone else touched me...
Daddy, stop...
But Miyuki, you're so wet.
No way, I'm sorry, I...
You seem to be craving my cock.
You're really feeling it, aren't you?
Yes, I'm really feeling it..
Daddy, please feel good with me.
I understand.
Whenever Miyuki needs me,
I'll be there for you.
Daddy... I'm so happy.
Now, let your father leave his mark
in Miyuki's most important place.
Yes, please give me more of your love!
Slowly lower yourself down onto me.
Okay...
Such naughty sounds.
You're already soaked.
No... I can feel you inside me...
Now, to go all the way.
I'm one with Daddy...
Yes, with this Miyuki is my woman.
That's great.
Daddy, does it feel good inside?
Yes, very good.
Miyuki is fine, so please do it harder.
No need to rush.
Co at your own pace.
I can feel you inside, it's filling me up!
Daddy, it feels strange!
Daddy, it's splitting me apart...
Daddy, please!
Harder, harder, I'm cumming!
How many times do I have to say it for you to understand?
You have to use careful strokes!
Look, once again!
If you do it like that, it'll look too different!
That's enough! Next period is independent study.
Everyone should use that time to do it over again!
You seem to be angry, Kawai-sensei.
About Motokawa-san and Nonomura-san...
Did they apologize to you?
Yes, they did.
I talked to the two of them
and gave them some suggestions.
Once they solved their own problems,
they were able to talk to Kawai-sensei more easily.
Including Yasuda-san, the three
of them are doing better, right?
That's correct.
Kawai-sensei, you must've accumulated
a lot of stress recently.
If the mind is tired, so is the body.
Y-yes...
I'm also an expert in this field.
Do you need me to relieve your stress?
Relieve my stress?
Yes, its quite simple.
First, you need to relax.
Fujimi-sensei...
Ah, Uehara-san.
Umm, about visiting my house...
I heard what Kawai-sensei said this morning.
What should I do?
Don't worry, I'm discussing things with Kawai-sensei.
Once I get permission, I'll be sure to come over.
Is that so? I understand.
Then I'll be sure to let Mother know.
Ah, take this home with you.
The sweet aroma will make things more relaxed.
Thank you very much.
This will make things easier.
Fujimi-sensei!
Kawai-sensei, this is the men's room.
Um, this is, uh...
In order to relieve your built up pressure,
you were playing with yourself, isn't that right?
Y-yes...
Fujimi-sensei!
Yes?
The stress built up in my body has become hot...
Cuess it can't be helped.
That's right... this is what I wanted.
Amazing, a man's smell...
A dick's smell...
Have you figured out the source of your troubles?
You irritable because your body wasn't being satisfied, right?
That is... I've been craving a dick...
I've been craving it so much...
I'm already soaked.
Please, put it in me.
Your dick... is so thick...
It's hot... it's very hot...
It's rubbing against me with such force...
Right there, it feels good!
Kawai-sensei...
Yes...?
I'd like to visit Uehara's home, if you don't mind.
Yes, I don't mind.
Then here I come at full force!
So good!
I'm sorry if I'm overstepping my bounds.
No, I don't understand Miyuki's feelings.
Ever since I got remarried, she's been in such pain.
I feel sorry for her.
But...
But?
It's embarrassing to say,
but it was difficult to raise her and
her two younger sisters alone.
I see.
Are the two younger sisters twins?
Yes, their names are Miku and Nami.
They're playing over at a friend's house today.
The twins accepted the remarriage quite
easily, which was very helpful.
Miyuki-san can't accept it, though?
Right.
I'm sure you already know why.
It all stems from her intense feelings for her late father.
Actually, there's one thing Id like for you to confirm.
Yes? What is it?
You're trying to build a new family...
Do you have any uncertainties?
That is... I'm not really sure.
It's not as if I don't still have feelings for my late husband.
As I thought.
I believe that Miyuki-san is picking up on your uncertainties.
So she is unable to forgive you for deceiving yourself.
There's something I'd like to try.
Using a false experience to speak with your late husband,
you'll be able to confirm how you feel.
False experience?
Yes, a form of psychological therapy using hypnosis
to deal with the memory of your late husband face to face.
This will allow you to understand yourself more deeply.
Understand more deeply?
When I snap my fingers, your late
husband will appear before you.
You will imagine that person to be here.
Kazue, its been a while.
Darling!
Is that really you!?
I'm so happy to see you again.
Ah, that's great.
My welcome home kiss, how was it?
Um, can I get a reward kiss?
Ah, that's right, I have to reward you.
I'm so happy!
These two were really kinky.
Interesting.
It's been so long since you've used your breasts.
It's wonderful.
It's been so long, I'd almost forgotten how it feels.
You mustn't forget.
You're to use them to serve me.
Yes, please use them to feel good.
You're also feeling it.
Your penis feels so good.
Now, use your mouth.
Use your tongue to please me.
Yes...
Hows it feel?
It's good... so good, Kazue!
Kazue...
You're massaging me perfectly!
It smells so good.
It's been a while since you smelled
something so good, hasn't it?
Yes, but I want more. Much more.
That's my Kazue!
I'm home!
Fujimi-sensei, are you here?
Sensei... Mother?
Ah, Miyuki. Welcome home.
Daddy!
These are some real slutty panties, Kazue.
This is the kind you liked...
So I always wear them.
Mom always wears them because she prefers you, Daddy.
I see, so you wear them despite being remarried.
No way, don't say such things...
Mom... you look happy.
Watch, I'll make her look much, much happier.
Feel how wet she's become.
Harder, do it harder!
Mom...
It feels so good.
Do you see it, this shameful appearance of mine...
Next, lets show Kawai how you and your mother get along.
Yes.
Excuse us.
Umm...
Yes, you are... Ueharas mother?
Our relationship is the best it's been since
the remarriage because of Fujimi-sensei,
so we came to express our thanks.
Remarriage? Ah, is that so.
He asked us to wait in this office, if that's okay.
Sure, that's no problem.
Ah, you two came.
It's kind of embarrassing,
but these two want to show their thanks to all of the Senseis.
I hope everyone accepts.
Umm, Fujimi-sensei?
Now then, get ready you two.
Take care of each Sensei with your bodies.
Yes.
Why are you two doing this?
It's okay, Kawai-sensei. No one minds.
What are you talking about?
Fujimi-sensei...
Look, don't get angry.
That would only build up more stress.
Your body's getting hot.
Okay everyone, come get your thank-you gift.
Doing such things... it's making me wet...
Sensei, do you want to join in too?
It's good...
Darling, hurry and put it in me!
Daddy, it feels so good!
Darling, you're so good.
Daddy's smell...
Ah, it feels so good, all my stress is gone!
You didn't need to remarry after all, Kazue.
I can feel my husbands love...
I feel it in me, too.
Now, show your thanks even more.
Arimine, the reports seem to indicate something
happened with the fine arts club.
Yes. Kawai-sensei asked that a few
of the members quit the club.
So, what happened?
Following Fujimi-sensei's counseling,
they managed to solve the problem on their own.
Is that so...
Not only helping a girl with her hatred of men,
but a family problem and a club dispute as well.
He may be talented after all.
Now it's your turn... to entertain me.