Susumu, make sure you study properly..
I'll be busy working away from home, don't laze around..
Strict
Mother
Well, I'll be going on ahead..
Oh, Susumu-kun, Good morning.
If you'd like to, stop by for some tea sometime..
No need to hold back, after all
you're just like family, Susumu-kun..
Kind
Aunt
Ah, Susumu-chan! Good morning! Ok mom, I'll be going!
Next time, help me with my lessons, Susumu-chan..
Innocent Cousin
You're in the way! Stop taking your sweet time!
Can't you hear the chime?
Why did I get him for a childhood friend!?
Firm Childhood Friend
Oh, Susumu-kun.. Just coming home?
You know, I'm getting married soon...
I'd like you and Sawa-san both to be there..
Sister to be
Ah, Good Day.. I'll be living here
starting today; my name's Murakoshi..
Nice to meet you.
X-FAP Presents:
The world of illusions and obscene dreams
Hypnosis Technique
Ok Susumu, I'll be going now..
I'll be late so..
You'll have dinner at Takase-san's..
Give them my regards.
Welcome Susumu-kun, come on in..
Our other student just came home..
After that, she had to go for some groceries..
So could you wait a while?
What is it, Susumu-kun?
I'll... teach.. the.. student.. about.. sex..
I'll.. give.. sex.. lessons.. to.. Susumu-kun..
Oh that's right, why don't I give you a lesson today?
I'll ask Noriko to do a little more shopping, so I'll mail her by phone right away..
If we're here, no one can hear us..
Because the lesson might get loud.
Noriko can't interrupt us when she gets back while we're like this.
My husband's always on business trips, so I'm lonely.
I'm glad that you asked me to
give you a lesson, Susumu-kun.
But.. is it really okay? For me to teach you?
Really? I'm glad..
Let's begin..
Our sex.. lesson..
Looking at me so seriously, you're embarrassing me..
This fluttering part is the labia.
Mine is thick and sticks out, however..
Younger girls around your age would have smaller ones with a lighter color, I think..
Even mine used to have a gentle shape but age took it's toll..
And due to the countless times I've done it with my husband, it's taken on this obscene shape..
This top part is the clitoris.
It's... one of the most.. sensitive parts of a woman ...
And this here, is the... vaginal opening..
Because I gave birth to Noriko, it's become so soft..
But I don't think the tightness is that bad..
Oh, My...
Susumu-kun, right here..
Put your stiff cock in, give it a try..
Come on, hurry..
That's it..
A little lower...
That's not the vaginal hole, it's on the other end..
That's right, right there... Just where I showed you earlier..
Just like that.. push your hips forward..
It's in! So thick.. Thicker and longer than my husband's..
Susumu-kun, good.. you're so good..
This is a first experience.. not just having a big cock,
but also having my breasts played with like this..
Good, so good, Susumu-kun..
You're reaching so deep in me!
You're hitting me deeper than my husband ever did!
I'm feeling it!
Such wonderful sex.. for the first time..
Susumu-kun.. Susumu-kun, are you feeling good too?
How does it feel being inside a woman for the first time? Feeling it?
Come whenever you feel like it, come anytime.. it's okay..
Just like that, keep giving it to me!
Give auntie your virgin load.. Let me feel it!
Let me feel it! Let me feel it! Make auntie feel it!
Good.. So good.. let me squeeze it all out..
Your young and healthy cum.. your cum is flooding me..
Susumu-kun, the thickness of your cum is quite incredible..
Is the lesson done? Mama, how was Susumu-chan?
It was his first lesson, yet, he did so well..
I believe that Susumu-kun is very talented.
Oh really? That's great Susumu-chan!
I'm home.. Oh, Susumu.. Still up?
What's wrong, Susumu?
Yes, my work was rough.. my shoulders are stiff..
But the most tired of all is my chest, so..
If I have my breasts massaged, I'll feel better..
Work's been rough, my chest feels heavy.
Getting tense can't be helped..
Susumu.. you'll give me a massage?
Thank you.. well then..
Please do so..
You're rather good at this..
Where'd you learn such a..
I see.. Shino, taught you..
Yes! yes.. that's the spot.. it feels crisp, doesn't it?
More.. do it harder.. it'll feel better that way..
Yes.. that's it! it feels so good!
Susumu.. More, harder.. more, do it intensely!
Mommy's.. just a little more! Little more...!
It's good, so good! Susumu!
That's it, that's it.. that's good, Susumu! more, do it more!
No more, I can't hold it..
I'm coming!
Susumu, your massage felt so good...
Well then, let's start today's lesson.
This time, we'll use this piano..
It's still new, so the sounds might be tense but..
Don't mind that and try it..
Surprisingly good sounds are coming out..
Keep going on, it's alright..
Mom..
What's wrong, Noriko?
What should I do? I got a- got a cock..
My! How splendid..
Noriko's also become an adult before I knew it..
What should I do with this, Mom?
It's alright, Noriko.. since it's a cock..
If we make it come a lot, it'll calm down..
Really?
Really! Just leave it to Mommy..
I'll make Noriko's cock shoot a lot..
Thank you, Mom..
I can't let my daughter get
me pregnant, so use this hole, okay?
I'll take your virginity with my ass, Noriko.
In exchange, Noriko, Mommy
will give you her anal virginity..
It's my first time so I don't know what to do..
But I'll take your virginity, Mom..
My anus.. my anus is being forced open..
My asshole.. asshole is..
Having something hard shoved in it..
It's a new sensation!
Ah, it's in Mom! Your insides feel good, so good..
My.. my cock.. is getting.. squeezed tightly..
Noriko, try moving now.. just like that... don't pull it out, move moderately..
Ok. I'll try, Mom.
My ass is getting torn apart.
It's almost like my insides are being pulled out..
Mom.. Mom, is it painful?
It's alright, it's alright, Noriko. It also feels good, so good.
Noriko's thick- thick cock is..
Rubbing my asshole.. it's so.. so wonderful..
Mom, it's amazing, it's so amazing..
My cock- My cock feels like
it's being sucked in by you, Mom..
Anal sex feels so good!
If it feels so good then, faster- go ahead and do it faster!
Mom-Mom it feels so good, sex feels so good!
I'm a girl yet, my first experience is using a cock!
Also, taking an anal virginity!
And my first time doing it, is with my Mom!
I'm.. I'm gonna go crazy..
It's alright, it's alright, Noriko! Sex feels great so..
It can't be helped if you go crazy.
Mommy too, is gonna come from your virgin cock!
Mom! It feels like something is coming out!
My cock is feeling eager! Is this- Is this pee?
No, no-no.. Mom's insides are tight! So tight!
It's coming!
It's alright, Noriko! It's not pee, not pee.. so..
It's alright if you come, it's alright if you let it out!
Is it really okay? No.. I can't.. I can't hold it- no, it's coming!
My daughter's cum, Noriko's cum..
is going so deep into my asshole..
Hot, so hot! My insides are burning!
Mom's.. Mom's insides are squeezing me..
My cock is getting pushed!
So, that.. that was anal sex.. that was such a wonderful sensation..
Doing it in the ass, I could get addicted to this..
Mom..
What is it, Noriko?
Still.. it's not getting smaller..
Ah, it can't be helped I guess.. Well then, once more..
This time, I'll do it with my mouth..
No, Mom.. it's.. it's dirty..
No need to worry.. Leave it to Mommy.
Mom, you're licking my cock that went into your ass..
It feels so abnormal and perverted!
It tastes bitter.. I wonder if this is the taste of my ass..
The smell is strong too, like fermented coffee..
Mom's- Mom's mouth is so
slippery and wet, it feels great!
The toppings on this cock, it's so delicious..
Mom- Mom, it's.. it's gonna come again!
It's gonna ejaculate, it's gonna come..
Let it out.. it's alright, Noriko.. In Mommy's mouth..
Noriko's smelly and sticky cum.. a lot.. let out a lot!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Noriko, your cock is all clean now..
But, it looks like it hasn't calmed down yet..
Noriko, I'll let you experience my
front hole now... Here, come.. Noriko..
Mom.
Noriko.. your cock is coming in.. it's coming!
Mom, it feels so good.. this is Mom's insides..
The place I was born from..
That's right.. this is where you were born from..
Mommy's happy that you've come back here..
Mom!
Noriko, you're such a sweet child..
You won't climb the ladder of adulthood until your virginity's given away..
Come, let's give Noriko her adult ceremony..
Congratulations, Noriko! You've joined us in adulthood..
Here, Noriko.. try moving..
You too, Susumu-kun..
No, wait.. Susumu-chan, your cock feels good..
Your thick thing is reaching
deep in me.. and Mom's insides are..
So hot and wet.. it feels great!!
Right now, Noriko, your cock is feeling the same thing Susumu's having..
And your pussy is feeling the same thing mine is..
I'm so jealous, so envious..
Mom, again.. I'm gonna come again!
Come, Noriko!
With both the pleasure of man and woman come! Come!
Mom! Susumu-chan!
I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come!
I'm coming!
Oh, Susumu.. you're late..
Oh this? I got it from the supermarket on the way home since it was cheap..
Yes, this octopus is fresh..  you can tell by it's color..
A very good color..
The octopus is- no!
No! No!
My breasts are sensitive! Stop! No!
My nipples are being sucked!
No, don't pull my nipple.
No, wait..
The legs are.. rubbing my G-spot!
It's sliding into my asshole too!
So rough, it's too much!
Yet.. I'm gonna cum.. No, no..
I can't hold it anymore..
I can't bear it anymore! No!
I'm coming! I'm coming! No! I'm gonna come!
So that's how it is, even you're a sham..
Looks like I'll create a paradise..
Translator:
BlessedR
Raw Provider:
Mydoom
Timer:
SatsujinShinzou
Typesetting:
Fukkii
Encoder:
TLC/Editor:
Alist1
www.Xfap-Fansubs.co.cc
irc.rizon.net #xfap