It happened one day during class.
Our Health teacher, Akira-sensei said something strange.
It looks like you all get sleepy just around the fifth period.
How about we all take a break and masturbate?
– Yay!
– Yeah!
Huh?
It's decided. Use the next fifteen
minutes to masturbate, okay?
I'll be joining all of you.
Se-Sensei! What are you doing?!
What? Masturbating in class is pretty normal, isn't it?
See? Everyone's doing it.
D-Doing it at school really gets me excited.
My nipples keep getting harder.
W-What? What's wrong with everyone?
Wh-Why don't you join in?
I-It's embarrassing, but it feels really good.
That's not good. N-Not following instructions and doing
your own thing is against school rules you know?
You're lying. I'm the class president, but
I've never heard of this rule before.
Everyone? You can be as loud as you want.
Be loud. Loud enough that you'll
turn the people around you on.
Just keep cumming as much as you want!
I'm starting to feel really good too.
Wow, I can't believe sensei is so into it.
She's letting everyone see her boobs and vagina.
Wh-What should I do?
I-I'm starting to feel kind of strange too!
That's right. Playing the good girl by yourself isn't fair.
You need to show your true self too!
There's no way something this illogical could be happening.
This has to be a dream.
I'm in some kind of horrible dream.
B-But since I'm in a dream, I can do bad things, right?
It's okay for me to feel good too, right?
The corner of the desk feels so good!
It's rubbing against my clitoris so hard!
No!
My hips are just moving on their own!
No! No!!
I might start doing this more often!
It's okay. It's fine.
Watch me. Watch me masturbate more!
I'm so turned on!
It's so hard and thick! I've never felt this before!
What should I do?
My pussy is going to break!
It smells so dirty. I'm getting so turned on...
I think I'm going to go crazy!
You can cum on me more if you want.
Use me to fap as much as you want!
Oh no, they're looking at me.
They're all looking at me while I'm masturbating!
It's so embarrassing and I can't help it, but...
I'm already so wet down there!
I never knew that dicks got that big.
They're so dirty looking.
They're all playing with their dicks
while looking at me masturbate.
No! Doing this in a classroom is wrong,
but... my hands just won't stop!
Masturbating like this feels really, really good!
No! I can't anymore!
I can't! My body's getting so hot, it's tingling!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!!
I'm going to cum too. It's fine. Cover me with it.
Defile my boobs and my pussy with your dirty semen!
Make me sticky!
We're all going to cum together, okay?
Your naughty self, your naked self...
release your inner self! Got it?
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm really cumming!!
Holy shit!
Oh, no! No! No! No!
No, don't look!
Don't watch me pee myself!
It's not stopping! It won't stop!!
Looks like she never realized even now.
Everyone in this class except for her is under my hypnosis.
Hypnosis Class room
~Turning All the Girls Into Sluts Before They Even Know It~
That's right. With this lighter, I can hypnotize
anyone whenever I want.
Okay, Inami-san.
Everything I'm about to do to you is just calisthenics.
Calis... thenics...
That's right. It's good for your body, so don't
disobey me no matter what I do, okay?
Okay. I'll do exactly as you say, Sumino-kun.
Okay, split into pairs and stretch.
Um, we're stretching, right?
We are. It's dangerous if you don't
loosen up your body first.
S-Sumino-kun?!
This seemed to be a little stiff, so
I'll put some extra effort in here.
P-Please do.
What's going on? I'm just stretching
out, but my body is getting so hot!
Not there! I feel so weak!
Inami-san, I think I'm kinda stiff too. Do
you think you could help me out?
Huh? But doing it right here is really embarrassing.
Inami-san, this is part of calisthenics.
Are you sure you shouldn't listen to what I tell you?
Y-You're right. It's not fair if I'm the
only one who gets loosened up.
I'm sorry. I'll do anything I can to help.
Good, then let's do this.
I-It hurts! It's going to rip!
Inami-san, you need to loosen up more
or you're going to hurt your body.
Stretch out on the mat.
O-Okay. I understand.
They can see all my embarrassing spots in this position!
It's so embarrassing!
Inami-san, you're already so wet down here!
No! Don't tell me that!
What should I do? My body feels
like it's floating! It feels so good!
My stomach... My stomach feels so hot!
It's making such lewd noises!
Wait, Sumino-kun!
I-If you keep being so rough...
You... You're gonna break me!
So, should I stop then?
No! Don't stop!
I want you to keep going like this!
You got it!
Inami-san, get ready! I'm gonna cum soon!
I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming!
It's so hot! It's pumping into me!
Oh, Inami-san, it looks like you're pretty stretched out now.
Y-Yes I am, sensei. I did my best.
During the morning, we had a surprise inspection.
And Sakura-san said the craziest thing.
Even if it's you, Daichi-kun, I'm not going to.
Huh, but this is an inspection. Do you have
something that's not allowed at school?
Hm, who knows.
If you're that hell bent on not showing me, then...
You leave me no choice.
Huh? That lighter...
Huh? W-What?
Oh, it's nothing.
Sakura-san, could you look at this for a second?
You can't disobey my orders, Sakura-san.
You need to do everything I say.
I understand...
You're being suspicious with the way you're
desperately trying to avoid the inspection.
I think I'll need to conduct a full body check on you.
F-Full body check...
Come on. Spread your legs wider.
Hey, Daichi-kun, do I really have to?
Yeah, you do. This is an order.
A-Alright.
It's embarrassing, so please don't look too much.
Y-You're going to look inside too?
Yeah, it's an inspection.
Why? He's just inspecting me, but my body
is getting so hot just from his gaze!
Are you hiding something in here?
Th-There's no way that I am!
Come on! Relax a bit.
N-No! Why are you moving your finger?
Lots of dirty liquids are flowing out for some reason.
Are you sure that there's nothing in here?
No! There's really nothing in there!
I wouldn't lie!
I need to thoroughly check the places
that I can't see, with my hand.
You've checked enough, haven't you?!
S-Stop!
Huh? This spot is getting kinda hard.
Maybe you are hiding something.
No! Not there!
No! I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Excuse me, Sakura-san. I'm thinking about inspecting
a little bit deeper. Do you mind?
W-What? He's not done yet?
More! Squeeze me tighter!
No! Stop!
Not my boobs!
I just came so I'm really sensitive!
No! I can't stop my voice from coming out!
I'm knocking against the deepest part of you, Sakura-san.
This is really suspicious.
There's nothing in there!
Don't do it so hard like that!
Don't be so hard on my pussy...
Does having a full body check really
feel that good, Sakura-san?!
No! It doesn't!
Stop already!
Please let me go!
Sorry, just hang on a little longer, I'm almost done.
You can say that, but I...
I'm... I'm already about to cum!
I'm cumming!!
I might've gone a little bit overboard.
But seriously, why was she so against the inspection?
Huh? This is the same as mine!
What is this?
What's going on?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч