Love Triangle
Let's settle this with sex then.
J-Just what I wanted to do.
What in the world am I doing?
I'm still a virgin, and here l am to trying to have sex with Suzumu.
But, I'll lose if I don't.
Shall I go first then?
Fi-Fine.
I can handle that kind of handicap.
That was close.
It's my first time, so I actually have no idea what to do.
It's in.
So a pussy can really take such a large cock in.
Suzumu's penis is inside Yuuki-chan s pussy.
Yes.
Your cock feels good, Suzumu.
Yuuki, your pussy feels great too.
Suzumu...
Please, do it to me too Suzumu!
You'll have to wait for your turn next.
I want to do it right now!
You're such a spoiled girl.
Then why don't you show me how much you want it by pleading.
You don't want to have sex?
F-Fine then!
Please have sex with me.
I want your cock Suzumu.
I'm going to give you my virginity.
I want to make you feel good with my virgin pussy.
Please thrust it inside me.
Rie, So you're still a virgin?
It'd be a waste if we just let it drip like that.
Yuuki, sorry but could you switch with her for a bit?
I guess it can't be helped.
But only for today.
Starting tomorrow you'll fight me equally as a non virgin.
Th-Thank you.
Here...
It... it hurts!
You were so determined to do it during
club practice, but it still won't open up?
Your hymen Is tougher than I thought.
Wanna switch back then?
Suzumu's cock is big, so it's not really for virgins.
I'm fine!
I-It hurts!
If you don't move, Suzumu won't feel pleasure from it.
I know!
As expected from a virgin pussy, it's really tight.
It really feels good Rie.
Suzumu...
I'll do this as well, Suzumu.
I'm about to cum.
I haven't taken any contraceptives!
I want to cum inside you Rie.
It's okay.
I'll let you cum inside.
Rie, here I go!
So this is how it feels to be cummed inside of...
This pleasant feeling from sex is great.
My turn now.
We've always ended it with a draw,
but I'm going to win this time around.
You may be my best friend,
but I'm not about to hand over Suzumu to you.
Now, which of us will you choose?