W-Wait, Kaname-san. We shouldn't be doing this here.
What's the problem?
We're engaged, aren't we?
I just wanted to see you so bad, Akira.
Oh my. You're not usually the type of guy to say that.
Wait! Are we really gonna do this here?
A student could walk in on us.
Sorry, but I can't wait any longer.
I'll make it quick.
Geez, fine.
But just make sure you keep the volume down, please.
It's coming inside me!
It just slid in!
Your pussy is drenched in your dirty juices.
B-But, how can't I be turned on right now?
No! I can't hold my moans back!
For whatever reason... you're more
sensitive than usual today.
What's gotten into him today? He's much
more aggressive than he usually is.
He's never this forceful. What should I do? I'm so turned on!
S-Stop, Kaname-san. Don't be mean!
Sensei, what's the matter?
Does it really feel that good?
W-Wait, Sumino-kun?!
Why...
It's been me the whole time.
Stop moving!
Wh-Why are you doing this?!
You're the one who said I could, sensei.
Don't you remember?
N-No. Th-That has to be some kind of mistake.
Hurry up and take it out of me. Take it out!
You're so stubborn, sensei.
You're actually enjoying this, aren't you?
D-Don't make things up!
There's no way I'd get pleasure from
a student having their way with me!
N-No! I know this isn't right, but my body won't
listen. W-Why won't it listen to me?!
N-No! Not there!
S-Stop that this instant!
Stop!
Your pussy is even wetter than before now!
Feeling pleasure from pain? You're
one hell of a pervert, sensei.
No! I'm not!
Please let me go!
If this keeps going, I'm gonna... I'm...
Your pussy just got so tight right now!
I knew it. You're sexually frustrated, aren't you?
No! I'm not...
No! No! I'm gonna cum!
You're gonna make me cum!
I'm gonna cum from my student's dick!
That's good, sensei.
I'm about ready to cum too!
No, please! Anything but that!
Not inside! Please no!
No! Don't!
Don't! Don't!!
It's twitching! I can feel my cum being sucked out of me!
No! My fiance hasn't even came inside me yet.
Don't worry sensei. Could you look here for me please?
You're going to faint and then when you wake up,
you'll forget everything that just happened here.
E-Everything? Forget?
Exactly. Everything was just a dream. Do you understand?
Y-Yes, I understand...
Hypnosis Class room
~Getting All the Girls in My Class Pregnant Before They Even Know it~
With this lighter, I can hypnotize anyone to have
sex with me whenever and wherever I want.
For example...
Okay everyone, I want you all to look closely at this flame.
After you're done cleaning the classroom, you need to
get naked and clean the dicks of the guys here too.
I need to clean the dick...
Yes, exactly. And you have to use your tits and mouth.
Use our tits and mouths...
That's what we need to do, right?
S-So, do we really have to do... this?
Of course. If you don't hurry up,
cleaning time is gonna run out.
That makes sense. This is part of cleaning
after all. We have to do it right.
Th-This is really big.
And there's also some kind of dirty smell coming from it.
Can't you keep it still?
Should I be licking all of it?
I feel like it's getting wet by itself though.
Y-Yeah, keep that up!
What's going on? This is just cleaning.
Why am I getting so aroused?
My body is getting so hot. What's wrong with me?
What is this? Something weird came out!
As class rep, you gotta clean up this mess.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean? Seriously...
Okay then, how about Inami-san takes over from here?
Okay, I'll do it.
So I just have to lick this, right?
Hm, let me think. How about you press it in between
your tits and then squeeze the rest of the juices out?
Press it in between, rub them, and then squeeze it?
Like this?
Y-Yeah. Just like that.
There's juice coming out from the tip.
I need to clean it up!
I-Inami-san, that feels really good!
Why would it feel good for you when I clean this?
U-Uh, you know. Doesn't it feel good
when something gets cleaned?
This is amazing. It just keeps twitching
and I think it's getting even bigger!
Your nipples are pretty hard too, Inami-san.
There's something wrong with me.
I'm just cleaning, but I'm somehow getting really turned on.
What should I do? I can't stop it!
S-Sorry, I came again.
Okay, I'm next, right?
S-Sakura-san?! W-Wait...
O-Oh my god...
I think the juices have already been sucked out by them.
All that's left is to suck it to make it clean.
So intense!
I don't know what's going on.
When I watched them clean this, I just
wanted to suck it so badly! So badly!
My body just got so hot and turned on.
I never thought you'd be this dirty of a girl, Sakura-san!
I'm behaving lewdly. I'm getting homy and losing my mind!
I'm just cleaning though. What's going on?!
S-Sakura-san, if you keep doing it
like that, I'm gonna cum again!
That's fine. This time when you cum,
I'll take all of it in my mouth.
Don't hold back. Give me everything you have!
I'm cumming!
S-Sakura-san?
It's all clean now, right?
What's the matter, Daichi-kun?
O-Oh, uh, nothing.
There was something that was bothering
me about Sakura-san.
Why does she have the same kind of lighter that I have?
And why's she keeping it a secret?
I could ask her under hypnosis, but
I feel like that wouldn't be right.
Daichi-kun? Do you have a minute?
Huh?
Sakura-san?
Did you notice?
About my lighter that is.
Huh? O-Oh, no, I...
Here's not a good place to talk. Let's go somewhere else.
So, the one who gave that lighter to you was actually me.
Huh?! That can't be true! After all, this lighter is from...
Huh? Wait, how did I get it?
I can't remember. Why?!
That's because I erased your memories with hypnosis.
You did?!
You kept pulling pranks on all the girls, so I tried to make
you forget all of that with hypnosis, but I messed up.
Oh, so that's what happened?
I tried to get you back to normal multiple
times, but it's never gone right.
I'm really sorry, Daichi-kun.
Sakura-san?
I came here today to atone for what I did to you.
Huh?
It's fine. Put me under your hypnosis.
You want to do dirty things to me, don't you?
Huh?!
I don't mind whatever you want to do to me.
You can do whatever you want to me.
Th-Then I want to do this with the way you are right now.
I want to do this with the way you usually
are, not the way you are under hypnosis.
I-Is that okay?
That's fine. I'll make you feel really good today, Daichi-kun.
Wa... S-Sakura-san? You don't have to go this far...
It's fine. I'll do anything for you if it makes you happy.
So...
Sakura-san! Th-That's not clean!
But it's part of you. It's fine.
I want you to show me all of your dirty places.
This feels so strange.
I feel aroused?
His asshole is twitching. It's so cute!
S-Sakura-san, not inside...
His dick is getting hot and there's
so much liquid flowing from it.
I-I'm gonna cum!
That means it feels good, doesn't it?
That's good. Don't hold back and
cum to your heart's content!
This is amazing. This is your licentious
liquid. It has such a dirty smell.
Sakura-san, I...
I know.
Let's both feel good together next.
You're a hot, wet mess down here too, Sakura-san.
Did you get turned on from licking my asshole?
Don't say that! Can you blame me? I couldn't resist!
Just by imagining this huge thing
going inside me, I couldn't even...
Sakura-san, are you okay?
Did you just cum?
S-Sorry.
I'm fine, so just move however you want, Daichi-kun.
I want you to make me feel you more.
Got it.
If it ever becomes too much for you, tell me, okay?
So deep!
Your hot thing is in my stomach!
It's pushing inside it!
Your insides just feel so good, I can't help myself!
W-Wait! If you rub my boobs at the same time, I...
No, not there! I won't be able to stop moaning!
That's fine. Moan more for me.
I wanna hear your moans, Sakura-san!
This is so embarrassing!
No!
I just came, so I'm still really sensitive...
No! No!!
Sakura-san, if you keep squeezing
that tight, I'm gonna... Again...
I'm sorry! I can't stop!
Your dick just feels too good, Daichi-kun!
I'm getting more and more lewd!
But if I cum too much inside you...
Oh my god, your dick is getting bigger and twitching again!
– I've never felt this way before!
– I'm about to cum!
Okay, do it. Cum!
I don't care what you do to me.
More! Move more!
Mess me up!
Sakura-san!
P-Please... Together! Do it together!
It's coming! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
So, can you hear anything?
Yeah, he's thrashing around in there.
Maybe he's surprised that his mother is so dirty.
Really? I should be saying that to you.
I knew about your sexual disposition to a certain extent,
but I never expected you to get
every girl in our class pregnant.
U-Uh, well, you know, I just get turned on more
than usual by having sex with hypnosis...
Then how about I put you under
my hypnosis again some time?
Huh?!
Did you forget?
I know how to use hypnosis too.
A-Are you serious? Are you actually angry at me right now?
Don't worry. No matter how much of a
pervert you are, I'll stay by your side.
I love you.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
encoder: nino
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч