The haughty blonde haired rich girl: Aiba Ruka
A beautiful girl with amazing grades and the luck of being the daughter of a wealthy family. She has a very straight forward and fastidious persoality which makes it hard for guys to even approach her. She carries a strong pride for her family and does her utmost to not bring any shame to it. Her family's influence and fame are especially known within the school. She begins to look down on Yukimasa, who despite being the son of the family who owns the land, exerts no authority and carries no ambition. Because of the way she treats him, the other people in the school naturally begin to treat him poorly as well.
The childhood friend, drifting through life: Ishidou Suzune
Because both her parents and Yukimasa's parents are friends, they've been together since a young age. However, because of the sour attitude that Ruka takes towards Yukimasa, she begins to follow Ruka's orders and ignore all of Yukimasa's glances towards her, looking for help. She turns the other way and looks down on Yukimasa together with her other friends.
The insular son of a large land owner: Domyouji Yukimasa
The insular son of a big family, though he makes it a point to not stand out. But that attitude of his becomes an outlet for stress relief. Ultimately, his so-called classmates and friends just end up using him as their own personal wallet. But it's not as if he didn't draw the line and refuse outright. He was being strung along. Ruka, who saw this all unfold became incredibly annoyed seeing him just take this and had some strong words for him.
Ruka was a beautiful girl who had worked hard to make sure that she would cause no shame to her family name.
As a daughter of the Aiba family, seeing the son of the prestigious Domyouji being passed around and used as everyone's wallet, struck a nerve with her. She then gave him a piece of her mind... And then the on person that Yukimasa would talk with, his childhood friend, Suzune, began to distance herself from Yukimasa because of Ruka. Even when he looked to her for help, she just ignored him...
Yukimasa went through those days of torment until one day he received an email. The contents of the email contained a download to a certain app. The nature of that app? It was able to make one's deepest, most hidden, and twisted fantasies a reality...
Hypnosis Academy
The Incontinent Beginning of Embarrassment and Swelling
Out of my way.
I'm the daughter of the well-renowned Aiba family
and you're just a defective product of the Domyouji family.
Are you not embarrassed with that face of yours?
Good grief,
you're pathetic.
You have it rough, Suzune-san.
My deepest condolences that you
have him as a childhood friend.
It's me not to say anything, right?
Suzune-chan?
Uh... What's up?
W-Wanna go home together?
Sure.
Sure is hot.
You're not too sweaty, are you?
I think you'd cool down a bit if you took off your panties.
Yeah, you're right.
This good?
Listen to every order I give without question.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Why not just go right here?
Oh, yeah. Good point.
He's watching me pee...
Better?
I feel so relieved now. It wasn't that bad at all.
Okay, well, I need to be somewhere.
H-Huh?
What am I doing here?
forgets everything.
What's going on?
Aren't you going inside, Ruka-sama?
You're Aiba-san, right?
Suzune-san, what's going on he...
Suzune-san?
Anyone would be surprised if saw
their friend suddenly get pregnant.
Y-You!
Wait! You can tell?
Of course. You're like a completely different person.
Rio, you too?
I guess you're doing all kinds
of dirty things when no one's looking.
It's inconceivable that I would ever
participate in such inappropriate activities!
In the first place, there's no way that...
You...
Noticed?
Rio?
Yeah.
Rio, what are you doing?!
It's embarrassing playing with my pussy
in front of you, Ruka-sama, but...
It feels so good!
Using you to masturbate really turns me on!
Watch me, Ruka-sama!
My pussy's dripping wet!
Ruka-sama!
So good! Ruka-sama, I...
I can't move my body!
It's so good!
Rio's making a face like that?
There's no doubt...
Hypnosis?!
Why?!
You thought I'd just forgive and forget the abuse
from the rich girl, and my childhood friend
who just watched it all idly?
All you had to do was speak up!
What does this accomplish?!
I'm going to teach you how the people beneath you feel.
What are you planning on having us do, you deviant?!
Move!
Don't be in such a rush.
Doumyouji-kun, your dick is so big and hard... it's amazing!
He's making her act like that!
It's okay.
Please give me a reward... give me your cum in my mouth!
She's drinking it!
Rio's making such an indecent face
while riding that guy's thing!
A reward...
This position...
My body's not listening to me! I can't stop!
P-Please stop this, Yukimasa-kun.
I'm sorry for everything!
Forgive me!
As always, you just go with the flow.
You couldn't care less about anyone else but yourself.
Are you asking me to do Aiba-san first?
No! That's not what I...
Tell me what you really want.
I don't think anything of this rich slut who
throws around her family's influence like it's nothing!
Huh? What did I... Why?!
That's exactly who you are, Suzune-chan.
That huge thing is going inside her!
It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun, it hurts! It hurts!
You're next, Aiba-san.
No! No way!
Stop! Please, it hurts!
Yeah, you're not wet, so I guess it does.
Right?
It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun's coming inside me!
It hurts...
Stop!
It hurts!
So happy that you're crying?
That gargantuan thing is violently...
This can't be real!
He's going to do that to me too?
It hurts!
No! I mustn't be frightened!
He's just moving it in and out, that's it!
No...
No, stop! It hurts!
Please, stop!
Fine. I'll finish things off
by leaving you with a nice creampie.
No!
You really wanted it that bad?
I don't want it! No!
Pregnant...
You're going to get me pregnant! No!
Stop!
Does he really plan on finishing inside her?
He knows he's going to get her pregnant,
but he's still going?
No! No! No!
No! No!
No way!
This can't be real!
It's coming out!
It's coming out inside me!
Wait! Stop!
I won't forgive you for this!
I can't see!
Take a good look, Suzune-chan.
Yukimasa-kun's thing is...
And there goes Aiba-san's virginity.
His thing, it's...
It hurts!
What is this thing?!
It's sliding inside her.
You can even see the blood!
What's going on?! It hurts! It hurts!!
It's too big!
It's gonna tear!
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop moving!
His vile dick is moving inside me!
Is this too much even for you, Aiba-san?
Even if you do this to me, I won't break!
I'd expect nothing less, Aiba-san.
Hang in there.
Hurry up... end already!
Just cum!
Your body's saying that
it's just getting started though.
What are you saying?!
Why... would I...
What's happening?
This can't be! Is this...
How can my breasts be making...
So, you're actually turned on?
Screw you!
This is painful!
I feel no pleasure at all from this!
Your hypnosis is making me...
At least your body's honest.
No! Stop!
Not inside!
I don't want a baby!
Stop!
No! No!
No! This can't be happening!
The most vile man on the planet's
semen is pouring inside me!
I'm really going to get pregnant!
Aiba-san's getting filled to the brim, just like I was!
No! No!
Not bad, Suzune-chan.
I am going to make you pay for this, you lowlife!
You're going to do it inside me again?!
Stop!
Suck it.
No!
Perfect fit. You're good at this
even though this is your first time.
It's fine. Drink it, okay?
I don't want to lick this disgusting thing!
But I can't stop!
Use those needlessly large tits of yours.
You're fast at adapting.
You're the princess of blowjobs.
Shut up!
This is disgusting, you lowlife degenerate!
I'll never forgive you!
I think this princess needs a reward.
Wait, he doesn't mean to...
No! My hips are moving by themselves!
Are you planning on cumming inside me again?!
Yeah, your body seems to want it.
That's not...
Just a little more!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч