First and foremost... I, Tanaka Hajime,
am a Sex Counselor appointed by the government.
Next... Before a couple engages in
things like kissing and having sex,
they have to undergo a counseling
from the sex counselor first.
Having sexual intercourse with the sex counselor
is nothing else but guidance.
You won't be cheating even if you
have sex with the sex counselor.
You won't be losing your virginity from it.
All of you girls, worry not and
entrust your bodies unto me.
This is all for the sake of your lovers, alright?
And lastly...
Everything that the sex counselor says is correct.
The hypnosis is now completed.
Saimin Seishidou
Hypnosis Sex Guidance
#1    The Case of Obata Yui
Yui's Room
I'm kind of nervous.
So, this is going to be filmed...
P-Please take care of us, Tanaka-kun.
Umm, well...
2nd Year / Class B
Girls Basketball Club
Obata Yui
2nd Year / Class B
Girls Basketball Club
Obata Yui
I think it's alright if we take things slowly,
but Daiki said that he wants to do it, so...
The girl that I love is now my girlfriend.
2nd Year / Class D
Track and Field Club
Tachibana Daiki
2nd Year / Class D
Track and Field Club
Tachibana Daiki
Of course, I'd want to hurry and
kiss and have sex with her.
I'm an unruly girl...
I really don't have sex appeal...
You see, that's why...
I want to give my first to Daiki properly.
I want him to enjoy it.
Oh, gosh!
This is so embarrassing!
Okay then, should we get started
with the fundamentals?
You're doing great, Obata-san.
Shall we try wrapping our tongues
together more lewdly?
Y-Yui...
I-I wonder if I'm doing okay...
I-I'm not really sure...
Okay, then...
I don't think that anyone would enjoy
massaging the breasts of someone like me...
That's not true...
Any men who'll grope these
cute tits would be glad!
W-Whoa...
H-He's groping me in such a lewd way!
H-Hey! Don't stare at it too much!
Daiki, you perv!
Th-This is counseling, so it would
be all for nothing if I don't watch.
T-Tanaka-kun?!
Umm, my tits are showing...
It's just as your boyfriend said.
This is counseling so we have
to let him watch properly.
B-But this is embarrassing.
Just bear with it.
W-Wow...
Listen, Tachibana-kun.
It'll hurt her if you squeeze them too much.
You have to gently massage them like this.
He's watching me... I'm being watched right now!
You also have to stimulate her nipples
by pinching them like this.
Then, can you try spreading them wide open?
I-Is this enough?
No, it isn't! I won't be able to
see them properly like that.
No...
W-Wait!
I'm not yet mentally prepared...
It's plump and puffing out, it looks
like a very delicious pussy.
I'm about to penetrate it, so we have
to properly loosen it up first, okay?
Huh?
No, this can't be! No way!
W-Wait! Time out!
Tanaka-kun, wait! I-I don't want this!
It's a little salty... This is how your pee tastes, huh?
N-No way, that's...
Come on, you have to relax your body.
Just leave it all to my tongue!
O-Okay...
Do you feel good here? Where does it feel best?
Th-There... Right here!
That went on for about thirty minutes...
Tanaka-kun's tongue has me totally engrossed.
Obata-san, your hymen is sopping wet!
It's twitching close and open, inviting
a man inside! Oh, how lewd...
Obata-san, this might hurt a little...
But you have to endure it
for your boyfriend's sake.
Okay, umm...
Put it in slowly, okay?
Tachibana-kun...
You should fap imagining how
your girlfriend's hole feels.
It is a simulation in preparation
for the actual deed!
Yes... I understand...
Daiki is stroking his dick.
He's looking on my bare-naked
body with admiration!
No matter how many times I do it,
this moment sure is the best part!
I-It's going inside...
D-Daiki, my hymen is getting torn...
Yui, the tip is already inside. Do your best!
I-It hurts!
D-Daiki...
I will take advantage of their mutual love,
and have the most precious moment of this happy couple
defiled!
The feeling of conquest is so arousing
that it drowns my brain with endorphin!
W-Wow!
Your hot and hard thing is deep inside...
I-It's reaching up to my deepest parts!
I-It's that deep?
Obata-san, here I go!
Ouch! It hurts, Tanaka-kun!
W-Wait, I can't! This is too much for me!
Huh, that's weird...
My cock feels good, right?
Look, the pain is gradually fading away.
This incredible pleasure is nothing
like you ever felt before, right?
H-Huh? What's this?
The pain... The pain is gone.
Th-This can't be!
That's great! You're now feeling good, huh?
N-No way!
Sex... Sex feels like this...
No... Wh-Why?
Isn't this nice?
Feel my cock even more, Obata-san!
T-Tanaka-kun! It's amazing!
Your dick is amazing!
I-I feel like I'm going crazy already!
Y-Yui...
Are you listening, Tachibana-kun?
Making the girl feel good is important on sex.
You should first try some variations like this
to find your girlfriend's weak spot!
He can see it all...
Daiki can see all of my embarrassing parts!
No way, what should I do?
My body feels so hot!
No... T-Tanaka-kun!
This is bad! No!
When you found her weak spot,
you should aim and tease it with full intensity!
It's hitting me...
The tip of your dick is hitting deep!
It's hitting deep inside me!
That's the spot! That's where
I'll give you a creampie in the end.
I'll teach you how to impregnate a woman, okay?
Huh? I-Inside... No way...
I'll end up having a baby!
What are you talking about?
This is sexual guidance. It's just a practice.
No matter how many times you get
creampied, this isn't actual sex.
This can't get you pregnant, right?
I-I see! That's how it works, huh?
I'll be fine even if you come inside me.
Me too...
It should be okay for me come, right?
Of course, it is!
This might be a practice, but it'll all be
for nothing unless we do it seriously!
Your dick is twitching, it's getting hot!
Coming... It's coming out!
Coming... I'm coming...
I'm gonna come!
That felt so good!
You'll be able to do anything you wish on this pussy...
I really envy you, Tachibana-kun!
Oh... Is that so?
How does your first sex guidance feel, Obata-san?
N-No way, this is embarrassing!
Don't look at my face right now!
We'll have your private counseling
starting next week.
Maybe I should have you self-study until then.
S-Self-study?
I-I'm filming myself while masturbating...
No way, this is so embarrassing!
I'm sure that Tanaka-kun will be watching this.
Huh?!
Record myself masturbating?
I want to monitor your erogenous zones
as a part of your counseling.
O-Oh...
I-I see...
I'll give you videos about other stuff
as teaching materials for your self-study,
so make sure to learn about them.
1st Year / Class E / Tea Ceremony Club
Sakagami Akeno
T-Tanaka-senpai!
I'm feeling weird!
E-Even though it's my first time
to do something like this,
I'm feeling good! It feels so good!
When their sensitivity is adjusted by hypnosis,
any girl will become like this!
Hey, no way! Don't look at me, Tomo-kun!
No way, this is embarrassing!
2nd Year / Class D / Track and Field Club
Fujima Nagisa
Yes, yes... Fujima-san, you're good at this!
You'll be well-liked when you
are proactive in our counseling.
H-hey, am I doing good?
I can go even harder than this!
Yes, just as I expected from
a track and field club member!
Thank you.
I might really be good at this!
2nd Year / Class B / Girls Basketball Club
Shinohara Misaki
Hey, hey! You're trying to escape again!
Make sure to hold her down, senpai!
Wait... Wait, wait, wait!
I'm begging you, today's a risky day!
N-No way, no way!
To make the moment when senpai
will be using this go smoothly,
I'll loosen it up and stretch it
wide until its baggy enough.
N-No more...
You can't, you can't!
You can't—!
No way! I already came a lot earlier,
but I'm so drenched right now!
I-I never felt this good from masturbating before...
So, why? Why am I now like this?
This is bad! My fingers are not enough!
Dick... I want Tanaka-kun's dick...
I want it! I can't take it anymore!
Huh?!
So, you're having another sex guidance today...
Yes, I'm just about to go to Tanaka-kun's house.
I'm sorry, Daiki.
Can you go home alone for today as well?
Aren't you doing nothing but that lately?
Why are you getting angry?
It can't be helped, right?
I've been doing this for you, Daiki.
Th-That might be the case, but...
Alright, then...
I'm making Tanaka-kun wait,
so see you tomorrow!
How is it, Tanaka-kun?
I wonder if you're feeling good...
You're the best, Obata-san!
You're very skillful at this now.
At this rate, you'll be done
with your counseling soon.
Umm, but...
I still have things that I don't fully understand yet.
Huh?
Tanaka-kun, you see...
It would be great if you still
have some time right now...
I wonder if it's alright to extend
my counseling for a bit longer...
I still have to provide counseling to others...
Just one more round.
Okay!
I'm sorry about this and thank you!
Saimin Seishidou
Hypnosis Sex Guidance
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization