Conceited Blonde Lady: Aiba Ruka
She's a daughter from a well-off household,
both a beauty and of academic excellence.
As a girl with a candid and fastidious disposition,
males find her difficult to approach, seeing her
as a "beauty out of anyone's league".
Possessing a great pride of her heritage, she strives be someone
that will live up to its name and not bring embarrassment on it.
This is even apparent with all the fame and clout she has in school.
She shows contempt on Yukimasa, who lacks both dignity
and ambition despite being a son of a wealthy landlord.
And as a result, everyone around Yukimasa
followed suit and shunned him as well.
Socially Adept Childhood Friend: Isurugi Suzune
Both of their parents were old friends, and as a result she and Yukimasa
became friends that got along together since their childhood.
But now with Yukimasa being shunned and isolated, she quickly followed suit
and abandoned him like a stranger to become one of Ruka's lackeys.
And to imitate Ruka, she turned a blind eye
to Yukimasa, who was hoping for her help.
Each of Yukimasa's friends followed suit
as well and started shunning him.
Introvert Son of a Great Landlord: Doumyouji Yukimasa
Despite his grandiose lineage, Yukimasa is asocial
and is someone who doesn't stand out much.
That social standing brings stress on him and to deal with it,
he started to hang out with his classmates.
These 'friends' treat him more of a 'walking purse'
taking advantage of him, but he just ended up getting
dragged along since he couldn't upfront refuse them.
It is because of that personality of his that Yukimasa got quite harsh words and treatment from Ruka.
The beautiful girl who works hard to perfectly become someone who won't bring shame to her family's name (Aiba Ruka),
sees how the heir of the landlord that's even
more powerful than her family (Doumyouji Yukimasa),
looks miserable and is just letting himself be mistreated
like a 'walking purse' by their classmates, and is willfully going along with it,
is aggravated and harshly gave him a piece of her mind.
Or that should have been the case......
"Wh-What's the meaning of this..."
Ruka wanted to run away, but she can't move
her own body as she is lying on her back at the platform.
Her untainted body up until now is now stained with bodily secretions.
On top of her is the now stripped Suzune on her fours,
having her important place exposed right on in front of Ruka.
Furthermore, Yukimasa's voice echoed across the room
as he spitefully and obscenely ridiculed them.
"You need to realize firsthand how the oppressed ones feel."
With harsh words followed the sudden pain as Yukimasa's meat stick
forcibly thrust and pierced through her tightening lower lips.
The two both got harsh insults and ill treatment
from his revenge as he deflowered them.
Yukimasa moved as he wished
while humiliating both Ruka and Suzune,
amusing himself on the shame he put
for the two in public with no mercy.
Original Animation
sai
min
gaku
en
Hypnosis Academy
~Cheeky Lady Pissing with Force~
Last Time On Saimin O Gakuen......
Move out of the way!
For someone who's an heir of a great landowning family,
you look nothing close on how a Doumyouji should be.
Are you not ashamed of yourself
looking all like that? Jeez...
You look miserable.
It must be hard for you, Suzune-san,
considering how you have been
childhood friends with such a guy.
Isn't it hot today?
Are you not sweating, Suzune-chan?
It will feel cooler if you'll take your panties off.
Is this alright?
[Follow Yukimasa without question.]
I'm getting watched while peeing...
Rio, what on earth are you doing?!
I'm playing with my pussy in front of Ruka-sama...
This is so embarrassing, yet it feels amazing!
This position is—!
I don't want this, but my body won't listen to me!
That huge thing... is going inside!
I-It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun, it hurts! It hurts!
You're gonna be next, Aiba-san.
No... No, no!
Stop it, please! It hurts!
There's nothing I can do since you're not wet.
Right?
It hurts!
Yukimasa-kun is inside me!
Is it... This guy's—
I-It hurts! What is this? His thing is—!
What is this? It hurts, it hurts!
It's way too big!
You're tearing me apart!
It hurts, it hurts!
Stop moving!
No! No—!
No, no!
Stop!
No way, no way!
The semen of the worst man is pouring inside me!
I'll really get a baby from this!
Inside Aiba-san is... just like what happened to me...
N-No...
No... No—! No!
Nice job, Suzune-chan.
For sure... I'll make someone
as lowly as you regret this for sure!
Doing as you please... in such a place...
Ruka-san is looking good.
They should just get married already.
You heard them.
Didn't you make them to be like that?
What a pitiful recluse you are.
Though I never did anything to their bodies.
You're kidding yourself! My body became like this
because of you as well!
You shouldn't have mistaken about it.
Inside again...
Stop this! Stop!
Any more of this and...
There's so much of it again!
I'll really end up having a baby!
Wait! No, stop! I'm begging you!
No way, this can't be happening!
No—!
No way, why?!
Stop!
No—!
You don't look proud for being a pissing lady.
This much is nothing for me!
Let's have a P.E. class this time.
I'll be giving everyone a practical lesson.
It's just gonna be as stupid as yesterday,
making me do all that non-stop!
Messing around in this place...
Take note, this is what you call a "tsundere".
I had to teach everyone as precisely as I can.
It's Suzune-chan's turn for today.
N-No... No.
I'm begging you, Yukimasa-kun!
I can't take any more of this... No!
Our lesson for today is about blowjobs.
Why is my body moving on its own?
No...
Lick it.
Yukimasa-kun, spare me!
I'm begging you, any more of these
embarrassing things and I'll really...
No way... I don't want to...
Yukimasa-kun, I'm begging you!
There's no way that huge thing will fit her mouth!
But... Suzune-san's body is involuntarily...
Not everyone is able to do this. It's called a titfuck.
That's most likely what he uses...
No...
What a closet pervert.
You're good for a first-timer.
Good. Just drink it like that.
No...
No... I'm sorry!
I'm really begging you... Not this, Yukimasa-kun!
Spread it open so everyone can see.
This is embarrassing... No!
If I just can do something about that smartphone...
Alright then, pee.
Huh?!
I'm sorry, forgive me!
Please, Yukimasa-kun! Relieving myself in here is...
Unthinkable?
I'm sorry! I'll do it now, so...
No!
No! It's coming... out...
Getting aroused from this makes you an exhibitionist.
No...
No, you can't! Stop moving your hands, Yukimasa-kun!
Doesn't it feel best when everyone's watching,
Suzune-chan the exhibitionist?
That's... I'm...
It felt like having some sort of freedom, it's not that bad.
Wh-What is that... I'm...
No way...
You won't feel good unless you're being watched.
You're even dripping wet now.
No!
No, don't!
You can't do this!
Use sexual terms when you speak.
Okay!
No... your dick is stirring my pussy up!
That despicable man! He's doing it while
making Suzune-san utter such obscene words!
You're gonna be next so prepare yourself, Aiba-san.
What a jolly fellow you are.
You're not gonna make both me
and Suzune-san submit to you!
Aiba-san...
No...
I'm looking forward for it, Aiba-san!
It feels cramped... deep inside me...
Suzune-chan is going to be pregnant with this.
No way... No!
Yukimasa-kun...
This can't be real, I don't want this! No!
No!
No way, I'll get pregnant...
I'll have a baby... No way!
I-I won't do such a thing!
Stop joking! There's no way I'll lick—
My body moves on its own...
No! Why would I? In such a place!
No, I am...
No, let me go!
...not with this filthy thing!
Aiba-san, you're giving me a clean-up blowjob.
No! Why? Even though I never want to!
No way! I'll have to kiss this thing!
It got dirty earlier from that!
I don't want to lick such a filthy thing, and yet...
Stop!
Use those needlessly large tits of yours as well.
No... I'm rubbing my breasts on it!
No... I'm moving them!
Use your mouth as well.
I'll definitely get that thing...
It's has an unsightly shape as always!
He's making me suck this thing
while sliding between my tits!
You quickly got the hang of it.
You're a blowjob princess.
S-Shut up!
S-Such a disgusting thing...
Lowly pervert! I'll never ever forgive you!
Here's a reward for the princess.
This... Don't tell me I have to...
No!
Stop!
Let go of me!
My throat is getting filled with disgusting stuff!
I-I can't breathe!
It's hot, it stinks and it's disgusting!
It's disgusting!
No matter how much you do these,
I'll never ever submit to you!
Don't get so angry.
Y-You just came but you're already like that again?
Seeing a beautiful face like yours made me aroused.
Humiliating me like this... You are the worst!
Making me move by myself...
So you're feeling good too, Aiba-san.
You're the one who made me do!
This is against my will!
Is that really so?
The pain is fading away...
My body is starting to get used to
being spread wide down there!
You won't be able
to dominate me from just doing something like this!
When that time comes, you won't
be able to make that smug face.
You won't ever succeed!
I will prevail against the likes of you!
My hips are moving on their own. No—!
Are you planning to come inside me again?
You started to crave for me now. Right Aiba-san?
This... thing...
Just a little more... Just like this!
Are you planning to...
come again inside me?
It's pouring in—!
This is...
There's a lot flowing into me!
I'm getting filled inside!
I won't ever forgive you for doing this!
Ouch—!
Aiba-san, you're so rowdy!
Suzune-san!
Are you alright, Suzune-san?
Thank you, Aiba-san.
His smartphone is broken now
so we should be able to move again.
And if he finds us, we have things we can use here.
We should somehow be able to make an escape.
Yeah, that's right. I think so as well.
Aiba-san, where are you?
You're ignoring me... It can't be helped.
Suzune-chan, answer me.
Yes!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization