This is terrible...
I had my first time before you.
I guess it really is normal for the elder
sister to become a woman first.
This vibrator feels great.
Now that you've lost your virginity too,
you can freely rub these things inside you.
If I had known that it would feel this good,
then I would have realized that protecting
my virginity was foolish.
Manami-chan.
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to lend this to you after I cum, Sayuri-chan.
I'm cumming!
Sayuri-chan...
No...!
So you're saying,
that despite being twins,
there is some social complex stemming from the fact that,
the younger one performs better.
Is that right, Kirishima Manami-san?
Y-Yes.
But according to your health statistics,
there are some categories where you perform better.
It doesn't make me happy if my breasts are bigger.
Hers may be small, but they're well balanced.
Are there other things that you're worried about?
Umm, it's about that...
"That"?
About my genitals.
No need to be embarrassed to say "vagina".
I'm a doctor.
Okay.
It's about my vagina.
Its shape looks, well... weird.
Can you show it to me?
Huh?
In here?
I can't tell what's wrong if I can't see it.
Well that's true, but...
No need to be embarrassed to show it.
I'm a doctor.
Yes.
I still can't see it well.
Can you use your fingers to open it wider?
I understand.
Is this okay?
Hmm, I don't really see anything wrong with it.
But it looks like my clitoris is protruding
out more than it usually does.
It feels twitchy and hot, and looks more revealed.
I see no abnormalities in the size of the clitoris and lips though.
The color even looks healthy.
But I can't urinate properly.
I wonder how this compares to your younger sister's?
I haven't seen hers for a while.
Though we used to show it to each other a long time ago.
So I don't know.
I see.
Anyway, both you and your sister are still virgins, correct?
Y-Yes.
I think Sayuri-chan is still a virgin!
Then how about having sex to help
you overcome that social complex?
Huh?!
If you experience sex before she does,
then you'd be able to stand at a higher position than your sister.
I see.
Besides, by using sex,
you can also improve the form of your
vagina with your partner's penis.
I've yet to experience having a penis inside my vagina,
so that explains why its shape looks weird, right?
You got it girl.
Then I should lose my virginity as soon as possible then.
If you experience if first,
then perhaps your social complex would also be treated.
I guess you're right.
I think I'd be more confident with the fact that
I'm going to be an adult before Sayuri-chan.
Well I'm a doctor, you see.
Doctors are always right.
You sure can be proud of these great breasts though.
Guys look at them indecently during P.E.,
and Sayuri-chan even sometimes look
at them with worry on her face.
I see.
But their sensitivity is excellent.
Is that so?
Now, how about we check out your vagina next?
Okay.
Something's entering in there...!
It's coming out...!
So you came, eh?
I also felt it from here.
All that's left now is your virgin vagina,
and you're all set to be an adult.
Shall we get you to experience it first now?
Okay, Sensei.
Leave it all to me,
I'm a doctor.
I'm a specialist when it comes to opening girl's holes.
Yes, please open my virgin vagina up.
That big thing is going inside my vagina?
That's right.
Don't worry, you'll get used to it soon.
Here I go.
It hurts.
That's the pain that comes with becoming an adult.
So now I'm an adult... with this,
We're just getting started!
Ouch.
It hurts.
Sensei!
Sensei, let's stop this already!
Please pull it out!
It hurts!
It'll soon feel great.
It hurts.
What's... this?
It hurts?
It hurts, but...
It hurts, but it feels good.
It feels good to become an adult.
I never thought it could feel this good.
I'm feeling pleasures that my sister has yet to experience.
It feels so good, that I might just die.
Here we go!
I've become an adult... before Sayuri-chan.
Doing it just once doesn't make it
that different from being a virgin.
l-ls that so?
I'll take the responsibility of turning you into a fine adult,
so make sure to come to the infirmary every single day.
Okay.
Sayuri-chan, does it feel good?
Giving up already?
Then that means I've won.
That's just plain dirty.
You weren't planning on betting anything in the first place!
Stop making such false assumptions.
Now then Kurihara Chisato-kun.
You're going to play this penalty game as well.
I'm not about to submit to some cheater!
I like that strong attitude of yours.
And with that, let's change our plans a bit.
I'll personally give the penalty, without
using any hypnotic suggestions.
Chisato-chan, remove your uniform and come here.
Now, can you give me your virginity?
Oh? You don't intend to lubricate it first?
I want to finish this as soon as possible.
It hurts!
It's piercing me deep inside!
It's no use if you just insert it.
You have to make me cum.
This is boring.
Let me fondle your breasts.
I want it raw.
Here I come.
No!
It hurts.
Here it comes.
It's coming out!
Something hot is flowing inside me.
Okay.
Everyone, the banquet has just started.
From now on, this academy is mine!
Grade Murakoshi
Everyone, you all look quite healthy.
Yes!
Since then, Murakoshi started to gather
all the women that he laked,
and does indecent things to them while he gives his "class".
Everyone seems like they're under his hypnosis.
Somehow, only Manami-chan and I are left with
our minds and consciousness still intact.
Okay, Manami-san and Sayuri-san, please move forward.
Sa-Sayuri-chan.
Sayuri-san will be reciting a few words from the textbook.
S-Sensei, what about me?
You will be enacting what's in the book as if you are the character.
Okay.
Now then everyone, please take off your skirts and undies.
Huh?!
Why do we have to do that?
We can't start our lesson if you don't.
Here now, take it off already.
No...
I don't want this, but my body just...
As Manami wraps her arms tightly around him,
she loses herself, and starts moving her hips.
Stop!
I don't want this!
Stop this Sayuri-chan!
I'm sorry, but my mouth just....
Saliva then drips onto her lips, and with
their lips wrapped around each other,
they start kissing each other.
No...
No!
While Manami shoves her big butt...
Hey Sayuri-san.
Put more emotion into it as you read!
There are no feelings in your monotonous words.
Put my feelings into this?
And just how in the world would I do that?
Well...
Why don't you start masturbating!
What did you say?
That way, you'll "feel" it better, right?
You're literally naked down there already anyway.
That's just stupid.
Rub your clitoris more passionately!
You need to put your feelings into it!
Sayuri-san, continue reciting.
Manami is currently holding the penis inside her.
She is craving for the pleasure it gives her.
Her insides welcome it, as it rubs deep inside.
That's...
Observe the two, and then make your thoughts
and impressions about them.
Don't forget the importance of feeling it!
Okay!
No, please don't look.
Manami finally drowns in ecstasy, her mind barely holding on.
She was unable to control the sexual
pleasures escalating within her.
My mind can't think of anything anymore
other than this ecstatic pleasure.
Manami... oh no...
...opens her womb and pleads.
"Release lots of it inside me" she says.
That can't be...!
Release lots of it inside me.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Good work, now receive my reward.
As I expected,
both your orgasmic reactions happened at the same time.
Sayuri-chan...
Manami-chan...
Murakoshi-sensei's exciting three-part lesson isn't over yet!
Up next is P.E.!
Sayuri, pass it to me!
When the opposing team gains a point, each member
needs to raise their rotor setting by 1.
Now, if you don't want to feel hornier, you need to do better.
Even if you say that...
Hey, insert it in properly!
Yes!
If you lose, then it'll be your turn to receive penalty.
Okay then, let's begin our penalty cleaning shall we?
Okay.
Here, you need to clean my butt.
It feels great to have the gorgeous
council president do this for me.
Chisato-kun, you're already getting used to handling my penis.
Hey, dig your tongue deeper inside.
Here it comes!
And now, the awarding of graduating students,
will be done by representative Kirishima Sayuri.
Yes.
Oh no!
If you do it that intensely...
I'll give birth!
It's okay, isn't it?
You're graduating already.
Besides, it's about time already, right?
Let's have your baby get a taste of it too.
Okay, show everyone your graduation semen.
Sayuri-chan.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Congratulations.
After days and days of those continued obscene acts,
Manami-chan's mind finally lost it.
If I were to lose myself here, how much farther would we fall?
Wow, the graduation ceremony has just
turned into a birthing ceremony!
Everyone's looking at me giving birth,
and it's making me cum!