Translation: Snake | Timing, Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Well, let's have a showdown of sex then.
For sure!
What am I doing!?
I'm going to have sex with Susumu
even though I'm still a virgin!
but, if I don't, I'll lose the match...
May I go first?
S-Sure.
I'll give you that advantage.
Phew. It's my first time so I don't
really know what to do.
It went in...
So a pussy can really take in something so thick!
Susumu's penis is inside Yuuki-chan's pussy...
Yes! Your dick feels good, Susumu!
Yuuki's pussy feels good, too.
Susumu...
Pleasel Do me as well, Susumu!
Wait a bit for your turn.
I want to do it right now!
Rie is so self-indulgent...
Well, try pleasing me so I feel like having sex with you.
What?
Don't you want to have sex?
I get it.
Please have sex with me!
I want Susumu's penis!
I'll give you my virginity!
I'll make you feel good with my virgin pussy, so...
Shove a dick inside!
So Rie is a virgin...
Then it'd be bad if I make you wait too much...
Sorry Yuuki, but could you switch?
I guess it can't be helped.
But that's only for today, get it?
Tomorrow well be equal non-virgins.
Thanks.
Here...
Ow! It hurts!
Your hymen didn't break despite your
tough training in club activities,
I guess it must be thick.
Shall I switch back after all?
Susumu's penis is big so it's tough for virgins.
I-I'm fine!
Ow... It, it hurts!...
If you don't move, Susumu won't feel good.
I know that!
As expected from a virgin you're really tight...
It feels good, Rie!
Susumu...
I'll do it for you as well, Susumu.
I'm cumming soon...
We're not using any protection!
I want to cum inside Rie like this...
It's fine... I'll let you cum inside!
Rie, here it goes!
So this is what it feels like to have it ejaculate inside...
The pleasures of sex...
It's my turn next.
It's always been a tie, but I'll definitely win today!
Rie-chan you're my best friend, but
won't give Susumu up to you!
Well? Who will you start with?