Kuyomi...
Usuyomi...
Your cock's amazing, Jin!
It's totally wet with precum by now.
The tip is really important,
but we mustn't forget about the base and the sack either.
It's so hot and rock hard!
I want to play with it more!
You can cum whenever you want, I'll drink it all!
I got covered by so much hot sauce!
But look, it's still so vigorous.
It's great! Move faster! Violate me harder!
More! Give me more!
Turn me into an ugly mess!
My pussy's demanding more!
I want to cum! I'm gonna cum!
No more!
I'm cumming! I can't take any more!
Look! My asshole's wet as any girl's pussy, isn't it?
It feels even better than a pussy!
Use me any way you want!
Don't... do that...
Don't tease my cock...
I'll... end up spraying cum!
That's great! My ass feels great!
It feels so hot I'm melting!
Please, give me a lot!
Fill my perverted ass with your cum!
You're nearing the truth.
What?
But at the same time you're facing more danger too.
That's it.
What do you mean?
Let us reach our destination!
Interesting. I shall see that truth waiting for me.
Welcome to my labyrinth!
To you beginner molesters! In this world only the determined can survive.
Those lacking determination shall fall.
You're a great bitch
Don't...
Don't do that, milady...
This is your punishment, Rin.
You got on the last molester train,
but you let that man get away.
I'm terribly sorry!
Devil Hand, the legendary molester, whose real name is Takatori Jin.
You must catch him next time.
Do you understand?
Y-Yes...
Next time...
Lady Kanon, if you do it so hard, I'll...
I'll lose my grip if you rub so hard...
You're already dripping wet.
So lewd.
Even your nipples are rock hard.
Could it be you're already near the top?
Yes! I'm terribly sorry! I'm cumming!
I can't hold back!
Rin. When we cum, we cum together.
Come, rub me harder!
Lady Kanon! Lady Kanon!
Let's cum together!
I'm the only one who can make you feel this good.
I'll never let a man defile you.
Thank you very much...
Why is it? Lady Kanon loves me so much,
yet I can't get that man out of my head...
I'm terribly sorry, Lady Kanon, but I'm already...
You are the perfect wife and the ideal mother who supports her daughter in everything.
You have a very well balanced, lewd body too.
I lie every now and then, but I've never denied the charms of a woman.
You are shining with the power to charm men.
Don't... say weird stuff!
What would Arisa think if she realized you enjoy getting molested?
Don't feign ignorance, I've been watching.
You really do enjoy getting molested, don't you?
Stop! Don't say that!
I was so lonely!
I don't have that kind of a relationship with my husband, so... I...
Some lewd smell's reaching my nose from you.
The other passengers've noticed too.
Please let me go... I'm not like that...
I just...
Sayuri, your lewd pussy is already dripping wet.
Don't... Don't!
They'll hear... the lewd noises from my pussy!
Don't tease me anymore!
Please! I'm feeling so weird!
This is the end. Fall!
Sayuri, come with me.
I can show you delights you could never dream of.
Okay...
Boys, in today class...
I'll show you biology in action...
Teacher, can we take an active part too?
No, you must just watch!
Watch as I get fucked and learn from it!
It's in me now!
Look at that! He shoved it up her raw and rare!
You all have your cocks in your hands...
You can fap to me if you want!
Teacher, please tell us how it feels!
I'm hopeless with so many people watching. I can't hold back.
It's great! Amazing!
Can you all hear the noise of my pussy getting... spread?
Can you hear this lewd, splashing noise?
Let me give you some more fun, Kanade.
My nipples... are getting... torn off!
Teacher...
Don't worry.
Your teacher's a masochistic pervert.
But... I'm... not a pervert...
No!
I'm... feeling... weird...
Teacher, you're really enjoying this?
Yeah! This feels great!
I'm a pervert!
I enjoy it a lot if someone hurts me!
Damn, I'm about to cum...
You mustn't! You'll get punished if you cum before me!
Then cum quick, teacher!
I... not yet... I...
Amazing! So warm and sticky... It smells so manly...
Students, listen well.
If you want to participate in further biology classes, don't tell anyone about this.
Then next time you might get a chance to join too.
I could get used to doing this every day...
It feels great...
Who would subject themselves to molesters willingly?
It must be because I started cosplaying.
When people are taking pictures of me,
I end up thinking "what if they raped me like this",
and I just couldn't stop myself imagining it...
This's good... It's a lot better than groping myself.
It's like you've got electricity in your hands!
Concentrate on the nerves under my fingers.
You might be able to cum with your nipples.
Cum... with my nipples?
Okay! I wanna try that!
My boobs feel so hot!
Look! Everyone can see you in this embarrassing situation!
I'm making such a lewd face...
It's embarrassing, but it feels great too.
Great. Try cumming, Kaoru!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming with my nipples! I'm cumming!
Very well. If you remember how to do it, you'll be able to do it by yourself.
Hey, I'm feeling so hot down there... I can't take this anymore.
Please take me!
A thick cock is in me!
It's twisting my pussy around!
It's amazing!
You must be some crazy pervert to enjoy it this much on a train.
Yeah, I'm a pervert!
I'm so happy to get nailed on a train!
I'm a filthy pervert!
Look, people are watching you.
Oh no!
I'm getting even more turned on from people watching!
I can't stop!
Watch me more!
Then let them see all to the end!
Okay! Cum inside me! Inside!
I'm... cumming again!
Your semen's filling my womb!
Kaoru, would you cosplay again?
Sure, okay...
What event?
The last molester train is a mysterious train that operates after the last train.
Only men willing to molest women and invited women can board.
I'm cumming!
Teacher!
There's still more!
You boys are amazing!
You cummed so much already, yet you can still go on.
Teacher, can I cum on you too?
Please do! Cover me in it!
Please make me sticky with cum all over!
Amazing!
Teacher, I'm there agai--
More! I want more!
Please, give your teacher more!
Give me more semen! More!
Teacher, can I take your pussy too?
Yeah, my pussy's craving too...
It's waiting for your cocks to mess it up...
It's so tight... But it feels good!
I love how rough it feels!
Teacher, your pussy's so tight! I can't get enough of it!
They're rubbing...
The cocks in my ass and my pussy are rubbing...
Teacher, your asshole's gripping me so tight...
I'll make it even tighter then!
You can do whatever you want with my holes!
Then I'll make use of your mouth.
Whoa, your pussy's pulsing so hard!
I enjoy being treated harsh!
I'm so turned on by getting ravaged!
You're really a masochist, aren't you, teacher?
I'm sorry...
I'm acting all high and mighty over you guys,
but actually I'm a masochistic pervert!
I'm about to cum!
Me too! I'm cumming too!
Please, let's cum together!
Let's all cum together!
I never even dreamt of actually titty fucking you!
It's okay, enjoy yourselves!
You can cover my boobs in cum!
You're very tight too! It feels great!
My pussy's a mess just from your cock rubbing inside of it!
They're taking erotic photos of me...
They'll fap to me later...
Crap, I'll get turned on even more from imagining that!
Next start teasing your nipples for us!
But if I did that, who knows what'll happen...
I might end up cosplay-raped!
I'm so turned on I can't take it!
If you do it so rough, I'll end up cumming...
I can't stop anymore!
You can cum on me anytime if you want!
Show me how semen bursts out of your cocks!
I can't hold out for much longer either!
You can do it harder! You can do it rougher!
Mess me up!
I'm cumming too! I'm cumming!
Take lots of pictures!
Take pictures! More!
More! Don't hold back, it's fanservice time today!
Fill all my holes with your sticky semen!
How does it feel to get fucked in front of your daughter?
Don't say that, please!
Arisa, I'm sorry!
Please... Please don't look!
If you can't have sex with your husband, I'll fill that space.
Don't... Don't grope my tits so much!
My milk will spill...
I can't take anymore... Let me cum!
My pussy wants to cum so much!
Please...
Arisa, I'm sorry!
I got molested many times,
and he raped my pussy a lot too!
He made me cum!
Okay, then you can have some more.
Amazing!
I'm so happy... that your cock's messing me up...
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Don't play with that, it's dirty!
Don't! Not there!
Your ass is great too.
It'll be your first time this way, right?
No way! Wait!
It's amazing!
Why... Why does it...
Why does it feel this good?
My ass feels just as good as my pussy!
Now report your findings to your daughter!
Arisa, I'm sorry, but my asshole feels great!
I'm getting lots of cum into both my perverted pussy and asshole!
Very well, I'll grant that to you!
Give it to me!
Fill my ass with semen!
Watch, Arisa, I'm cumming with my ass!
I can't do this after all...
Please forgive me...
There's nothing to forgive.
You desire this!
They're... watching me in this embarrassing situation!
It's time for the show now!
We shall see your lewd body!
It hurts! Stop, it hurts!
Don't hurt me more!
Does it really just hurt?
You're mean...
That's... good...
Why would a feminist Train Guard Squad officer want to get molested like this?
Don't say it like that!
I just...
Try saying it!
Look over there!
You were recording this on video?!
That's not all of it.
We're streaming this video to the Train Guard Squad's headquarters.
I can't believe this...
Rin, my Rin, has fallen to molesters...
Ouch!
That's a nice voice.
Cry even louder so that Kanon could hear you too!
I'm terribly sorry, Lady Kanon,
but I'm... getting raped here...
It hurts! Stop!
If it hurts so much, do you want me to stop?
Don't stop! There's something...
More! Do it more!
Rape me wild!
Really? Then I should!
Rin's... Rin's enjoying it so much!
It's her first time, yet she enjoys having sex with a man so much?
It's amazing! It's just amazing!
It's coming in so deep inside me!
It's great!
Wonderful! You're a great bitch, Kurosaki Rin.
Let me take you to the top.
No! Stop! Don't! So deep!
Very good, Rin! Embrace your orgasm!
I'm cumming too!
It feels so warm!
I'm at the top! I'm cumming!
This is bad... My body feels so hot...
I want them to do that to me too...
It's okay! I'm fine...
Do it once more!
The men seek women,
and the women please men embracing an even greater lust.
The last molester train will never stop operating.
I'm a mere... a mere molester.