www.SubDESU-H.net
Oh no...
I shouldn’t be aroused by this.
B-But... having everyone watch me like this makes me...
It’s embarrassing.
My pussy is all wet.
Making sexy noises.
No... this isn’t right.
I’m not really this slutty.
Ple... Please, stop. Have mercy. If you do any more...
I’ll... I’ll start moaning.
No...
Yes... I’m gonna cum...
I’m cumming, cumming.
Oh no...
Don’t watch me!
Now... It’s Showtime.
We’ll have them watch you.
「I’m just...an average            」
molester
W
What...
Never mind, never mind.
It’s all okay.
Hey, that hurts!
Captain, of the Train Security Police.
You’re under arrest for public molestation.
Oh please.
And I was hoping you’d satisfy me.
What a sorry excuse for a man.
Don’t.
You bitch!
What was that for?!
Couldn’t you tell she was enjoying it?
She wanted to be touched!
No matter how many of those beasts I capture, it’s meaningless.
The one I’m looking for...
... is the one who holds the key to the clues about the The Last Molester Train.
He's Takatori Jin.
The Last Molester Train?
But isn’t that just a rumor?
It’s no rumor.
He’s a legendary molester said to have the “hands of the devil.”
Takatori Jin.
There’s no mistaking it... he’s somewhere on this line.
Kurotaki Rin, eh?
What a waste to have her as the captain of the Train Security Police.
I’m sure that woman... would be a suitable guest for The Last Molester Train.
Put your other leg on that hand grip.
Spread your legs more.
L-like this?
That’s right.
I want to see all of your important areas.
But this position....everyone can see everything... it’s embarrassing.
I feel strange.
You won’t mind it in time.
At first, I was so embarrassed and bitter about it.
But eventually I found myself excited.
I wanted to be molested.
I wanted to be violated more and more to feel the animal thrill of womanhood.
Do you want my dick, Shinobu?
I do. I want it.
I want your dick.
Where do you want it?
Pu... My pussy.
I want it in my pussy.
I couldn’t hear that.
Answer more clearly.
I said... my hymen... my clean hymen...
I want it burst open!
Wh... Why?
I almost came.
If you want to cum that badly, you need to bring yourself there first.
Come on, you can see it, right?
Cum by watching yourself masturbate.
Don’t do that... that’s so cruel.
Inside a train, I’m molesting myself.
With my pussy exposed.
Why am I so perverted?
I’m embarrassed... I’m embarrassed, but... it feels good.
I’m so aroused, I can’t stop.
Allow me to assist.
I’m cumming!
I... I’m almost... I’m cumming... cumming!
Shinobu... do you want to feel even more animalistic pleasures?
Yes... I want more amazing... things...
What should I do?
I... I’m becoming a slut.
By this molester... I’m so excited.
Up until now, I was always yelled at by my coach.
He said my technique was good but my artistry was absent.
But... ever since he started molesting me,
my coach said I'd gotten prettier... and more vibrant...
What?
What...
... is this?
From all that athletic training you do... your thighs are so nice and toned.
I’m not happy to hear that.
Even if you tell me that... stop!
If you yell loudly, others will see.
S-see me... in this sort of place...
Doing this sort of thing with your dick...
It’s rubbing... so hot...
Arisa, focus on others watching you.
I can’t...
It’s embarrassing.
Being watched will make you more beautiful.
Expose your entire self.
No... my hips are moving...
I can’t stop... no.
See? All the passengers are watching you.
Wow! Your dick is so hot and hard.
I’ve turned into a slut...
Everyone... look at me...
I’m gonna get more slutty.
Oh, you’re moving so much... it feels good...
Say it more clearly.
It’s like performing.
Don’t be shy.
Don’t tease me.
Your dick is rubbing so much...
Your dick is rubbing so much.
My pussy feels so good.
My pussy...
That’s good.
Now cum just like that.
I’m cumming... this feels so good.
I’m cumming...
Oh no... I...
So much hot stuff...
Before your next swim competition, I’ll give you one final lesson.
I had an interest in this molester.
Because the girls molested by him didn’t seem to protest.
That’s why I wanted to make sure, whether the molester was bad or not.
Yuri... do you want to feel more pleasure?
Do you want more intensity than you’ve felt before?
Yes. I do.
I want you to teach me more.
If I can have even better experiences than this, then I don’t care what happens to me.
That’s a good answer.
I feel strange.
Like I’m not myself.
I... I’m scared, but I want to feel more.
It’s throbbing it feels...
Why?
How?
Oh... dear.
But... I can’t... stop...
They... they’re watching me.
Watching me, being so slutty.
You showed them something quite interesting.
I’m sorry! Please forgive me!
In a public place... I was so disgraceful.
You need to be punished.
Yes! Please, do as you wish!
I want to do as you command.
The Last Molester Train.
It’s a mysterious train that runs after hours.
Beautiful.
Having so many men wanting me like this...
Wow! I can’t stand it anymore.
Woah, she’s lactating.
When I’m aroused, milk comes out.
See, my tits.
See how good it feels?
Look at how my nipples are erect.
Oh, shit. I’m about to cum.
More... treat me more roughly.
I’m cumming too.
I’ll take in all your pent up semen.
Wow... This is so great... it’s slashing my throat.
Fill me up with so much hot stuff.
Spray more on me!
The ones who are allowed to board are men who wish to molest...
... and women who have been invited specially as guests.
I’ve been wanting you this whole time... and I had no idea you were such a slut.
I’m sorry. This is who I really am.
Chief clerk, can I rub your tits some more?
Yes, you can.
In this setting, there is no job ranking. You can do to me as you please.
What would happen to me if I boarded that train? – of course I knew the answer.
Woah, cute!
Arisa-chan!
Wow.
Everyone is staring at me with lustful eyes.
My dirty pussy is ready for you any time.
That’s just how naughty my hole is.
It wants a big cock.
I’m being fucked by my subordinate!
If he fucks me much harder, I’ll rip apart!
Chief clerk, you’re a fucked up masochistic whore!
Yes, I know.
I’m fucked up and a whore.
But do me more.
Fuck me up more.
I’ll take this virgin hole here.
So tight.
Chief clerk, does it hurt?
It hurts, it does.
And it’s very embarrassing.
But it excites me even more.
This is what I’ve wanted all along.
My pussy and my asshole and my mouth,
having everything fucked so roughly that I don’t even know what’s happening anymore.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Chief clerk, we’ll all spray it all over you again.
Do it, do it, do it!
It's okay to cum inside.
Your hot, stinky semen. Spray it all over me!
You found everything out about me.
You found out that I’m just a whore... a whore who just wants to be fucked.
Yes... fuck me up so much.
Oh no...
So pretty...
Arisa-chan...You’re our hero!
Arisa-chan!
We all love you!
I’m so honored.
I’ll do my best at swimming.
So please use all my horny holes.
Make my pussy and asshole fall apart.
Make them all sticky.
Your cocks... they’re getting bigger inside.
Oh, I can’t hold back.
I’m cumming... please, let me show you everything.
I’m having my ass fucked in front of people...
My asshole is being spread so wide.
Being watched like this makes my body throb.
Your asshole... looks like it’s been used a lot before.
Please forgive me.
My asshole has had cocks in it so many times.
As you can see, it’s a nasty hole.
So that’s how much you love cocks.
Yes.
My asshole loves to be fucked.
I love everyone seeing how depraved I am.
My pussy loves it too!
Your cocks are all so big.
I’m sorry... I’m so nervous...
That’s right.
Piss for us now.
Ri... Right here?
Yeah... And then serve it to the passengers.
For the sake of the passengers and their mighty cocks... I will piss...
I will piss plenty!
What a gem she is. She uses the words cock and pussy freely.
Please don't say that...
I’m so shamed...
With a cock in my ass.
Come on! Squirt it on her already!
Oh no, I'm...
It would be my honor for you gentlemen to drink my piss...
Captain of the Train Secret Police... Kurotaki Rin, correct?
Are you Takatori Jin?
What do you say? Wanna duel me?
Duel?
I will molest you here and now.
If you’re able to resist it and not cum, then I’ll let you arrest me.
Molest me?
The duel will last until our next stop.
If you cum... then you’ll let me go today.
What do you say?
Very well.
I accept... your duel.
There should be only three minutes until the next station.
No way am I going to cum.
No... oh dear...
Why....
This can’t be...
Why am I getting aroused by a molester?
No. I need to stay strong.
An officer like myself can’t let a molester get to me.
What’s wrong? Does it feel good?
Of course it doesn’t! I’m not aroused.
No... stop it...
If you do that... It hurts, but...
No, it’s starting to feel good.
This is a first for me.
Oh no... wow...
You’re already so hot.
This can’t be... don’t say lies.
That can’t be.
This isn’t... please, don’t touch that part, or I’ll...
No... don’t look at me.
My boobs and my pussy, they’re all watching!
Is it so embarrassing you could cry?
Very well. Do your worst.
I won’t lose to you!
Look how wet you are.
I can hear the slurping noises.
No!
Please... hurry, end it quickly.
If this keeps up, I’ll lose my mind.
But we’ve barely started.
No, not there...
So embarrassing.
Just as I thought. You’re sensitive here too.
Stop it! Stop tweaking strange places.
Ouch... oh no...
My insides... are being stirred up...
Stop it...
Not so rough...
Oh no... it’s coming...
Something’s coming inside!
Very well.
Then I’ll let you cum.
No. I can’t cum!
Oh no... this can’t be...
Everyone’s watching me...
But I....
Welcome to my labyrinth.
Your insides are perfectly animalistic.
Animalistic?
I will awaken them for you.
I want you to awaken to your animalistic side.
Who... are you?
I am... just a... just an average molester.
I’m a molester.
I’m not a police officer or a PI – I’m just a molester.
And if that’s the case, my only way of life is to live to molest.
Why...
Why... is this... is this happening?
You were unable to arrest Takatori Jin while riding The Last Molester Train?
That’s not like you, Rin.
I apologize, Sergeant.
Take off your clothes.
I want to see if your body has been defiled by the molester.
I understand...
Is this enough?
Don’t hide yourself, Rin.
Okay.
That’s a relief. Your body is still clean.
Thank you so much.
I would never let a man touch this perfect body... unforgivable.
Sergeant, you mustn’t. Not here.
It’s okay.
I’m the only one here.
Rin... I need to have you punish the molester in time.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Saishuu Chikan Densha NEXT.
Molester 2:
will be released in Autumn, 2012.
That woman...would be a perfect guest...for The Molester Train.