www.SubDESU-H.net
Fukuyomi...
Amazing.
So this is Jin’s dick.
So much juice is coming out...
It’s already so wet.
Getting the tip is good and all, but we need to suck on the base, too.
It’s so hot and throbbing.
Makes me want to tease it more.
It’s okay. You can cum whenever you want.
I’ll drink it all for you.
It’s so hot.
So much is on my face.
But it’s still so erect.
It’s okay.
Move harder if you want.
Fuck me as hard as you want.
Harder!
Fuck me harder.
I want you to tear up my pussy.
My pussy is throbbing so hard. I just can't stop it.
I want to cum.
I really want to cum...
Please...
Oh, no!
I’m cumming.
I can't take it anymore!
See? Look.
My butthole... It’s so wet.
Just like a pussy, right?
It feels way better than a pussy.
You can tease me whatever way you want.
That!
No, not there!
Don’t tug on my dick!
I’ll cum.
I’ll ejaculate.
Oh, yes!
My butt.
It’s so hot it’s making me melt.
Please, cum inside me.
Release it all inside my naughty butthole!
You are getting closer to the truth.
What?
You’re getting closer to the same danger.
That’s what we mean.
What are you talking about?
Let us see you through it.
Sounds interesting.
I need to find out what sort of “truth” awaits me.
Welcome to my labyrinth.
Those who are insufficient as molesters – indecisive molesters – will perish.
Only dedicated molesters who are ready for anything will survive.
W
「You are the perfect         」
woman
Not so...
Oh, no...
K-Kanon-sama...
This is your punishment, Rin.
You boarded the last molester train... but you let him get away.
M-My deepest apologies!
The legendary train molester whose rumored of having the "hands of the devil", Takatori Jin.
Next time, you will catch him.
Understood?
Y-Yes...
N-Next time... Next time definitely...
I'll get him... So please don't be rough with me!
You’re rubbing so hard... I’m losing it...
Rin, your pussy is so hot and wet.
You’re really slutty.
Your nipples are also so hard.
Could it be that you are about to cum?
Y-Yes.
I’m sorry, but I’m cumming.
I’m gonna cum!
Rin, when you cum, let's do it together.
Come on, rub me harder and rougher.
Kanon-sama... Kanon-sama... Let's cum together!
I'm the only one who can make you feel like this, Rin.
I will never let a man handle your body.
Thank you so much.
Why?
Kanon-sama loves me very much. I can tell.
Yet, I can't forget about that man.
I'm so sorry, Kanon-sama.
I-I can't... anymore...
With your husband gone, you alone take care of your daughter. You are the ideal mother.
And it's understandable that you are very hungry for flesh.
I do lie at times,
but I have never resisted a woman’s true allure.
And you are overflowing with the allure that could enslave even the proudest man.
No, please stop saying embarrassing things.
I wonder how Arisa would feel if she found out you were a pervert.
Don’t play coy.
I’ve been watching you.
And this proves that you're a pervert.
P-Please, stop it. Don’t call me that.
I was just lonely.
My husband stopped giving me pleasure, that’s why...
Oh, no!
Your entire body is exuding an intoxicating aroma.
The other passengers have taken notice as well.
Please, forgive me.
You’re wrong. I’m not...
But your slutty pussy is already swirling hungrily, Sayuri.
Don’t... Don’t do this...
They’ll hear us...
They’ll hear my pussy’s squishing noises.
P-Please, stop teasing it already.
I’m losing my mind.
And the final blow... Surrender now!
Sayuri, come with me.
I will show you an even more intense ecstasy.
Okay.
Everyone... today’s lesson will include a live demonstration of the reproductive system.
S-Sensei... can we join, too?
No.
You will only watch.
You will watch me being naughty and learn from it.
It's inside!
Is this for real?
He's doing it raw!
Everyone... you’re all stroking your dicks...
You’re using me to jerk off...
Sensei...
How does it feel? Please tell us.
B-Being watched... makes me so horny.
I can’t hold back.
I love it.
I love it like this!
Everyone... can you hear it?
Can you hear the sounds of my pussy being spread open?
It’s going “squishy-squishy” – making such naughty noises.
Kanade, let’s give them some more fun.
My nipples... They're going to tear off!
Sensei!
Don’t worry, your teacher is a masochistic pervert.
No... I-I’m not a pervert...
Don’t!
I-I’ll lose my...
Oh, stop...
Sensei, does this really get you off?
Yes, it does.
It feels great.
I’m a pervert.
When I am subjected to pain... I get even more aroused...
Oh shit, I’m gonna cum!
N-Not yet.
Don’t cum before me, or I’ll punish you.
S-Sensei! Please, hurry and cum!
I’m almost there...
I’m... I’m...
Wow.
So hot and drippy... It gives off a manly smell.
Young students...
If you wish to enjoy more lectures of this nature, don’t tell anyone about this train.
If you keep quiet, you might be able to participate in the next lesson.
I think I could get used to this.
It feels so good.
I never thought... that you’d ask to be molested.
I think my first time cosplaying put me in the mood.
Getting my pictures taken while getting raped in this provcative dress...
And I’m ashamed to say that the notion of that excited me.
Yes...
My tits feel much better when they're squeezed by someone else.
It feels like electric, like shocks are running through them.
Focus intensely on the movements of my fingers.
You might cum just from nipple stimulation, you know?
My nipples... make me cum?
Yes... I want to cum.
I want to experience cumming from that.
My tits feel so warm.
Look. Your naughty image is being reflected perfectly by the window.
I look so naughty right now.
It's so embarrassing, yet it really feels so good.
Very good. Keep showing that naughty face.
I’m cumming...
...from my nipples.
My nipples are making me cum.
Cum, cum, cumming!
That’s very good.
Once you remember how the sensation works,
you should be able to cum on your own next time.
Please... My pussy is so hot and I can’t hold back.
Fuck me... right here.
Your dick feels so hot inside of me.
My pussy is throbbing so hard.
It’s so amazing!
To be this aroused when being fucked in a train... You're such a perverted slut.
Yes, I am.
I am perverted.
Being fucked in a train makes me so happy.
I’m a slut.
Look. Everyone is watching you.
No!
They can see everything, but it’s just making me hornier!
I-I can’t stop it.
More...
I want them to see more.
Then let’s have them see more...
...until the finish!
Oh, yes!
Inside... Cum inside me!
I’m cumming again.
Cumming...
Semen is spreading inside my uterus.
Kaoruko, wanna try cosplay again?
Oh? I don't mind.
But what’s the occasion?
The Last Molester Train.
It's a mysterious train that runs after the last train of the night.
The only passengers allowed are men who wish to molest and women who are invited.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I’m cumming.
S-Sensei!
It’s coming out again.
You’re all so amazing.
You came so many times and you still have so much left.
Sensei, I wanna cum all over you.
You may.
Please, cum all over me.
Make me sticky and wet with semen.
Amazing, sensei.
Sensei!
I’m about to do something bad again.
More... I want more...
Please, drench me in semen!
Release your cum.
Release it!
Sensei!
I want your pussy, too.
Very well.
My pussy is throbbing so strongly.
So please, fuck it up with your dicks.
My butt... feels stuffed.
But it feels good.
I like it this way.
Sensei... your pussy is so tight.
It’s perfect!
I feel them rubbing together...
Your dicks rubbing inside my butthole and pussy.
I feel so full!
Sensei!
Your asshole is squeezing my dick.
More... I’ll squeeze you more with my asshole...
Use my ass-pussy as you please.
Then, I'll have you use this mouth as well.
Oh, no!
Your pussy is throbbing!
That's because feeling this pain makes me feel so good.
Being tormented thrills me to no end.
Sensei, you're truly a masochist, right?
I’m sorry. I always put on a proud front for students,
but your teacher really is a slutty masochist!
More is cumming.
I’m cumming, too.
I’m cumming!
Please, cum with me!
Let's all cum together!
I-I never thought that I’d get a titty fuck from the real deal, Reya-san.
It's okay.
Use my tits as much as you like.
You can get my tits all soaked and sticky with cum.
Th-This hole is also so tight! It feels great!
Ofcourse, having your dick rubbing inside me...
...just makes my pussy so wet.
Ah, they're taking photos.
Dirty photos of me.
I'm sure they'll masturbate to them.
Oh, no.
Just the thought of it makes me excited.
Next time, let's do a special photoshoot with you totally naked.
Eh? B-But if you do that, I’ll definitely lose my mind.
I’ll probably become a ero-cosplayer.
The thought is really turning me on.
If you rub it so roughly, I’ll cum.
Don’t tell me to stop. I can’t stop!
When you’re going to cum, cum all over me.
I want to see your dick cum.
I-I cannot hold back anymore!
Then go further and deeper.
I don’t care if you break my pussy. Just go as far as you can!
Yes!
I’m going to cum, too.
Please, take a lot of pictures with that camera.
Take them.
Take them!
Wow...
Don’t hold back, guys.
Today, is the first service.
Please, defile all my holes with your semen.
Ma'am, how do you feel...
...being fucked in front of your daughter?
Please, don’t say it.
A-Arisa...
I’m so sorry.
Don’t watch. Please. Don’t watch this!
If you need a sexual replacement for your husband, I’ll take over as often as you want.
No, my tits... Don’t squeeze them so hard.
It’ll come out... Milk will come out.
No, it’s no use.
I want to cum.
I want to cum from my pussy.
Please!
I’m so sorry, Arisa.
But I have turned into a total pervert.
I’ve been fucked countless times and my pussy has gone crazy!
Well, time to cum inside you again.
Amazing!
I’m so happy.
Give it to me! Mess me up with your dick!
I’m cumming... Cumming...!
I’m cumming, cumming, cumming!
Don’t touch me there. It’s dirty.
No... Not there...
Not there...!
Your butthole is also first rate.
Ma'am, isn't this your first time doing anal?
N-No way, wait!
How awesome can you get?
Why... Why does it feel so...?
Wow, my butthole is aroused just like my pussy would be!
Come now, Ma'am, describe this to your daughter in detail as well.
A-Arisa, I’m so sorry.
I love being fucked in the ass.
My dirty pussy and asshole
are both gonna be filled with semen.
Very well, Ma'am, I’ll cum in you.
Please cum.
Fill both my pussy and asshole with semen!
Arisa, watch. Please watch.
W-Watch my butthole be filled with semen!
H-Hey... I really don’t think I can do this.
Please, let me go.
I won’t let you go.
Because this is what you wanted.
They’re watching.
Watching me doing something so embarrassing... They’re all watching.
Now, time to begin the show.
We’re going to show them everything.
That hurts!
That hurts, please stop it!
Don’t tie me up too tightly!
Is that pain only that you are feeling?
You tease...
Don’t twiddle it so...
I never thought a prideful policewoman would willingly seek to be molested.
Don’t say that...
No...
I'll...!
Very good. Cum for us.
Rin, look that way.
No, don’t...
You’re videotaping this?
Not only that.
We’re streaming this video live into the police department’s main headquarters.
I can’t believe this.
Rin, my Rin, being violated by a molester...
Th-That hurts!
What a nice voice.
Cry louder so Kanon can hear you.
I apologize most deeply,
Kanon-sama.
I’m being fucked... and you’re watching...
That hurts! It hurts!
If it hurts that badly, want to stop, Rin?
No! Please don’t stop!
Something’s coming.
It’s almost there.
More, please! Fuck me more!
Fuck me much harder!
I can?
Then I will.
Rin... Rin is so aroused.
It’s her first time having sex with a man.
Does it really feel that good?
W-Wow! So amazing!
It’s getting deeper and deeper into me.
Wow!
Magnificent.
You are the perfect woman, Kurotaki Rin.
Allow me to guide you to paradise.
No! No! Not like this...
Wait, not yet...
Very good, Rin.
Cum now.
I’ll cum with you.
I feel hot stuff rising inside of me...
I can’t stop... I feel it...!
No good.
My body is so hot.
I too... I want to be fucked just like her.
Very well.
I’ll be fine.
Fuck me once more, please!
The men hunt the women.
The women seek men who can sexually satisfy them more than anyone else has before.
The Last Molester Train will continue its journey.
I am merely a solitary molester.
www.SubDESU-H.net