The Cuckold Records of Sakuramiya Sisters
Here... Say "aah"!
We often used to buy cheap snacks on our way home
and compare how they taste.
I knew it! This tastes sour, Saya-nee!
That's why I told you not
to push yourself eating one.
That's because I want to also love
the same things you do!
I love everything that you do though, Hinata.
Ahh... Jeez, that's unfair!
Then, want to have another plum?
Don't you want to love it too?
Huh?
I'll have a little. Just a little bit!
I saw the video. So those two
really are the Sakuramiyas.
I fapped lots of times on that!
Is it true that you're lovers despite being sisters?
I knew that something was off!
So many men confessed to them
but they never seemed to date anyone.
Hey, stop resisting.
We know everything about you two.
I'm a little disappointed.
Who knew that the Sakuramiyas are such sluts?
No way...
Why are you all...
The photography club said that they need our help.
Weren't you two doing as you were told?
Get along together with all of us!
Hey, look!
She's wearing such naughty underwear!
No, the photography club
told me to wear these!
So you were secretly wearing these, huh?
Are you not ashamed wearing these at school?
Don't look... I'm begging you.
Look, they're so skimpy
that you can see her butthole!
Those two sisters are wearing
something like those!
Won't their public image get ruined?
Hey, I can't get a good view! Move over!
No...
Ow! You're pushing me!
Follow the order of our turns!
I'll take a picture! I'll definitely
use this as a fap material!
For real? Me too! Me too!
On that day...
Since the day when I received that picture,
We've been falling deeper and deeper...
And then...
N-No...
S-Stop...
Hinata is getting sullied before my eyes once again.
No...
The older sister seems quiet.
Is it lonely to be not holding your sister's hand?
Don't worry, you'll be banged with your little sister.
Oh, I'm sorry...
Looks like this sudden turn of events scared you.
We gathered such a huge crowd
after mentioning your names.
Aren't you as popular as usual?
How was it?
How did having male students tease
your whole body at school feel?
You're the worst!
They're both your fans.
You see some familiar faces around, right?
You'll be taking care of everybody here.
I'm looking forward to this.
I'll film you two being gang-banged.
Wait!
Saya-nee is...
She's not feeling well today!
The tournament is close as well...
I'm begging you, please let her go home!
Hinata?
I'll be taking care of everybody instead.
You'll be able to film a movie that's
good enough even if I do this alone!
No way... Don't do this, Hinata!
Is that the so-called sweet sisterly love?
That's fine by me.
It's quite an interesting suggestion.
But since she's already here,
Saya-senpai will be watching this.
I'll let her go home if you are able
to satisfy everybody, Hinata-senpai.
I'm begging all of you...
You may use my body as you wish,
so fuck me a lot!
Seriously? We can fuck Sakuramiya?
I think I'll be able to go for
as many rounds as I can today!
It's crazy that we can use
this body as much as we want!
I fapped on her many times!
This is like a dream!
Damn!
Whoa... He really is having sex with Sakuramiya!
Her pussy feels so good inside!
Gobble it deeper inside!
Yes, they're shaking!
She's good at giving head!
The way she shakes her hips is crazy!
She's coiling around me!
Just how many times have you done this? You're too experienced in sex!
You guys, switch with us already!
I think the younger sister really won't be enough!
No, not Saya-nee!
Here... You can also use my asshole!
For real? So you've been
trained in anal sex as well...
I'm fine putting it in there,
but will you be alright having a cock inside your ass?
I cleaned it thoroughly inside,
so please shove your cock inside just like that!
That Sakuramiya is saying such a thing!
Isn't that crazy? That's just being a nympho!
Is it our turn yet? I can't wait any longer!
Look at that.
Just how much does Sakuramiya love cocks?
She's sucking one cock after another!
No, I'm coming already!
Hey, take a look at that, Saya-senpai.
They look like ants swarming on sugar.
It's like Hinata-senpai is getting devoured.
Every man had a go and gang-banged Hinata.
They poured sperm over and over into her vagina.
Just from witnessing her looking like that...
I reached orgasm...
Wow, semen is flowing out of her!
Just how much have you guys dumped in her?
What the hell? I never had my turn even once yet!
But isn't Sakuramiya rather wasted already?
Huh? Are you done already, Hinata-senpai?
Now that won't do...
There are plenty of guys yet to be satisfied.
Doing this alone is too much in the end...
Shall we have Saya-senpai help you
from this point onwards?
Please get along as you sisters get banged.
We can finally fuck the older sister!
Alright, I'll do her first!
Huh? That's not fair!
Put them next to each other! We really
should fuck the sisters together!
That's enough, hurry up and fuck them!
Sorry, Saya-nee...
I never managed to save you from this at all...
Things shouldn't have gone like this from the start...
I'm so horrible!
No... You're wrong...
I'm the horrible one...
Wow...
Seeing you getting raped
makes me horny...
Saya-nee?
That's fantastic!
I've been wanting to film you two looking like that!
Having sisters fucked as much as we want is the best!
And it's those sisters on top of that!
I'll be able to nut no matter
how many times with this!
Aren't they dykes?
Isn't it cruel for them to get gang-banged by guys?
Coming... I'm coming!
Here, drink all of it!
Keep licking my asshole just like that!
The sisters get easily matching creampies!
Those are incredible creampies!
They hauled plenty of semen!
Don't worry, we still have lots of semen for refills.
The next guys should fuck them already!
Don't give them a break!
Keep shoving cocks in their pussies!
Sakuramiya's vagina feels warm!
Those who already came should get switched!
Aren't you already done earlier?
Use any available holes! Make the queue move!
Hurry up!
Don't give them any breaks!
There are still lots of cocks on queue!
Wow, they are being fucked
by cocks all this time!
Getting to fuck this pussy as we please is the best!
Umm, Hinata-san... I've always
been in love with you, so...
What are you confessing for in this situation?
She's not your lover. She is everybody's
cum dumpster right now.
We need to properly record
how many men nutted them, okay?
We won't lose count if we write it down like this.
After all, we'll be banging them
for the whole night!
Then, that went on for the whole time...
...until our bodies went numb.
Hey, don't doze off!
Or rather, are you still alive?
So how many men did they have in the end?
Their holes are gaping wide after one night!
Hey, you two! I'll be taking a picture so smile!
Hey, why is this locked?
Isn't someone in there?
I'm a teacher! Open up!
Do you hear me?
Shit... Isn't that a teacher?
Why? Shouldn't nobody be coming in here?
Let's make a run for it for now!
What about the Sakuramiyas?
They'll definitely find this out!
Then, what should we do instead?
Saya-nee... Are you alright?
Sorry...
I'm sorry, Hinata... I'm...
It's alright, Saya-nee...
We'll be together no matter what happens...
Hinata...
I couldn't reach you no matter
how far I stretch my arm.
That is why I wanted to ruin you...
I wanted to etch a trace of me in your lives...
Oh...
You two truly are beautiful...
It's already been a month since that night at the gym.
The teacher who saved us made us
explain the whole thing that occurred.
Since a lot of students were involved this time,
the school somehow wanted
to sweep it all under the rug.
We also wish not to get the police involved,
so several students agreed to transfer out.
However, the rumor of us two getting gang-banged
by male students have spread within the campus.
Part of it was because our videos and pictures
seem to be getting passed around.
Hello, Hinata?
Yeah...
That's right.
I'm done with my practice earlier.
I'm alone in the clubroom right now.
Yeah.
Saya-nee...
I'm in a hotel right now...
Not so hard! I'm on phone right now...
The guys that were hitting on me last time...
They're making me come again for the whole time...
I'm letting them come as many times as they like again!
I'm filled to the brim both in front and back...
I'm having sex again today...
They're ejaculating again!
Saya-nee...
Are you getting horny?
Yeah... I am so horny right now...
Hinata...
Saya-nee...
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji