The Cuckold Records of Sakuramiya Sisters
Saya-nee...
No...
Not there...
That was great!
Your lesbian play is so arousing!
We'll shoot you with the club members next,
so please wear the clothes
we prepared for you two.
Alright...
Let's continue filming, then.
How did this happen?
We were always together.
We became sisters from remarriage.
We both grew up from single parents,
so we got along together immediately.
Before we knew it,
we became more than family.
And one day,
Tachikawa from the Photography Club
found out about our secret.
That one photo
messed up our lives.
Hinata tried to protect me,
and I tried to protect her.
Hinata!
But he played us like fools.
I later found out that he brought both
of us in separate hotel rooms for fun.
Saya-nee!
Are you alright, Saya-nee?
Why are you...
Sorry... I'm sorry, Hinata...
Hey, tell me what's happening here.
This isn't what we agreed on!
You said that you won't involve her!
Oh yeah, we had that agreement.
I'm sorry,
but I want to film you both no matter what.
I thought that it'll definitely be amusing!
A couple of lesbian sisters gets
gangbanged to protect each other.
You're both dripping with semen, isn't that so erotic?
Oh, I got to record something better
than I expected. I'm beyond satisfied!
Situations like this are rare.
Did you two unexpectedly enjoy this?
There's no way that we enjoyed this!
Don't treat us like fools!
Saya-senpai, seeing your
little sister raped arouses you.
Feel the pleasure just like that while watching her.
I...
How about you, Saya-senpai?
Seeing Hinata like that...
You promised so I endured all this,
but I won't ever forgive you for
laying your hands on Saya-nee!
H-Hinata...
Now that it came to this,
I'll expose everything that you all did!
D-Don't!
Everyone will end up seeing your videos!
Who knows what they'll do
if you'll fight back now!
She's right.
I can spread the video of you two
online or at school when I feel so.
We don't want to ruin your lives though.
We'll do nothing of that sort if you'll
play along with our filming.
We'll end this when we're satisfied.
How is it?
How does it feel to wear those while at the campus?
You both look so good in those!
This pervert...
Please try not to raise your voices too much.
We're at the far end of the building,
but who knows when someone might pass by.
Or could it be
that you want other students to see you like that?
Not this pose...
Hey, didn't you say that it'll only be among us here?
I'm just kidding.
I don't want outsiders getting
in the way of our filming.
After all, this is our first shooting
with you two together.
The shapes of your pussies...
And even how different your ass holes are...
I'll be recording every nook
and cranny of you two today.
Ouch...
Have you two taken a good
look at each other's bodies?
Don't use weird stuff on Saya-nee!
No, they'll get stretched out...
What are you playing around with...
Isn't it so fun to look and compare them like this?
Twelve... Thirteen... Fourteen...
They can hold more than I expected.
Isn't it the first time for both of you
to have marbles in your pussies?
It's as if we're toys...
Their faces look so absurd!
Hey, stay put just like that.
Here, I'll make you drink plenty of my drool.
Keep holding it down there!
Your little sister is gonna beat you!
A pussy duel between sisters is so erotic!
They filmed us as they treat us like playthings.
I can't...
I'm gonna lose...
Oh... Hinata-senpai's pussy has been defeated.
The loser will play a penalty game.
Hinata-senpai will be having sandwich sex.
You just want to do that, don't you?
Oops, you found out.
Can I borrow that camera?
Okay!
It's alright, this is gonna feel good.
No, Saya-nee is here!
Saya-senpai!
Can you help us here a little?
Eh...
I thought that I should let you record the video.
Can you see the screen?
Hinata...
Isn't Hinata-senpai perfectly caught on camera?
Look, cocks are going inside her!
Hinata-senpai's body is now able to easily
take two of them inside at the same time.
How is it?
Is it more arousing to watch it across the screen?
That's not true at all...
Even though your pussy is this wet?
I'll make you feel even better, then.
H-Huh?
Wait, not now... Stop...
Could it be that you came just from having it inside?
It's like you're biting my cock off!
Hey, come on!
You have to properly hold
the camera, Saya-senpai!
P-Please...
I can't do this...
Please make sure to record your little sister!
Hinata-senpai, this tight pussy
will make me come in no time!
Hinata-chan's ass hole really is the best!
How did it come to this?
I should have fought them back with Hinata...
Saya-senpai, are you properly filming?
Hey, you have to move your free hand.
This pussy is terrific!
It's squeezing me hard the whole time!
I'll sully this jet black hair!
Why can't I take my eyes off Hinata as she gets raped?
The idols of the Archery Club
became mere meat holes!
I can fuck such a hole that feels good
as I please! This is so incredible!
Hey, open your mouth!
We'll be using every hole you two have.
What do you think? Their pussies are now connected!
Whoa... This is so erotic!
Senpai, use your butt more! Move it!
Here, have your butts kiss each other!
Have it go deeper like a French kiss!
Alright, then. Let's do it in one go.
Oh... This hole feels really good!
I'm gonna give it a creampie just like this.
D-Don't!
Don't shoot it inside Saya-nee!
You're seeing the part where
Hinata-senpai and I are connected!
Th-This is incredible!
No...
Not her...
Here, aren't you happy that
you can kiss each another?
With faces smothered with semen, that is.
Their lesbian kiss makes me horny for real.
Take over the camera from me next.
Mine's not settling down...
Can you two come here for a moment?
No...
What's next...
Well, we've only been filming in the dark...
It's brighter when we do this, am I right?
Oh, it looks like the third years
just got done with their classes.
We're quite far, so maybe they won't notice us.
Okay, then! Please let them fuck you two.
Look, there are people at the courtyard.
They'll easily see us if they'll look up here.
Don't look... No...
No...
Want to let everyone see how lewd
both of you look right now?
D-Don't!
Since then, their demands have escalated.
Here's the Women's Archery Club,
participating in the Prefectural meet.
Please greet everyone.
Here's the second-year student and
club president, Sakuramiya Saya.
All of our members will show...
the result of our constant training...
and will go out there...
to fight to the utmost of our abilities...
We hope that you will root for us.
Before we noticed it,
getting raped by these men
and getting filmed
have all become normal for us that
we readily strip down every time.
Hey, hey...
Haven't the Sakuramiya sisters
been looking sexier lately?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
It's like some sort of a charm
just from looking at them.
Could it be that they now have boyfriends?
Huh, really? I was aiming for them too!
Don't be stupid. They're way beyond your reach.
Hey, just where are we going?
Don't you know that we have
a competition this weekend?
Let us go home already!
Your competition is coming soon,
so we want to film you two before then.
Wait!
Are you planning to film us here!?
We had a hard time getting this place ready.
We had various people help us.
And since we went this far...
Whoa!
Whoa, the Sakuramiya sisters really came here!
Whoa! This is amazing!
So that video is real...
Damn, I got hard.
This isn't a prank, right? Are we really doing it?
The Photography Club sure is amazing.
I called a bunch of male students for today.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization