A long time ago when wishes could still be granted.
There was a beautiful princess called Eifa in a certain country.
Her skin was as white as snow.
Her mouth was as special as roses.
Her eyes and hair were as deep as black pearls.
As if she was as beautiful as the moon shining in the night sky,
hence Eifa was called the moon princess.
Her brother's name was Alois.
He had hair like it was combed with gold.
He had eyes like honesty.
That gallant and gentle person was extolled as the Sun prince.
Sun prince Alois and Moon princess Eifa, these two siblings were the pride of the country.
Wandering Dirty Lunatics
- First Part -
Presented by Masurenai-fansubs
Alois nii-sama...
Alois nii-sama.
It's Eifa.
Are you awake?
Thank goodness.
Alois nii-sama is asleep.
Umm... Alois nii-sama.
I'm coming in, okay?
I'm sorry, Nii-sama.
Amazing!
Eifa?
Eifa, what are you-
Stop it!
Alois nii-sama's has gotten big. Amazing!
W-Wait, Eifa. You can't do this!
It's a bit bitter.
Eifa, why...
Because recently we never...
How are you two? Are you two happy?
Yes.
Oh I see. That's great.
By the way, how was your horse-riding?
Well, I saw various things!
Like a deer this big!
Is that so?
That was really amazing.
Yeah!
Forget about it, just don't think about anything and have fun.
I understand.
Yes!
Alois-sama, this time you will dance with me, okay?
Alois nii-sama...
What's the matter? Being in this place.
Nothing...
You shouldn't have such a bored face during this rare evening party.
No, I wasn't bored. I'm just a little tired.
You don't have to hide.
You are bothered about Alois, right?
I can't stop a person's love.
Not as your mother but as a woman.
I will give this to you.
This is a medicine to let two people fall in love with each other.
First you will drink it.
After that let Alois drink it...
...by using your mouth.
If both of you have the same feelings,
this will grant both of your wishes.
I know it.
Before you get betrothed with a prince from another country whom you never seen,
you'd want to throw yourself into the arms of the person you truly love.
Here.
That's why I drank the medicine.
Please look, Alois nii-sama.
Eifa's place.... has become like this.
Wait, Eifa.
No.
I can't wait any longer!
You should really stop it, Eifa.
It's alright, Alois nii-sama.
It's really painful but I'm happy.
Amazing!
It feels good.
Alois nii-sama.
I wonder why...
Eifa is supposed to be my younger sister...
Nii-sama, nii-sama.
Eifa loves me to such an extent...
Alois nii-sama.
Eifa, I'm sorry.
Alois nii-sama?
Eifa, I love you.
Nii-sama.
Eifa...
I was afraid all along that I'd lose you as my younger sister.
If it really happens one day,
I know I won't be able to turn back.
So, Nii-sama also loves...
Nii-sama.
I'm putting it in.
Yes.
This place? Eifa, do you feel good at this place?
Nii-sama, it's amazing. Nii-sama, it's amazing.
My that place is making really lewd sounds.
Eifa, Eifa!
Nii-sama, Nii-sama. Alois nii-sama!
Nii-sama is cumming!
Alois nii-sama...
Eifa.
Nii-sama.
Again... You're cumming again!
Nii-sama!
I'm cumming, Eifa!
Alois nii-sama.
Eifa, you don't regret, right?
With only a little of tonight's memory...
With only the memory of being embraced by Alois nii-sama...
I'll definitely live on my life.
dokomademo fukaku nume youni
I'm a failure anywhere, like I don't have a name.
sono hitomi wa watashi wo nomikonte yuku
Those eyes start to understand me.
mou nani mo hanasanaide
I won't let go of anything anymore.
yasashii koe mo kikasaenaite
I also can't hear the gentle voice.
shirabaro watashi no kakera
Playing dumb about my fragments.
hiroi atsumete amata ano te no naka ni
You picked up and collected many of them, within that hand.
futari umarete wa kieru
Both of our births disappeared.
inori no rasen
The spiral of my prayers
tonari tokirenai yori
is like the never-ending time beside me.
kono ai hakanai
I won't betray this love
hikari dato wakaa demo
even if the light is young,
I cannot live without you
anata dake nagai itoshii
You're only my love for a long time.
Never leave me alone
You never leave me alone
Heart of me