That is unfortunate news that I never even tried to think of.
The prince whom I'm supposed to marry has died from an epidemic disease.
Thus I remained in this castle, keeping that night a secret deep in my chest.
Time passed like nothing had happened.
Alois nii-sama is interacting with me just as gentle as in the past too.
I thought that nothing had happened.
But...
Alois nii-sama.
Nii-sama... Nii-sama.
My body can't forget about that night.
My body becomes hot. Every night, every night, I'll remember what I did with my brother.
Who's there?!
Princess, it's me.
Mother...
It seems you can't forget about Alois nii-sama.
Do you still remember this? The medicine from that time.
Use this and return back to Alois nii-sama again.
And then, just like that time.
This medicine is slightly different from the one before.
First, you have to drink all of the medicine, then kiss Alois.
The two of you will then be just like that time.
M-My body is hot.
Wandering Dirty Lunatics
- Second Part -
Presented by Masurenai-fansubs
Seems that the time has finally arrived.
The moment to throw those siblings out of this castle.
How long have I waited for this caste since I married into the noble family.
Finally this country is going to be mine.
Eifa is already very wet.
You fiddled with it while thinking of Alois every night, right?
You're a bad girl, aren't ya, Eifa?
To that kind of a child...
This is an object to punish bad children.
If I put this into Eifa's lewd place...
Whenever Eifa thinks of Alois and her body wriggles, it'll start to move in her place.
I don't want such a thing.
No, Eifa. This is a punishment.
Whenever you think of Alois,
This will wriggle about and make it unbearable.
Come, stand to clip it on tightly so that it won't drop.
I'll help you to put it on.
This way, you won't be able to do those lewd things.
Without this key, you will keep on staying like that.
Eifa.
Mother, I don't want such a thing.
No, Eifa. I can't take that thing off.
S-Stop it. If you do that, I'm going to get excited again.
If you get excited, the lump in your body will start to move.
It'll make you feel very good.
The only one who can take it out is your brother, Alois.
You better beg him to do it.
It's about time Eifa has kissed Alois.
Well, let's start the final finishing touches.
But before that, let both of them have some fun.
Back to the forbidden night and let them love each other once again.
Who's there?!
I can't move my body.
Alois, have you waken up?
Before you meet Eifa,
let me be your partner for awhile.
How's this?
I think it's ready.
You want to meet Eifa, right?
Eifa, enter the room.
Eifa...
I'm sorry, Nii-sama.
After this, I'll teach you two various things.
Eifa, stay there and look at us.
Eifa can't forget about you.
She usually does lewd things alone.
Eifa does...
Alois-kun, you can't forgot about Eifa too, right?
Eifa, what are you doing?
I'm in pain.
Geez, you can't bear not to fiddle with it, can you?
You shouldn't. Control yourself.
I beg you.
It can't be helped, huh? Do you want this?
The younger sister who can't stop doing lewd things is receiving her punishment like this.
Let me relieve you of your pain, Eifa.
See. Such a thing is moving inside.
Prince, please lick her properly.
You really wanted to do this.
Eifa, this time you will lick your brother's penis.
Just like this, you should try it too.
Like this?
Licking alittle more to the back will make him feel better.
It's moving jerky.
It's twitching and entering the hole...
That's right. You do that soon too.
Prince, how's it? It feels good, right?
I'll change with your younger sister soon.
Alois nii-sama.
I want it too... I want it too...
If you move this intensely, the male will be pleased with it.
Alois nii-sama, do you really feel it that way?
You're cruel... If it's Eifa... If it's Eifa, you'll get...
Are you jealous, Eifa?
Then, it's almost time...
Come, let's change roles, Eifa?
Alois nii-sama.
I really wanted Alois nii-sama's.
Alois nii-sama's has gotten this big!
I can see your lewd hole clearly.
If you do that at such a time...
It feels so good.
Let me touch this part of yours.
It feels good...
Eifa, Eifa...
Although I know we shouldn't do this,
I just can't forgot about you, Eifa.
I can't let go of you anymore.
Nii-sama, I don't want to let go of you too!
I have understood both of your feelings.
Let me grant that wish.
Alois nii-sama, inside me... Ejaculate inside of me!
Nii-sama's is really hot...
Eifa, women do have another hole that can please men.
Another hole?
Eifa, use this place.
Let me lick it so that he can put it in more easily.
Nii-sama's thing is going to enter this place...
See. It has enlarged this big.
Use your hands like this and lift yourself.
So that your hole will become tighter.
It's even better if you move this intensely.
Touch it.
It's drenched, isn't it?
Even the butt hole can get this wet.
My butt hole is starting to twitch...
Let both of us service him together.
Alois nii-sama, does it feel good?
Ah, how lewd. It's twitching.
Are you tired already, Eifa?
Well then, let's use a rod toy for awhile.
If you use this, you will be able to know how Alois feels.
How Nii-sama feels?
This is the same as a male's penis.
It feels good, right?
What's this? This is my first time feeling it.
It's like the feeling when the female's clitoris is stimulated, isn't it?
Touch it yourself.
This is the same as Nii-sama's thing.
It's a weird feeling.
Just like that. Moreover, this thing can even ejaculate.
It feels good...
How do you feel being stimulated in all three places simultaneously?
I-I can't resist it...
What's this feeling? It feels weird.
It's really stimulating...
No! This kind of feeling is...
I'm cumming!
It's finally time to use your hole.
Alois nii-sama, don't tease me.
This isn't Eifa's hole...
Eifa feels so good, whether it's the butt hole or dick.
I'm cumming again.
Now, it's about time for the ending.
No!!
Don't! No, no!
No, don't come over here.
Don't save me.
Nii-sama and Eifa's dicks...
It feels good.
Nii-sama, I'm almost...
Eifa, me too.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
Enjoy your last night to the fullest.
Alois nii-sama.
Eifa, do you regret?
Not at all.
I just need the memories of tonight and the love I got from you.
I can surely live on.
Unforgivable...
Long ago, there was a beautiful princess called Eifa in a certain country.
The princess was deeply in love with her brother,
and drank the medicine she got from a malevolent witch.
Both of them fell in love due to the power of the medicine.
However it was discovered by the King.
The King burst into a rage and imprecated both of them.
And then, both of them were destined not to meet each other again.
Thus, day is Alois while night is Eifa.
The journey of the wondering pair has started.