In the small, prosperous country of Kuzuryuugawa,
there was a castle named Ootsuzuka.
This era was a time six months
after the old head of the Kagurazaka clan passed away...
Samurai Hormone
You have just soiled the name of the Fuuma clan.
You cheeky brat!
There!
Ouch!
Here's more!
It hurts!
And another one!
Father, I beg of you, please forgive me!
What are you saying after failing your mission?!
How dare you have the nerve to come back and
complain that you could not accomplish it?
Speak!
Brother, please don't be so harsh...
This still isn't enough for your foolishness!
F-Father...
Brother...
Please have mercy on me.
Horimon Juurou, I presume?
My name is Hori Monjuurou.
Not Horimon Juurou.
Shut up!
I shall claim the secret scroll which you hold!
Die!
This is really bad.
Giv it up.
I'm done for!
What?
This is...
An Onmyou technique.
TL note: Jigokugumo = Hell Spider
Jigokugumo
You, when did you...?
You... you...!
This is wonderful.
P-Please forgive me!
No mercy for those who fail their mission!
For you are but our doll, our carnal vessel.
Here you go, I'm going to give you all of my smegma.
Yes, I shall gratefully accept your smeg-
You shall have a taste of it for as long as
you're unable to bring back the scroll.
Here, lick it.
Seems my younger sister is better
at licking my dick than I thought.
Shizune, what are you doing?!
What is this overwhelming pleasure?
That's good...
Here, let's see how your back hole is.
Shizune, from now on we're going to violate and cum inside you.
No, father, please don't cum inside me!
Silence!
I'm the one who raised you to be Fuuma's own sex hole!
You...!
And we're the ones who will decide what
we want to do with this sex hole!
Here, take my dick deeper into your throat!
There!
Hey, don't push your cute little sister too much.
It'd be a waste if she dies.
I'm going to drill my dick more and more into your pussy.
Tt note: kunoichi = female ninja
Good, now I finally feel some purpose
into training you as a kunoichi
I'm going to cum inside you, Shizune.
Stop, not inside me, please.
I'll really get pregnant.
I really mustn't!
I'm cumming!
Here, I'm also cumming all I've got in here!
That was a good meal.
Do your job next time, okay?
Master, this is...?
Master!
Just you wait, Horimon Juurou.
I'll definitely take that scroll from you!
I hope you haven't forgotten about me...
Whoa, whoa, as expected of Kojuurouta-sama.
I didn't think I'd get caught so easily.
I'm sorry, but I shall not let you pass any further.
Where did you hide the Master's head, Monjuurou?!
The Master's head? I don't know of such a thing.
Okay then.
Now it's clear that you are the one who
killed father an stole scroll!
Kojuurouta-sama, have mecy, please have mercy on me!
Just kidding.
That felt quite different...
Now I shall take my leave!
Wait!
What...?
You're... the kunoichi from before!
That's right, and as a souvenir, I'll gladly give you my name.
My name is Shizune!
Damn, if it's going to end like this, then kill me already!
Actually...
I feel head over heels with your pussy the first time we met.
Wh-What are you saying?
Well, I'm saying that I can be your partner tonight.
This is embarrassing...
No need to feel nervous.
Because it'll just be pleasure from this point on.
Wh-What are you planning to...?
No, not my breasts!
Shizune, your breasts feel really tender, they're great.
That's, don't touch me there...
Slowly, we'll do it slowly, Shizune.
It's coming inside!
Your big thing is penetrating me.
Shizune, your pussy is the best!
It's drilling inside me.
It's going deep into my pussy.
Shizune.
My Shizune!
You're the cutest and most beautiful woman in the world!
That's just...
It feels great for me too, Shizune!
No, it's hitting inside.
This is the first time I've felt like this.
How is it, Shizune?
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...
I'm going to cum!
It's all right, cum all you want.
Oh no, oh no...
I'm going crazy.
I'm at my limit!
Shizune, your pussy is all wet.
No, this is embarrassing.
Don't look...
It's hitting deeply...
It's hitting deep inside my pussy!
I'm cumming, Shizune.
Please, please cum!
It's okay.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's all wet and sticky.
Horimon...?
I'm in the middle of an important mission.
It's unfortunate that I can't take you with me,
but I shall never forget you.
Farewell.
Horimon Juurou.
I can no longer go back as a Fuuma.
I'm going with you after I give my stupid
father and brother a good whack!
Why are you surprised?
You didn't think I could make it past Oyakiriyama?
You can apologize to him once I've sent you to the other world!
Though you probably won't meet him
because you're going straight to hell!
Oh crap!
Kojuurouta-sama, are you all right?
Man, this guy's really troublesome.
Maybe I should wipe his back for a bit.
What in the world is this?
Kojuurouta-sama, it's you, right?
These are real boobs!
Don't tell me... that he's actually a she?!
I can't believe this...
You! What are you trying to do?
No, that's not it!
I was just trying to nurse you earlier!
You saw them, right?
The secret that only my father and I know.
Yes, I definitely did.
And I can't believe that you're actually a woman.
Now I really can't let you live.
I never betrayed the Master!
Long ago, disputes and conflicts were rampant across the empire,
all because of the scroll that was presented to the emperor.
The scroll was said to be a sacred treasure,
which has the capability to grant any wish.
My grandfather took the life of a priest in order to obtain it,
and it's a sin which the Master will forever carry.
In order to protect that land and its people,
he took the priest's head, and as his dying wish,
requested me to deliver both his head
and the secret scroll to a certain place.
I didn't know anything.
Then, he simply treated me as an ordinary woman.
Hori Monjuurou,
make me into a woman.
Please, I ask for your gracious forgiveness.
Am I not attractive enough for you that
I would be able to bear your children?
Kojuurouta-sama, your beauty is unlike any other!
This is embarrassing, and yet...
I want to do it.
So this is the thing that will impregnate me.
It feels really hard and bulky.
I'm putting it in.
Oh no, this thing won't fit...!
Not my nipples!
Something's coming out.
I'm starting to get really wet down there.
It means that you're now ready to take it inside of you.
It's ripping into me.
It's tearing me apart!
It hurts, no...!
Shall we stop, Kojuurouta-sama?
No, don't.
It hurts, but I'm happy.
Please relax.
Now then, I'll move.
I'm starting to feel weird.
Oh yes, this is amazing!
It feels good!
Kojuurouta-sama, I'm about to cum!
Yes, oh yes!
Cum. Just cum!
Impregnate me!
I'm happy...
Your pussy is starting to become more lewd, Kojuurouta-sama.
D-Don't look...
You're the one who put me in this embarrassing position.
Your love juices are overflowing.
Your thing really wants it inside, right?
Here, take a good look at your own love juices.
I...
I can see my own lewd pussy...
This is...
Your thing is hitting deep inside, and it feels hot...
More, more...
It's coming, it's coming again...
It's welling up again, do it more...
Oh yes, oh yes...!
Push it farther into my pussy!
Push it into my womb!
Oh yes...
Kojuurouta-sama, I'm cumming!
Me too!
I'm cumming...
Let's cum together!
Monjuurou, promise me.
Promise?
That you'll make me pregnant.
And you shall never do it with any other woman.
But what if I cannot keep my promise?
Then I shall cut you down.
What is this spoiled blockhead samurai saying?
He already slept with me before, you know.
What did you say, you failure of a Fuuma ninja?
Hey; hey, can’t we all just get along?
Wait!
Are you trying to escape, Horimon Juurou?!