Jousei Academy
A man who finds delight from making authorities submit to him:
Kawabata Ryou
Using his status as a student, he sets his eyes upon the nearby authorities:
Female Teachers
The only one who he failed on out of several female teachers
he forced into submission: Hagiura Yuuna
and her younger sister: Hagiura Aina
Both of them have equally beautiful and voluptuous bodies
that can fuel a man's desire.
For someone who possesses a strange fetish like Ryou,
there are no better preys than them.
And thus, Yuuna triumphed over Ryou and had him transfer schools.
Before he starts attending to Jousei Academy, the new school where he ended up,
he met Yuuna's identically looking younger twin sister named Aina.
Wanting to get back at Yuuna for getting the better of him,
Ryou uses Aina to lure her.
The rhythmic gymnastics club adviser Aina can only stare,
gnashing her teeth while gagged, as she witnesses
her older sister Yuuna being a total slave to his meat rod.
Ryou then takes Aina's virginity, forcibly and ruthlessly penetrating her.
Ryou utilizes every skill he has
to thoroughly push Aina to submission.
Her desperate attempt to hold onto her moral principles
only fuels up the lust of his twisted sexual disposition.
He uses Yuuna to threaten Aina,
savoring the top-notch titillating woman
as he relentlessly uses her mouth.
"You keep doing cruel things to nee-san as well...
You won't get away with this! I absolutely won't give in!"
Aina shouts, glaring at Ryou as he violently screws
her unbloomed flower bud that nobody else has ever touched before.
He uses his meat stick, standing stiff in arousal and veins popping out,
on Aina while Yuuna lies down collapsed on the floor and dazed in orgasm.
In front of Ryou lies Aina,
another woman whose face looks the same, tied down and restrained.
The pain she had from Ryou's meat rod last time is now gone.
What he gently pushes onto her supple, bulging, and bare breasts...
...is the tip of a brush.
Sansha Mendan
Three-shot Interview
Chaining Humiliation • School of Training
Original Animation
La
Last
Last Ti
Last Time
Last Time on
Last Time on San
Last Time on Sansha
Last Time on Sansha Men
Last Time on Sansha Mendan
Last Time on Sansha Mendan.
Last Time on Sansha Mendan..
Last Time on Sansha Mendan...
Hey!
Wh-What are you doing?
You already know it.
I-I understand.
Stop, I'm gonna do it!
Something like this is...
I love your cock!
You're getting in the mood now.
I happened to see it.
After my sister went away
yesterday, you met with her!
Why were you two inside the men's restroom?
No, that was...
I looked up about you.
Didn't you come from my sister's school?
So, you already know that much...
Wait... You went straight away...
Let your voice out just like the old times.
Idiot! Like I can do such a thing!
You're wrong! Idiot!
No...
Were you backed up from the last time?
No, wait...
You're touching me down there!
There's nobody else here,
so feel free to get wild.
No, I can't do that!
You're being rough!
You're teasing it forcefully!
Stop thrusting your cock!
Aina can see us, I'm begging you!
That's too late, your little sister
already saw your true colors.
No, let me off! Stop thrusting your cock!
Stop making my pussy feel good!
Your anger is misplaced.
I'm even giving her so much pleasure, see?
Can you feel it on where she's touching you?
You're way lewder than your sister
despite your innocent looks.
Your cock is reaching deep in my womb!
It feels good, you'll break me down!
Aren't you glad that you never woke her up?
Nee-san, now it's my turn...
...to protect you!
I'll never ever give in!
I'll never lose against something like this!
Oh, Hagiura-sensei.
What are you here for?
Should I be saying it out here?
Alright, speak up.
Leave this place otherwise. I'm busy right now.
I understand. I'll just talk to Yuuna-sensei.
A-Alright, then.
I'll listen to what you have to say. That will do, right?
What do you think you're doing?
Looks like an apathetic bitch needs
to be disciplined by her master.
B-Bitch... Disciplined...
Don't be stupid! Who would...
It's fine if you can't do it.
Someone else can take your place.
She looks so much like you
and is compliant as well.
Y-You're a coward!
Didn't you say it yourself?
Stop doing this!
Isn't that enough?
Giving up already?
Jeez... If you're like this, then
I'll have your sister work hard...
No, don't lay your hands
on my sister anymore!
Settle on me instead...
Be honest, then. You're even
drowning in pleasure right now.
There's no way that this feels good!
You're forcing me to have sex with you!
But in contrast, your insides
are sucking me intensely.
That's not true, I'm not feeling good at all!
This only feels painful for me!
You'll be playing tough only this time.
No, wait! You're kidding me, right!
Are you planning to come like this?
Hey... No, you absolutely can't do that!
No, no... I'm begging you, that'll knock me up!
You absolutely can't! No, no!
I'll impregnate both of you sisters.
No, no! No—!
It's flowing inside me!
Why would you do such a thing?
No—!
It's twitching...
No, stop moving it around!
That's because you're licking it lewdly.
Lewdly, you say...
Like I'm doing that to this nasty thing!
Don't think about trivial stuff.
Come on, gobble it down.
G-Gobble this thing down?
I'll do it, alright!
A man's thing is in my mouth...
You're sucking it good despite hating it.
You're wrong! Stop saying weird stuff!
No... Even though this is disgusting...
Even though I hate this...
There's so much gooey stuff!
W-Wow...
Looks like that's not enough.
I have to put a stop to that nasty stuff.
Any more of that cruel stuff and I'll...
Worried about something, Hagiura-sensei?
Oh, no. That's...
What are you doing here?
This is no place for people like you!
Now, leave!
People will start to wonder if you speak so loud.
W-We're currently having club activities.
Non-members should leave.
Isn't this something important?
Huh?
What were you thinking, calling me here?
And worse, while I'm in these clothes!
That's mean. Also, you could've
come here after changing.
Stop treating me like a fool!
That's a threat! I don't have
any choice but to come here, do I?
Come to the art room wearing spats. I'll go to Hakushou instead if you won't.
So, you're aware of your place.
S-Stop staring! This pose is embarrassing!
You're about to enjoy what I'm gonna do to you.
There's no way that I'll enjoy this! Untie me!
Want Yuuna to take your place?
I think that you'll enjoy this
if you're the slut that I expected.
I'm not the slut that you think of...
No, don't look at me!
They're exposed, no way...
It's time to have some fun.
Huh? No, stop!
No, don't look! Stop staring!
Here, watch this.
Is that nee-san?!
Why what's the meaning of this?
Delete that immediately!
That is what we call a slut.
Doesn't the same blood as hers flow in you?
Y-You're wrong! That isn't my sister at all!
You're wrong... S-Stop!
No, stop that! Stop tracing over my breast!
It feels pricklish, no...
Did you start feeling good?
You're wrong! It never felt good at all!
You're not like your older sister at all, sensei.
That's...
Or are you saying that you're
a slutty teacher like her?
No, neither I nor my sister
is a slut in any way!
Let's check it ourselves.
No... No, no, don't! Not there!
What do you mean "there"?
No, my tits...
Stop teasing my tits!
You're moaning with pleasure.
I'll take care of you down here,
just like how I did to your sister.
That's not true...
Nee-san!
No, no!
No, don't! Stop staring! Please, let me go!
Somebody, help me!
You may scream or do whatever,
but nobody will come here.
Don't do that!
No... Not down there!
Please, let me go!
You really are sisters. Look at that.
Nee-san, why do you look
like you're enjoying it...
What is that? No, it feels tingly!
What is that thing? No!
Is it your first time having a rotor?
It's your sister's favorite.
I don't know what that is!
Nee-san!
Come just like your sister!
Don't! That thing is... I-I'm already...
I'm coming... I ended up coming!
Didn't that feel good? That is the female instinct.
You'll feel good even when being raped.
You're wrong...
Saying that it's instinct is the same
as being a beast. I don't...
Humans are fundamentally beasts inside.
I'll be teaching you about that fact.
Are you still planning to do something on me?
We'll have sex.
I'll show you how to have sex like beasts.
Sex... N-No, stop!
I won't allow that!
No...
No, stop!
No!
It's dripping as it loosens up,
overflowing with your pussy juice.
What else is this besides beastlike?
You're wrong! I hate this!
You're wrong, and yet...
No!
Not my tits!
Stop groping me down there
as well! Any more of this and...
You've been coming over
and over for a while now.
You're just all talk, and your body wants this.
That's not true, I've never been coming at all!
This isn't me! I won't accept this!
This is your true self.
Not inside!
Stop playing with my pussy!
Ever heard about uterine stimulation?
I'm going to pour it inside you just like this.
No, I don't want it inside!
I don't want to get pregnant!
No, no... Stop, don't come inside!
There's so much of hot stuff going inside me!
Semen keeps flowing inside me!
Make it stop, no...
This isn't right...
I should be hating it...
Now you know your true self, right?
That you're a female masochist
who feels good from being raped.
I'll never ever forgive you!
Oh...
After getting herself that wasted,
she recovered within the next day.
What a woman.
I'll have to to check the status
of our club activities.
Thank you very much!
What are you here for?
You're acting haughty, unlike earlier.
Of course, I am! To begin with,
having nee-san in that state...
Delete that immediately!
Hey, cut that out already.
Do you want to be recorded
in a video in place of hers?
What...
You... I'll never ever forgive you!
She still needs more training.
Sensei, what's wrong?
Uhh... Nothing, sorry... Umm...
Open your textbooks on page 37.
Don't mess with me!
Of course, I can't use something
like that while teaching at class!
Then, I'll ask your sister instead.
You coward!
Alright then, we'll be...
G-Going through stuff
that'll appear in the exam...
Are you alright, sensei?
I'm sorry! Well, you see...
I have a mild cold.
I-It's vibrating!
Someone will end up hearing it!
No, I can't hold a lesson in this state...
It's getting stronger again!
That will make her give up right away.
Again...
This is bad! If this goes on, right in front of my students during the lesson...
I can't leave them during the lesson.
But I'll end up coming in front
of everyone if this goes on!
I can't! That's one thing I can't do!
Everything from here up to the last
part will appear next exam.
Be sure to study them.
All right, that would be all.
N-No need for salutations. Please excuse me.
She endured it. However...
You both are slutty sisters.
Y-You're wrong...
Neither I nor my sister is like that!
I'll never ever accept that!
Making me go through this...
You have quite the resolve, huh?
Wh-What are you doing here?
I just thought that I should grace you
with my cock, slutty Aina-sensei.
D-Don't mess with me!
What grace are you saying? I'll pass!
That amount demands some mopping.
You didn't come while in class, did you?
I'll never do such a thing!
I'll never ever yield to a cruel man like you!
That's the Aina-sensei that I know.
I'll also brave myself up
and make you fall from grace.
You're pushing your cock into me
while we're at such a place!
It's so deep!
No... Stop doing this!
I'll thoroughly push you into orgasm like this.
No, my tits!
Stop this! Not here, we'll quickly get...
OUT OF ORDER
No one will be coming here.
No, any more of this and I'll come...
Not so deep! Don't!
If you keep doing this to me...
Not down there!
Stop being stubborn and just be honest.
No, I can't! I don't want to feel it, and yet...
No... I won't give in!
I absolutely will...
...never give in!
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
GiT GuD Reikisha