Jousei Academy
As a result of stirring up trouble,
he was forcibly transferred to another school.
Although unaware at first, he was dumbfounded for a little while at what appears in front of him.
"Are you not the transferee who came here last time?
Have you started getting used to it here?"
His eyes were locked on the bright smile of this woman. Her name is Hagiura Aina.
She is a female teacher in his current school, Jousei Academy.
And on his former school, Ryou was caught for overstepping the limits
in humiliating his victims. To avoid a worst-case scenario this scandal might bring, he was transferred away.
On the school where he ended up, he meets someone
who shares the same face with a certain woman.
"Yes, everyone has been nice to me, so I got used to it here in no time."
Ryou smiles back at her, as his unbearable rage
gets redirected towards his nether region.
He couldn't know any better the reason why he felt like that.
Aina is actually the younger twin sister of Hagiura Yuuna,
the mastermind of him getting transferred away.
Similar to her elder sister, Aina is hugely popular on
students for her good looks and broad-mindedness.
As the adviser of the rhythmic gymnastics club,
she possesses an athletic and energetic body
with a top-notch figure that'll titillate every man.
Aina fails to notice as Ryou stares at her,
like he's licking every nook and cranny of her body.
A man who feels delighted from making authorities submit to him:
Kawabata Ryou
Using his status as a student, he sets his eyes upon the nearby authorities:
Female Teachers
The only one who he failed on out of several female teachers
he forced into submission: Hagiura Yuuna
and her younger sister: Hagiura Aina
Both of them have equally beautiful and voluptuous bodies
that can fuel a man's desire.
For someone who possesses a strange fetish like Ryou,
there are no better preys than them.
"Wh-What is the meaning of this!"
"Aina... Hey, stop this, I'm begging you!"
Aina and Yuuna meet each other in a classroom with nobody else around.
The rope restraining her is digging into her body,
accentuating the plumpness of her heavy and huge breasts.
Ryou's hands crawl over them in an indecent manner,
as he relentlessly squeezes them out of shape
In order to undo his past blunder, he sinks his fangs into the beautiful
female teacher sisters as he starts getting himself a blowjob.
Sansha Mendan
Three-shot Interview
Chaining Humiliation • School of Training
Original Animation
Bye, sensei!
Goodbye.
Oh, you're not going home yet?
How is it, have you started
getting used to it here?
Hagiura-sensei... Yes...
Everyone has been nice to me
since I transferred here.
You're going out. How about your club?
I have an appointment.
Well, then.
Okay, cheers!
Gosh, this isn't a drinking party, you know!
There's that late night watch
on loitering students lately.
It's too much for a passive teacher like you, Aina.
Gosh... Was that in the sports field?
You shouldn't worry too much
if they're just goofing around...
Littering the assembly hall with cigarette butts...
And even taking too long when called,
isn't that troublesome?
Really?
Is there a student in your
school that does that, nee-san?
What...
Oh... Yeah, right...
There was one I worried about in
the past, but that's over now.
So that happened.
Talk to me when something is up, though.
Since you've always been all ears to me.
Yeah, I'll tell you firsthand if that time comes.
Huh, Hagiura-sensei?
Huh?
Oh, my! Fancy meeting you here!
Yes, I just went to get something
that a friend borrowed.
How about you, sensei? Umm...
Oh, her name is Hagiura Yuuna.
She's my elder twin sister.
He's one of our... Hey, nee-san?!
N-No, it's nothing! Nothing at all...
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you! That's right!
Nice to meet you, of course!
What's the matter, nee-san?
N-No, it's nothing!
Oh, sorry. I have some stuff to do
and barely have any time.
Oh, I-I'm sorry for that.
She usually doesn't act that way.
Don't be. I was just a little
surprised, that's all.
Why is that boy...
He's one of our...
Could he have been transferred to Aina's school?
So, the stuff you suddenly needed
to do was meeting with me, sensei.
You!
The popular Aina-sensei is good at teaching
Japanese history, just like her older sister.
S-So you really are...
D-Don't do it! Don't lay your hands on Aina!
Only if you won't tell her about me.
Okay, I get it. I won't tell her anything about you.
You'll have to prove it.
Hey!
Wh-What are you doing?
You already know it.
I-I understand.
No!
Stop, I'm gonna do it!
I-It's so hard and huge!
This is pretty nostalgic!
How did I end up doing this?
Do a good job unless you
want her to take your place.
Alright, I know!
This is frustrating... I don't want this...
But this is good!
Something like this is...
I love your cock!
You're getting in the mood now.
Okay, then. I'll let you drink it.
I-Isn't this enough?
Don't ever lay your hands on Aina!
Okay, the same goes for you.
I get it.
I was worried what's gonna happen
when I got cornered and transferred,
but this a nice turn of events.
Hey!
Hagiura-sensei, what's the matter?
You're making such a scary face.
I want to ask you about something.
Wh-What would it be?
Did Yuuna blurt out something about it?
But, I had her shut her mouth yesterday...
Come with me.
We'll have a talk here.
What is your relationship with my sister?
Huh? Are you talking about Yuuna-san?
Don't dodge my question!
I happened to see it.
After my sister went away
yesterday, you met with her!
Why were you two inside the men's restroom?
No, that was...
I looked up about you.
Didn't you come from my sister's school?
So, you already know that much...
Do you have something to do with
her strange behavior in the past?
I understand. I'll talk.
O-Okay...
Aina... This can't be happening!
Are you Hagiura-sensei's sister?
The truth is, Hagiura-sensei
collapsed! Please hurry!
If anything happens to Aina, I'll...
Aina!
Why are you... Did Aina collapse...
Huh, what? Was that a lie?
Calm down, Aina really collapsed.
Or more accurately, I struck her down.
What did you just say?
L-Let me see Aina!
If you want to see her that much,
you shouldn't be acting like that.
Wh-What do you want me to do?
H-Hey, where are we right now?
We're in an unused classroom.
It's soundproof, exactly what we want.
What a convenient room.
So, you're planning to do strange
things at this school as well?
That's against our deal.
Just like I said before,
I'll end it here after we do it.
I also won't lay my hands on your sister.
Wait... You went straight away...
Let your voice out just like the old times.
Idiot! Like I can do such a thing!
No, that's...
Didn't you use to love it when I do this?
You're wrong! Idiot!
No...
You're pulling my nipples...
You're kneading my tits hard!
You're getting in the mood now.
Not down there!
No... Don't, don't do that—!
What are you saying when
you're this sopping wet?
Were you backed up from the last time?
No, wait...
Don't touch me down there!
There's nobody else here,
so feel free to get wild.
No, I can't do that!
I can't go wild!
You're being rough on my clitoris!
You're teasing it forcefully!
You're stirring deep inside my pussy!
It's driving me crazy, I'm gonna come!
No, don't! I'm gonna come already! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
That was such a gaudy orgasm.
Really, what a miserable bitch...
No, you're lower than dogs.
I'm lower than dogs? You're so mean!
But that's arousing!
We can end it here if you're already satisfied.
N-No! We're not done yet!
Let's go all the way!
I want your cock in my pussy!
That's a good answer. There...
No way, hey...
Aina! Why are you...
Huh, no way! Have you been here all along?
Stop thrusting your cock!
Aina can see us, I'm begging you!
That's too late, your little sister
already saw your true colors.
No, let me off! Stop thrusting your cock!
Stop making my pussy feel good!
Your anger is misplaced.
I'm even giving her so much pleasure, see?
No! Don't watch us, Aina!
He's making me feel good!
You shouldn't be watching this!
Are you jealous? You'll have
to wait until I satisfy her.
Are you saying that she's next?
No way, that's not our deal! You can't!
I'm begging you, I'll take care of your cock.
I'll give it lots of pleasure, so spare Aina...
You make Aina come, then.
Huh, you're so cruel!
No way... Such a thing...
Aina, I'm gonna make you come...
I have to do this, so forgive me!
Can you feel it on where she's touching you?
You're way lewder than your sister
despite your innocent looks.
Aina, is this alright? Are you feeling good?
That's great.
We're both feeling good since we're twins!
I'm glad that we're both getting off!
Get aroused as you pleasure
your younger sister.
You sisters should come together.
That's so deep!
Don't do that!
Don't you like getting it this rough?
No, Aina is watching us...
And yet, you're driving me crazy!
Your cock is reaching deep in my womb!
It feels good, you'll break me down!
Aina, my pussy is feeling so much pleasure!
I'm coming... I'm coming... I'm coming!
Your semen is splashing in my womb...
No matter how much you glare at me,
you sat on a desk used by students to study
as you drip with love juice and reach climax.
What kind of person are you?
I won't ever forgive you!
You should be ashamed!
And how are you not forgiving me?
I'll call the cops.
Obviously, after humiliating
my sister like that...
Fine with me.
Otherwise, I'd be raping you for nothing.
N-No, stop!
You shouldn't add up any more
crimes than you already have!
Thanks for the advice.
No, don't put it in!
Are you still a virgin, sensei?
Your pussy is tight as hell.
Th-That's right, I never did it before.
That's why you have to stop!
Popping the cherries of both
you sisters is the best!
Did you do this same cruel thing
to my sister? I won't forgive you!
Not that I care, but you'll wake your sister up.
This makes you my woman as well.
Ouch... Stop moving!
Aren't you glad that you never woke her up?
Nee-san, now it's my turn...
...to protect you!
I'll never ever yield!
I'll never lose against something like this!
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Next Time on Sansha Mendan...
I hate how this feels...
You suck too good for
someone who hates this.
No, this is gross...
And even though I hate this...
I'm not indecent!
No, don't look!
No, they're exposed!
Here, take a look.
Is that my sister?
Why? What's that? Delete that immediately!
That's what we call indecent.
Doesn't the same blood as hers flow in you?
Y-You're wrong! That isn't my sister at all!
You're wrong... Stop!
No... No!
No, you can't! Don't look!
Let me go, I'm begging you!
Somebody help me!
Scream or do whatever,
but nobody will come here.
Don't do that!
You're wrong! I hate this!
You're wrong, and yet...
Not my tits!
Stop groping me down there as well!
Any more than this...
Alright then, we'll be...
Going on stuff that'll appear in the exam...
Are you alright, sensei?
I'm sorry! Well, you see...
I have a mild cold.
I-It's vibrating!
Someone will end up hearing it!
Again...
This is bad! If this goes on, right in front of my students during the lesson...