Oh yes...
Come on!
Move over.
Jackpot.
Such a good catch.
Looks like you've got something good here.
Alright, lemme taste you.
Good grief.
You're already seriously out of you mind.
What?
Just who the hell are you?
Oh, could you be that?
Did you come here to be specially taken care of by me?
Whatt'ya say?
No. I came here from the heavens to take
care of the wild beast over here.
Now we're getting somewhere.
We'll have you try to do it, then!
A few hundred years later...
That bastard.
She told me she'd release me once
I reflected on my wrongdoings.
Wait, don't tell me she already forgot all about me?
Curses!
If this wretched piece of talisman wasn't
stuck in my pussy I'd already have...!
My name is Sanzou.
I'm still under training,
but under the orders of the emperor,
I'm on a journey to the western end of the world,
where a place named Tenjku can to be found.
I just started my travels, so many hardships still lay ahead,
but I'm doing my best to arrive at Tenjiku.
I'm... about to leak!
I really shouldn't do this, but...
Please forgive me on this occasion...!
Hey you there!
What are you doing below my foot?
Where the hell are you looking?
Up here!
Having the boldness and guts to
just pee below my foot like that,
you sure have balls, huh?!
I-I'm sorry!
I never noticed that,you were there!
I'm really sorry!
Goodbye, then.
Just wait a sec!
Wh-What is it?
Well, you see...
Sorry for yelling at you like that.
How do I put this...
I'd actually like to ask you one thing.
Ask me... one thing?
This ain't something hard.
See down there? Just take off that wretched
talisman off me and you're done.
Talisman?
U-Umm...
I-I'm actually a Buddhist monk,
so I can't really do that.
Stop yer stupid excuses!
If you're really a monk, then wouldn't it be your
priority to save those who are in need?
Or what?
You just want to leave and forsake a
poor helpless person on the road?
What's it gonna be?
I understand.
It's true that one of the duties of Buddhist
monks is to help those in need.
Which is why...
Yup, yup!
Now we're talkin'!
W-Well then...
Huh?
It won't peel off.
Just pull it harder!
O-Okay!
Ow, ow, ow.
Alright, alright, alright!
Now I'm back!
Hey you...
You pulled way too hard!
Now my pussy's completely shaven!
Even if you say that...
Though, it's true that you did save me.
I'll let you off this time.
U-Umm...
I shall take my leave now.
Whoa, wait a sec there.
You did save me back there.
Now I have to show my thanks.
Y-You don't have to do that.
I just did what's natural for a monk.
Just go with me.
No need to be so uptight.
H-Hey!
What are you doing?
I saw it while you were peeing.
Despite your looks, you actually have something amazing here.
P-Please stop.
Y-You can't touch me in those weird spots!
That's probably what your mouth says,
but this one here is reacting pretty wildly.
N-No way...
Well then, why don't we fully expose what's actually in here?
As I thought,
you really have an amazing dick over here.
I just touched it a bit,
and yet it's already this hard.
So you really do get aroused with the tip.
Then I'll make it even easier for you to get aroused.
Nice color here, I guess it's bound to be like this
after being covered for such a long time.
Also, it's already this wet.
It's even smooth and nice to touch.
S-Stop.
If you keep on touching the tip like that...
What? I was just playing with the tip and you already came?
Jeez, such a green uncut dick.
Man, this is such a waste.
All of this cum just thrown away like this.
Oh well, it looks like it can still be used anyway.
So just forget that.
What are you going to do?
What, you ask? Why thank you for saving me, of course!
Then why did you have to tie me up?
Well, that's because if you tried to resist,
I might accidentally kill you!
Now then,
let's dig in now, shall we?
Man, having a dick after 500 years really hits the spot.
And your thing fits snugly inside.
The tip is even reaching up to this point.
What?
Your dick is twitching hard inside my pussy.
Perhaps you're already about to cum after just putting it in?
Yes.
That's why...
Which is why, please hurry and pull it out.
No need to to hold back.
Just cum inside.
Well, no matter what you do,
I'm not letting you rest until I feel satisfied enough.
Hey now,
how about this?
Feeling good?
Oh yes.
This totally feels great.
Come on, do it more.
I've decided!
I can tell at a glance, you're currently on a journey, right?
Indeed, yes...
You...
I mean, I like your dick.
So,
I'm not really sure where you're headed,
but I'll accompany you all the way.
My name is Sanzo.
I'm currently traveling to reach Tenjiku.
But the way, it seems rougher than before.
What's this feeling?
What are you doing?
What do you think?
Please don't talk while you're stuffed with my dick!
Well, I noticed it was up and lively
early in the morning so I just...
I just thought of relieving you for a bit.
Th-That's just how my body naturally reacts.
It's not anything that you think.
Now, now,
it's already like this anyway,
so just cum at least once, okay?
Hey,w-wait...!
Hey...
Please stop...
You like this position, right?
Come on.
You can't do that!
Doing it in this kind of place...
It's fine.
No one will care what we're doing here.
Hey, move some more.
It feels good, right?
So do it more... more...!
Come on, push harder.
Move your hips more!
I'm at my limit.
I'm about to cum.
Already?
Stop, stop, don't cum yet!
Alright, next round!
I'm not thinking about that!
What are you saying?
You're a guy, right?
Come on, just keep it up and do it once more.
No good.
I'm going to completely run dry even before I reach Tenjiku.
I have to do something.
Oh yeah.
I remember my master saying something
before I started my journey.
Your tribulations will be centered upon a woman.
If, during your journey, you've finally run into such a fate,
simply open this talisman bag.
It will surely be of great use to you.
I wonder what this is.
A ring?
There's also some kind of a letter here.
Let's see...
Wait, so this is...
No way.
One more...