Come on!
Out of the way!
Jackpot. Just what I wanted.
You're really packing it, aren't ya?
Well then, let's get right into it.
There's something seriously wrong
with all of you monkeys.
Who the hell are you?
Oh, are you looking to fuck me too?
I am a messenger from the heavens,
sent to deal with you savages.
That so?
Then give me your best shot!
Several hundred years later...
That bitch... she said she'd
let me go after I repented.
She hasn't fucking forgotten
about me, has she?
Fucking hell!
If only there wasn't a goddamn
seal on my pussy, I'd...
My name's Sanzo.
Although I'm still a trainee,
the Emperor has sent me forth on a journey
to the west; to a country called India.
My travels have only just begun,
yet all sorts of bad things have happened already.
But despite all that,
I'm doing my best to make it to India.
Uh-oh, I'm busting...
I really shouldn't be doing this, but...
Buddha, forgive me!
Hey, you little shit!
What te hell are you doing in front of me?!
Where the fuck are you looking?
Up here, dumbass!
You've got some real balls, pissing in front
of someone without even a second thought!
I-I'm terribly sorry!
I didn't see you there!
I'm really sorry!
I'll be on my way now!
Hold it, twerp!
Y-Yes?
Well, y'see... Sorry for yelling
at you and all that.
Yeah...?
I kinda have a little favor to ask you.
A favor?
It's nothing too difficult. I just need you
to take this disgusting seal off for me.
Seal?
B-But I'm just a monk, I can't really...
Come the fuck on! If you're a monk,
aren't you supposed to help people in trouble?!
Or are you saying that you'll just
ignore someone who needs help?!
I guess you're right...
Yeah, helping people is definitely
something that I should be doing.
Damn right it is!
Well then...
Huh? It's not coming off.
C'mon, put your back into it, goddamn!
Y-Yes!
Ouchie.
Here it comes! Here it fucking comes!
I'm back, bitches!
You fucker! You pulled way too damn hard!
Where the fuck's my hair's at?
B-But you said...
Well, either way, you did save me.
I'll let you off the hook.
R-Right, so I'll just take my leave now...
Whoa, there. You just saved my life,
I gotta repay you somehow.
N-No, don't worry about it.
I was just doing my duty as a monk.
C'mon, don't be shy!
W-Wait! What are you doing?
I got a glance when I saw you earlier,
but you've got a real beast under there,
even with that cute face and all.
S-Stop! You can't touch it!
You might be saying that,
but this guy says otherwise.
N-No...
So how about we take a look
at the real deal now?
I knew it. You have a really nice cock.
I barely touched it but it's already rock hard.
I guess you're really sensitive at the tip.
I'll make it even easier for you to feel pleasure.
You've been keeping it safe all this time,
so it's got a really nice color to it now.
And it's so wet, too!
Not to mention smooth,
which makes it easier to work with.
N-No, don't...
If you keep touching
the tip like that, I'm gonna...
I just played with the tip a little
and you already came?
Goddamnit, this is why monks have shitty cocks.
Man, that blows. What a waste.
But it doesn't look done quite yet,
so whatever, I guess.
What are you going to do to me?
I'm going to thank you for saving me.
So why'd you tie me up?!
Well, if you resisted too much,
I might've ended up killin' you by accident!
Now, then...
Let's dig right in.
Oh man, my first cock in five
hundred years feels so good!
It fits perfectly.
Your tip is all the way up in here.
What's this?
Your cock is twitching inside me!
I just put it inside me,
but you're going to cum already?
Y-Yes...
So please take it out of yourself quickly!
I don't give a fuck. Just let it out inside me.
It doesn't matter too much.
I'm not gonna let you rest until I'm satisfied anyway.
Come on! How's that?!
That feel good?
This is great! This is so fucking great!
Come on, more!
I've made up my mind!
From the looks of it, you're on a journey, right?
Yes, I am...
I've kinda come to like you. Or, well, your cock.
So, I don't know where you're going,
but I'll stay with you until then.
– My name's Sanzo, and I'm on a journey to India.
– Which way are we heading? Let's get going!
– Oh man, I'm fucking hyped!
– My journey seems like it will be a long one.
What is this feeling?
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't try talking with your mouth full, please!
Well, it was kinda standing up,
so I thought I'd suck it down to size for you.
Th-That's just a normal,
biological reaction. It's not a signal to...
Whatever, now that it's like this, just let it out.
W-Wait!
Please, stop!
You like this, don't you? Come on!
We shouldn't be doing this here.
It's fine! No one gives a fuck.
Come on, it feels good, right?!
Do it harder! Harder!
Move your hips more!
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum!
Already? No, don't cum yet!
Next round!
Let's take a break!
What are you saying? You're a guy aren't you?
Grow a pair and let's go again!
This is bad.
At this rate, I'm going to be
dead before I get to India.
Oh, right! Before I left,
the priest gave me something...
You will be met with great obstacles.
If you are ever in trouble during your travels,
be sure to open this pouch.
I am sure it will be of help to you.
What is this?
A ring?
Oh, there's a letter with it. Let's see...
Wait, so this is a...
Just one more time...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: fyurie
editor: aux
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч