– Good morning kid!
– You're seriously doing it again?!
Why do you have to do this every single morning?!
Not there...
Wait! I have the protective bag!
Goku-san, um...
If you don't mind, how about I...
I'll... your...
Hm? What's gotten into you?
Aren't you being a little more
aggressive than usual today?
There we go.
Okay, here you go.
So it gets like this?
Hey, what are you doing? Come on, hurry up!
Do me too!
R-Right!
So first, I put this here...
What the hell is this?!
I can't take it off!
Hey, what the hell is this?!
You little... what the hell did you do?!
All is of Buddha's teaching.
All without form become one.
Let those in vain become whole.
Purge them of evil. Void of the Buddha.
Hey... What's this?!
You piece of...
No matter how much you try,
the only one who can take that off is me.
All is of Buddha's teaching. All without form become one.
Don't fuck with me. You really think this will...
Let those in vain become whole. Purge them of evil. Void of the Buddha.
Shit! It feels so good, I can't even move!
That is a noble treasure called an Aureole.
It is blessed with divine power that will give
great pleasure to the one it's attached to,
but it will not allow them to reach climax.
You'll be stuck in a state of ecstasy
with no chance at relieving yourself.
What is this? It feels so good, but...
I just need a small push to orgasm, but...
Even if you try to pleasure yourself, it won't work.
The only way to relieve yourself is to...
with the caster of the magic... me...
You have to accept me...
I want it! I want his cock so bad!
I want to cum with it so bad!
If you pledge yourself to me as my disciple
and vow to follow the path of Buddhism,
I will do whatever you need me
to do to make you feel better.
What the hell? Who the hell
would want to be your disciple?
You seem to be hanging in there quite well,
but how about now?
Expand!
Cock! I want his cock!
If this goes on any longer, I'm gonna lose it!
Everything's going blank...
How about now?
Will you be my disciple, or...
Fine! I will! So please...
You will devote yourself to Buddhism
and become my disciple, correct?
I will!
I will! I'll be your disciple or whatever
the hell else you want me to be!
Please! Please, hurry! Give me your cock!
By becoming my disciple you will revere Buddha,
help those inflicted by disease
and those less fortunate than you.
I'll do it!
I'll do anything you tell me to!
So please hurry, hurry and shove
your cock into my pussy!
Okay, then...
I'm not doing this with any impure feelings...
This is all to make Goku-san my disciple.
This is unavoidable.
Hurry! Give me your cock!
Here I go!
It's here!
It's in! It's going so deep inside me, all at once!
What's going on? It's so tight!
It's like it's trying to squeeze me dry!
I'm cumming! It feels so good, I... I...
Me too, I'm gonna cum too!
I haven't even moved, but I'm gonna cum!
It's flooding into me!
Now I'm sure Goku-san will...
And so, from that day forward,
Goku-san became my disciple.
She still had her violent tendencies, but...
She stopped going after me when I was asleep.
However, as a result,
I started feeling a little weird myself...
Master, if seems like I still need much more training.
No... not there...
Is it okay if I peel this?
What do you mean by that?
You haven't peeled your dick before?
No...
Okay then, watch closely.
See?
Wait, not there...
I... I'm gonna cum!
You can't yet!
Huh? Why not?
Your cum goes in here.
Huh? It won't go in.
Wait.
Don't be in such a rush.
Now, just slide it in.
This is... amazing!
I'm gonna cum!
Cum! Give me lots of your cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
If you keep moving like that, I'll...
It's fine, don't hold back. Cum!
I'm cumming!
More... I want more!
Human sacrifice?
Yes, every year,
we sacrifice a boy from the village as
an offering to the god of the mountains.
I see.
This is most likely the work of
a type of demon, probably a fox,
deceiving you into believing that
they are a god of the mountains.
Rest assured.
Now that we are here, we will make
sure that this evil spirit is exorcised.
Will you really?
I can hardly believe you would go
so far for a village unable to repay you!
It's fine.
Our stop here is just another point
on the path that Buddha has set for us.
I believe that helping those in need
is a step on the path of virtue.
Goku-san, are you really standing guard?
You're not sleeping on the job, are you?
Goku-san?
What's the matter?
Hey,
if you're there, answer me!
Goku-san!
Who the hell are you?
You finally showed yourself, huh?
You fake god!
Huh? Are you getting in the way of my offering?!
Sorry to disappoint you, but this kid is with me.
I don't know what kind of
lowly breed of demon you are,
but by opposing me, you've sealed your fate.
That's my line!
She threw her staff?!
Take this!
She's strong!
No... if this keeps up...
I've no choice, I'll use my last resort.
It is my loss!
Wh-What?!
I'm terribly sorry about earlier.
I had not the faintest idea that
you were a being of such power.
Please allow me to call you
"onee-sama" from now on.
Yeah, that's good! Glad you know your place!
Here, Monk-san, please drink as well.
Please do not be so reserved.
I-It's so delicious.
G-Goku-san?!
Huh? I'm starting to feel sleepy as well...
W-What is this?!
Goku-san? What's the matter?!
Please get a hold of yourself!
Can't you be quiet? My head is throbbing like hell.
The hell are these?
Seems like you two are finally awake.
To think you'd fall for that act so easily...
I barely broke a sweat.
I guess it's true when they say
that monkeys have no brains.
It's not my fault!
This kid forgot to bring everything,
even his protective charms!
What is it that you want?
Oh, isn't that obvious?
I'm going to take really good care of you. Really good.
No, stop!
Hey, what the hell do you think you're doing?!
That's my cock!
No, it's mine!
All right, it's about time we got this party started.
Oh my, I touched it only a little,
but it's so hard already.
Let's have a face to face meeting!
Wow, it's so big, but the foreskin
is still covering it like a child's.
I wonder what the place you've been hiding looks like.
Oh, so it's sensitive?
Just by being touched, you get turned on?
I guess if I do this, you'll get even more turned on?
You're getting so aroused that
your balls are bulging this much.
No, stop! I'm gonna...
Hey, you can't cum yet!
I'll do something even better for you right now.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Even when it's sandwiched in between
my boobs, I can still suck it, huh?
Oh, come on... Now I'm all sticky with your cum.
I think some punishment is in line for you.
Wh-What are you going to do to me?
Don't worry, it won't hurt at all.
What a cute ass you have.
It's so squishy, even though you're a guy.
Hey, wait, what are you doing?
You can't! Not there!
You're doing something so immoral!
No, don't!
Aren't you even harder than before?
Did you get aroused from having your asshole licked?
Come on, how about you give your little monkey
over there a treat from her master?
This is so unclean!
So unclean!
My mind is...
I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
You're still hard, even though you came so much.
Looks like you aren't quite done yet.
Next, I'll have you cum lots inside my pussy, okay?
It's inside me!
This is good!
I love the feeling of it reaching all the way inside me!
It's hitting the entrance of my womb!
At this rate, I'm gonna be killed!
I'll need to bet everything I have on this!
All is of Buddha's teaching.
All without form becomes one.
Why? Why right now?!
What the hell is he thinking?
You came so much,
but you still have a lot to offer, don't you?
Hot! My body's getting so hot!
I can't think of anything but cock right now!
Right in front of my eyes, his cock... my cock is...
I want it... I want his cock!
My...
Cock!
No, don't do that...
Thus, we defeated the demon
pretending to be the mountain god, but...
Master! Onee-sama!
How could you leave me behind?!
Well, I had no intention of making
you my disciple in the first place.
Please, I beg you!
Right? Right? Onee-sama,
please say something to him, too!
Fine, I will! Stop rubbing my tits!
Onee-sama, your boobs are so bouncy!
Hey, stop it!
– I have a feeling that this journey will never have a dull moment.
– No, I don't want to! I'm going to keep rubbing them!
– Stop it already!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч