Evan Metcalfe Subs.
SECRET JOURNEY VOL.2
Really, Again?
Why do you do this every morning.
There it is ahhhh
I have the seal.
Excuse me, Miss Monkey.
If you can,
I have to be comfortable.
Oh how timely this morning has been.
Bring it on.
Here is her vagina it looks like this, ahhhh.
Are you ready to eat me out yet? Let me feel good too.
Ah so I put this around her clitoris... right here.
What the hell is this?
Take it off.
Hey this is going.
You little shithead you think you can get away with doing anything that you want
(magic spell)
what the hell.
You little shit.
No matter how hard you struggle only I can remove it.
What is this nonsense?
My entire body is tingling.
This magical artifact is call the hoop of lust.
It uses vibrations to give pleasure.
But, you will never orgasm while you are wearing it.
The pleasure will build up and drive you crazy.
It will help you learn to curb your greediness.
What is this.
The feeling is amazing.
When I am this close to orgasm.
If you want to orgasm, masterbating is useless.
If you want to solve the problem.
Only the one who put it on you
can satisfy you with their penis
I want to fuck her.
Want to satisfy her with my penis.
If you are willing to repent for freedom
convert to buddha and become my apprentice.
As soon as you do I will ease your suffering.
You idiot, what nonsense.
Who wants to be your disciple
I know.
It is hard to come to terms with
(chanting)
Want sex, sex, sex.
If this continues I might not be able to hold out
I want his cock in my pussy.
Well, what do you say?
Do you want to be my disciple?
I understand, hurry up.
So do you want to convert to buddha, and be my disciple?
I don't care I will convert to your disciple.
So hurry up and fuck me!
After become a disciple of Buddha.
You must be polite and humble
I will listen to you, no matter what!
So come over here and fuck my pussy.
This is not the typical mood to have sex during.
This is to make Goku my disciple, and to make her polite and courteous in the future.
Hurry up and fuck me.
Here I go.
Come inside.
Come deeper.
Plunge all the way inside me.
What's happening.
It is so tight.
It is squeezing me so tightly
I'm cumming.
And you just put it inside.
Wukong I'm cumming too.
Hold still please.
Release it inside me.
So wukong will.
From this day on, be my disciple.
Although we do it in some crazy locations, I no longer get attacked in my sleep.
But I have some strange feelings.
After all that practice teacher, I failed.
Such a place.
Can I peel it back.
Do not peel the foreskin.
Well.
It looks so good.
Do you see?
That there.
You need to release some but.
It still isn't cumming.
Why.
You can only cum in my pussy.
It isn't easy to get it in.
Wait a second.
Don't try so hard.
To come in.
This.
Is amazing.
Here it comes.
Shoot it all inside
oh my god, oh my god
Lane.
It's okay cum whenever
I'm cumming!
I want more, so much more.
Eh!
A sacrifice!
The sad fate of our village is to sacrifice a beautiful boy every year.
I understand.
This is probably the.
Rudeness of the fake gods.
These are the kind of monsters they are.
Please don't worry about it.
Since I will use the Buddha's power to chase these monsters away.
Wow this is really.
We would be willing to pay you, as well as let you marry into our village.
I can't believe you would do this.
Coming to this village is the will of the Buddha.
Saving lost sheep is the true spiritual path.
Wu is missing from sight.
You better not be sleeping secretly.
Wukong if you want food, you better answer me.
Wukong.
Who are you?
Finally you show your face.
It's about time.
All you want from this journey is gourmet food.
Sadly for you, this boy is my first love.
Although, what realm are you even from monster.
I dare you to stop me from doing things that need doing.
Thats my line.
What a move to perform at the start of a fight.
This is bad.
She is strong.
Sure enough, it is going poorly.
So I have to use THAT trick
I surrender.
What the Hell.
When you are the bottom in strength you have to watch out for others.
Would you like a refill sister?
Oh well I understand.
Monk also don't hesitate to indulge.
Oh it is delicious.
Wukong?
I feel strange.
What is this?
Wukong are you all right, pull yourself together.
Shut-up my head hurts so bad that I want to die.
What are these?
Finally awake?
I can't believe you were fooled by such a cheap trick.
I am shocked you follow such a weak master.
Pssh, what can I do.
He used a spell on me.
What do you want?
I am not sure yet.
To love you, or well... it.
Stop that!
What the fuck you asshole.
That is my cock.
Actually, it's mine.
The lets get started, shall we.
After touching it a few time it is already this hard.
Let me see your cock.
Wow you are clearly huge and it isn't just foreskin either.
Under the foreskin is what I want.
Ah you are quite sensitive
I just peeled it back and you are already feeling it.
So you should feel this even more.
You are so aroused your balls are already constricted.
Ah, wow.
Is it necessary to do this.
Oh now, no cumming yet
I know something very nice to do next.
Does it feel good?
You are so big that I can still lick it.
Ah.
You made some very sticky milk.
You are a bad boy, now I will punish you.
Why do you want to?
No reason don't worry.
This won't hurt a bit.
You have a cute ass.
It clearly is a boys, but it is so soft.
Hold on what are you doing?
You should not do anything at this place.
You are licking that dirty place.
Stop I can't take it.
You seem to be harder than before.
Is it because you were really feeling good while I ate your ass.
Don't you want to give Wukong some of her master thick creamy milk.
Stop that isn't clean.
She is stirring my insides.
I'm going to die.
I have never seen anyone shoot so much cum so farm.
It seems not as flashy, but.
This time blow your load in my pussy.
It feels very good
I am feeling it in my deepest parts.
Even at the tip of my womb.
I may die of exhaustion soon.
I must take a risk
(incantation)
Why now of all times?
What exactly is he thinking?
Few are worthy of shooting inside me.
Only the very strong.
My body is so hot
I want his cock so badly.
I want to have sex right now.
It's Mine!
Penis.
Ah.
What? I cant!
After we drive out the counterfeit God for all the evil monsters in the village.
We embark on a journey to india.
Master and sister you are so mean leaving me behind, what if I got lost?
No not that, I meant I didn't take you on as a disciple.
I beg you.
Well well well big sis is also giving some helpful advice
I know stop rubbing my breasts.
Sis has some amazing breasts.
Stop it.
This trip seems to be becoming a very lively one.