Her breasts feel really nice.
I really can't see her face, though...
You don't have to do a single thing.
Just keep that stupefied expression and let yourself go.
This voice...
This hair...
And these big tits...
Miyako-san, she's really gotten into my head...
Just cum as your dick is enveloped
by the breasts you love so much.
Oh no...!
Oh crap, I was just about to let out at the moment.
Miyako-san?
Good morning, Kabuto-kun.
Good morning.
Wait! What are you doing to me while I'm asleep?
I thought I'd wake you up,
but then I found something that was already 'wide awake'.
I just wanted to ease your thing up a bit.
That's not what I meant!
How did you get in with the door locked?
Your grandmother gave me a thumbs up, along with the keys.
That woman, because she's the head of the school
I'm leaving my grandchild to you
she feels like she can do anything that she wants!
Hm? Don't you want it?
I want it.
This salty combination of dirt and sweat...
Tastes a bit bitter too.
I happened to have fallen asleep right after masturbating.
I haven't taken a bath yet, either.
You don't have to masturbate.
You just need to tell me that you want it.
Because your fluids are my nourishment.
Just keep your thing stiff and big,
and cum whenever you want to.
Are you listening, Kabuto-kun? Let it all out inside me.
I did say that I don't mind the dirt,
but this is more than I imagined.
You're drooling.
Did cumming feel so good for you that your mind just melted?
It already melted quite some time ago,
and you're the one who did it.
I've been able to resist her allures and advances till now, but...
The normal truth
The fact where a single
truth is to be accepted
with absolute certainty
Why are you telling me that?
Don't mind it.
I'm just saying it to myself.
You've just made it all slimy.
I don't think the smell will go away even if I wash it.
Wait... so is she going to swallow it?
Figures.
Hey, Miyako-san.
I'm someone who left my home.
So there's no need to follow such customs and traditions.
You're the only one who thinks that.
The headmaster and your grandmother
still consider you as part of the clan.
I can't really inherit the family name,
or should I say I don't really want to.
No matter what you choose, the only
path for me is to follow yours.
It's always been like this,
after Miyako came into this school and
introduced herself as my fiancée.
She'd constantly say that it's all for me,
and seems do to lots of things for my sake.
Even going so far as to go a little overboard with lewd things.
I actually still haven't officially accepted her as my fiancée.
Hey, why do you have a change of clothing
stocked inside my own drawers?
I thought there would be situations like this,
so I prepared by slipping in a few pieces of clothing each day.
And not just your uniform...
Don't you have a problem hiding your underwear inside my room?
If you want to wear one on your head, then go ahead.
Just remember to throw them away afterward.
That's just harsh.
If you're really going to be my wife,
then I'd rather have you go around
for the entire day without panties!
You sure are something, ordering a girl to go without panties.
I think I'm actually impressed.
Eh? So you're thinking about it like that?
Then it's good that I'm your fiancée.
Sexual harrassment is just... no...
Kabuto-kun.
Miyako-san, don't people ever tell you
that you've got a sharp tongue?
How rude.
I only say these kinds of things to you.
That's even worse!
If you'll excuse me.
Miyako-san!
I wanted to thank you.
I heard you collected and brought the reports here.
I just did what I had to.
Y-Yeah, I guess you did.
Then, shall we go home?
I have to get my bag from the classroom first.
She s really aloof, as usual.
Well, she does help me with classwork,
and assists me,with my fencing rehabilitation.
Not to mention having big tits...
Guess she really is the best as my wi-
Wait just a moment, Miyako-san!
Why aren't you wearing panties?
You told me not to, right?
then I'd rather have you go around
for the entire day without panties!
For real?
Why did she have to actually do what I said?
So... since morning?
That would be correct.
Then that means, it's been rubbing
with her stockings the entire day.
Miyako-san, would you be so kind
as to give me a little of your time?
So, can I touch it?
Do whatever you want.
Wait!
Use that table over there, and do a sexy pose for me?
Is this to your liking?
That's the best!
Amazing, for me to get this aroused just by letting you do this.
I thought it'd be a bit rougher,
but I never thought you'd simply blurt it out.
It makes me feel uneasy.
Well, your pussy looks really beautiful.
So I just...
Oh? So that's the only beautiful thing about me?
Please don't say it like that.
My head is already occupied too much with this.
You're such a coward for someone who
easily goes with his own feelings.
If you want, then I shall accept any kind of sex play that you desire.
Then, I'll take you up on that.
Just getting into licking it instead of having sex....
This feels kind of complicated.
Now you're getting pushy.
Sorry, Miyako-san.
But I can't hold back any longer.
It's part of my responsibility,
so it's no problem for me.
It's tight!
Miyako-san... is this your first time?
Don't worry about me, just continue.
Sorry, I thought you already...
That I already experienced it?
But, you acted really fine with these kinds of things.
Are you going to stop then?
I won't force you to.
I'll continue, I'll continue.
But, you'll have to tell me if it becomes too much for you.
Alright I'll let you know if it does.
That's kind of half-assed.
Move more.
How exactly do I control myself in this kind of situation?
It feels like my insides are being pulled out.
Moving your hips vigorously like that...
Does it feel that good inside me?
Yes, it feels so good I can't think anymore.
Oh no...
You're about to cum, right?
Your dick is bulging inside me.
Just cum wherever you want to.
I'm about to... I'm about to...!
Cum sure is amazing, looking at it again like this.
For you to be able to release this much jelly-like stuff.
Hey,
did I do well?
Well? It felt really good.
I see.
It's good that you're happy with it.
How about you?
It felt really painful.
I thought I was about to die.
Just kidding.
What are we going to do tomorrow?
Why don't we just proceed as normal?
Huh?
You're right. It'd be too weird if we suddenly
act differently toward each other.
I just did what a wife would rightfully do.
So I'm still going to follow you.
Then that means, she doesn't really like me,
and does all of this just for my household...?
Kabuto-kun.
Are you familiar with this?
That's...!
That's the one that suddenly disappeared
from the pocket of my pants!
My precious thing!
That explains why I somehow keep losing things lately,
so it's her doing after all.
"My Workplace is Actually Erotic" series.
"Family Restaurant" chapter.
Stop!
It's not what you think!
I understand that it's not just part of the norm.
I bought them knowing that there isn't
a single shred of reality in them!
You seem to have a really extreme hobby here.
Right now, there are two cold toys... lodged in my ass and pussy.
Now that you mention it, she looked like she
was having a hard time walking since earlier.
So, what do you want me to do?
I want you to let me into your perverted hobby.
Then, why don't we see first if you can
make it to the dorm with that?
The way you try to get into my hobbies like that,
is in a way, already considered perverted, right?
Not really.
A better way to captivate you is to actually
concentrate on porn mags.
I'm just studying the various sexual fetishes that you have.
It's frustrating that I can't even complain.
You sure love watching girls as you make them do this.
What a brute.
Should I take that as a provocation?
This is really fun when you see her react like that!
The vibration reverberates further when I try to hold it in tighter!
Miyako-san, these two in front...
Good day, Onee-sama.
Good day.
Congratulations on getting to the finals.
Thank you.
Of course,
Ruriko-sama is one of the winning candidates.
I just have to do it... right?
Everything's over once they find out,
but I want to try shaming her till the very end!
Ruriko-sama?
Are you not feeling well?
I-I'm... alright.
This is nothing.
Nothing, eh?
Guess I'll have to see how much she can muster.
Oh no!
It's going to leak if this goes on.
Umm, Ruriko-sama?
I think you really need some rest.
She's fine, don't you girls worry.
Miyako-san's just busy lately,
perhaps she just caught a bit of a fever, yeah, that's right!
Well then!
Get well soon.
My heart's about to explode.
Were you satisfied?
Satisfied?
Another different problem was about to happen
if I'd continued watching you like that.
It's soaking wet.
Your dick is already stiff too.
Quite a nice moan you have there.
Well, it's very wet here already.
That's because my pussy got teased and stirred up.
Of course it would be wet.
Not deep inside...
My insides feel tingly,
My pussy might get molded to your dick's shape.
You sure are getting the hang of my dick.
Yeah, I am.
All the while imagining your dick within me.
It wants it so badly that I'm actually trying to ease the urge.
I'm honored to hear that.
It's suddenly inside my ass...!
It can still fit.
Then I'll go all the way.
I actually had to insert the vibrator carefully in there.
My body is slowly transforming into the
slutty form that your dick wants it to be.
I'm starting to get used to your tightness too.
Your dick... it's going in and out of my ass.
It's pleasuring both my holes.
If you keep pushing into my ass that hard,
it'll loosen up.
Then I'll just have to keep it sealed with my dick.
Just say that you want to keep fucking my ass forever.
It's coming.
I'm being fucked hard in both sides.
Oh yes...
I'm about to cum.
Okay then, just let it all out in my asshole.
It's pouring inside.
It's overflowing inside my ass.
No, don't!
This is all your fault.
Now both my holes feel loose.
Hey, Kabuto-kun.
We continue to have sex like this,
but I wonder why the distance between
us still hasn't changed one bit?
That's, my own issue. Or my family's issue, I suppose.
Not being clear with it, huh?
Sorry, but can you wait for a while longer?
Fine.
Even after you've played with my body countless times,
even if you've found another woman at that time,
I promise that I will never, ever hold anything against you.
Scary, scary, scary!
Is Miyako-san, who grew up following
family customs and traditions,
really happy staying with me like this?
I'd be happy if it's because of me, and
not because of the family household.
In the end, the only thing I'm certain about,
is that she has a very erotic body.
What's wrong?
You seem unable to focus.
You know, I'm quite grateful to you.
live already given up armored fencing once.
But thanks to you, I am now able to wield the sword again.
You're saying too much.
That's just part of my responsibility.
You don't have to be too uptight about it.
The usual response again, huh?
Miyako-san, are you having fun when you're with me?
Why do you ask that?
For you, it might be very important to adhere to family customs,
but I think there are many other ways for you to enjoy life.
Ways that are outside those customs.
I guess what I want to ask is, what do you really want to do?
Kabuto-kun.
I'm sorry!
Duel with me in a fencing match.
Huh?
Right now, I'm very upset.
Because someone just trampled upon my way of life.
And it is at a level that I've only felt for the first time.
I understand.
Let's do it.
Way of the Knight
I am honored to duel with you, Knight Ruriko.
I vow to fight with my all in this match.
I-I lost.
Miyako-san, that technique earlier...
It was the technique that you once used
against an adult opponent before.
At that time, I was pressured by an outdated education
system, and harsh fencing training.
My heart sank as I asked why it should be me.
I then saw you,
wholeheartedly enjoying fencing
amidst the boring adults who only seek to approve
those who are already talented in the first
place, no matter how good you become.
I felt like I saw my salvation at that time.
I'm not as great as you think.
I was literally just enjoying myself at that time.
Then, what I saw was simply a vision
that I enforced myself to believe in.
I thought you did those things for me simply
because of your family customs.
Then, I'm the one who simply forced
myself to believe in my own vision?
The you that I saw as a child soothed my heart.
So this time, I want to save the dream that you hold dear.
Then, from the very beginning you...
I came to you of my own free will.
Using my family customs, and my fiancée status as an excuse.
Family customs just aren't enough to let me
give my own self to a man I do not love.
I would have liked for you to realize that yourself.
S-So... then,
in preparation for tomorrows finals,
our duel is now over.
Yes?
Miyako-san?
It'd be hard to walk with it bulging like this, right?
But, tomorrow's match is important.
I want to do it.
Can't I?
Please do.
Kabuto-kun, just stay there.
His bodily fluids mixing together feel so sticky
that my tongue might just get stuck.
I don't think this will be enough.
Could she take it in just a bit more?
Your face tells me that it's not enough for you.
I want it inside you deeper, I guess.
Then you can use this mouth however you want to.
Here I go then.
Wrap your tongue around it more.
I can let it out now, right?
Then savor it.
It's going down my throat,
I feel it sliding slowly inside me.
Now it's your turn to feel pleasure.
Wait...
You came?
Don't move.
If you stimulate my pussy now...
But, you're the one moving.
Why?
My hips won't stop.
I'm more aroused, now that I've seen your cumming face.
No, don't say that.
Miyako-san.
What?
I love you.
If you say that to me now...
I'm going to cum again!
Oh yes...
I can't stop myself from rubbing your dick inside me.
Oh no...
I'm cumming again.
It's okay, just cum as many times as you want.
I don't want to cum alone.
I want you to cum with me too.
Your opponent will be Claris.
Are you good to go?
TL note: Keigan Shishin-style = "Discerning Ruling Heart" style
I shall prove the superiority of the Keigan Shishin-style.
I'm thinking of going back to my place
once the tournament is over.
Do you want to go with me?
Scared to go back home alone.
Quite the klutz as usual.
I don't mean that...
I want to tell my parents about you.
I see.
Oh, Kabuto-kun, your necktie isn't properly fixed.
Hey, we haven't done that one important 'ceremony' yet, right?
A kiss.
You were too busy with my body,
that you didn't even take notice of my lips.
Sorry, you're absolutely right.
It's time.
Watch carefully.
For I shall fight, and win this duel for you.
Yeah, end it quickly, and let's finally kiss!
That's quite a heavy demand, we're talking about Claris here.
Onee-sama, do your best!
Ruriko-sama, you're wonderful!
Hey, Kabuto-kun.
Do whatever you want.
Was that wrong?
I mean, you can love me now.
I'm not taking that faked tsundere act.
I love you, Kabuto-kun.
Why are you smiling?
Was that wrong again?
No, it's just that I can't hold my happiness in.
Hey,
let's kiss, right here, right now.
In here?
But that's just...
Look, everyone's watching us now.
Oh, but you were the one who promised a kiss after the match.
Yes, I did indeed say that.
The sequence of events might be out of order,
but I want you,
to take my first time here.