Whats going on?
He sure does have a cheeky penis despite having such a cute face.
My lower body feels somewhat refreshed.
I thought it would be smaller, but it sure is big.
I can hear something.
I feel good.
I see. That's good.
It made you all googly-eyed, and you went all for it.
Am I hearing voices in my dreams? No, that's not it.
This isn't a dream!
You're finally awake, Kenta.
Good morning, Ken-kun.
What are you two doing?
What do you mean? You can tell just by looking.
We're giving you a hand job.
Th-That's not what I meant. Why are
you doing it so early in the morning?
There's no way we wouldn't devour
a virgin living under the same roof.
Right? They do say that it's a woman's shame
not to accept a man's seduction.
So just get eaten up like a good boy.
You have a look on your face like this is your first time.
You're so cute, Kenta.
This is the first time your nipple has been
licked. It's popping up just like a girl's.
It's like I'm sucking a dick.
You're about to cum, aren't you?
Am I right? I can't tell.
Exactly. The dick in our hands is telling us everything we need to
know, even if you go red in the face
from holding back your moans.
Just cum already! Squirt your cheap virgin milk all over.
I love cum.
I want you to cum all over my hand.
Fap fap, squirt squirt. Fap fap, squirt squirt.
Ah! There it is!
It's squirting like a fountain.
You sure came a lot, Kenta.
Piping hot dick milk that might burn me!
I got plenty.
Holy Slut Sisters Banding Diary
Ah, I'm so hungry!
Saki-nee, Maki-nee, breakfast is ready!
Ah, it looks so yummy! Good job, Kenta.
Auntie wasn't kidding when she said that
she taught you how to do Chores.
What's the matter, Kenta? You seem down.
W-Well, you guys did that to me this morning.
Hey, not fair, Saki-chan! What do you think you're doing taking
advantage of the situation and playing tricks on Ken-kun?
Let's step back. Step back.
How did things turn out like this?
I started living with relatives about a week ago
due to circumstances at my new school.
That's when I had a reunion with my two cousins, who are
sisters, and who I used to play with a lot when I was little.
The sexy Yankee-type, tanned girl is Saki-nee.
This is how she looked when I first met her, by the way.
This fair-skinned, slightly naughty girl is Maki-nee.
This is how she looked when I first met her.
But there isn't a shred of those looks left anywhere in these two.
Oh? Hmm?
Crap!
What have you been staring at all this time, Kenta?
I see. Ken-kun is around that age.
No, I didn't! I didn't look at anything!
You're so-lucky, Kenta! You get to live
with these two beautiful twins.
Right! There may be some sexual happenings as well!
What are you two doing?
I don't have to pay for rent or food. I only
take care of these two in exchange.
That was the arrangement made between both families.
I knew it sounded too good to be true.
Hey, I have a question for you, Kenta.
Sure, I'll answer if I can.
Don't worry, it's an easy one.
Hey, Kenta... are you a virgin?
Who would have thought that the two I looked
up to would turn into such slutty beauties.
Or rather into hot chicks.
By the way, Ken-kun, have you made up your mind?
Made up my mind about what?
He's going to choose me of course. Right, Kenta?
What are you going on about?
Geez! We told you to decide which one
of us is going to take your virginity.
What? That wasn't a joke?
Of course, his first time will be with the one he likes.
Why does it have to be you, Saki-chan?
Shut it! You can just go have kinky sex with that rich geezer.
I already broke up with that upstart geezer.
You can just meet up with that pig who gives off that
good-for-nothing sleazy vibe that you love so much.
You idiot! I dumped that loser a long time ago!
Come on, you two!
There's only one way to settle this.
You're right. Here I go.
Bring it!
Calm down, you two!
Rock, Paper, Scissors! Match!
I'm going on ahead, so hurry it up.
Match! Match! Match! Match! Match! Match~!
I'm home!
*Mope mope mope mope*
I'm home...
What's the matter with Maki-nee? Ah, whatever.
Hehe!
Saki-nee!
Ups-a-daisy!
You see the thing is, I won your virginity since
I'm such a natural at Rock, Paper, Scissors.
What?
Aw, Ken-kun! No fair, Saki-chan!
At least let me have the tip!
I can't trust you to stop at just the tip with a guy, Maki!
Let's get started, then! Hehe!
What, you're not into it?
Of course I'm into it.
Well then, who do you like more, me or Maki?
Well...
You look so cute when you're flustered, Kenta.
Well, anyways, let's have sex!
Okay.
Take these off me, Kenta.
You have such a cute look on your face!
This means that you love me, Kenta.
Here's Saki-nee chan's pussy!
You're breathing so hard! That tickles, Kenta!
Well then, I have to get you even more excited.
This is your first kiss too, right?
Yeah.
I stole your first kiss, Kenta.
Your dick is so responsive.
I made this little guy throb.
Geez, I can't focus on your training.
I want to touch you too, Saki-nee!
Go for it!
I'll get it wet.
Really? Me too.
Well then, what would you like me to do, Kenta?
Well...
Check it out! My bottom hole wants to eat
virgin dick so much that it's drooling!
I want you to do it.
I can't understand you if you say it so gently.
I want you to take my virginity, Saki-nee!
You finally said it! Let's get to it then!
See, it's going in!
I've got a virgin dick!
It's been a while!
I'm going to cum already, Saki-nee!
But I haven't even started moving yet.
But your hole just feels so good, Saki-nee!
It's a pussy, not a hole. Say it!
Saki-nee's pussy feels so good!
Your pussy feels so good, Saki-nee!
Hehehe! You're so completely innocent, Kenta!
Does this feel good, Kenta?
It feels so good that I'm going to cum already!
Good! Nice answer!
This is your first time. You want to cum from great sex, don't you?
It's better than great!
You're so cute, Kenta!
Your dick is a great fit, Kenta!
I might get addicted to this!
Saki-nee!
You look so cute grabbing my tits!
Do you like my tits that much?
I love them so much!
Sorry! I can't help myself!
What is a guy who was a virgin until just a moment ago saying?
Hey! Don't go shoving your dick in any deeper!
Th-That's...!
Does it feel good, Saki-nee?
Of course it does!
This is too sudden!
Hey!
Saki-nee! Saki-nee! Saki-nee!
I'm Saki-nee, I got it! Slow down!
I can't stop!
I'm going to cum, Saki-nee!
Just hurry up and cum already!
You can cum with your smelly virgin milk in my pussy!
You can cum in me!
I'm going to cum! My sperm will be inside you, Saki-nee!
Cum! Hurry up and cum!
My body specializes in drinking it up!
You came! You came inside!
You came so much, but you're still so hard!
Here it comes! Your thick dick is so big, Kenta!
Saki-nee! I can't do it so soon!
I'm going to suck your dick dry.
My pussy will drink it all up!
Here it comes again! I'm going to cum on your virgin dick again!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum! My legs are so shaky!
I sucked your sack completely dry!
My stomach is full since you came completely inside me.
Dicks are so great!
Kenta, you came way too much no matter how you look at it.
Well, I guess it just means my pussy felt that good!
Saki-nee is drinking my sperm.
My pussy juices are mixed with your cum.
It tastes really sexy.
So how was your first time?
It was amazing.
You're still so hard even after cumming that much.
I-It's because you're too sexy, Saki-nee.
It's my fault, eh?
I see. Well then, I have to take responsibility for it.
Saki-nee!
Stop right there!
Maki-nee!
You can't do something so unfair! It's my turn next!
Huh? How will one more time hurt? He's still hard.
Ken-kun will run out of sperm! My turn!
Your big, hard dick was pretty good, Kenta.
Or rather, thanks for the virginity.
You suck! I won't forgive you!
Not only did I, virgin-hunter Maki-chan, miss out, but you
took Kei-chan's virginity, and are rude to me on top of it!
What are you getting at with those two points?
I'm going to gather up all your vibrators and throw
them away on the next plastic bottle trash day!
Um, you can't recycle vibrators. Wait,
you collect vibrators, Saki-nee?
You'll just surprise the trash man, so give it up!
Well, there's no use crying over spilled milk.
But I'll make Ken-kun's second virginity more romantic!
Come on, Ken-kun!
Wh-Where are you taking me? Let me put on some clothes!
Hmph.
Hehe. You're all alone with me, Ken-kun.
I look a lot different than when I used
to take baths with you, Ken-kun.
Yeah. You've become really beautiful, Maki-nee.
Thanks!
But who would have thought that the bed-wetter
Ken-kun would become so cool.
Let that go already!
No can do!
The fact that we're about to have sex despite that,
just makes me hotter.
Um...
You're blushing. You're so cute, Ken-kun!
Maki-nee?
Saki-chan stole your first kiss, didn't she?
Yeah.
I want one of your first too, Ken-kun!
Maki-nee...
I got it!
Do you like my tits, Ken-kun?
Yes, they're fluffy like marshmallows. I love them.
Alright then. Then I will take your titty-fucking virginity.
Look! I got your entire dick!
I'll give you a dick massage with the
tits that you're always staring at.
Your big hard dick is going crazy inside my tits!
You sound like a girl. You're so cute, Ken-kun!
W-Well...
There we go! Rubby rubby! Rubby rubby!
Your dick scent is going to seep into my tits!
Your tits feel so good, Maki-nee.
You're so cute and innocent.
I'm going to make you feel even better then!
Maki-nee!
Your dick is so hard. You're so bad, Mr. Dick!
The scent is so strong.
You're rock hard. How cute!
I'm going to cum if you do that to me, Maki-nee.
Well, I'll go all out, then!
I'm cumming, Maki-nee!
Rubby rubby! Cum in my mouth.
Feel free to cum a lot!
I'm cumming!
Thanks for the treat!
Maki-nee...
You dick is so strong, Ken-kun!
It's still so rock hard and throbbing even after cumming so much!
Do you wanna keep going? Yeah.
Yeah.
Isn't it pretty?
It's so beautiful it's making me excited.
Look! My bottom hole wants you so bad that it's quivering.
The clitoris is on top, below that is the pee
hole, and this is the pussy opening.
It's so wet.
It's so wet because it wants you sloshing around inside it.
Hey! Don't come on so strong, so fast!
Does it feel good, Maki-nee?
N-No! I want it to be from your dick if I'm going to cum.
Come on! You can fuck me as hard as you want, Ken-kun!
H-Here I go.
Come on already!
Finally!
Your entire dick is in me!
You look so sexy, Maki-nee!
Make me look sexier.
Your dick is so long that it won't come out
even though you're inexperience.
This is great!
Maki-nee.
Make it feel even better, Ken-kun!
You can do it, Ken-kun!
Wow!
Your dick is so big!
Maki-nee!
I can't take it! It's too big!
You're pounding me so deeply!
My pussy gives up!
My pussy is going to cum already from
your big dick that just lost its virginity!
You're cumming!
It's spilling in all the way to the back.
My pussy was dominated by your dick that just lost its virginity.
Stop! Stop!
Stop! You're still going? Stop!
You're going to tear me up!
Maki-nee! Maki-nee!
Maki-nee!
W-Wow! Wow!
Sorry, Maki-nee! I can't stop my hips!
I can feel it! Your big dick is grinding so hard inside of me!
I'm cumming!
Cum! Cum in my pussy, Ken-kun!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You saw it. You saw your sperm seeping out of me.
We still have a long night ahead of us, Kei-kun.
I'm done for, Maki-nee.
Even though your dick is still hard?
Don't worry. I'll be gentle this time.
Hold it!
Saki-nee!
Damn, you found us already!
It's my turn this time! Move, Maki!
No way! You got to take his virginity, Saki-chan! I get another turn!
Stop fighting, you two!
Geez! Who do you- Like better, Kenta?
Hey, that's...
You're not just going to say that you'll marry us
both like you did when you were a kid, right?
Ah, Ken-kun is so indecisive.
I-Is that so bad?
Whatever.
That's one of your cute points.
Alright then. That just means that Kenta's
dick belongs to the both of us.
We're going to keep at it until morning!
Nooooo!
Well, as for what happened to me after that...
You're even good at thrusting deeply, Ken-kun! So good!
Pound it even deeper!
Your dick is so great!
Cum a lot, okay?
Gross! Your dick is so perverted!
It's getting harder and harder. I like it!
Geez! In comparison to when you first got here...
You're already this good with your hips!
I ended up dating them both, or rather
being toyed around by them.
My pussy is melting even though Maki is watching!
You're so amazing, Ken-chan! Fuck me too!
I'm gonna take the picture!
Hurry up and make me cum!
Let's take a commemorative photo with that face!
Hurry up and cum already, Kenta!
Fap, fap fap! Three, two, one!
Yay!
Spending every day with these extremely sexy ladies
doesn't seem to be coming to an end any time soon.