Hey, you know which school this uniform is from, right?
It's the real thing.
Sacred Prostitutes
~ Sex Slave Training Academy ~
Pure Like a Saint, Indecent Like a Prostitute...
Iroha-san, l saw the show last night!
Oh!
Out of all three people, you were the cutest!
Oh, that? It wasn't a big deal.
Miyamae Iroha
But even though the broadcast was
short, it took all day to film.
I see, being an idol must be hard work!
You're right about that.
Shirosaki Yuuri
Kamijo Tsubassa
Katsuragi Shion
White Lily Hill Academy.
A public boarding school filled with
mostly affluent young women.
But this school has another hidden side to it.
Yes! You are all high-class female prostitutes.
Everyone!
Today this female prostitute is going to display herself.
I will take plenty of what’s on display!
Don't hold back, please thrust deeper inside me!
I don't hear you complaining about how good this feels!
I don't want anyone else's cock inside me.
I want your cock to stay hard and keep pumping!
You're tight and I want to cum so
bad, I can barely stop myself!
Of course, I'm so tight that you feel like cumming.
We've kept our pussies closed and tight
so we'll feel really good for you!
Oji-sama, your dick is so strong.
It feels really good!
Please always stay connected to my pussy!
Yuuri-chan's heart is like an angel's!
I want to grant anything you desire!
I'd do anything to continue this fucking!
Yes, this school also exists to train females
to fuck with high-class VIPs.
My duty is,
to discover the obscene wishes that
lay deep in the hearts of men.
Then the girls receive the men's wishes
and make them come true.
That is what makes them high-class female prostitutes.
Yes, it's that simple.
These girl prostitutes are truly obscene!
Ecstasy!
Welcome! Good evening, everyone!
Half angel, half little devil,
My heart isn't going to run away!
I'm Iroha Miyamae of Three Piece!
Three Piece Live @ Tokyo!!
As I suspected, the most eye-catching member
is the lead member, Iroha-san.
The more I look at her the more
I see a flower about to bloom.
That girl seems like a tenacious youth
with a haughty personality.
She'd make an optimal prostitute!
Hey! Don't talk about that kind
of strange stuff in this bar!
Huh? C'mon, a little bit of carefree talk is okay, isn't it?
You don't even have other customers in here.
Ok, everyone! Here we go!
Piece!
It's disgusting.
H-Hey, do I really have to do it?
You came this far, how can you say that?
If the person who has those dirty
images of you releases them,
it will spell the end for the beloved Iroha.
Haying dirty pictures taken of you is forbidden, isn't it?
That-That’s right, but...
If you can just do as I say tonight, it will all be over.
Please try hard.
3, 2, 1, go!
Nyuki, nyuki nyuki nyuki nyuki!
Tada! It's everyone's idol, Miyamae Iroha!
But tonight, just for tonight, I'll
be Iroha, an Iroha just for you.
I'll give myself to you!
So, is your penis ready to go?
Let's start. I'm waiting, waiting...
Don't make me cum before you do!
Can you tell?
You're making electric shocks
run through my whole body!
Fantastic!
Will that person really not release
those photos if I do this for you?
Don't worry.
He's also a big fan of yours.
If we send this video to him, then...
You say that, but can't he just blackmail
me with those photos again and again?
Don't worry.
If he tried that I’d threaten to release
some of his secrets online.
In other words I’d ruin his life until he stopped.
T-Truly?
Next, it's time to suck my cock.
Filthy...
Hey, you agreed to act the part.
Shut up! I know, I'll do it.
I'm Three Piece's...
You’re filling my entire mouth!
Yes, yes! Like that!
You're acting as I expected you would.
You're an idol and your number one goal
is to give 100% to whatever you do.
In this way you hope to gain more love and more fans.
You act this way in order to lead a gorgeous life.
But you’d get more love and attention as
a high-class prostitute, wouldn't you?
Iroha-san, I'm going to cum soon.
Please report to the camera.
You're going to cum soon,
so I know we're both going to feel really good.
Amazing, it's warm and sticky!
It's so lewd.
That was really great acting, Iroha-san!
Why don't you act in addition to being in Three Piece?
And was the acting... real?
You're satisfied with just this, aren't you?
It's over with this.
No, no, the actual performance is starting now.
What, the actual performance? That's...
You haven't realized it yet, Iroha-san?
It's tingling...
First off, let's watch this great video.
What's this? A classroom from my school?
That's...
Yes. The heiress of Katsuragi Group, Katsuragi Shion-san.
No way, that's...
She actually has another hidden side to her.
She's a high-class prostitute at the academy.
What!?
Until one month ago I thought it would
be impossible for me to be a prostitute.
But then I finally allowed a cock to enter me.
I want you to see me entirely as I really am.
Katsuragi Shion
I don't understand...
No matter what I do, just feeling your
thick penis against me makes me hot.
Now, for your own sake let yourself feel good.
Your pussy is so wet.
This man has made me masturbate countless times,
Again and again I've taken in his cock,
And with even my butt hole taken,
I've become a perverted girl!
Why do you want more?
I'm embarrassed to say it,
but I want your cock and my pussy to stay connected!
You said the right thing!
N-No way!
Yes.
This girl truly is a great whore.
Don't you think so, Iroha-san?
What kind of services can you do
with your pussy, Shion-san?
My pussy can make us both cum at the same time,
so you won't feel lonely.
That's something customers really want, isn't it?
If you could love my pussy with all you have,
I become willing to accept anything!
I'm hitting your womb deeply now!
I feel like I'm going to cum right now, but
I want to cum at the same time as you!
My pussy has to be patient!
You have a good heart, don't you?
I'll give you your wish.
My womb is pulsating.
I can't hold back anymore! I'm
going to cum, I’m cumming!
Ok, let's cum together!
Cum, cum!
Shoot a huge load of cum deep inside of me!
It's hot!
Shion-san, is using your pussy the only service you offer?
No, it's not just my pussy that can be bought.
If someone is looking for another
hole, I can give them my anus.
In that case, I won't hold back.
It's really tight.
Take a look at your thick cock
going to down my deep hole!
Shion-san, what is it about anal sex that you like?
When the cock comes out my ass
tries to clench and keep it in,
And it feels good to have a cock
inside a place that's so dirty.
And the cock is positively, dripping when it comes out!
Like this?
Just like that!
You've completely become a pervert, haven't you?
Your cock is making my ass feel so good.
It's making my body become even more of a slut!
My body is responding in ways I never imagined,
I want to keep doing this forever!
Anal is the best!
Ecstasy!
Look at how much she was enjoying getting fucked,
And after that she continued fucking for money.
Don't you think she makes a great prostitute?
Prostitute, what do you mean?
I mean that White Lily Hills Academy
has a different side to it.
You girls were sold to the school.
No way, I don't believe you!
Before we talk about that, there's, something
you need to get straight.
You exist to serve and give joy to men.
You're terrible! What kind of person are you?
I'm a pimp.
A...pimp? What’s that?
I make a living,
by transforming you girls into high-class prostitutes.
Liar!
Have you prepared your body?
Let's exploit you now!
No... Stop!
Your pussy is so creamy I don’t need
to prepare it to take my cock.
Just like before, look at the camera and
give a great performance please!
I can't do that!
Then gather your strength... I'm going in!
I'm too tight, it can’t go in deeper...
I can't get enough of your cock inside me,
Keep putting it in me so I feel better and better!
See? It seems that it's the first time you've felt
so good from having a cock inside of you.
You're filling me up...
In order to make your customers feel good,
You need to make them want to stay inside your pussy!
I can't stop, I'm going to cum soon!
Keep plunging your cock deep inside
and making me feel good!
Will you let me cum deep into your womb?
That's...
That's okay, isn't it?
Okay. I want you to cum deep inside,
and make me cum too!
Ok, then look at the camera!
Everyone,
please look at this slutty idol as she is creampied!
You can't miss this, the iroha from Three Piece is...!
is going to cum from semen pouring inside her!
It feels fantastic, it feels so good!
I'm cummlng!
I'm cumming!
Three Piece
H-Hello!
Hello!
Thank you for coming to this event for us!
I love you, Mitsune-san!
I'm so happy that you came!
I-I've been a fan of yours for a while!
Don't be so nervous!
Okay!
Let's handshake!
Kyoko-san!
Iroha-san, your hands...
I used to be afraid to do this, but
now it's my favorite activity.
Do you not like me like this?
No, I really like you Iroha-san!
Look!
I've had this inside since the promotional event!
If I don't have something inside me it hurts!
From now on I'll always be cheering you on!
That makes me happy!
It's awesome! The sperm is flying out of your cock.
Let's do this again in the future!
Yes!
Thanks.
Yahoo! Iroha's the best!
Pieeece!
I-Iroha-chan!
Does it feel good?
Nobody’s seen these breasts before,
and these nipples will make you feel good!
Iroha-chan, your nipples...
your nipples are caressing me!
My nipples are getting erect because
you're making me feel good!
I'm really warm, aren't I?
Yes! Iroha-chan is so erotic!
That's why I'm giving only you
a breast massage right now!
The feel of your nipples on my cock is making
me want to cum! I'm cuming to cum!
It's ok for you to cum! Spurt a
lot of cum all over my breasts!
Iroha-chan!
So much! You're cumming so much
and it's covering my whole body...
There’s so much cum everywhere.
I'm sorry! When I heard I could get a blowjob
from you I stored up my cum for a week...
You didn't need to do that.
But you saved up a lot of cum for today... thank you!
Yes, I tried my best!
You just orgasmed, and yet your penis is still really hard.
What should we do about that?
Iroha-chan! To tell the truth, I
came here with some friends.
So... I can't...
It's okay! This is a special handshake
just between the two of us.
Go ahead, you may enter.
Okay.
Thanks.
Iroha-chan!
Hi!
Ready to give lots of fan service, Iroha-san?
So this is Iroha's pussy...
That's because my pussy is giving
your cock a handshake!
Handshake, handshake...
Iroha-chan!
I want you in here...
Is it really okay, Iroha-chan? Is it alright?
Yes, my asshole is ready to give
you a good handshake too!
Oh my god, oh my god...
I'm being totally filled up, both my pussy and my ass...
I can't wait to cum all over your insides!
I'm still giving you a tight handshake.
I’m taking your fan appreciation and giving
you a warm embrace in return...
Give me more!
If you go deeper inside of me my pussy
will give you a tighter handshake...
I'm going to cum!
Me too!
Let's cum together!
All of us cumming together will be the best feeling ever!
Iroha-chan, I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
Please, go ahead and cum!
I'm cumming!
Everyone! Thank you so much for all of this semen!
I'm so happy!
My pussy feels really terrific!
One, two, and Piece!
There are women who have obscene
fantasies locked away in their hearts.
It's my job to unlock those fantasies
and bring them to the surface.
I teach them how to grant the wishes of men.
That's how you make a high-class female prostitute.
This bar doesn't allow students to enter.
I'm sorry. But I absolutely have to meet
that person here. If I don't...
I don't know why you need to see
him, but you should reconsider.
You can't become involved with that guy!
He's a despicable man.
Well, it looks like I'm too late.
It looks like I've made you wait... young lady.
Translation:
Ainomiko
Timing:
Loserbait
Typeset & Encode:
ShocWave
Presented by:
Erobeat
#erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
http://www.erobeat.net
tsumetai tsukiakiri no shita
Under the cold moon light,
shiroi usagi wo mukie ni konakute
Note even the white rabbit is here to greet me.
madara moyou no asufaruto
On mottled asphalt,
ippiki no chou ga kogoe shinda
A butterfly has frozen to death.
sotto kami wo nadeta
I gently stroked her hair,
jubaku no you na akui sasayakarete
As I whispered malicious incantations.
mou nammo kikoenai yo
Now I can’t hear anything.
sukui no kami no koe sore sura todokanai
Not even God's voice of Salvation can reach me.
tsun no omosa buzama na kokvuu
The weight of sin, clumsy breathing.
yuri no hana ga ochiteku
Lily flowers fall.
hikarinaki moumoku no shoujo no saga
A sex girl left blind without the light.
neon shikake no kamisama ni
To the gods of the neon gimmicks
utsukushisi no daishou wo sasageru
I offer the price of beauty.
mafiiyu no chou no you ni
Like a midwinter butterfly,
douka adeyaka ni
Please make me bewitching.