Coming Soon
Men's
Lemon Coffe!!
You forgot something.
I expect you to be early for your shift tomorrow.
Okay.
By chance,
do you want to have sex with me?
Sei yariman gakuen enkou nikki
Holy Yariman Academy.
Compensated Dating Diaries.
Hey, where are we headed next?
Where else?
We'll be doing our first round at the usual place.
Wow, I'm excited!
Let's try using all sorts of "items" this time.
You're such a maniac.
What old man?
Would you please stop ogling me?
Eh? No, I'm not...
You're just not young anymore.
Why don't you just go home and fuck your wife, old man!
Keep the change.
Thank you, please come again!
Hey, hey, I want to go to that hotel again!
Please don't mind them.
But it's true that you should be headed home now.
Won't your wife get worried if you're out too late?
Well, it's okay.
I'm no longer...
That's right. I'm divorced
After working endlessly for 30 years,
my wife and daughter left me without any hesitation.
All that remains
is the status and money that I obtained during my youth.
What else is left for my life...
Hey, mister.
Are you free, perhaps?
I...
don't really have time.
But you were just spacing out, weren't you?
I just divorced my wife, today.
Eh? Divorced?
I see.
After 30 years of marriage, youigot divorced
because your wife had an affair.
But mister, you don't really look that sad about it.
We were only together for convenience, I guess.
It also became sexless...
Mister, do you realize that you just told a very
personal story to a girl that you've just met?
Maybe you're a bit drunk?
Well, I do feel slightly drunk.
Besides, I may have wanted to talk to someone about this.
I see.
But, isn't being sexless bad?
Men and women are supposed to be stuck with one another.
So then, I have a suggestion.
A suggestion?
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to share some sticky, intimate moments
in a private room with you.
What do you think?
Shall we "develop" some love there?
In that lovey-dovey space?
Maybe it's good for me to let loose every once in a while.
Oh, you cute old man!
You can't say "let loose", because you're already letting it off!
Whoa, so it's set up like that.
Mister, you seem to be really into this
even though it's your first time.
Maybe the other guy has already has gotten it off down low?
You're getting rather audacious too, aren't you?
If I remember right, the Holy Marian Girls
Academy is a missionary school?
So you really don't know much about these things.
Our school, you see,
is also secretly known as the slut academy.
Besides, we have a saying:
"Thou shall love thy cock."
That should be "neighbor".
It'd be the same if the neighbor's a guy.
That's why...
Let's forget the details.
Just think about my pussy and let's have fun.
Wow, that's some amazing development.
Your thing down here has also developed nicely.
Wow, is this for real?
My, oh my!
It looks like it's completely natural!
This is totally over the top!
Even the smell is amazing.
It's so hard... and stiff,
and it twitches so hard when all I do is lick it.
Wow, what should I do?
I'm about to get fucked by this cock.
If I'm penetrated by this monstrous cock;
it might reach somewhere that's not been reached before.
I want it to hit that spot over and over again!
This is the first time in my life that I've
done done something like this.
I'm so blown away that I'm really getting aroused.
Oh my, if you say that,
I'll feel like trying to do something surprising to you.
And I'll definitely come up with something for you!
What's this?
My cock feels like it's melting!
Does it feel good?
Yeah! Yeah! It's the best!
You can cum anytime you want.
You can spray all that stinky semen into my mouth.
It's like a giant straw that's getting sucked on.
Come on, release it! Release it!
It's really...
It's really okay if I cum there, right?
I'm going to shoot it all deep into your throat.
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
So much saved up...
It's so thick that it feels like a little like jelly.
Your semen is swimming in my stomach.
If I get filled up this much,
then I might even get pregnant from my mouth!
This time,
I want you to thrust that thing in as deeply as you can
and fuck my pussy like a wild monkey!
That gargantuan cock...
Please put it in me already!
Condom. Where's the condom?
What are you doing, mister?
What? It'd be bad if I didn't use a condom, right?
You don't need one.
If it's something amazing like your
dick, I'd rather have it au naturale.
Then, I'll pay a bit extra.
You don't need to worry about that either.
Just give me that amazing, raw cock of yours already, okay?
Hurry up, hurry up!
Oh no, oh no!
This is amazing!
My pussy's being filled!
You've finally lost your composure, Miho.
It's just...
It's so long and thick!
You just instinctively love having sex with men,
even with cute face such as yours...
Oh no!
Your cock is hitting so deep inside my pussy!
This is really bad!
Is it really that bad?
Your cock is really, really naughty.
And you even took the lead earlier...
Now you're acting like a girl who's
being fucked for the first time.
You too, mister.
Your being sexless seems like a lie.
Given a choice, I'd want to have your cock every night.
I'd also like to do it with you,
every night!
If I could have this cock every night and
get paid for it, it would be perfect!
Your hip technique is driving me crazy!
Mister,
you're hard, so hard!
You're just so hard!
But it's still not enough.
Make it even harder!
Do something even more amazing!
Okay, I'll do something even better then.
You're a beast.
You're a absolute beast!
Mister, that's so good.
Your face is showing how amazing this is!
Miho...!
Hey mister, let's keep kissing just a little...
No, I'm cumming...
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming,
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming right now!
I'm cumming right this moment!
Mister, it's pumping into me.
It's flowing, flowing, flowing, and it's going to come out!
I think I'm really going to get tilled with this.
Mister, you truly are a beast.
That was amazing, mister.
So, as a bonus service,
I'll let you have as many rounds as
you want for the price of one.
I apologize for being a little late...
Thank you for calling.
This is DMC, Daichi Business Affairs.
Yes, yes.
You heard what happened to our department chief?
He's absent today, and he's headed off somewhere.
It's so unusual.
They say he's divorced, eloping with other
women, and diving into prostitution.
No way.
No, no. He's exactly the kind of person
that would go out of control
after not letting off any steam for a while.
Holy Marian Girls Academy
Misono?
Misono Miho?
Absent, huh?
You think Miho fucked the guy she snagged
yesterday for the entire night?
No way.
Even if it's Miho, she'd break down after doing that.
You beast!
Mister, you're such a beast!
Fucking me non stop last night and now all day...
It's your...
It's your fault you know.
It's because you keep squeezing me so tightly.
It feels too good.
That...
That's...
If this continues, I'll get completely addicted to it!
My pussy will become your personal hole!
Miho, Miho...!
Your body is mine!
Miho!
No! Not my nipples!
You're squeezing...
You're squeezing my breasts too much!
It's also going all the way inside me.
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum!
Eh? No, that's...!
Mister, not there...!
See, Miho? It's okay!
You can lose it now!
It's here right? Miho, it's here, right?
I'm cumming!
Miho, I don't care what happens anymore!
I'm cumming... I'm gonna cum, Miho!
Mister, your cock is the best. It's the greatest.
Eh, what are you doing mister?
Ah, this karaoke has cosplay services.
I wonder what we should pick?
A maid uniform? Chinese dress?
Oh, so there's a nurse uniform, too!
You really are the biggest pervert!
Yah, hiya~!
Hey, the engine's not turning on.
From then on, I got hooked.
During the day, I did it with Miho and her friends.
I was feeling completely satisfied.
It was during that time that I first met Rei.
Hey old man, shouldn't you apologize for bumping into us?
But I've already apologized, haven't I?
You don't seem serious about it!
You know, I think this guy needs a
few bucks for medical treatment.
Who and what are you?
Gangs are really lame nowadays.
Leave now, before you get hurt.
What was that?
We won't hold back just because you're a woman!
Let's kick her ass!
Thank you! I'm saved.
It's nothing.
They were just such an eyesore that I had to get rid of them.
And you shouldn't just go confronting them like that!
Anyway, this place is filled with morons like that, so be careful.
Hey, wait just a second?
It wouldn't feel right if I couldn't repay you somehow.
How about letting me treat you to a meal?
I want meat.
Hey mister, is it alright for you to
hang around the city this late?
Are you still single at that age?
You could say it's punishment.
The divorce was last year.
Oh, I see.
Umm... Sorry about that.
It's okay.
I'm feeling confident now that my mind and
body can feel so fulfilled in this new life.
Oh, so that's how it is.
That's right.
You know... I don't really have a father,
so I think I understand your situation.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Pardon me, but would it be alright to take the empty plates?
Please do.
Yeah, and can you bring me a coffee?
Certainly, sir.
Anyway, what are you doing at this hour, Reiko?
Nothing really, just my part-time job.
Part-time job, you mean as a hooker?
No... No way!
Don't you recognize this uniform?
I'm from the Holy Marian Girls School!
Virgin Mary would be upset with me if I did that you know!
I see.
Then, I'll show the cute, little Rei-chan something.
Huh?
This person... is from the same class as me...
But this... this kind of...
Excuse me, here's coffee you ordered.
Thank you.
This must have been forced.
Not a bit.
If you look at her face, you'll understand.
It's a mutual agreement.
M-Mutual agreement?
Something this big couldn't possibly fit inside her.
Did you know that your school is known as the slut academy?
So you don't know anything, huh?
Are you a virgin, Rei?
What?
What are you saying?
Stop saying such weird things!
Well, I just thought it would be a waste if it is true.
For a cute girl like you to be oblivious
to sex. It would really be a waste.
W-What are you saying?
How about this?
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to provide you with a more adult
way of showing my gratitude.
I could be a better, first partner for you at
my current level than those guys outside.
You're going to be taking that off anyway.
Why put it back on again?
Got a problem with that?
Not at all, but does that mean you
want me to take it off for you?
That's not it!
I'll take it off myself!
Then, are you scared?
Who is?
Well, I guess you're right.
Try to remember the boys you beat up earlier.
I'd really like to give you a deep kiss.
I don't know of any other woman as
strong and beautiful as you are.
You're lying.
It's the truth.
If you don't want to kiss me, then you can just stay quiet there.
I'll do the kissing.
No, my uniform's going to wrinkle.
Eh, don't...
No, this is embarrassing!
You can kick me if you don't want it.
D-Don't say something like that!
Can you raise your leg?
Wait... Huh?!
Aren't you going to take it all the way off?
Why do this kind of half-assed...
Because it's more erotic this way.
Here, loosen up.
Try to relax.
Relax.
Look, it's getting really sensitive.
Don't play with my breasts!
This is what it means for a man to desire a woman.
I'll be sure to prepare your feminine body for it,
so let's become one okay?
Huh?
Yo-Your finger is going in...!
It's okay.
Leave it all to me.
Okay.
Even though it's my first time,
it's already so intense...!
This is amazing.
Your insides are sucking me inside.
You're not just beautiful.
You have the potential to be something great.
You idiot!
Idiot, idiot!
Don't say those kinds of perverted things.
You say that, but I know better.
Your wet pussy sucked it all the way in, and
it doesn't want to let go of my cock.
Here, I'm going to push it in deeper for you.
So relax.
Okay.
No way I'm getting penetrated this deeply...
Is my body alright?
When he hits the right spots, my pussy
feels like its throbbing all over.
I'm not going to be able to contol myself
much longer if this continues.
Rei, I'm going for my Carnal Piston!
No way... Don't...!
No! My pussy is throbbing so hard...
No! I don't want to feel this good anymore.
Your breasts are bouncing cutely.
I see, so you really want them to be fondled, eh?
Here.
Oh no, my nipples feel great.
I can't take this anymore!
I don't want to feel good anymore.
My pussy and my nipples are going numb...
I can't hold it in...!
Not yet, Rei.
We have to cum together.
– Here, here!
– No!
– Together... We'll cum together!
– Don't, don't, don't...
– I'll get pregnant... No!
– I'm going to release it inside you!
– Don't... Don't release it inside me!
I'm going to release it inside pumping you in this position!
Huh? I can't move.
My body only reacts to that cock.
Whenever that cock throbs and thrusts in,
I feel electrified inside.
Why?
Why is my pussy so hungry for this?
Why is my womb anticipating the release of his semen?
Here I go.
I'm going to release it inside, Rei!
No way...
You're kidding right?
This hot stuff... is semen?
No...
No.
No!
After all that, we did it ten times during the night.
Huh? Rei?
Hello! Rei-chan?
About this budget sheet, the proposed amount
was put together rather carelessly.
If we cut off Company A's supply connections, we'll
be able to squeeze out a lot more from them.
Yes, sir.
Also, for Company B's affected sub-companies,
it'll be too late if we don't do something about it today.
Review it from bottom to top.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Our chief has been really fired up these last few days.
Could he really be feeling young again?
How would you put it...?
He's a carnivorous, middle-aged man.
That's it.
Welcome.
Please present your identification.
Thank you.
Amazing, those two in the center are amazing.
The girl's so young and beautiful, and yet she's so into it?
She must be really horny!
Anyway, what's with that cock?
Is he going to drive it in?
Whoa, even the insides are throbbing now right now.
When I think about how I'm going to insert my cock here...
I'm cumming...!
This cock...
I'm happy.
Now, turn around and straddle me.
Yes...
Yes! Yes!
My insides are squeezing it in.
This is amazing.
Push deeper inside me, all the way to my womb!
Get it all the way in!
Rei, look around you.
Wow...
I really wanna do her...
I so wanna squeeze those amazing breasts!
What is it with this bunch?
They're playing with themselves...
No way...
These are some amazing tits!
Hey, I'm going to cum.
I'm gonna cum inside.
Here, have a taste of it!
No...
No, you can't...!
That's impossible.
There's no way a man's cock could resist cumming
inside a such an inviting pussy.
Don't say it like that!
Here, take my first shot!
No! It's hot... Stop...!
Wow.
It's still twitching so much.
This is the best.
There's no better pussy than this!
Hey, switch over!
Woah, this feels great!
Then, I'll just get along with this cute mouth.
I'm taking these monstrously big breasts!
Hey, it's breast milk!
That's just too erotic!
Damn, I can't get enough of this!
I want to pound my cock into this pussy forever!
Whenever I drive it into her mouth, the head of
my cock rubs back and forth. This is the best!
For her to release milk while taking in three cocks in one go...
She's too cute and way too homy!
You seem troubled there, eh Rei?
You really started moaning and getting absolutely soaked
after you realized you were being watched.
Now, we have to show our gratitude to the ones watching us.
Come on everyone, whoever wants
to cum should release it here!
A single "hole in one" will cost you 10,000 yen.
You all...
I won't forgive you...
You're so cute Rei-chan...
I think I can cum and shoot a huge load in her.
Yeah, I'm about to cum too.
Hey, squeeze it in a bit more.
Rei-chan's breasts look really cute.
Watching them while cumming really is the best!
That's...
Oh no, I'm totally absorbed within these countless cocks...
I'm going to be torn apart if this continues...
Here everyone, go ahead!
This here is the hole!
It's in! It's in!
– It's gone in!
– Mine too!
It was so erotic that I thought I was gonna
lose myself for a second there.
This borrowed bitch is the best!
Asking me to do it there...
That was terrible, mister!
Hey, not "mister" but "papa", right?
Oh no...
P-Papa...
That's right.
From now on I'm your Papa,
and I'm ready to listen to whatever request you may have.
You just want to do something perverted again, right?
Don't you want to?
Not that... I don't want...
I'm also like you papa.
Cause I'm a slut.
I guess there are many kinds of living creatures, huh?
Thank you for attending the performance.
The next show will be at around 01:30 PM...
Mister, hey there!
P-Papa.
How was it?
It was really fantastic!
Those critters just kept on snapping and snapping.
It was wild.
Now I'm hungry because of it.
Why don't we go eat lunch then?
Okay!
Let's order a full course at the hotel.
The most expensive one!
Hey, Miho...!
What are we going to do after lunch then?
Wanna do a threesome?
What are you saying?
Well, even Rei had recently...
H-Hey...!