At the Aobadai General Hospital
Nursing Academy...
the aspiring nurses took part in the
ceremony, in which they received...
their nursing hats and started
their training at the hospital.
The hands-on nursing work was
much harder than they had expected.
This is a story about Yumi Asakura,
who has given her all,
and her hardships in becoming
a nurse, a very demanding profession.
I'm gonna do it!
Nurse Me! Nurse Yumi
ShamefuI Nurse Training: Session 3
lt happened
one beautiful morning.
You're caIIing me a rapist?
Risa was very angry
because she had found out...
what Dr. Miura had done to Yumi.
That's right! It's rape!
You raped Yumi, didn't you?
What are you taIking about?
You didn't do it?
You reaIIy think you didn't do it?
WeII, whatever happens between
me and Yumi is none of your concern.
Don't teII me it was
a mutuaI agreement!
At first I thought Yumi was
dating you because she Iiked you,
but you were onIy
using Yumi as your toy!
I feeI so guiIty towards Yumi.
We're roommates,
and I didn't reaIize it.
Say something!
What you've done is a crime!
So, what is Yumi's dear friend
asking of me?
Stop pIaying dumb! You need to give
Yumi an apoIogy and compensate her!
Oh, an apoIogy and compensation?
And how much are you going to take?
l'm gonna cum. l'm gonna cum.
l think l'm gonna cum.
It's the shocking footage
the security camera shot.
Don't think you're going
to get away with bIackmaiIing me.
This isn't bIackmaiI!
Anyone who sees this tape
wiII think so.
They'II think a perverted nurse
who has sex in hospitaI rooms...
came up with a story
to bIackmaiI me.
Who do you think you are?!
Let go! You bastard!
What a Ioudmouth!
You'II need a different prescription
from the one I've given Yumi.
Meaning I don't need
to hoId back anything!
Etsuko!
Doctor, I need your signature.
Sure, but I'm in
the middIe of something.
Can you wait a bit?
Damn it!
Risa! The doctor is a busy man.
Don't troubIe him so much.
Damn you!
You two were in on this together!
You just got an order
from your superior.
Ow... It hurts!
Stop! I said, stop!
Risa!
Move! Get off of me!
I said, get off of me!
There!
What's wrong? You're not wet!
You don't Iike oIder men?
You seIfish bitch!
Get your softy out of my face!
N... No!
It's pointIess to fight me!
Stop! Stop!
I'd rather die
than get raped by you!
You'II be gIad you're aIive
in a minute.
Stop! Don't!
It's nice and tight.
I thought it'd be stretched out...
from fucking so much.
-It hurts! Ow... Ow...
-But you don't have...
much depth inside.
Stop! You bastard!
It hurts! It hurts!
It's hitting my uterus!
I'II shove it in there.
Ordinary guys can't do this!
No! Let go! Let me down!
I think I'm gonna cum.
AII right, I'm gonna cum!
Damn you! I'II remember this!
It's interesting to see a nurse
with such an attitude cry.
Doctor, I need your seaI
on the documents.
On the other hand, Yumi...
was oblivious and
taking care of Takayuki.
No! I can't do that!
PIease, Yumi!
Takayuki, the handsome guy
with porcelain skin,
would be leaving the hospital soon.
To make his stay at the hospital...
a more memorable experience,
he asked Yumi to have sex with him.
Yumi!
When I get out of the hospitaI,
I'm going to go home, far away.
I'II never be abIe to see you again.
So pIease! It's my Iast request!
You make it sound Iike
it's a poIiticaI eIection.
Yumi could understand
how Takayuki felt.
But she had her reasons
why she couldn't do it.
lf Takayuki got better from it,
what l did as a nurse...
wasn't a bad thing.
But my pussy has been
completely spoiled now.
l can't let Takayuki in there!
No! l can't do it!
I guess you're
turning me down...
Yumi, who can't say no
when someone asks her a favor,
was thinking.
''ls there anything else
l can do for Takayuki?''
If you're okay with it...
you can do me in my butt.
B... Butt? You mean anaI sex?
lt's beautiful.
And it smells so good.
Yumi's not an angel in white.
She's an angel who's wearing white!
Don't stare Iike that.
S.... Sorry! Then...
Okay.
Huh?
Does it hurt?
No, it's aII right. I'm okay.
lt's so warm.
l'm inside Yumi right now!
l don't know why she preferred
her ass, but that doesn't matter.
l'm in awe!
l'm completely, utterly in awe!
lf l could, l would have given you
my vaginal virginity.
l'm sorry, Takayuki.
Thank you, Yumi,
my angel in white!
Etsuko took Yumi
to the VlP hospital room.
An executive from a pharmaceutical
company was admitted in that room.
Yumi, have Mr. Oshima
watch you masturbate.
Huh?
''Huh?'' isn't a proper answer.
Sit here.
Y... yes.
Do it Iike you aIways do.
P... PIease stop!
Yumi, stop fooIing around!
This is a necessary treatment
for Mr. Oshima.
You're Iying! I've never heard
of such a treatment!
Are you changing your nursing
attitude depending on the patient?
Fine, then. Do as you wiII...
But don't think you can become
a fuII-fIedged nurse...
with that kind of attitude.
She couldn't have stabbed
Yumi's heart any worse.
She's right. l can't change
my nursing attitude...
depending on the patient.
I understand.
Yumi, where did you get this?
That's... It's my dream.
Your dream?
Yes. A wonderfuI nurse gave it
to me when I was a chiId.
I Iooked up to her and I decided
I wanted to become a nurse...
whom everyone wiII Iove,
just Iike her.
I see.
Yumi, Iisten to me. I saw
a beautifuI dream Iike that once.
But the reaI worId isn't an easy
pIace where your beautifuI dreams...
can come true exactIy Iike that.
You understand what I mean, right?
If you want your dreams to come true,
you can't Iook away from reaIity.
No matter how hard it is
and how spoiIed you get,
if you aIways strive to give
your patients the best care,
I think that's when you truIy
open the path to becoming a nurse...
whom everyone Ioves.
A dream wiII end if
you onIy see it as a dream.
You can do it, Yumi.
A dream wiII end if
you onIy see it as a dream.
She's right! lf l keep
running away from it,
my dream will end as a dream.
For my dream to come true...
You can do it, Yumi.
l have to masturbate to the best
of my abilities for the patient!
I'm so sorry!
l'm getting hot.
l'm really starting to feel it.
l hope the patient sees
how l'm really feeling.
Yumi continued to masturbate,
and prayed.
She's so cute.
Th... This feeIing...!
Mr. Oshima!
M-M-Ms. Kawai!
PIease take care of this matter!
Yes!
What an amazing orgasm!! Im in awe!!!! I'm in awwwwwe!
Thank you! Thanks to you,
my impotence is cured!
Ten years...
It's been ten years...
since I've had an erection,
and I even came, to boot!
Thank you. Thank you so much!
You were amazing, Yumi.
Thank you.
Yumi's heart filled with a great
feeling of accomplishment.
Unfortunately, that feeling
didn't last long.
Very nice...
You're...
Hey!
Risa!
Risa explained what had happened
to her in Dr. Miura's room.
Yumi felt terrible about
what happened to her, and...
her heart was filled with
an unexplainable ominous feeling.
So she caIIed us so we can get back
at the doctor and the head nurse.
Revenge?
We need to get back at Dr. Miura
for what he did to us, too. Right?
I'm going to expIain
our revenge pIan.
First, you'II Iure
Dr. Miura to a hoteI.
H... HoId on a second!
Why do I have to...
What? Whose fauIt is it that Risa had
to go through something Iike that?
That's...
You! It's your fauIt!
It's your fauIt Risa got raped!
I... I understand.
Her ominous feeling had come true.
Yumi had to take part...
in a revenge plot against Dr. Miura,
before she had time to realize it.
Yumi followed Funato's orders
and lured Dr. Miura out.
According to the plan, Funato was
supposed to bring Etsuko here...
and get back at her
along with Dr. Miura.
You know some interesting pIaces.
Um, this was Iisted
in a women's magazine.
Doctor! Let's take a bath first!
Yumi didn't know
when Funato would get there,
but until then, she'd unwillingly
have to spend time with Dr. Miura.
Your body has matured, now that
it knows the joys of being a woman.
N...No! No! No! Nooo!
Why are you saying, ''No?''
You're the one who asked me to come!
But that's... Your back!
I'II wash your back!
I think you'd be better as a
bathhouse prostitute than a nurse.
How couId you say that?
Yumi was screaming inside,
''Please, everyone show up soon!''
and dragged it out as long as possible.
Um, Dr. Miura, what is this?
Doctor! Dr. Miura!
ShouId I start off with candIes
and sex toy basics first?
No, maybe the whip. Or shouId I
tickIe her with this feather?
Huh? What's this?
No!
What a great view! I can get a good
Iook at your pussy from here.
No!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm saying I'II examine you.
Being a nurse is tough,
so some nurses negIect to wash up.
I just washed it.
That's why I'm examining you!
I'm going to see if you
missed anything or if it smeIIs.
Doctor, that's...
If you can take
every Iast bit of my cock,
then your pussy
is working normaIIy.
Here I go!
No! No! I don't want it!
What a great tantaIizing dance!
What man wouIdn't get horny
from seeing you Iike this?
PIease don't do it!
PIease don't get horny! PIease!
That's not happening!
That's when...
HoId it right there!
Who is it?
Look at this!
That scar on your penis...!
The crescent scar on my dick...
It's the invincibIe scar
against authority!
You're the thug who got
kicked out of our hospitaI!
Funato!
It took us a whiIe to get here.
Sorry we're a IittIe Iate.
A mistress deIivery
for Dr. Miura!
What's the meaning of this?
Whoa! He's huge!
Damn. He fucked
Risa and Yumi with that?
Yeah! He raped me
with this giant poIe!
lf these pictures got out,
Dr. Miura's future would be ruined.
Knowing that, Funato made him promise
to stay away from Yumi and Risa,
and to financiaIIy
compensate them.
WeII, if you'II excuse me now.
Hey, what about your mistress?
Huh? I couId care Iess about her.
Do whatever you want with her.
Doctor!
It's over, Yumi.
Yes.
Yumi thought it was finally over,
and was able to relax. Then...
That shouId do the trick.
You bastards! Don't think
you can get away with this!
HoId on, aII right?
Whoa! You can see everything!
No! Stop! Don't tape me!
Might as weII use these toys
if they're here. Let's try them out.
If we're pIaying doctor,
we have to use this.
Ooo! Good caII!
It hurts! Stop!
That's not a toy!
You're our toy!
It's the mystery
of a woman's body!
It hurts! Stop... PIease stop!
You get coId easiIy, right?
It's not hot.
It's bathtub water.
No! It's hot! It's hot!!
No!
Come here!
No! No! No!
It'II be over
before you know it.
Just a little longer...
lf l deal with it...
just a little longer,
everything will be over.
Yumi had given up
all hope at this time.
But...
Etsuko... Risa...
''l'm saved!'' Thinking that,
she was relieved, and fainted.
Yumi! Yumi!
Yumi, get a hoId of yourseIf.
Are you aII right?
Etsuko. Risa. How did you...
That bIockhead did
a crummy job of tying us up.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry, Yumi.
It's aII my fauIt for caIIing them.
Yumi, Iook at this.
That's...
It was a gift to me.
To you?
I was so surprised. We both wanted
to become nurses...
for the same reason.
Etsuko.
But I was so harsh on you.
Yumi, wiII you find it
in your heart to forgive me?
There's nothing to forgive! I...
Yumi couldn't stop crying after
thinking it was finally all over.
As she wept, she emanated
her mysterious pheromones everywhere.
Then...
Yumi is so...
cute.
Um... Huh?
Yumi, Iet's forget about men.
It'II be just us women from now on.
We'II heIp each other.
But... wait!
We need to strengthen
our friendship.
Wait. PIease hoId on.
You saw what Dr. Miura did to me!
You can't count on men.
That's why we have
to stick together.
But... But...
That doesn't mean we have to...
Of course we do!
Etsuko! Risa! PIease stop!
Risa, we'II both
caress her here.
Yes.
But! But!
Lick it, Yumi.
Yumi, move your butt.
More... More... More!
What am l doing?
ls this also another hurdle...
to becoming a good nurse?
Yumi couldn't understand
what was happening,
so she quietly listened
to what they said.
Oh! She was quiet,
but she let out a moan
every now and then.
No! Why are we doing this?
We're women!
No! Risa, it hurts!
Stick it in me, too.
I think I'm going to cum.
l can feel Etsuko and Risa's heat
coming inside me...
lt's like our hearts
are becoming one.
ls it really okay for me
to be doing this?
l get it! lt's okay!
Yumi felt like she
had gotten over something.
The nurse she looked up to...
had said it was all right.
She didn't need to wonder anymore.
Etsuko, Risa, pIease.
More, fuck me more.
-Yumi!
-Yumi, you finaIIy understand!
More! More!
Fuck me harder! PIease!
Thanks to
Etsuko and Risa's friendship,
Yumi has learned a lot.
l'm sure one day she will
become a great nurse...
whom everyone will love.
l'll pray that day will come
as soon as possible. Yumi, fight!
All right! l'm gonna do it!
The End
The white page records
that painfuI day.
I cover my eyes
so I can't see it.
You can't hear my quiet
scream fade into the darkness.
It chases away
my unbearabIe IoneIiness!
PIease don't show me
that sweet smiIe anymore.
Because this kindness
is taking off and won't stop!
Once the tears are gone,
these indeIibIe feeIings...
wiII be swept away
so the Iight can shine through.
If I couId just Iive
forever by your side,
you know I couId
overcome any sorrow.
Bonus!
It's the end-of-third-session
goodbye message.
To everyone who
has cheered me on...
Stay at a hotel with Dr. Miura
for one night: Lose a turn.
To everyone who
has cheered me on...
Anal sex with Takayuki:
Move two spaces forward.
Our time to say goodbye is here.
This and that... So many things
happened every day, but...
Iooking back now,
they're aII fond memories.
The next time we meet,
Iet's do you-know-what!
Mushroom picking
The next time we meet,
Iet's do you-know-what!
Banana for dessert
The next time we meet,
Iet's do you-know-what!
Goodbye, from Yumi Asakura!