At the Aobadai General Hospital
Nursing Academy...
the aspiring nurses took part in the
ceremony, in which they received...
their nursing hats and started
their training at the hospital.
The hands-on nursing work was
much harder than they had expected.
This is a story about Yumi Asakura,
who has given her all,
and her hardships in becoming
a nurse, a demanding profession.
I'm gonna do it!
Nurse Me! Nurse Yumi
ShamefuI Nurse Training: Session 2
What? Yumi Asakura?
She apparentIy fucked Dr. Miura,
the head surgeon,
aII night Iong in a hoteI suite.
I heard they did
every position imaginabIe!
ReaIIy? An affair?
I can't beIieve she's that desperate
to get a good grade.
I bet she did it for money.
Who cares if she did or not?
I'm impressed she got her hands
on the head surgeon.
Big slut
Why? l thought
they were all my friends!
Etsuko Kawai
Aobadai General Hospital
Nursing Academy
Yumi.
She's so cute.
Etsuko?
How terribIe.
You can't work in that.
Fine, I'II Iend you
a different uniform.
Etsuko!
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Um, Etsuko...
What is it, Yumi?
Isn't this a IittIe too smaII?
I Iend you a uniform
and you can't even thank me?
I didn't mean it Iike that.
Thank you.
Yumi, maybe you haven't
reaIIy understood...
what being a nurse is about.
Your Iife doesn't seem
to be in order at aII.
You seem to be
everywhere at once.
But... I...
I won't have you
taIking back to me!
Put your hands up against there
and stick out your butt!
Now!
Um, Etsuko, Iike this?
Stick your butt out more.
Like this?
Yes, just Iike that.
Ow!
Stop, Etsuko! What are you doing?
Stop! PIease stop.
I want you to become
a great nurse.
This is for your own sake,
understand?
Yes.
Ow!
No! No! PIease stop!
This ass! You seduced
Dr. Miura with this ass!
It hurts! It hurts! Stop!
I'II show you!
I'm Dr. Miura's onIy mistress!
You're... You're onIy a sex sIave!
Nooo!
As punishment, Yumi was ordered...
to work without underwear
for the rest of the day.
Yumi tends to get cold easily...
so this was very harsh.
But that wasn't
the only thing Etsuko ordered.
This patient's name is
Mr. Yamamoto.
He has to get his appendix
removed tomorrow,
so make sure
you shave aII his pubic hair off.
What do you think? I have
nine siIicon baIIs in my dick.
Look.
They're gIowing, right?
This is what I caII modern art.
Here, take a good Iook.
It smeIIs.
Huh? You're not
wearing any underwear.
No! No! No!
Stop! That's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
-Now, now. Come over here.
-No! No!
You're not wearing
a bra, either!
I see. I see... So this is
what you were hoping for. Okay!
Leave it to me!
No! Stop! Don't touch me there!
-PIease, don't touch me!
-Missy, you're such a pervert.
- PIease, don't touch me!
- You're aIready wet.
-PIease, don't touch me!
-You're dripping wet.
I'm not... I'm not wet!
She was lying.
Yumi was very wet from working
without any underwear on.
No... Nooo!
Come on, move your hand.
I said Iet go!
No! No! No!
That hurts! That hurts!
See? You're dripping wet inside.
Don't say that.
Don't say that, pIease!
Come on! Lift that ass!
No. Mr. Yamamoto, pIease.
I beg of you. PIease stop.
Stop. PIease, no more.
What did you say?
Did you say ''stick it in?''
Don't be so hasty.
I'II stick it in you
in a minute.
That's not what I said.
AII right, then!
I'II stick it in now!
No! No! Nooo!
Yumi Asakura
was in big trouble!
And that's when...
What are you doing?
No!
Are you aII right, Yumi?
Yes, um, thank you very much.
Sanae Murota.
She's slightly older than Yumi
and is someone she can count on.
Cheers!
Yumi was getting very cozy
at Sanae's apartment.
''Sanae will protect me
from perverted patients...
like Yamamoto and
the evil clutches of Dr. Miura,''
is how she was feeling.
Our hospitaI is so strange.
There's no need to shave off
the pubic hair for appendicitis.
I knew it.
This is between us, but maIpractice
coverups happen aII the time.
ReaIIy?
Every time that happens, we're
kind of bIackmaiIed to stay quiet.
Thanks to that, I've become
such an insomniac.
See? SIeeping piIIs. Extra strength.
I stoIe them from the pharmacy.
I can't deaI with this job
unIess I take these.
Stop! Don't Iook at me Iike that.
I'm sorry. I'm wondering
if I'm going to be a good nurse.
I'm starting
to Iose faith in myseIf.
You'II be fine.
Sanae.
You can cry. It's aII right.
Yumi, do you hate me?
I don't hate you!
Then do you Iike me?
Yes.
I'm so happy.
''l like you, but not like this!''
is what Yumi wanted to say, but...
she felt guilty towards Sanae,
so Yumi kept quiet.
I Iike you, too.
I want to cherish this feeIing.
Do you understand?
B... But...
Stick your tongue out.
Y... Yes.
Poor Yumi.
Your butt is so swoIIen.
I'II take care of you.
Um, S... Sanae!
Yes, stay stiII, Yumi.
Sanae... That's my...
Shhh. I'm in
the middIe of an exam.
ReaIIy?
''ls this really an exam?''
is what she wanted to say, but...
she felt guilty towards Sanae,
so Yumi kept quiet.
Yumi, show me your breasts.
No! I'm so embarrassed.
You're so cute, Yumi.
They're so soft and yummy.
No...
''l can't do this!'' is what
she was thinking, but Sanae knew...
what she was doing, so Yumi
was feeling it inadvertently.
Yumi, I want you
to examine me too.
Yes. Suck it harder.
Lick me aII over.
Bite! Bite it hard!
You're so good, Yumi.
You're so good.
Yumi, do the same to me!
Yes, Sanae!
Let's Iet our nippIes
kiss each other.
It sort of tickIes...
but... but...
No!
Your pussy is so beautifuI, Yumi.
I envy you.
It's dirty.
It needs to be disinfected.
Stop, Sanae.
CaII me Sissy.
Sissy.
Yumi,
I want you to do it too.
More... Lick my butt more...
Lick my butt hoIe.
Suck it. Suck it
as hard has you can!
-It's so cute. It's so cute.
-Sissy, pIease don't hit me!
-Yumi, your butt is so cute.
-Don't hit me.
Yes...! Do you want me
to put it in?
But... But...
Not that!
No! No! No! Nooo!
Sissy, I can't anymore. I can't!
You can cum! Just Iet it go!
Yumi! Yumi!
I want you to cum!
Hey, Yumi.
Let me examine you again.
Sissy.
Thus, Yumi and Sissy Sanae's
night continued.
The next morning,
Yumi was feeling more refreshed...
than she had
in a very long time.
It ended strangeIy somehow,
but as Iong as I'm with Sanae...
I'II be fine at this hospitaI.
Yup! UntiI the day I become
a nurse Iike her, I can't give up!
Okay! I'm gonna do it!
Y... Yumi...
Takayuki. It's time
for your bed bath.
Yes, ma'am!
I'm coming in!
He's covered in sweat.
l wonder if he has a fever?.
He somehow looks
like he's lost weight.
Yumi!
Are you in pain?
I am. I've been in pain ever
since you gave me a hand job.
I've onIy been thinking about you.
But...
I want a favor. Just once more...
PIease do it just once more!
I can't.
I Iove you! I'm hopeIessIy
in Iove with you, Yumi!
Takayuki... But I'm not the kind
of woman you think I am... I'm...
I've been spoiIed.
That's a Iie! You're beautifuI!
You're an innocent angeI!
He's calling me an angel?
And his eyes...
They're not clouded
like Dr. Miura's and Mr. Yamamoto's.
His eyes are so pure.
Yumi!
Okay. Just Iike Iast time?
I onIy have to touch it
Iike I did Iast time, right?
Yeah.
Takayuki was nervous in front
of Yumi, the woman of his dreams,
and was completely stiff
except for his penis.
Huh?
What shouId I do?
Your breasts...
If you can show me your breasts...
PIease.
As always, Yumi couldn't say no when
someone asked her for something.
If you couId squeeze
my dick with them...
l'm so embarrassed... But... But...
lt's a nurse's duty to comfort the patient.
Huh? lt's getting really hard.
l feel strange... My nipples are...
My nipples are...
I'm going to cum soon...
Yumi, pIease suck my dick.
I'II get it aII over the room,
so can you put it in your mouth?
B... But...
I'm gonna cum. Hurry!
I understand.
Thank you, Yumi.
You're my nightingale angel.
Emergency Exit
Yumi!
Yes!
You've finaIIy reaIized
what being a nurse is about.
I'm taIking about Takayuki.
Come with me. We're going
to do a speciaI Iesson.
Yes!
You might fall down,
but you always get up in life.
Etsuko praised Yumi
for her hard work.
Yumi was able to gain
a little confidence.
Um, in the surgery room?
Yes.
Sanae?
Oh, it's you, Yumi.
Good timing.
Sanae Murota was steaIing
sIeeping piIIs from the pharmacy.
When Dr. Miura and I
questioned her,
she begged us not to teII anyone
and started to do this.
''You might fall down,
but you always get up in life!''
That wasn't the Sanae Yumi knew.
Yumi, you're going to take off your
underwear and go fuck Dr. Miura.
I hear you're
Dr. Miura's favorite.
If you ask him,
he might go easy on her.
B... But...
This is a big probIem.
It's her first offense,
so she'II be put on suspension, but
she can't avoid discipIinary action.
She'II get fired, and her nursing
Iicense wiII be taken away.
Don't you care
about your friend?
B... But...
l never want to do it again.
l never want to have sex
without love... Never again...
But...
Sanae...
I see. So you can't do it? So that's
the type of person you are.
When you're in need
of heIp, you take it,
but when your friend's
in troubIe,
you abandon her?
You're heartIess and don't care
about your friends, do you?
Etsuko...
Yumi! A heartIess person Iike you
has no right to be a nurse!
I...
Fine, I'II forgive you.
R... ReaIIy?
Instead, give him a bIow job.
Don't teII me you don't want
to do that either!
Yumi! Get over here! If you
don't hurry, I'm going to cum!
That's right. As long as
l deal with it, Sanae will be saved.
My mouth... As long as
it's only my mouth...
Yumi! Hurry up and suck
my nineteen-centimeter cock!
I don't want to! I don't want
to do it! No... no...
What's taking you so Iong?
Hurry up and suck it!
Y... Yes...
Not bad... Take a Iook, Etsuko.
Nurses today can't even
do their jobs right,
but they're good at this.
Yumi, where did you
Iearn that technique?
I bet you work part time
at a whorehouse.
No...
You used to be so grossed out by it,
but you know you Iove it.
I bet your pussy is dripping wet
from sucking him off.
What a sIut.
Etsuko, get the thing!
Yes.
Um, is this...
You're a man, you understand?
Use that to fuck Sanae Murota.
That's not...
That's not what we agreed!
Fuck me, Yumi... PIease!
Sissy... I can't... I can't!
-Yumi! If you're not going to do it,
-No! No!
I'II use this.
Nooo!
Not that... PIease, no more!
No, no! No more! No more!
Y... Yumi, pIease! Give it to me!
I want to get fucked by you.
What are you going to do, Yumi?
Yumi!
Sissy, no!
Yumi...
Yumi... Give it to me.
I want your cock, Yumi!
Yes, Sanae...
Hurry! Fuck me now!
Like this?
Hurry... Stick it in me now!
Sissy!
More! Fuck me harder!
Move it around inside me! More!
Yumi! Yumi!
Yumi!
l feel like l'm a man!
Yumi didn't know
how to handle this at first,
because it was
completely different.
But she was gradually able
to get the hang of it.
My breasts... My breasts.
Bite them! Bite them harder!
Yumi Asakura... She doesn't have
that much sexual experience,
but she somehow makes
men and women lust over her.
l don't want to lose.
l don't want to lose!
Yumi! Yumi! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!!
Me too! Me too!
Ow!
It's too soon to cum!
That's right! You can't cum
without the doctor's permission!
I'II give you
the reaI prescription.
No! HeIp! Not that!
Not the reaI thing! No!
-This is a man, Sanae.
-No! No! PIease stop!
-Better than a woman, right?
-No! No!
No!
Sanae!
No... Is there no one Ieft
in this hospitaI who wiII save me?
Back! Back, I say!
Who are you?
Don't you see my famiIy jeweIs?
Mr. Yamamoto?
You're not supposed
to be in here!
Didn't you see
the operation Iamp on?
You caII this an operation?
No!
I see. I see.
This kind of operation!
I'm good at this kind
of operation, too.
Mr. Yamamoto, this isn't good.
You had an operation this morning.
You need to rest up today.
Yeah, but my boy
doesn't need to get any rest.
Come on, doctor. You don't want the
entire hospitaI to find out, right?
Right? Right?
I guess I have no choice. Make sure
you don't push yourseIf too hard.
Don't you think so too, Sanae?
Y... Yes...
I know... I know...
N... No!
Mr. Yamamoto just had an operation!
You mustn't fight back!
B... But...
So you want your friend
to get fired, do you?
N... No! I...
Then stay stiII!
How convincing do you think
you are with this thing on?
You reaIIy are
a perverted missy.
You're such a pervert, Yumi.
No! This is embarrassing!
AII righty! I'II give you some
damn good Ioving, so you be ready!
No! Stop! Stop!
I don't want to have any more sex!
Here I go!
Yumi, you Iook so cute
when you cry.
You give me goose bumps.
No... No... No. No. No. No.
Oh, Yumi. Your nippIes are
getting hard. Are you feeIing it?
No! I'm not... I'm not...
I knew you were feeIing it.
You're such a Iiar, Yumi.
You're wrong!
-Stop! Stop!
-It feeIs great!
It's been so Iong
since I fucked a broad.
No! No! PIease stop! No more!
Stop thrusting in me!
Come on, Yumi! You need to move.
Mr. Yamamoto is a patient!
No! No! I don't want to!
No! No!
Stop being such a baby.
You're a nurse!
You mustn't burden the patient!
Yes.
Come on! Come on!
Yumi, you need to move faster!
Yes.
I can't anymore...
If I move any more, I think
I'm reaIIy going to go insane.
That's right! Doesn't my
bazooka cannon feeI good?
It feeIs good, right? Say it!
How is it? Say it! Say it!
The siIicon baIIs are bumpy and...
it's rubbing my insides...
That's right! How big is it?
It's big! It's so big!
What?
I can't accept that!
Here! Open your mouth!
I said, open it!
There. Which one's bigger?
The one in your pussy or your mouth?
Which one? Come on! Come on!
It's mine, right?
What's going on?
l'm so embarrassed...
Say it!
I think the one down there
is a IittIe bigger...
What?
But that's because of
the siIicon baIIs.
Just by size, yours is much--
That's right! That's right!
Come on, use your tongue more!
Sanae, you shouIdn't
be sIacking off.
No! No!
Don't suck it! Don't suck it!
If you suck that hard...
If you do that... I'm going to...
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts! No! Stop!
Let me warn you...
I'm not gentIe.
Stop! No! No! You're terribIe!
You're terribIe, Etsuko!
It's so good.
Your pussy tastes so good.
No... No...
Are you feeIing it?
Who's better, Yumi or me?
-Nooo!
-Who's better?
Suck it and Iube it up.
Yes.
Want me to stick it in? You want me
to stick it in, don't you?
No. No. No.
Doesn't it feeI good?
Aren't I better than Yumi?
Huh? Huh?
She's tightening!
It's a masterpiece!
Her pussy is
a reaI masterpiece!
I'm gonna cum! On your face...
Let me cum on your face!
No! No! Don't cum on me! No!
You don't want me
to cum on your face?
So you want me to cum inside.
Fine, I'II pour my cum
into your pussy.
No!
What? Then you want me
to cum on your face, then?
I'II hose your face in sIime!
More... Shake your butt
and rub it against me more!
I'm going to die!
Yumi! I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
Me too! Me too!
H... Help. Please, no more!
l'm in pain... l'm in pain...
l'm going to break.
Yumi! Yumi!
Sissy!
-Yumi! Yumi!
-Sissy!
WeII, Yumi?
Did you Iearn anything?
Ow!
Oh, no! His wound opened up.
Etsuko, prepare for surgery!
Yes! Sanae! Yumi!
Disinfect this pIace immediateIy!
It hurts! I'm gonna die!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
Are you Iistening?
-Hurry up! Sanae! Yumi!
-Sanae! Yumi! Come on!
Mr. Yamamoto wiII die!
PIease! Snap out of it!
This is a story about Yumi Asakura,
who has given her all,
and her hardships in becoming
a nurse, the most sacred profession.
To be continued!
The white page records
that painfuI day.
I cover my eyes
so I can't see it.
You can't hear my quiet
scream fade into the darkness.
It chases away
my unbearabIe IoneIiness!
PIease don't show me
that sweet smiIe anymore.
Because this kindness
is taking off and won't stop!
Once the tears are gone,
these indeIibIe feeIings...
wiII be swept away
so the Iight can shine through.
If I couId just Iive
forever by your side,
you know I couId
overcome any sorrow.
Here's a bonus.
It's the end of the second session.
Now for the third session preview!
I'm Yumi Asakura.
Are you feeIing bad anywhere?
But what am I going to do
if you reaIIy are in pain?
Because right now aII I can do is rub
where it hurts. Is that aII right?
If that's okay with you, Iet's
meet again in the third session!
That's a promise!