This is the Aobadai
General Hospital Nursing Academy.
Today, these women are
participating in the ceremony...
in which they'll receive
their nursing hats.
These ladies are angels in white,
who descended from the heavens...
to save people's lives.
They're future nurses.
Yumi Asakura!
Yes!
This nursing hat ceremony
is an important event,
where we reaffirm our decisions
to become nurses.
I hope you wiII become a nurse
whom every patient wiII Iove.
This is a story about Yumi Asakura,
who has given her all...
to become a nurse,
the most sacred profession.
I'm going to become a wonderfuI nurse
whom everyone's going to Iove.
Nurse Me! Nurse Yumi
ShamefuI Nurse Training: Session 1
Room 201
Risa Nakayama
Yumi Asakura
Risa! Huh?
Is someone here?
Risa! The ceIebration's started!
Risa?
Oh, no! He's giving her
mouth-to-mouth and a heart massage!
Yumi is very innocent,
so that's what she really thought.
Here I come.
Risa! Are you aII right?
Yumi?
I don't know who you are, but
thank you. I'II take it from here.
Huh? What are you taIking about?
I want Funato to do me. Why don't
you ceIebrate with Matsuzaki?
CeIebrate?
Don't act so scared.
You're hurting my feeIings!
I'm sorry I screamed.
I was surprised.
Yumi! Let's do
what they're doing!
Yes... It feeIs so good.
lt was the first time Yumi had seen
someone having sex in front of her.
Yumi is a virgin.
l kid you not.
She's never gone out with a man
in her entire life.
That's why Yumi was so surprised,
and was unable to look away.
Her body started to get hot,
and her pussy became moist.
-No! No! Stop! Stop! PIease stop!
-Yumi, congratuIations on...
-receiving your nursing hat!
PIease accept my
congratuIatory party popper!
I don't know what you're
taIking about, but no thank you!
Am I not good enough?
My party favor's a hundred
and fifty miIIimeters Iong...
and thirty-two miIIimeters thick.
I don't understand
what you're saying!
No! Ew! That's gross!
Don't say that!
You're hurting my feeIings.
I... I'm sorry. N... No...
Risa, heIp me!
Risa!
Yumi's cries echoed in vain.
Cute panties.
No, no, no!
PIease stop.
Don't Iick me there!
Don't Iick me...
PIease, no more!
Y... Yumi.
-No!
-Yumi!
Stop! PIease stop!
Here I come!
No!
NO!
Yumi really didn't understand
what happened.
But she was very sad. She was so sad
that she ran out of the room.
Yumi?
Funato...
Yumi Asakura.
Okay? You have to have
everything memorized up to here.
I can't get it out of my head.
Something's wrong with me.
Yumi, pIease come here.
Eh?
Hurry!
Y... Yes.
Get on this.
Yes?
I'm impressed, Yumi.
UsuaIIy no one wants to do this.
I want you to get on aII fours.
Huh?
We're going to do
the enema Iesson.
Enema Iesson?
Etsuko, what's that?
An enema Iesson
is an enema Iesson.
You voIunteered to
be the patient, didn't you?
I didn't know...
There's no need to be embarrassed.
CIass can go on, thanks to you.
But that's...
Come, get on aII fours.
Y... Yes.
Yumi always had
a hard time saying no.
Everyone take a good Iook!
No!
Yumi, imagine how the patient feeIs.
You don't Iike this, right?
That's why we have to do this
as fast as we can.
The patient's...
The patient's feeIings...
lf she went through with the enema,
she'd be able to be a nurse...
who could better understand
the patient's feelings.
Yumi mustered her courage
and made up her mind.
I understand.
Then move your hand.
Y... Yes...
You're beautifuI, Yumi.
I'm so embarrassed.
We wiII use this.
Make sure you don't stick it
in the wrong hoIe.
You wiII insert it in
the patient's rectum...
and pour in the soIution.
Can you expIain how it feeIs?
Embarrassing... No, I mean...
The coId soIution is coming in from
the bottom and circIing its way up.
My stomach is starting to hurt.
Are you putting more in?
ReIax. It's just a IittIe more.
It hurts... It hurts... Ow! It hurts! It hurts...
PIease, no more... PIease...
I can't. I can't take anymore!
No! No!
Now does everyone understand?
Insertion and withdrawaI
must be done quickIy.
Being carefuI is important,
but if you move sIowIy,
it'II cause the patient
more pain.
Bathroom...
This doesn't aIways appIy
to just enemas.
May I go to the bathroom?
Did you say something?
I need to go to the bathroom.
Yumi?
Yes?
Now do you understand
how the patient feeIs?
Yes. I have a very good
understanding now.
Wait three minutes, then.
B... But!
I can't anymore... It's going
to come out... Bathroom...
Do you understand
how the patient feels?
This must be... This must be
a hurdle to becoming a good nurse!
AImost there...
Out of Order
Nooo!
I can't hoId it anymore! No!
It's going to come out!
No! No! No!
Bathroom... Bath...
No... No...
Later on, Yumi put this experience
to good use and was labeled...
Enema Expert Yumi. l'm not too sure
if she was happy about that, though.
The next patient's name is Takayuki.
He's very weak, so he's been
hospitaIized for a whiIe.
That's why he needs
a coIostomy bag.
Takayuki Kudo... He's really hot.
Takayuki, I'm going
to take your temperature.
She's really cute. l've never seen
such a pretty nurse.
Yumi, insert the catheter, pIease.
Yes.
WeII, we can't put the catheter in
if you're hard, so...
Yumi, make him ejacuIate.
EjacuIate?
There's nothing to be
so surprised about.
B... But I...
What's wrong?
Um, weII, I don't know
how to do it.
ReaIIy? At your age?
Yes.
Fine, then. Watch me do it.
Wh... What are you doing?
It's okay. If you feeI Iike
you have to ejacuIate, go ahead.
That's aII you need to do.
If you do that...
I'm reaIIy gonna...
Let it aII out.
Yumi, take it over. It'II be over
shortIy if you foIIow what I did.
But...
lt's hot. lt's hot and it's
beating fast. He must be in pain.
Yes...
Etsuko, am I doing it right?
Use both hands.
Like this?
You have to wrap it
from underneath.
Yes.
Yes, good. You're pretty good.
Thank you very much.
You're so Iucky, Takayuki.
You're getting a hand job
from a pretty nurse at the hospitaI.
l can't believe such a hot chick
is jerking me off.
lf this is a dream,
l don't want to wake up.
Yumi, you can Iet go of it now.
Get ready to insert the catheter.
Etsuko Kawai, Head Nurse,
28 years old,
is able to switch from erotic mode
to work mode in .07 seconds.
Y... Yes!
Takayuki, pIease stay stiII.
Umm... Go in!
Every day, when Yumi
makes a boo-boo, the patients...
fondle her breasts,
caress her backside,
or stroke her panties.
Nooo!
Furthermore, when Yumi
makes a boo-boo, the patients...
twist her nipples,
poke her rectum,
or tickle her clitoris.
Nooo!
Why am I so bad at this?
When my favorite uncle was
unexpectedly hospitalized,
Operation
When my favorite uncle was
unexpectedly hospitalized,
Operation
l was worried sick, and a nurse
came over to comfort me.
Operation
Don't worry,
your uncle will be fine.
She not only saved his life, but
kindly took care of him afterwards.
She's the reason
l wanted to become a nurse.
l was inspired,
and l admired her work.
l could never face that nurse
if l were defeated here.
Okay, I'm gonna do it!
Shigeo Miura, Head Surgeon.
He's a talented surgeon,
but is also rumored to be...
the next hospital president.
Obviously, he's also talented...
in hospital politics.
So this is the nurse
you recommend?
Yes, I think she has
a Iot of potentiaI.
I see. She does seem
to have potentiaI.
I've actuaIIy had
my eye on her before.
Miura speaking.
Hmm, I see.
Etsuko! A car-accident patient
wiII be admitted shortIy.
Yes, sir.
Funato?
Yes, it's the patient who was in a
car accident. He was just admitted.
I want you to take care of him.
Yes, I understand.
Funato as in Risa's Funato?
lt can't be. That's too much
of a coincidence.
Funato! I'm coming in!
Hey, stop shaking so much!
You're hurting me!
But...
Ow... Ow!
You're hurting me! It hurts!
I'm going to cum...
I think I'm going to cum...
I think I'm going to cum.
Make up your mind!
I'm cumming!
R... Risa?
What a fatefuI encounter!
Yes, what an ironic encounter.
Um, I didn't mean to peek...
I was put in charge of Funato and...
Yumi, keep this between us.
It won't be good...
if the hospitaI finds out I was
fucking the patient in his room.
I won't teII anyone!
I wonder about that.
She knows that I snuck into
the women's dorm, too.
Don't you think it's better
if we have something on her?
Yeah...
That's... I won't teII anyone!
I'm joking.
Yumi, you're so cute.
No smoking here, Funato.
I'II see you Iater, Yumi.
Take care of him.
So there you go!
Take good care of me, Ms. Nurse.
No, I'm stiII thinking about it.
H... Hurry!
Are you aII right?
My dick is swoIIen.
Stop joking around!
It's after Iights-out,
so pIease be quiet.
We'II Iet you go
after we're done with you.
Nice face. Can't wait untiI
the pictures are deveIoped.
What do you think you're doing?!
Hey, Risa. Come back
for another round?
Yumi, are you aII right?
Risa.
You're an asshoIe!
I'm sorry, Yumi.
I knew he was an idiot, but I never
thought he'd go after my best friend.
Did he reaIIy
onIy see your breasts?
Yumi couldn't bring herself to say,
''He took pictures too!''
She's so cute.
l'm a woman, but...
Risa?
Her pheromones are weird.
l can understand why she makes
that idiot Funato act like that.
Hey, let me show you
something interesting.
l want to spend
some time with you later.
Huh? Yumi? Excuse me...
Yumi, I've been in Iove with you
from the beginning.
It was Iove at first sight.
You're dating Risa.
Who cares about
that Ioudmouthed bitch?
You're off today, aren't you?
No one's going to save you.
Nooo!
-No, stop! What are you doing?
-Yumi!
No, no! PIease stop it!
You're aIways so beautifuI!
D... Don't Iook at me! No!
-Stop! Don't touch me!
-Yumi! Yumi!
No!
If you don't shut up, we're going
to post these everywhere.
So this is the sexy nurse
Yumi Asakura's dynamite body, eh?
No... no...
No.
Matsuzaki, Iook.
She's feeIing it.
She has such an innocent face,
but she's a sIut.
I didn't expect her
to be this way.
She was being tortured,
but Yumi was feeling it.
Ambivalence!
Yumi became confused
and lost her will to fight back.
No... No... No...
I'm gonna stick it in her pussy.
No! No! No!
Then I'II put it in her mouth.
Yumi Asakura is in deep trouble!
And that's when...
What do you think you're doing?
Doctor! Yumi! Are you aII right?
Thanks to you, Yumi's aII right.
I'II take care of the rest.
PIease take care of her.
''l'm saved.''
After thinking that,
Yumi lost consciousness.
You're awake?
Doctor! Ow...
You had a IittIe
too much to drink.
Shigeo had asked Yumi
to go to dinner.
Yumi couldn't say no to the doctor
who'd saved her virginity.
Yumi normally doesn't drink,
but she had a couple
to loosen her up.
Um, I'm so sorry about this.
It's okay.
You had quite a day today.
You don't have
to worry about Funato.
I expeIIed him
from the hospitaI aIready.
Thank you very much.
That's a reIief.
Um, by the way,
where are we?
This is the cIassroom I readied
for you for our speciaI Iesson.
We're going to have cIass now?
Yes, put this on.
To be honest, you have
a very serious fIaw as a nurse.
I have a serious fIaw as a nurse?
What is it? PIease teII me!
I'II be frank with you.
It's the fact that you're a virgin.
You being a virgin is the cause of aII
these probIems. Isn't that right?
It is?
There's nothing good about
being a nurse and a virgin.
My observation is a scientific fact
based on years of empiricaI data.
Oh... I had no idea.
Yumi doesn't understand
the concept of being suspicious.
That's why I'm going to have you
graduate right now...
from being a virgin.
What do you mean?
This!
At first Yumi couldn't understand
what that meant, because...
Shigeo's penis was nineteen
centimeters long! lt was so big,
Takayuki's and Funato's looked
like chili peppers compared to his.
You mean...
No, pIease stop, Dr. Miura!
PIease! Stop it! Stop!
You're not gonna get a passing grade!
Are you okay with that?
No, I need it...
But... But... If this means
a passing grade, I don't want it!
Etsuko got a passing grade
back in the day.
No, stop it! Stop!
Your breasts feeI amazing.
Your bone structure and fIesh
are baIanced out perfectIy.
That's what I'd expect from
the schooI's number-one student.
No... No... Stop!
Doctor, pIease.
No! No... Stop, no!
You're hurting me! Stop!
PIease stop!
PIease stop! I'm serious, stop.
Yumi.
No, what are you doing, Dr. Miura?
No! PIease stop!
-Yumi, I thought you were...
-No! No! No! No!
-a better student than this.
-I don't want to!
Come on, spread your Iegs.
What are you doing? Spread 'em!
No... No...!
I don't want to!
Come on, Yumi.
Spread your Iegs Iike this.
Are you embarrassed?
Are you stiII embarrassed?
-I'm embarrassed, Doctor...
-Are you stiII embarrassed, Yumi?
-I'm embarrassed...
-A nurse shouIdn't feeI embarrassed.
Stop... No... PIease stop.
Then spread your Iegs.
Are you going to do it, Yumi?
I understand...
I understand. I'II do it...
That's the way, Yumi.
How beautifuI!
It's the sexuaI organ of a virgin!
No... This is embarrassing.
No, stop...
What are you doing? No!
It's the newest sex cream.
You'II be begging
for a man after this.
You're Iying. That won't...
He wasn't lying.
The areas where he'd smeared
started to feel hot and numb.
It's starting to work.
It's not working.
It's not...
Good... Stay stiII.
This is interesting.
I didn't think it wouId work this weII.
Come here!
Why? Why is this happening?
My body is moving on its own.
ls it the medicine?
l knew it.
She has real potential.
l'm glad a punk like Funato
didn't claim your virginity.
You'll be my new sex slave!
-I feeI so numb.
-Amazing! It's amazing...
how much you're feeIing it!
No... No...
I don't want to get that wet!
It's fine. This is the reaI you.
Let's move on to
the penetration ceremony.
W... Wait! This isn't...
I don't want to... I don't Iove you.
Love? That's so unscientific!
I'II teach you the truth
about medicaI science!
Here I go!
It hurts! It hurts!
I'm onIy at the opening!
Loosen up!
No! No, no!
S... Stop it, pIease!
No...
lt was the moment
Yumi Asakura lost her virginity.
The heat was more prominent
than the pain.
WeII? How does
my 19.9-centimeter cock feeI?
Did you know this position is
the most prone to get you pregnant?
Now do you understand?
Sex doesn't need Iove! Sex is sex!
Why? Why?
lt's my first time--
why am l feeling it so much?
Amazing, Yumi! You're amazing!
Yumi, I'm going to cum!
No!... No! No!
No! No!... No! No!
You better run fast
or I'm gonna cum!
l can't believe this... l had thought
he was such an amazing doctor...
l can't believe a guy like him
took my virginity!
I'm amazed you feIt it
this much on your first time.
It's because of
the medicine you put on me.
Medicine?
Oh, that.
It's just amenity goods
that came with the room.
It's ordinary toothpaste.
You've far exceeded my expectations
for how much you'd enjoy my dick.
Meaning you are a true
perverted sIut, Yumi!
Yumi Asakura is a perverted slut...
Yumi's soul parted from her body
and saw a dream...
where she became a nurse
whom all the patients loved.
l won't give up, no matter what.
l'm going to work hard.
You can do it, Yumi.
This is a story about Yumi Asakura,
who has given her all,
and her hardships in becoming
a nurse, the most sacred profession.
Nooo!
To be continued.
The white page records
that painfuI day.
I cover my eyes
so I can't see it.
You can't hear my quiet
scream fade into the darkness.
It chases away
my unbearabIe IoneIiness!
PIease don't show me
that sweet smiIe anymore.
Because this kindness
is taking off and won't stop!
Once the tears are gone,
these indeIibIe feeIings...
wiII be swept away
so the Iight can shine through.
If I couId just Iive
forever by your side,
you know I couId
overcome any sorrow.
Here's a bonus.
It's the end of the first session.
Now for the second session preview!
I'm Yumi Asakura.
How is everyone doing?
When you come in from outside,
do you gargIe your throat...
and wash your hands?
I might take care of you
if you get sick.
That's why I want to become
a nurse as soon as possibIe--
so I can be your private nurse.
Let's meet again
in the second session!
That's a promise!