It's been a while, Vanessa.
Yes, it's been a while.
I'm really sorry to summon you.
I know you traveled from far...
lets get to business.
Sure.
Rosaria, please leave us.
O, OK, I'll take my leave.
It's been a while, Liz.
Same to you, Vanessa.
I was wondering who the guest was.
It's just you.
Liz, how long are you going to keep the door open!?
Whatever.
I need to discuss something important in private.
Please leave us.
Something important ehh?
Or do you mean something illegal?
Liz, she is a guest.
Fine.
Fuck!
She sure gives me a hard time.
I'm really sorry for her behavior.
She's just being a woman.
You mean a girl.
Hey, you'll make her cry with those remarks.
Liz?
I can't take this one.
The quality's too high, people will know it's stolen.
I see, that's fine.
Oh?
I shall give you this item as a gift from me.
You sure know how to push a girl's button.
I will gladly repay you back for what it's worth.
Well, well...
It's big, it's bigger than last time.
Thank you for the compliment.
I have to make sure that you won't get disappointed by me cuming too soon.
My my, you think you can handle it?
Not at all.
You always...make me feel like a virgin.
But you sure know what you're doing.
I'm going to cum, alright!?
Yes, please go right ahead.
Here!
Feels like you're going to suck me out dry.
I told you I'll repay you for what it's worth.
I'll make you feel even better.
I think I'm going to hit empty soon.
Stop lying...look at you.
Damn, I'm nearing my fifth orgasm!
Cum on my face this time.
Cuming!
So warm.
Five times, this must be a new record.
You're definitely a keeper.
Thanks, but your compliment won't make me happy.
Oh, why do you say such things?
I'm not entirely in agreement with sex for trade.
I see...you're getting hard again.
Don't you want to feel good too?
Well, a little.
Oh, you're offering your pussy?
What, not satisfied?
It's not that and you know what I like.
Perhaps next time.
So deep!
Your pussy is something, it's the best!
I say the same about your cock.
Well, isn't pussy good too?
Yes, especially yours.
It's just as tight as one's ass.
That's right, mine's special.
You're so beautiful when you're having sex.
Amazing...you're great, but I won't let you make me cum.
You're such a bitch.
Damn, I'm cuming!
OK.
So good.
Give me more.
Cum, I'll make you cum!
So deep...
Great, it's wonderful.
Going to cum soon!
No, no!
Faster, faster, cuming!
Amazing!
Cuming, cuming, I'm cuming!
So I came.
Already finished?
You still want more?
Until there is no change left.
You're greedy, but I'll let it slide.
Alright, lets go then.
Wow, it's already so hot and hard.
It's bigger than before!
Come in.
Your food is ready.
I'll be right there.
Is there something else?
No, there isn't...
Why the expression?
Was the Father fooling around with you?
I mean after Vanessa left last week, it does seem like he's depraved.
So he was fooling around with you.
T, that's not it!
What is it?
I was bored so I was snooping around the church.
Then I found this place in the wine cellar.
The wine cellar?
According to this Rosaria...this place has been locked since before she came here.
This is...
A torture room underneath the church?
Sure looks like it.
Why so late?
I wonder what he wants.
Father?
Long time ago, there was a witch hunt in this region.
Rosaria, kneel in front of me and confess.
Depending on your attitude, I'll promise to null this agreement.
Now, confess.
Yes...
You promised, Father.
What!?
It's a medicine from the Far East, given by Vanessa.
Don't stop, continue.
OK.
Alright, you can stop.
Lets continue over here.
What's wrong, do you want something?
Whatever it is, looks like you want it now.
T, that's not...
Be more gentle.
Not there!
I can't wait any longer!
For what may I ask?
Well, uh, my butt...
Your butt?
What do you want me to do with your butt?
I beg you, please play with my butt.
Sister, you want me to play with your butt?
Look, your pussy is soaking wet.
I, I can only be satisfied with my ass now.
More, give me more, I want more in my ass!
Hm, I see.
The contract is gone, I decide where to fuck you.
No, please fuck my butt!
Forgive me!
I'm not done yet.
I'm going to give you my week's worth of cum!
What are you planning?
You're in the basement with her almost all day long.
Seriously, what's on your mind?
I plan on using her as a transporter.
For that, I need some insurance of her loyalty.
Insurance?
I always knew you were bad,
but planning to get her pregnant so you can have a hostage? Now that's pure evil.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Is that what you stopped me for?
No, a group of vandals wants to see you.
H, help me!!
Are you finished, Liz?
Too easy, I killed them without a drop of blood.
Good job.
That's it?
Who started this mess?
It's your fault, you won't pay attention to me.
Looks like you need a punishment.
I don't know what to do with you.
What?
Please be gentle.
S, so good!
Rubbing...inside!
Please stop.
Stop what? How do you explain this?
Please, hurry!
Looks like you need a ''tighter'' punishment.
I can't...take this much longer!
I know they were bad, but all four at once?
No wounds either.
Sure is a scary story.
I gathered you all here for one reason.
The cause of the their death.
After checking the books, I found out that this is the work of a succubus.
Once possessed, the target will think of lewd acts, eventually leading them to their own deaths.
I want you all to keep this a secret but...
Sister Rosaria has been possessed by this succubus.
What, the Sister!?
Can't be.
In order to save her, I need everyone's help.
What can we do?
I brought you all here so that you can lend me a hand in freeing her.
Now, each of you pray and take her to peak of pleasure!
Understood!
P, please stop, don't!
Forgive me!
No, don't!