I'm a teacher of the Holy Blossom Academy,
Nanashi Gouto.
I guide students everyday with lively lessons.
Of course you're my number one, Ai.
Don't you believe me?
I believe you.
But,
you're also nice to the other girls.
That's because.
Won't they find it weird that only
you get preferential treatment?
But.
Besides,
everything I do, even this... I do for my beloved Ai.
You know,
I'm really to do many thing for you, sensei.
And I'll endure everything.
That's why,
please make me your wife when I grow up.
Yes, of course.
I promise.
But you can't talk to anyone about this, okay?
Okay, I won't.
It'll be a secret between the both of us.
The way it rubs feels great.
I'm starting to feel weird again.
Good, rub it in more.
That's right, keep it up.
I love you, sensei.
I love you very much.
Sensei.
Now then,
who should I "teach" her next?
No matter what happens,
I'll always believe that you did it just for me.
Okay, sensei?
I'm disappointed with you, Nana.
I thought you'd do a lot better.
I'm sorry, sensei.
I'll do my best to improve.
Did I say you could talk?
Come on, what's wrong?
You're going to improve, right?
Okay.
I'll teach you perseverance.
Hold that position for thirty minutes.
If you fall down, or try to get away,
the next lesson will be ten times worse.
Wait, this position is just.
Wait, please wait!
That's enough, right?
No.
The garment's crease is one's own crease.
We are conducting a very important measurement.
That doesn't mean.
You can just rub it there and nowhere else.
Sakura, you seem quite defiant as usual.
Besides, what's the meaning of this?
You're supposed to maintain it so it doesn't build mildew.
It's even written in the student's handbook.
But,
it's just polka dot panties.
I can tell even if you're trying to hide it,
after frequently exposing it like that.
That's not true.
Idiot!
Sakura-san!
That's not a polite thing to say to someone older than you.
Have you been stressed lately?
It's nothing.
If there's something you're worried about,
just let me know.
I think I can find a good solution to whatever it is.
Sensei, I said not there!
Can you be more explicit about what I should not do?
Tell me the specifics.
Sakura-chan?
Mikan-chan!
My oh my.
It's almost time to go home, you know.
Is there something wrong?
Well.
I just forgot something.
I see.
I'm currently conducting an impromptu
uniform inspection here.
Here it is!
But you've passed,
and are free to go.
Goodbye then.
Wait, me too, I'll!
Let me go!
No.
As punishment for enticing guys
to such a soiled undergarment,
I'm confiscating this!
Don't!
Look here.
Your flower is overflowing with nectar.
It's a sign that it wants a man inside.
Wh-What are you trying to say?
I didn't get that at all.
During Sex Ed, I saw you immersed
in all the sex reading materials.
It's definitely more than just a superficial interest.
If you're aroused this much,
you can't possibly deny it anymore.
Admit it already.
That this wet hole of yours is craving for it already.
I'm not!
That's not true!
I said, it's not!
Just leave it to me.
Your budding blossom, the heart that's yet to open,
shall open through me.
Stop, stop.
Don't worry.
This shouldn't be scary.
Once you bloom, everything shall feel better.
This blossom is clamping down on me really well.
I'll gradually widen it.
I can tell.
The way your blossom twitches as it expands.
Don't.
See?
Feels good, right?
Idiot, idiot!
Sensei's such an idiot!
Be honest with yourself.
Say that it feels good.
I won't say it.
Never.
It doesn't feel.
You say that,
but who's the one moving her hips right now?
That's not true.
That's not real!
I-It's just,
it's just... just that.
Stop!
Don't!
It's... unfair.