Dear God,
Please...
This body of sin...
This soul, dampened in sin...
Please show the way.
l wish he would've screamed more...
kind of a let down you know?
We're not here to play games, Liz.
No one is ever going to come into this forest.
So, why did we need to kill him?
l get it, you're going to disguise yourself
as a priest and hide at some village's church!
You can think what you want, now
dispose this body and get dressed.
And l was looking for this.
The title of an Observer.
l feel like a holy maiden now.
OK, lets go.
Dark Chapel
The Forbidden Sin
Sister, l have a problem.
My husband hasn't been around the past three days.
l want to know what he's doing every night.
l have a feeling he's seeing a young girl.
Sister...Sister Rosaria!
The Father...The Observer is in town.
A sister in training is also with him.
it seems that he would be staying here for a while.
A priest who's an observer?
A high-priest came to check on
Sister Rosaria's accomplishments.
Sister Rosaria always accomplishes her job well!
That's not all, he would be able to tell us
about God in a way l wouldn't be able to.
Welcome to this chapel.
Greetings...
Sister Rosaria.
Y, you are...
Do you know him?
Um..ah, please come this way.
l'll carry this, Father.
l'm sorry.
We passed by a town where thieves tried
to steal our luggage, so l was nervous and...
You must be very tired then.
Sister Rosaria, please show the priest to his room.
Y, yes.
Chapter 1 : Holy Pact
l'll admit we're safe here, but...
We just need to wait until the
jewel theft incident cools down.
While we're here, you are a
sister so you will act like one.
Sister Liz.
Understood ''Father Edward''.
The Jewelry Thieves...don't tell me...
That's right.
We are those cruel Jewelry Thieves.
And the priest and sister that
was originally coming here...
They are now with God thanks to us.
Why did you tell me....
l thought we shouldn't hide anything from each other.
The villagers trust you.
As long as you corporate...
l'll assure you their safety.
Sister Rosaria.
Alright...
Please promise me that you won't hurt the villagers.
ln the name of God.
l'll show you to your room.
You mean yours.
What's wrong?
This is your room, why don't you relax.
How did you know l was here?
l wanted to chat with you since it's
been years since l've last seen you.
But if you insist...
A lot of shit has happened ever since you fucking left!
That's how big your existence was.
But you tormented me, how can you...
Torment?
Really...how ever it may have
looked, we both enjoyed it.
N, no l didn't, you forced yourself on...!!!!
You played with yourself while
l was away, didn't you?
l...don't want to talk about it!
That means you did things you can't talk about?
T, that's not it, please don't speak nonsense!
Your tits got bigger.
lt's been a while.
Lets have fun just like before.
l don't want to do that.
Such a sin!
A sin...
After you ran away, l was dismissed from the church.
l was only welcomed in the underground.
And now, l'm a felon.
lt's all your fault!
l told you earlier that you hold
the villager's lives in your hands!
Besides...
T, that's!
Yeah, it's the pact you made in front of
God, stamped with the print of your anus.
ln front of God...
Dear God...please forgive me.
Please stop this, Father!
God will punish us for this!
Why....don't!
Your beautiful face and body....
Your body that's screaming for attention
ever since the loss of your husband...
Those factors are the reason for my doings.
l sense you're in need of help and offer my service.
You just confessed that you touch yourself in
order to achieve sexual gratification, did you not?
That...that was just a one time temptation.
Forgive me, Father.
Why are you asking me for forgiveness?
Shouldn't you be asking that to
God and your deceased husband?
lf you really care about the Lord and
your husband, l will not disrespect them.
lf you sign this pact and promise to God.
A pact...?
Yes, instead of this...
You will offer me your ass.
And you will be my obedient ass slave.
N, no, l don't want to, never!
Then l have no other choice.
l will take your valued possession.
Stop, l'll promise, l'll promise!!
Good, well then...
Sign right there!
lt's embarrassing, it hurts!
Alright, l will, l will sign it!
What!?
As evidence, l need a stamp
from your ass with your signature.
Not...please don't stick it in inside!
ln order to get the stamp, l
need to ink the inside as well.
No!!!
And the pact has been made.
lt hurts, don't!
Don't...no...it hurts!
No...don't tie...please don't tie me...
lf you speak loudly, the villagers will hear.
Don't...
Don't do that.
My nipples are going to rip!
l, l don't like this post...don't spread me!
lf l don't, l can't lick it.
So beautiful like a virgin.
So embarrassing.
Rough...
Too rough!
l know you like to touch yourself.
While l was not around playing with your ass
You were looking for an alternate
way to pleasure yourself, the clit.
Don't touch me right there!
No, don't!
l knew this hole was more sensitive.
lt's deep, if you continue, l'm going to...!
Hmm, l feel something at the tip of my cock.
Look like that problem came back after you left me.
So embarrassing...l just want to die.
lf you...!
Looks like Sister Rosaria has shit stored up inside her.
No, don't say that!
lt hurts because you're holding in your shit, Sister.
l am going to ejaculate soon!
T, that's not a place to have it, it's a s...!
No, don't!
Sister Rosaria, you got a great ass.
You are definitely the best.
Why am l...
Please...please untie me now!
Only if you answer my question.
Sister, what are you planning to do after l untie you?
l can't say that.
l see...
Lets wait until you're ready to speak then.
Villagers have left for dinner it seems.
They are no where to be seen.
l'll say it, so please untie me.
What are you planning to do once l untie you?
B, bath....
Speak loud enough so that
even the Lord can hear you.
Please...don't torment me.
How am l tormenting.
l just want you to do as what you've said.
Alright, it's a bowel movement!
l need to go to the bathroom so please until me now!
Sister, you...
Need to take a shit after l screwed your asshole.
Yes, you stimulated it and now l need to go bathroom!
l can't hold it, l can't hold it!
Fine, show me like you did before.
Show me yourself taking a shit like an
animal, oh so prestigious Sister Rosaria.
Not like this...
Come on, let it out Sister Rosaria.
God, please forgive me.
Please save me!
God...
Looks like you're back to
your old ways, Sister Rosaria.
That's...
l won't allow you to touch your clit to reach orgasm.
You can only reach orgasm
with your ass, Sister Rosaria!
But!
Cuming, cuming, cuming!!
Every single damn night.
She says she's a sister, but in reality a slut...
Shit, l can't take this any longer!
Forgive me...
Not this.
The villagers will think strangely if you moan loudly.
Good morning Sister.
Good morning.
Good morning, Liz.
Good morning Sister.
How did you sleep...?
Frankly, l'm sleepy because your
moaning kept me up all night.
Um, well, that's...l.....
Stop acting innocent!
My clothes is going to get dirty...
The sister is naked!
lt's so beautiful!
Come, it's alright, come here.
There's no need to rush this.
My thing is inside Sister's thing!
lt's so soft!
Sister has great tongue techniques!
She's sucking it well!
lt's a gift from God!
ls this suppose to be an offering?
Oh, you were looking.
Yeah, it's your freedom with what you want to do...
But if this becomes public, we
won't be able to stay here.
Then...
You hold me.
Come.
Fuck!
W, what?
Stop, please stop, not here!
...That's!!
So tight, l've never experienced...
lt's a trial from God, hold it in!
Good...now for the next trial.
Can't...no more!
You still don't believe in me!
Promise in front of God.
Or else, l'll keep you here with your
shit until the morning's sermon!
Say that you will be my obedient slave.
l will...as of today...
Will disobey God and become an anal slave!
That was well said.
This is...your reward!
This is a reward you have never received!
l will piss inside your ass!
lt's warm!
A lot, it's a lot!!
Don't pull out, it's coming out, out, no!!!!