Sensei touched Sakura-chan here...
If anybody else touched me down here, I'd...
Just by imagining that, I...
Life Guidance!!
— Shino • Mikan • Ren —
No matter what happens, I'll believe in you!
Okay, sensei?
The school is now...
Closing.
What's the matter?
You need to speak up!
A-All students still on school premises...
Please leave immediately...
This isn't practice if you're gonna be like that.
It looks like you need more guidance, Shino.
T-The school is...
A-All students...
Please!
I'm cumming!
Women's Bathroom
P-Please leave immediately...
Ever since I saw Sakura-chan and sensei doing that, I...
My body's been feeling really hot.
It scares me, but I can't help but...
Mikan? Mikan?!
Wake up!
S-Sensei?!
What's the matter?
Are you okay?
Um, I...
I tried calling out to you but you didn't
answer and the door was still locked.
I was really worried!
I-I'm sorry!
I'll go home now!
Wait a minute!
I knew it.
You were hiding because you were doing
something naughty, weren't you?
No... I wasn't! I really wasn't!
You shouldn't lie.
Look at how wet you are.
What's the matter? Huh?
Did she really just cum from that?
Color me surprised. I've never seen
a student this sensitive before.
Oh, geez, look at the mess you made.
I'm worried about your future, Mikan.
If this keeps up, it's only a matter
of time before your mind is ruined.
My mind?
Yeah, your mind went blank, didn't it?
In that instant, millions of neurons died.
M-Millions?!
But with the right training,
you'll be able to avoid becoming an invalid.
S-Sensei, what kind of training?
You want me to show you?
Se-Sensei, it's happening again! My mind's going blank!
Hold it in.
Try suppressing that feeling
like you're holding back your pee.
I-I can't!
Are you even trying? Do you want to become stupid?
Didn't think so.
If you don't want that to happen, then listen to what I say.
S-Sensei, what are you... No!
I'm trying to arouse you with my fingers.
This is to get you aroused quicker.
It feels weird there! My head is going crazy!
She's tight down there, it's like she's sucking
my thumb! I can't get enough!
Just like that, Mikan. You got it?
You gotta stay strong even if it hurts, okay?
N-No! No!
I told you to be strong, didn't I?
It doesn't hurt! Deep in my stomach...
it's starting to feel weird!
My head's feeling tingly!
My mind's going blank again! It's going blank!
Not yet.
But...
If you keep cumming like that,
there's no point to this training, right?
Or perhaps you're willing to live
the rest of your life as an invalid?
No!
Sensei, stop!
Stop!
My stomach's... my stomach is...
You need to hold out a little longer.
Don't cum yet!
No! I can't! I can't hold on any longer!
I already feel like my mind's emptying!
Okay, you can cum now!
I'm cumming!
I'll be back to train with you again.
Ren, the headache medicine worked pretty well, right?
So well that it made your headache
and consciousness disappear.
I've...
been waiting all this time for this.
You know, I don't really want to do this either.
But, Ren, this is on you.
You kept saying that you're scared of men
and because of that, I never had an opening.
This is fucking great!
Don't worry. There's nothing to be afraid of, Ren.
I promise I won't hurt you. After all, I love you so much.
What a beautiful color!
This is better than I've ever imagined!
This hole's so small. If I just shove my dick in, it might rip.
This might be a waste, but I might need to widen it a bit.
First up is...
Here I go!
It went in!
How's that?
It should be okay if it's widened out this much, right?
Now we can finally become one.
You woke up at the perfect time!
I'm going to deflower you with my dick now, Ren!
No! Sensei! No! Don't!
Save me!
Hey now, don't get the wrong idea.
I'm just here to help.
I want to help you overcome your fear of men.
Your pussy's swallowing my dick whole.
This is great, Ren.
How is it? It feels great, doesn't it? I feel great too!
Ren, your love juices are flowing around
my dick and making incredible noises!
Tell me how it feels! Don't be shy!
Does my dick feel good?
No!
Come on, tell me.
Ren, you really have a good hole here!
Does it really feel that good? Huh?!
It feels so hot inside me!
My head's starting to feel weird!
No!
I'm...
I'm still cumming!
And this is why I can't stop "guiding" students!
That's not guidance!
Y-You girls!
Ren-san!
What's going on?
You're the worst!
Sensei!
You did this to everyone?
Th-There’s a perfectly good explanation for this.
Let's hear it then.
Just what good explanation is there?
H-Headmistress?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч