G-Good morning.
Well, umm...
I was surprised by your message yesterday.
I never thought that you felt that way about me, Uno-kun.
It would have been okay a few years back.
But now we're in different classes,
my legs are a bit plump, and I'm a little overweight.
Also, I still don't have plans to...
Azusa, good morning.
Good morning Saori.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Let's go.
Hey listen to me, yesterday Eto-kun just...
Oh yeah, did something happen between
you and that pretty boy in class 2?
You mean, Uno-kun?
Did he confess to you?
Y-Yeah.
I knew it.
Then your days of masturbating are over.
There you go again.
I'm not telling you anything then.
Sex feels good, you know.
But that depends on the cock though.
You always say that.
How about you, Saori?
Going well with Eto-kun?
I'm thinking of breaking up with him.
That basketball-maniac cums too quickly,
and it's always S&M play with him, so it's a bit of a drag.
Cums quickly? Just how fast?
Shorter than you'd ever imagine.
R-Really?
Then how fast is it normally!
How fast can a guy normally cum?
And what does it mean when they say
it's painful when a guy has it built up?
Hm? What did you say?
Well, I just read a small book recently and...
What a poor plump girl you are.
Oh yeah, speaking of class 2,
there's one creepy guy there, right?
He's called Shimoda or something.
He's been watching you quite intensely.
You should get fat cocks from anyone
but except those kinds of guys.
Why don't you just give Uno-kun a go?
You think so?
I'll be waiting at the regular spot.
Sensei, my tummy hurts, can l go to the infirmary?
It hurts again because it has built up?
The tip is sticky.
Hey, does every guy really have this clear sticky thing?
Really?
I'll start now then.
It tastes really weird.
I don't really know how to do this.
Well?
Like this?
Deeper?
You think my face looks weird?
Every girl will if they're trying to suck on this thing.
How about this?
Does this feel good?
The smell is getting into me.
And it's really bitter.
Is this okay?
This?
Faster?
Should I do it faster?
Is it okay?
Should I do it?
Okay.
About to cum?
It's okay to release if you want.
It's coming out.
Is it over?
So it was really built up inside.
Look.
This is yours.
I'm going to swallow it now.
You took pictures of it again.
I'm going to clean it up, Shimoda-kun.
Are you still upset about Uno-kun's message?
I already turned him down so cheer up.
Was it unsettling ithat we were childhood friends?
But, I only do this to you.
What?
I'm still not ready to have sex yet.
It squeezes tight perfectly, and looks sexy.
Pervert.
You're not changing Saori?
It's "that day", so I'm just gonna watch.
Liar.
That was last week, right?
Asuza, did you just eat squid?
Nope.
It stinks like squid around here.
I wonder where it's coming from.
It stings.
Saori?
Eto-kun?
Stop them!
This is terrible, Eto-kun.
Please, let's break up already.
I'm not going to tell this to anyone.
What should I do? What should I do?
Saori is in trouble.
Don't rub your cock on me.
Hey, stop this.
I don't want to...
It's inside.
His cock is inside me.
This thick thing is inside me.
What's this?
It's different.
Totally different from Eto-kun's.
Oh wow.
If's thick.
I don't want it inside. Please.
Don't cum inside me.
He's cumming.
Cumming inside me.
She go ejaculated inside.
That's totally not okay.
No, stop.
Don't enter so deep in me.
It's deep.
It's drilling me.
It's piercing inside.
No!
I'm starting to feel weird.
I'm going to feel weird.
Cumming?
Are you going to cum inside me too?
Something hot is getting released inside.
And your thing is twitching.
Saori's pussy is dripping with semen.
Eto-kun is next?
Oh, he's inside already.
Wow.
Amazing Eto-kun.
You were usually the first to cum.
Feeling sore that I'm getting horny with them?
Okay then, just keep it up.
You can do it if you want to.
Do it more.
Thrust it in me!
Are you about to cum?
Can't hold it in anymore?
It's okay.
Cum inside me.
Fill it all up!
Wow....
Your tadpoles are bouncing and swimming inside me.
I just can't do that!
My insides would probably break.
Saori, you were absent from P.E. earlier.
Yeah, something came up.
Hey,
I've decided to stay with Eto-kun.
I see.
That's good for you.
Umm, you see,
I already told you this before.
I'm busy at the moment.
I won't be able to answer all of your messages.
It's homeroom already so I got to go.
How's this Shimoda-kun?
Hey, you at it again?
I'm trying lots of different variations because
you don't seem to enjoy it anymore.
Cumming now?
Okay.
Cum.
Huh?
Why did it go limp?
I'm about to cry.
Shimoda-kun, you jerk.
I wonder if he's sick of my blowjobs already.
So guys really want sex, huh?
But that large cock just won't fit.
It's Shimoda-kun.
Who is that girl?
That's terrible.
That's just terrible, Shimoda-kun.
He never tried to pat my head like that, no
matter how hard I tried with my blowjobs!
Azusa?
She seems to be in a bad mood.
About to be in her period?
Hey, there's no one here, wanna do it?
He's the worst.
What's he getting all lovey dovey like that for?
I went out with him because that was the
first time someone confessed to me.
He always told me to clean his thing up
so I always took his white stuff into me.
And it was even hard for me to hide that stinky-squid smell!
Geez, geez, geez!
No, that does it!
Do you have time today?
I can go to your place if you want to.
Blockhead!
I mean I'm going to have sex with you!
Geez, Shimoda-kun you pervert.
You just got a hard-on-too quickly.
Hey, kiss me.
This is embarrassing.
His cock has really gotten stiff and hard.
The tip is getting wet already.
You're ogling too much.
Looks fat, right?
Sorry about this.
Your eyes look scary.
And the wet tip is hitting me.
I'll drink your spit so here.
I need to open wide?
But it's still bright.
Your face Is too near.
Does it look gross?
Creeped out by it?
Does it smell weird?
That's cold.
Oh no, I'm moaning.
I'm sorry.
You just tasted it.
Not there.
I don't want it there!
Don't suck it!
Your tongue is inside.
It's inside.
Don't open it wide.
It's too embarrassing!
Don't look there!
No, please don't!
It's really dirty there so don't!
Please stop it already!
Why won't you listen to me?
Put it in.
Just insert it in already!
Can you tell where it is?
Should I widen my legs more?
Umm, won't you use a condom?
You want it raw for our first time.
You really won't use it?
Condom would spoil the fun?
Because it's boning?
Cum outside, okay?
Don't cum inside, okay?
I think it's a bit further down.
It's big.
Your cock is big.
It's big, it's big.
It's big.
No, I can't take it in.
Be more gentle.
It's still pushing in?
It's not totally inside yet?
It's stiff.
No, no, no!
I don't want this if you do it like that.
What's this?
I can't take this anymore.
I'm going to break.
I'm going to break there.
I don't care about this cock anymore.
I don't want this cock.
No...
Something's weird.
Are you cumming?
Do you want to cum?
You can't.
You can't cum inside.
You really want to?
You absolutely want to cum inside?
Do you really have to?
I love you.
You came already?
It's coming out already, right?
I'll feel a bit anxious if you pull it out immediately.
Stop, I can't continue anymore.
I don't know what's happening there anymore.
Don't insert it anymore.
Don't take pictures of it!
Onii-chan, mom's going to be home soon.
This is amazing, Shimoda-kun.
If you keep doing it I'll start to moan.
No...
But I want you to continue.
Yes, there.
You cock feels good.
Are you cumming?
Are you going to cum inside again?
Are you recording a video?
You can't do that!
You can't take any pictures or video today!
I said I'll only do a blowjob.
Oh wow, It's different from the usual.
No one else will be home?
Then I'll stay for the night.
Dad won't get mad if I say that I'm staying at Saori's house.
Let's see how many times we can do it and make a new record!
You've been ignoring me lately.
And you're trying to hide it by using those weird toys.
You're doing it alone again, aren't you?
I already said that you can't do that, you know.
If you want to cum, cum inside me.
Just look at how I'm left out.
Onii-chan.
So you're interested in that.
There's a guy named Uno-san in your class, right?
Earlier, he... No, nevermind.
Azusa, have your boobs got bigger?
Doing it a lot with Shimoda-Kun lately?
Don't say it.
It's ok to have sex often,
but I feel left out.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel lonely?
I already broke up with Eto-kun.
Huh?
He's such a dickhead.
I'm tired of guys already.
Hey Saori, does it feel good to do it with another girl?
Wanna try it once?
I'll try my best.
Stop rubbing your teeth in me.
Sorry, I just finished adjusting it.
Oh no...!
I think I don't want it recorded after all!
Don't show it to anyone else, okay?
Promise me, okay?
It's big.
Your cock is just too big, senpai!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming.....!!!!!