It's alright!
Onee-chan will make you
come as much as you want!
Onee-chan!
Oh, that's fantastic!
Come on, come on! Does my handjob...
Co
Come
Come on,
Come on, co
Come on, come
Come on, come on!
Come on, come on! Do
Come on, come on! Does
Come on, come on! Does my
Come on, come on! Does my hand
Come on, come on! Does my handjob
...feel good?
Come on, come on! Does my handjob f
Come on, come on! Does my handjob fee
Come on, come on! Does my handjob feel
Come on, come on! Does my handjob feel go
Come on, come on! Does my handjob feel good
Come on, come on! Does my handjob feel good?
Onee-chan, I'm already...
...coming—!
Stupid brother!
BWAAARG!
What are you doing, you perv!
A-Ayaka?!
Chiaki and Fuyuno are here as well?!
I found them.
These are my panties.
Ah, shoot...
Mine are here as well...
They're drenched with Shuntarou's semen.
I can't wear them anymore.
Those are... Well...
Y-You...
Oh my... This is but a display of affection
towards my younger sisters, so forgive...
Don't ever touch our panties again!
It smells like squid.
Dum-dum!
I am hated by my younger sisters.
Well, It's kind of my fault since
I used them as fap materials.
However, it's no exaggeration that they loathe me.
They always talk down to me,
and they go on mistreating me.
That is why I yearn for a kind older sister.
So, I'm gonna play adult games for today as well!
Older Sister Week-long Experience
New Game
Continue
Options
Huh, what's this?
Older Sister Week-long Experience?
Have I ever installed something like this?
Huh? It's not starting at all...
What the hell is this? What's going on?!
What a bad day...
I'll just hit the sack.
Seikatsu Shuukan
A Week-long of Daily Sex Life
Wh-Whoa—!
Wh
Wh-Wh
Wh-Wh-Wh
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What's with this?!
Hey there, stupid brother!
You're being loud in the morning!
At least let us eat breakfast in peace.
You're noisy as hell...
Huh?
Th-This is...
You see...
Y
Y-Y
Y-Y-You...
Y-Y-You... You
Y-Y-You... You... Y
Y-Y-You... You... Y-You...
A-Aya-chan?
Y-You're so cute!
Oh, that's right.
Aya-chan, you're a huge shotacon. Am I right?
My body turned back to a child!
What on earth just happened here?
Hey there...
What is your name?
M-My name?
I have to handle this smoothly
or I'll suffer the consequence!
Shun...
No, it's Koharu.
I'm Shuntarou-san's online friend.
He invited me to stay over
for the Golden Week holiday.
Oh...
Then, where is he now?
H-He seems to be away
for some urgent business!
Well, who cares about my stupid brother?
Koharu-kun, let's eat breakfast together instead!
Huh, but...
It's decided, then!
Th-Thank you for the meal!
I don't know why I turned back into a child,
but it's not the time to be doing this...
Anyway, I need to find a way to turn myself back...
Umm, I should be going now...
Hmm?
Koha-kun, want to have some pudding as well?
Huh?
It's yummy!
Ah...
Fuyuno is giving me some of her
favorite pudding? Moreover...
Her breast is peeking out!
W-Well, maybe being a child isn't that bad at all...
Ah...
Whoa! Koharu-kun, watch out!
O-O-Ouch...
This is bad! Now I'm gonna get
beaten up until I'm half-dead!
A-Aya-chan, are you alright?
I-I'm alright.
Sorry, Fuyuno, but can you fill in the bathtub for us?
I'll be taking a bath with Koharu-kun!
Huh?
Huh?!
I even got some of it on my hair...
You got pretty drenched as well, huh?
Here, face this way so that I can wash you.
Doing this makes me feel like
I got myself a younger brother!
A-Ayaka-san!
That's not right!
Properly call me "onee-chan"!
O-Onee-chan...
Whoa... My little sister's stark naked
body is right in front of my eyes!
Then, I'll wash your body next.
Huh?
Huh?!
I always wanted a little brother,
so this feels so new to me!
Umm, I can wash my own body...
Nope! I have to wash you properly!
Listen to what your sister says!
This is bad, my body is starting to react...
Then, your front's next...
This is... Umm...
W-Wait!
I see...
You're a boy, after all.
So, you got aroused because of me.
Whenever this happens,
we'll have to make it squirt once to settle it down.
B-But...
It will be alright.
It's also my first time doing this,
but I can't just leave my little brother in trouble.
She's the same Ayaka who hates me so much.
And now, she's rubbing my cock...
Koharu-kun, I wonder if you'll be
able to ejaculate properly...
This tickles!
Come on, make it squirt!
Your dick turned so red and it keeps on twitching!
It looks kinda cute!
Does it feel good?
It feels so heavenly!
Even though there's a lot
of slippery stuff oozing out,
I wonder if this will be enough
to make you ejaculate...
No, I'm already on the verge of coming!
That's right. If I'll suck it out...
O-Onee-chan!
Does this feel good, Koharu-kun?
Are you about to squirt?
This is my little sister's...
Ayaka's mouth-pussy!
Wow, you came this much...
Was that refreshing?
Yeah...
Good, good!
You managed to ejaculate properly, huh?
Good job, Koharu-kun!
She's being so nice to me. Am I like,
on heaven or something?
If that's the case...
W-Wait, that's my...
Onee-chan, I love you!
I love you, I love you! I love you so much!
G-Gosh...
So, you love me that much...
It can't be helped, then...
Just a bit...
It's gonna be just for a bit...
Koharu-kun, can you see it?
This pushing through sensation...
It's inside my crotch...
That's where your dick is going in, Koharu!
Aya-chan!
How's the bathwater?
Huh? L-Let's see...
It feels kind of tingly inside!
Oh, I added some stimulating
bathwater additive there.
S-She's right...
I'm starting to get used to this... It feels hot...
It feels so good!
Ayaka's bare pussy is gripping my slippery cock!
It feels crazy good!
This feels...
...incredible!
I might end up getting hooked on this!
I see... That's good to hear.
Damn... She's so sexy...
I can't hold myself back anymore!
I want to have my way on her as well!
Koharu-kun, you're teasing my nipples...
Oh, can I have that pudding in the fridge?
O-Okay!
Eat them just as you like!
If you like them that much,
eat them even a lot more!
Thanks!
Take your time and enjoy it inside there.
I'm taking my time and enjoying it inside!
That's it. It feels good, Koharu-kun!
Use my pussy even more,
up to my deepest parts!
Her insides are coiling around my cock!
They're squeezing me dry! I'm already at my limit!
I'm coming! Even though this is my first time...
Your shota cock is about to make me come!
I'll give my little sister a creampie
as she presses me down!
I'm coming!
H-Hey!
That's bad, Koharu-kun...
You shouldn't come inside me...
Onee-chan, I wanna do it more!
Whoa! W-Wait...
Don't! Don't do that!
I'm coming!
I'm coming already!
I can't believe this! I really am
having sex with my little sister!
Don't tease my pussy!
K-Koharu-kun, you're a naughty boy!
Koharu-kun, Koharu-kun!
Not a chance ever will the adult me
be able to do this with my little sister!
And now here I am, with her
who scorned me up until now...
I'm banging her like a monkey!
No way... Don't do that!
Koharu-kun, Koharu-kun!
She's so cute!
This feels so good!
Right there, your thing is
reaching deep inside me!
Onee-chan, can I shoot it out again?
Is it about to come out?
Is it going to squirt even more?
Is your shota cock gonna ejaculate?
I-It's okay, shoot it out!
Shoot it all out—!
Wow...
There's so much spilling out...
Being a little brother is so nice!
After that, I stayed home for Golden Week and...
O-Onee-chan... I'm already...
Yeah, it's okay.
Huh, doesn't it kind of smell funny in here?
Y-You think so?
To keep our sisters in the dark, Ayaka took care of me
by herself as she smothered me with attention.
M-More...
Then, come here.
It's alright. Until your cock is satisfied...
...I will take care of it for you!
O-Onee-chan, I'm already...
Yes, you can shoot all of it
inside me right now.
More! That's amazing!
Koharu-kun, your cock is amazing!
This little sister of mine who
actually hates me so much
that I couldn't lay even a finger on,
got creampied by me over and over!
Come, shoot it all!
Fill the pussy of this big sister of yours!
A-hah! It's still hard!
I will use my breast to make it squirt
and lull you to sleep, alright?
Okay!
I'm being pampered this much,
all thanks to me becoming her little brother!
I knew it, older sisters are the best!
School day?
That's right. Chiaki and I both
have to attend school today.
That's why I won't be back until evening.
Aya-nee, taking care of Koharu-kun
is fine but we'll be late.
I-I know!
Huh? What's up?
Is Chiaki glaring at me?
What...
But I can't just leave
Koharu-kun by himself...
It's alright, I don't have school today.
Looking after him is no big deal for me.
Oh... I-Is that so?
Then, I'll leave Koharu-kun to you.
Okay, bring home some pudding for me!
Yeah, yeah.
Chiaki, were you up late on
your computer again?
You should get proper sleep, okay?
Okay, I'll be more careful.
Among the three sisters of mine,
Fuyuno by far hates me the most.
She puts up a cute front, but she is so selfish and mean.
And now that we'll be alone at home,
I can already guess what things
I'll end up hearing from her!
Shuntarou, seriously... You really are useless!
Koha-kun!
Y-Yes?
For today...
Let's play a lot together, okay?
Huh?
You see, I've been looking forward
to us playing together!
Umm, then what should we play?
What, you ask?
Isn't it already obvious?
It's that same game you're playing with Aya-chan.
Let's do it!
Don't tell me you saw...
Your thing is rubbing against mine!
Come on. You strip as well, Koha-kun.
H-How did we end up with this?
Should I tell you a secret of mine?
I'd get a strong urge from time to time.
That's why at school, I sometimes gather up the boys...
And then, we play the climax game.
C-Climax game?
Yes, the climax game.
I suck all of the boys' cocks...
I shove them into my pussy...
The one who makes the other come wins.
Their cocks are as hard as nails,
lewd, and agitated from impatience...
I use my lewd pussy, mouth-pussy, and hand-pussies
to make them twitch lots and lots...
I defeat them by ejaculation.
Playing with cocks feels so good,
and it feels so refreshing!
Aya-chan should've been taking care of you
for the holiday, but you two
were doing that here at home.
I tried to suppress my urge by playing with my own pussy yesterday.
So, that's why...
...you'll have to play the climax game
with me today, alright?
This girl... She's way beyond impish,
she's a demoness herself!
The one who comes loses, so try to endure it.
Wh-What's up with this mess of a situation?
The same mouth that usually abuses me verbally...
It's delectably slurping my cock so much right now!
Moreover, she's so used to handling cocks
that she became too good at this!
Hey, come on!
Hurry up and start doing me better
before I make you come!
I never lost at this game yet!
This damn bitch! If that's the case...
Here, here you go!
I will never lose!
My little sister's love juice tastes so good!
Come!
Come already!
That's one win for me.
Onee-chan, you just came. Am I right?
N-No, I didn't!
I just twitched a little.
Jeez... Little brothers should just listen
to what their older sisters say!
This cock of a cheeky little brother like you
will be wrung out dry
by me, your older sister.
So damn good!
My pussy is so thrilled to have
its first cock in a while!
Somehow, It feels to me...
...that your cock is really huge!
It's practically an adult's cock in the first place!
My nipple... I love it on my nipples!
Oh no! This is crazy...
This is crazy...
This is crazy!
I love how you're scraping my insides!
Something huge is coming!
My little sister in heat is pressing
me down and fucking me raw!
Her pussy is squeezing me so tightly!
She's so sexy, lovely, and she feels so good!
Oh, Fuyuno...
You're so cute!
Hey! W-Wait...
I-I'm sensitive right there!
It's sensitive! It is! It is!
Don't!
No...
Koha-kun, your stuff is flooding into me!
What? What's this?
I'm coming again!
Onee-chan, if you can play with cocks...
I can also play as I wish, right?
Wait, wait...
The game is now over, It's a draw...
Aren't you the one who invited me?
I want to keep pounding you more!
Jeez! Stop pounding me while
you're still coming inside!
As an older brother of this bitchy little sister,
I'll make sure to reprimand her by impregnation!
No more! It's my loss!
I'm fine with losing!
Your cock has already defeated me!
Inside your pussy!
Don't come inside of me any more than that!
No...
No, don't!
Onee-chan, I'm coming again!
Coming, coming, I'm coming!
I'm coming already! I'm coming already!
I'm gonna come again!
Koha-kun, Koha-kun!
I'm coming!
Your lewd juices keep on overflowing!
No, no, no!
You're reaching deep inside me!
Koha-kun, your cock is
reaching my deepest parts!
If you keep doing that, I'll end up...
...coming again!
I never knew such a cock exists!
I never knew that a cock can come so much!
Onee-chan, I want to keep going on!
No more! I really can't take any more of this!
Let me off already!
Koha-kun, you're way too incredible!
This is so crazy...
I'm pretty sure that my pussy is now
beaten into a sloppy mess...
Now I can't think of anything
besides your cock, Koha-kun!
Take responsibility for this, alright?
What...
What happened here—?!
Fuyuno!
What the hell have you done to Koharu-kun?!
We got so engrossed and overdid it.
Aya-chan, you're also banging him a lot yesterday.
It should be fine for me to have some.
What... Were you watching us...
Aya-nee... You were banging him a lot?
No, that was just... You see...
You shouldn't monopolize him, Aya-chan!
Koha-kun promised to play with
me throughout the whole day.
What...
He'll be sleeping on my bed tonight.
Koha-kun, we'll have all of your semen today
ejaculated into my pussy, okay?
Hey! You can't come in my mouth.
Haven't you heard me?
Make sure to pour it in my pussy!
Fuyuno...
You dumbass!
Onii-chan!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization