Sensei has...
done something to Sakura with this part.
Whenever this sensitive part of mine gets touched,
I...
I'm just fantasizing about it and yet.
No matter what happens,
I'll always believe that you're doing it for me.
Okay, sensei?
Just a few minutes before school ends
school dismissal hours.
What's wrong?
Engage you diaphragm to let out a louder voice.
S-Students still remaining on campus,
should immediately leave the grounds and head home.
We can't practice your oratory skills
properly that way, you know.
Looks like you still need some more guidance, Shino.
No way, please.
That's.
Kindly inform...
all those who are...
still within the campus grounds...
I'm cumming!
...to go home as soon as possible.
Ever since seeing Sakura-chan and sensei do that,
my nethers are constantly warming up.
I'm scared,
but I just can't.
Mikan. Mikan!
Wake up!
Se-Sensei?!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Umm... well, I...
I called out after you ran away, but you never responded.
I was worried, you know.
I-I'm so sorry!
I'll go home now.
Just wait a moment.
As I thought.
You were hiding while doing bad things like this, right?
N-No, I wasn't.
I'm not doing anything!
It's bad to lie, you know.
You're already very wet.
What's wrong? Eh?
She already came just like that?
This is surprising.
This is the first time I've ever met a student this sensitive.
Ah, what a mess.
Mikan, I'm worried about your future.
If this continues, it'll only be a matter of time
before you become a complete dunce.
A dunce?
Yup. Your head becomes all fuzzy when you do this, right?
A few million brain cells die during such moments.
A few million?
However, if I train you properly to
achieve a specific stimulation,
you won't become a vegetable.
Se-Sensei.
How should I deal with that?
Do you want me to teach you?
Sensei, no.
My head's going fuzzy again.
Endure it.
Try to hold it in as if you're holding your pee.
I really can't do it!
That's disappointing, you know.
Do you really want to become an idiot?
Right?
Then pay close attention.
Sensei... what are you?
I'm touching the rear as well,
in order to achieve that stimulation.
I-It feels weird down there.
My mind feels all messed up.
It's tightly clamping down on me as if it's trying to suck me in.
Man, I'm loving this!
That's good, Mikan.
Just keep that up.
You'll have to endure this, even if it hurts a bit.
I told you to endure it.
That's not it.
My depths are.
It feels all weird down there!
I'm feeling all tingly inside.
It's getting fuzzy.
It's getting fuzzy again.
Not yet.
But...
If you keep cumming like that,
our trainmg will be for naught.
Or maybe you want your brain cells to keep
dying until you become a vegetable?
Sensei, please stop it.
Stop it.
My insides... my insides are!
Endure it a bit more.
No cumming!
O-Okay.
Oh no...
I can't hold it back anymore.
I'm really going to become an idiot.
Alright, you can cum now.
I'm going to cum!
I'll provide guidance again... soon.
See? The headache medicine worked pretty well, right?
Made her lose consciousness, though.
I've always.
I've always yearned for this moment.
I really don't want to do this, you know.
But Ren,
this is all your fault.
Saying that you're afraid of men,
never giving me the right opening.
I can't get enough of this!
Don't worry.
This won't be scary at all, Ren.
I'll never hurt you,
because I just love you so much.
Such a lovely color.
It completely exceeds my expectations.
It's so small, that it might rip apart if I suddenly fuck her.
It's such a waste,
but why don't we plug it up with something else?
First.
Here we go.
It went in.
How is it?
Is it okay to open it this wide?
We can finally become one with this, right?
You woke up at just the right moment.
I'm about to make you fully bloom with my semen.
No... sensei.
No, stop.
Somebody, help!
Now, now,
don't misunderstand this.
This is a form of shock therapy.
I just wanted you to recover from your fear of men.
It's sucking my thing deep inside.
This is amazing, Ren.
Well? Our body heat is really something, don't you think?
It's the best for me.
Your love juices,
they're coating my entire dick, emitting sloppy noises.
Hey,
don't just remain silent, say something.
Say that my dick feels awesome.
No!
Come on, say it!
Ren, your hole is truly an amazing thing.
It really feels that good, eh?
My insides... my insides feel hot!
It's making me lose it!
Stop.
I'm at my!
It's still coming out.
This is why I can never stop providing guidance.
Guidance, my butt!
What? You all!
Ren-san.
What's the meaning of this?
You're the worst.
Sensei.
So you're doing this to everyone too.
I-I can actually provide a proper explanation.
Let us hear it, then.
The "proper explanation" you're speaking about.
V-Vice principal?!