My name is Shuntarou.
One day, when I opened my eyes...
For some reason, I turned into a cute little boy!
This caused my relationship with my little sisters
who totally hated me to take a sudden turn.
The closet shotacon Ayaka
and the stylish loli slut Fuyuno
both didn't recognize that it was me.
They kept on doting on me
from morning until night!
How did things even turn out this way?
Koha-kun, breakfast is ready!
Okay!
Well, there's no use worrying about it.
I'm gonna fully enjoy having sex
with my little sisters for now.
Seikatsu Shuukan
A Week-long of Daily Sex Life
Does my hand feel that good?
My hands feel better, right?
Wow, he won't stop ejaculating!
There's so much semen!
We have to clean this up.
Then, I'm gonna make it
all clean using my pussy!
No way! You'll do it with me, right?
My relationship with my little sisters has changed
due to what happened two days ago.
Fuyuno, you're not allowed anywhere
near Koha-kun from now on!
Huh, why?
I only wanted to look after
Koha-kun as an older sister.
In what way?
Of course...
...by fucking him.
I've been saying that you can't do that!
I promised to personally take care of him!
Moreover, Koha-kun likes
his older sister being big.
Yeah...
I like them big!
Oh—?
If that's the case...
Take a look, Koha-kun...
Don't you want to give this tiny pussy
of your tiny older sister another creampie?
Stop talking nonsense!
Koha-kun likes me better.
I also like them tiny!
Whoa!
I'll be able to better satisfy Koha-kun!
You don't have to bother yourself!
Then, the one who'll better satisfy Koha-kun
will become his older sister.
Bring it on...
...you slutty little sister of mine!
Both of them got more intense at
taking care of me to outdo each other.
Let me drink plenty of your semen, okay?
Isn't this lewd scent making you horny?
Shall we have our third round just like this?
You had sex with Fuyuno again, hadn't you?!
I'm sorry!
It's morning already.
Fuck me with your morning wood!
It's not about deciding who's more
worthy to be my older sister anymore.
They became engrossed with
their little brother's semen instead.
Ah, I'm coming!
Koha-kun, are you listening?
Don't shoot out everything you have!
Toilet...
I ended up doing it with Ayaka
and Fuyuno for the whole time.
Huh?
The lights are still on at Chiaki's room.
What could she be doing this late at night?
Ch-Chia...
What?
W-Well, umm...
Maybe I can help you if you like, or something...
S-Sorry! I'm going back to my room...
Huh?
Chiaki is making a face
that I haven't seen before...
She's not resisting...
She always seemed to have
no interest in sex, though.
That's my...
No!
She's letting out sexy moans
and her wet pussy is twitching!
Her juices keep on dripping out!
P-Please... I'm already...
She came so easily.
K-Koharu-kun...
Oh...
Stop nibbling it...
Onee-chan, me too...
L-Like this?
Yeah...
Does this not hurt?
It's alright...
Her clumsy hand movement...
Her inexperienced manner...
Do it harder...
This pleasure feels new to me!
Yes, squeeze it out!
It feels so hot...
Did that feel good?
Did I seem like an older sister for you?
Huh?
Y-Yeah...
I see...
I'm glad...
She's somehow different compared
to Ayaka and Fuyuno.
She's gentle and good-hearted.
I want to do it with you, onee-chan!
Can we?
Okay.
She's so adorable!
Onee-chan!
Wow, your hole is oozing!
Wait... Don't be rough on me...
We'll wake those two up...
So let's keep it down...
O-Okay...
Keep it down and slower...
That would be...
That would be... Impossible!
Don't be rough on me!
Don't! No, you're being too intense!
Onee-chan, your insides are coiling around me!
I can't hold back!
Onee-chan!
Koharu-kun...
Just wait...
Not in front of the mirror!
You're gonna see my face!
I want to see your face in pleasure
even more, onee-chan!
No... No way!
Wait, don't!
No way, this is embarrassing!
Chiaki-oneechan, you're so cute!
I love you so much!
I love you... I love you...
I love you! I love you!
Me too!
I love you, I love you... I love you!
I'm gonna come already!
Yes, come!
Shoot it into me just like this!
I love you, Chiaki!
I love you too...
I love you... I love you... I love you!
I love you so much!
Chiaki...
I love you... I love you!
I-I love you so much...
Shuntarou...
Chiaki!
Stealing from others is not fair!
She's right, Koha-kun belongs to us...
Huh?
Eh?
Uhh...
Shuntarou?
Chiaki, we need to go.
Shuntarou... No, I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming too! Let's do it at the same time!
You let out too much, Shuntarou...
They'll find out about it in school...
Sorry, Chiaki. Your insides felt so good...
I should be going now...
I-I'll be on my way now!
Oh... How did it go?
Same as before!
Koharu-kun was Shuntarou all along...
What the hell does that even mean?!
This really is the worst thing ever!
Just remembering about it grosses me out!
What's worse, to think that Chiaki
had feelings for Shuntarou...
Seriously, I don't get what's happening anymore!
Shuntarou, you're hard again.
It's because you're so cute,
Chiaki. I couldn't help it...
That makes me happy!
Chiaki has been looking for a chance all this time.
The shy and reserved Chiaki
was unable to express her feelings
for me who's hated by her sisters.
She didn't have a choice but to act like them.
And one day, she noticed me getting
hooked on older sister games.
She thought of something like this...
"What if I make myself seem like an older sister?"
She made an app which when launched,
will hypnotize anyone who looks at the screen
Week-long
Older Sister
Experience
Week-long
Older Sister
Experience
to see someone as a little brother figure.
But due to some stroke of bad luck,
the other two girls ended up
looking at the screen before her.
Until the week-long experience ends,
Chiaki couldn't do anything but watch in dejection
as I get along with our other sisters.
Have you been masturbating
while thinking of me all this time?
Yes! It's because I was so jealous!
The truth is that I wanted you
to be doing it with me instead!
If that's so, I'll give you a creampie
to make up for all of those times!
Shuntarou, I want to have
your sperm in my pussy!
We can do this anytime from now on.
Okay... Let's do it again when I'm back.
I wonder if Chiaki will be home soon...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Shuntarou!
Chia-chan who's getting in my way is finally away.
Fuyuno?! Wh-Why?
Y-You... Don't you hate me?
That's right, I hate you so much.
However...
This one...
I love this cock...
Koha-kun's cock is the best of them all!
Alright, then... I'll help myself with this!
Hey, wait...
Yes, here it is!
This is it! This cock...
I've been longing for this cock!
So, are you fine with anyone
as long as they have nice cocks?
That's right...
Doesn't your little sister's pussy
make you feel good too?
And besides,
I'm not the only one who thinks this way.
Right, Aya-chan?
Wh-What are you talking about?!
I only came here to check how you're doing...
You're not being honest, Aya-chan.
You can't help wanting to get pounded
by Koha-kun's cock as well.
Weren't you actually envious of Chia-chan?
You crave for this cock so much that
you're dripping wet, itching for it.
A-Are you stupid?
I've never been like that...
Oh—?
Whatever.
Just watch there as Shuntarou
brings me to climax.
Don't get carried away!
You're reaching deep inside me!
I want more of that.
You can treat me like an onahole.
Whoa! J-Just wait...
Uhh...
What's this? I'm feeling good...
Huh, am I blindfolded?
Is that you, Chiaki?
Yeah...
I see...
It's nice to do it blindfolded
once in a while, huh?
Go and get me mistaken for
someone else, you idiot!
I'm only using your cock
as a tool for my masturbation!
But this taste and shape...
They're just like Koha-kun's!
Chiaki, you got better at giving heads.
I'm only licking him,
and yet my pussy is throbbing!
Chiaki...
Stop teasing me... Hurry!
Who the hell would ever
want to do it with you...
This is bad...
Doing this only makes my throbbing worse!
Even though I want to come... Why?
Aya-chan...
Huh? What...
Fuyuno?! And Chiaki too...
That's not what you really
want to do. Right, Aya-chan!
It can't be helped, so I'll lend you a hand.
Hey, stop!
Here, use Koha-kun's cock
to make onee-chan's cheeky pussy honest.
Are you sure about this?
Give her lots of love!
You're kidding me... No way! No way!
Don't put it inside!
Not with someone like Shuntarou...
Not with someone like him!
You squirted just from getting penetrated.
Y-You're wrong! I didn't come!
Something like this...
...doesn't make me feel good!
I'm not feeling anything at all!
Your love juice gushes out with each thrust.
That's so lewd!
Come on, Chia-chan. Help her out as well.
Ayaka, you look like you're feeling so good...
Having the cock you love so much
plunged into you feels good. Right, Aya-chan?
I-I don't feel anything at all!
Not with the cock of someone like Shuntarou!
Your clit seems to be swollen from delight!
Ayaka, your pussy tightens up upon climax!
I'm coming too!
Don't! I don't want it!
Not a creampie!
Yes, come!
No way!
No way! No way!
No way! No way! No way!
No way! No way! No way! No way!
Not a creampie! Don't come!
Aya-chan came from getting
her insides smeared with semen!
Alright, now it's my turn.
H-Hey!
What about your promise to get
Shuntarou back to me if I help you?
Oh, that promise?
That was
That was a
That was a lie!
What...
You can't! Shuntarou is mine!
Hey, stop pulling me!
This cock only belongs to me!
H-Hey, you two! I'm gonna fall...
Whoa!
Nope!
What?!
Hey, Aya-chan!
There's no way that I'll let you two
deal with such a nasty cock.
That is the reason why...
...I have to do something
about it as the eldest sister.
What's up with that?
You just want him all by yourself!
Shouldn't we each get
our turns at times like this?
You can't do that, Ayaka!
I'll take care of all of Shuntarou's needs!
Oh... Girls!
Here you go, Shuntarou!
Doesn't my squishy loli crack taste good?
Fuck me...
Put it in here!
You can't!
Shuntarou's cock belongs to me!
This nasty cock is so bad!
It's the worst!
Hey, you three...
You're all being rough on me...
I got stained with your semen.
This is the worst.
It's gross and it stinks. How filthy!
Shuntarou, spray more semen on me!
I love semen!
I love it so much!
Shuntarou...
Shuntarou... Shuntarou...
Jeez, hogging his cock is not allowed!
Slurp!
It's twitching and swelling up inside me!
You cheeky slutty little sister!
No, don't!
I'm coming already!
I'm gonna come now!
If you all want to do it that much...
Then, as your older brother,
I'll take care of you three
altogether using my cock!
No way! No!
I hate you!
I'm coming... I'm coming! I'm coming already!
Shuntarou! Shuntarou!
I can't take it anymore! I'm coming!
I'm coming—!
I hate you so much, Shuntarou!
Wake up already, you idiot!
How long are you gonna sleep,
you stinky brother!
It's been a month since then.
My little sisters are as unruly
towards me as they've always been.
Try to at least do your job properly!
I know!
If there's one thing that changed...
Uhh... Gosh!
We don't have that much time!
So, who are you gonna take care of for today...
...onii-chan?
I got over my fondness for older sisters,
and my younger sisters...
They became a little bit gentler towards me.
Umm... Oh no...
I dozed off on the sofa...
Whoa?!
Rise and shine, Koha-kun!
A-Ayaka?!
You shouldn't bluntly address me by name!
Isn't it supposed to be "onee-chan"?
It can't be... Did I turn into Koharu again?
Enough of that. Here you go!
H-Huh?
What's the matter?
You don't have to hold back.
Treat yourself with my tits
as much as you want!
Here you go!
You can do anything you want
with them, Koha-kun!
I-If that's the case...
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!
It's okay!
Fuck them harder just like a pussy!
Here, don't spill any of it.
I want all of it in my mouth!
It's gonna come out!
You're still hard despite coming so much.
Is that how much you want
to have sex with me?
Yeah...
Alright, since you did a good job on my tits...
I'll be milking you out a lot next.
Koha-kun, your cock is reaching deep inside me!
I-It feels good!
I want it in my pussy...
Spray lots of it inside, okay?
You're back at my tits again?
My gosh... Koha-kun, you perv!
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!
My dick is being swallowed by your pussy!
I'm gonna come in no time!
Koha-kun, do you love me?
I love you, onee-chan!
I feel the same! I love you!
I love you so much, Koha-kun!
That's why give me a lot more of it, Koha-kun!
It's coming out!
Koha-kun, your sperm is spurting out!
Wow...
There's so much...
Koha-kun, let's keep going on.
Uhh... Okay...
We had four more rounds after that.
You sure came a lot.
Who would've thought that the smartphone
in Chiaki's room has the
"Week-long Older Sister Experience"?
Koha-kun will be mine now using this.
Oh... I get it now...
Huh?
So, this can turn Shuntarou into Koha-kun
whenever and wherever you want.
Uhh... Hey, how long have you been around?
M-My smartphone!
Hey, wait! Give it back to me!
I don't wanna!
I-I'm the one who made that!
I can't come anymore...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji