I'm a teacher at the Holy Tsubomi Academy, Narashi Bouto.
Every day I'm helping my adorable
students find their path in life.
But of course, you're at the top of the list, Ai-chan.
I don't know if you believe me though.
I believe you.
I do, but you're nice to other girls too, sensei.
Yeah, but that's only because if I'm only nice to you,
everyone will know about us.
But...
Everything I do is for your sake because I love you so much.
I can do anything for your sake.
I'll put up with anything for your sake too, sensei.
I'll do anything, so when I get older, please marry me!
Of course. I promise.
Just don't tell anyone, okay?
Okay, I won't.
It'll be our secret.
It feels so good when I rub against it!
I'm starting to feel weird again!
That feels great, rub it more!
Yeah, just like that!
Sensei, I love you!
I love you so much!
Sensei...
All right, who's next on my guidance list?
Life Guidance!!
Ai / Sakura / Nana
No matter what happens, I know that it's for my sake.
– Right? Sensei!     – Right? Sensei!     – Right? Sensei!
I'm so disappointed in you, Nana.
I thought you were a little smarter than that.
I'm so sorry, sensei.
I'll try harder and become a better girl from now on.
Did I say you could talk?
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to be a good girl? Huh?
All right, Nana, let me teach you
what it means to hold back.
Wait there like that for half an hour.
If you fall over or try to run away,
expect ten times the punishment.
Sensei, please wait. I can't... wait!
Gym Storage
Isn't that enough?
Nope. Poor clothing choices are
a reflection on one's poor character.
But that doesn't mean you can...
You're only touching down there.
You're just as rebellious as always, Sakura.
Also, let me ask, why the polka dots?
You can't wear flashy underwear to school.
It's written in the student handbook.
They're just ordinary polka dot panties.
You can try and hide, but I can tell.
You're trying to show them off.
That's not true! Stupid!
Sakura-san, you shouldn't be talking
to someone older than you like that.
Are you stressed out or something?
I'm not...
If there's anything you're worrying about,
try talking to me about it.
I'm sure we can work something out.
Sensei, not there!
Hm? Could you tell me exactly what
and where I shouldn't be touching?
Sakura-chan?
Mikan-chan!
Oh, isn't it almost time for all the students to go home?
Did you need something?
Um, I just kind of forgot something.
Oh.
I was just doing a surprise inspection
on her skirt length, but...
Found it.
You look like you're fine. You can leave.
Okay then, bye.
Wait, I'm coming too...
Let go of me!
Nope. As punishment for wearing flashy panties
in order to seduce guys, I'm confiscating these!
No!
Look, your budding flower is so wet.
This is proof that it wants a man.
What are you even saying?
You're not making any sense!
During health class, you were reading
a book on sex really intensely.
You must be really curious.
If you're already this wet and sensitive,
I guess you can't deny it anymore.
Just tell me the truth.
Your pussy's already craving for it, isn't it?
No, it's not! It's not!
Stop!
Just leave it to me.
Huh?
I'll be sure to make your flower bloom.
No, don't!
It's okay, don't be afraid.
After your flower blooms, it'll all be okay.
This flower bud's pretty tight.
Let me loosen it up a bit.
I can tell that your small flower petals
are quivering in pleasure.
No!
See, doesn't it feel good?
You jerk! You jerk!
Sensei, you jerk!
Just be honest already.
It feels good, doesn't it?
I won't say it. Ever!
It doesn't feel goo...
Really? Then who's the one
moving their hips right now?
That's not... That's not me!
But... But...
No!
Don't! Don't!
Geez, you're so mean.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч