You...
...should not sprinkle the sacred water recklessly.
lf you follow the drain, the feelings will pour.
Eventually you will be on the natural path.
He's so stupid!
ln this passage here...
...it's describing the spring's...
Hey, hey, about Mr. Sakimori...
...l bet his ''thing'' is so small, don't you think?
l so know what you mean!
Hey, Mr. Sakimori.
Mr. Sakimori...
...you seem tired even though you've just started.
No, not really...
Don't you have to go advise for the club activities now?
We need you to work hard for us.
To tell you the truth, having to juggle...
...the swim club and the archaeology club is a little hard.
Ah, it's not that l don't want to do it.
What are you saying!
Because you have that kind of attitude...
...the students are not picking up on your passion!
You...
...should not sprinkle the sacred water recklessly.
lf you follow the drain, the feelings will pour.
Eventually you will be on the natural path.
Archaeology Club Meeting Room
l-l'm sorry!
Wait...
Mr. Sakimori...
What?
Please don't tell anyone...
...that l'm doing something like this.
Y-Yeah...
l won't tell anyone.
Come here...
...Mr. Sakimori.
Shinsuke Sakimori...
How is he going to be...
Huh?
You... you are...
Mr. Sakimori, you don't know your own student's name?
O-Own student?
Mr. Sakimori...
Saya is your student.
Saya?
Saya Yuuki?
You remember me now?
W-What are you...
Mr. Sakimori.
This part of you is already so big.
Mr. Sakimori...
l can't wait any longer.
Please...
W-What do you mean ''please''?
M-Miss Yuki...
Mr. Sakimori...
Mr. Sakimori!
l'm gonna come!
l-l can't hold it in anymore either.
Mr. Sakimori...
Please come with me...
l can't...
...hold it anymore!
Mr. Sakimori...
l'm...
...really happy...
No...
lt was my first time.
What?
You were a virgin?
Here it goes, Mr. Sakimori.
Huh?
lt's going to come out!
l-l can't hold it in any longer...
M-Mr. Sakimori!
l-lt's a mistake!
Mr. Sakimori! What do you think you're doing right here?
What, it's not stopping!
l'm sorry!
Mr. Sakimori!
Peeing outside at this traditional Karin Academy...
...is a disgrace!
On top of that you're naked from the waist down!
Miss Shiori?
ls this...
...the chosen one?
What?
Miss Shiori!
Are you okay?
Master...
Please...
More, more sacred water please...
Master...
lt is delicious...
After all, you are the chosen one, Master.
What?
l-l have to pee again...
Look...
My pussy...
lt's drenched.
Miss Shiori, what's going on?
Master, l want you to be like yourself...
W-What do you mean?
Please forgive me for all the rudeness l had towards you, Mr. Sakimori.
What is going on.
l should just go with what Miss Shiori is saying for now, shouldn't l?
Okay.
Stand up.
M-Miss Shiori!
Call me Shiori!
Master!
Today is a weird day.
You're late!
Huh?
Mr. Sakimori, where were you!
l went looking for you.
Today is the day you give me my personal training.
Ah, yeah, that's right, Miss Mizushima.
What is this? Again with the urge to urinate...
That's true...
So, let's start the training.
Mr. Sakimori, what was my time?
No!
What are you doing!
Mr. Sakimori?
From here on out...
...the real personal training starts.
Please forgive me, Mr. Sakimori...
No...
The effect of the sacred water isn't that good...
No!
Mr. Sakimori, what happened to you?
Ow!
Okay, l'll let go of you.
l'll add more sacred water to you.
You better feel honored.
Please...
Stop...
Stop it...
Do you know what l'm going to do?
You think it's this one here?
lt's not this one.
lt's this one!
l'll give you the sacred water right now.
l-lt's hot!
Mr. Sakimori...
l...
l... was a bad girl.
l'm sorry.
Please...
...give me yours...
Well done.
You finally became obedient.
Good, take your clothes off.
But, there's still the sense of shame you need to feel.
Let's have you beg over there.
Mr. Sakimori, please pound it into my blackened...
...pee-smelling pussy.
This is great!
Well done! Good girl. l'll give you a reward.
Mr. Sakimori...
l-l feel like l'm gonna come...
You want me to come inside you?
lf you want it say, ''Please come inside me.''
M-Mr. Sakimori...
Please... pour it... right into my pussy!
l can't believe a perv like you is a virgin.
Okay! Here it goes!