Wait, I don't think I can.
Drinking isn't.
Oh no. What should I do?
Hey, you're not even trying to get along, Miss Newcomer.
The king's orders are...
Absolute!
I was at a newcomer's party for the university tennis club.
It happened on such a short notice.
If my kind and honest girlfriend was swayed
by the worst SEX group on this earth...
Now, now, Yuu-chan.
Sour beer doesn't really have much alcohol content.
It's also quite easy to chug down.
Come on.
Th-Then...
Alright then.
I'll drink it.
I'll drink it straight.
H-Huh?
Whoa, that's good.
Wh-What's this?
My head's all muddled.
Now, on to the next!
Who will be... the king?!
Come on, pick one, too, Miu-chan.
O-Okay.
No.5 and No.6, do a Pocky game!
Them's the rules.
Then...
Such a short Pocky stick.
Well then.
It got even messier after that.
They made me drink beer so many times.
The club members did all kinds of lewd stuff to me.
I never thought the club would be like this.
I never imagined.
Alright, next is No.6 and No.8.
How about stripping down to your undies
and standing on the sofa first?
I-I can't do that.
I can't go that far.
It's okay!
Undies are essentially the same as swimsuits.
Strip down! Strip down! Strip down!
No way.
Jeez, I guess I'll relent.
Se-Senpai?
Come on, everyone, take a gander.
Hey, you need to strip, too.
B-But, I...
Look, I'm the senpai here, and I stripped first.
I-I'm sorry, senpai.
I-I got it.
I'll strip, too.
I wonder what kind of undies she's wearing?
Why?
Why did things turn out like this?
Is this, okay?
Whoa, that embarrassed expression is cute!
Good, good.
Now, you two will be doing a blowjob contest.
You're going to fight for whoever gets to make us cum first.
It's a club tradition.
No way.
We always do this whenever we play the king's game.
I can't wait any longer.
What? It's so lively already.
You've been storing up so much?
Se-Senpai's really sucking it.
Miu-chan, give me a blowjob, too, please.
Wait, please don't push that onto me.
What are you saying?
You're going to lose if you don't do it quickly.
Lose? But, I can't do something that embarrassing.
You're going to get penalized if you don't win.
Are you okay with that?
Penalized?
I think you have an idea of what might happen.
Now, let's strike while the iron's hot.
B-But, I haven't even done it once with him.
It kinda stinks, too. Do I really have to lick this?
I-I don't like it, but...
Don't blame me if you lose!
Come on!
That won't do. You have to suck and rub harder.
N-No... no!
It's all wet.
I can't breathe.
It's going deep inside.
It's getting really stiff. You're that aroused, huh?
Oh crap. I'm gonna cum if you keep that up.
It's twitching hard. I see you're about to cum already.
How cute.
No. What should I do?
If this keeps up, I'll lose.
It's being enveloped! It's clamping down real tight!
This mouth pussy's great!
I can't breathe,
but I have to endure.
It's hard, but I have to hold out.
Is Miu-chan feeling good, too?
Your eyes seems quite dazed.
That's not true!
But, my body does feel hot.
Why?
Her mouth pussy's wet, too. It's amazing!
I'm about to cum.
J-Just wait.
I'll be done for if I don't hurry!
Just cum. Let it all out whenever you want to.
Please, please cum already!
Let this end already!
Please!
This can't be.
I'm cumming!
That's too bad, Miu.
You lost.
N-No way.
P-Please stop.
I beg of you.
No can do.
You have to take the penalty.
No... I have a boyfriend.
So anything but that!
Oh? You have a boyfriend?
Then, I bet you're used to it now.
Used to it? That's not true.
So please.
You're soaking wet already.
That can't be.
Stop!
Your body doesn't seem to mind, though.
Looks like you've loosened up.
It'll hurt if you don't relax.
No, please pull it out.
Idiot. No way I'd stop doing something so pleasurable.
I'm going to properly record our slutty Miu's lovely first time.
Stop, don't!
Don't record it.
Why? I'm looking at a healthy, erotic lady over here.
The boys will surely have a blast watching you.
Stop. Cut it out. Please stop recording.
I'll save this one for the porn books.
I'll probably distribute it via pay-to-view SNS.
Stop, you definitely mustn't!
Are you an exhibitionist?
You're really wet right now.
No way. There's no way that's true!
Why don't we add an impregnation scene for that porn dip?
Stop, stop, stop. You absolutely mustn't!
This one might just be extra thick.
Don't blame me if you do end up becoming pregnant.
No.
It's squeezing me so tight!
It's not even about thickness anymore,
it's going straight to the womb.
See? None of it spilled.
Guess you're pregnant now.
Just go home and let your boyfriend cum inside, too.
He'll never notice if he does.
You've got no time to rest.
I still have to release my own thick stuff.
No, not anymore, please!
Oh? You're letting me know I should fuck your ass, eh.
I'm not!
N-No, I don't want this!
You don't need this, you know.
I can perfectly see your sullied pussy.
No, please don't look.
Come on, lift your slutty ass so we can see it more.
Your cute pussy's so clear in this shot.
This is embarrassing.
Please stop recording me.
Alright, I'm gonna go full force on this one!
It's wrapping around really good.
Your erotic pussy is the best.
Stop. Let me go already!
It's so wet.
You really are a gigantic pervert.
Somebody, please save me!
I can't think clearly anymore.
It's gotten even tighter!
Amazing.
Oh man, I'm about to cum.
Be sure to squeeze out all of mine, too!
Stop. Please don't cum inside.
I'm going to get pregnant.
Stop!
The main course's just getting started.
We're going to release all of our cum inside you, Miu.
Th-This can't be.
We're not done yet?
Now, who's next?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Masa-kun.
Alright! My score!
Do I really have to take it off?
Of course. That's the rule, you know.
I gave you a nice head start earlier,
so come on and strip already.
Okay.
Hey, that's two points for a time violation.
Huh? N-No way.
You're questioning the referee?
One more point then, for a total of three.
I-I understand.
If you don't hurry up, more points will be taken from you.
Wow. Miu-chan's really into it!
Hey, are you still not done?
Give the serve already.
Okay.
One jiggly serve, please!
Th-That kind of serve is.
That hurts.
It's going to leave a mark.
Hey, this is violence!
Strip one more time for your point deduction!
But I.
Got a problem with it?
No, I'm sorry.
If so, then strip already.
O-Okay.
Oh, sorry. That's a set already, so that means you lose, Miu.
Losing means getting a penalty.
Well then, shall we begin?
Do it like we told you.
O-Okay.
E-Everyone,
I, Miu, lost the match,
therefore I will masturbate.
Wrong!
You legs should be on the bench,
then you open your erotic pussy with
your fingers for everyone to see.
What? I-I understand.
Don't forget your lines!
E-Everyone,
please, take a gander,
at my very slutty pussy.
Wow, Miu's pussy is twitching!
Why?
How did it get to this point?
Everyone's watching me masturbate like this.
Miu-chan, could it be that your pussy's already wet?
Yes. I feel so horny as everyone continues watching me.
My pussy's so wet already.
My love juices are starting to overflow.
Well, Miu? Can you take it from here?
I-I can't!
I can't possibly cum in front of everyone.
Can't be helped, I guess.
Then we'll just have to cum till the end ourselves.
No way.
Y-You can't.
It's gushing already.
Th-That's not true!
Your insides are totally wet.
Why? They're all just forcing me to do this and yet.
It's gripping me so tightly.
My body's starting to feel horny.
Anyway, your first shot is coming soon.
What should I do?
I'm getting really horny.
I'm starting to feel pleasure being violated like this.
Wow, it really is getting tight.
I'm giving my shot as well.
No.
Hey, let me in on this, too.
Your mouth feels so soft.
I'm going to push all the way to your throat.
You're getting the hang of this, Miu-chan.
Your pussy's totally into it.
And it feels so good!
His dick is twitching, and it's getting hotter.
He'll cum inside.
I don't want it, and yet I'm about to cum.
I'm about to cum, too!
Your hot flesh is dinging to me.
No, I'm cumming!
No!
– No!
– Whoa!
– I'm cumming!
– No!
I can't keep it up anymore.
I-It's so good.
Umm, it's the club's celebration party, right?
Is it really okay for me to attend?
It's totally fine!
Anyway, why don't you have one-shot first?
Oh, okay.
It'd be more lively if Miu-chan's boyfriend joined us.
She'll definitely love it.
Sorry for the wait.
I've brought him here.
Miu!
Perfect timing.
Masa-kun, please.
Don't look.
Please don't look at my shameful self!
Stop!
How about you show him how you cum already.
Oh no, I'm cumming again.
Right in front of Masa-kun, I... no... no!
I'm cumming!
Stop... it.
Come now, you have to properly watch her horny side.
Masa-kun, this isn't what you think it is.
This isn't it.
I'm just being forced to!
Stop lying.
Your pussy's already this wet, you know.
That's not true.
You seemed to be enjoying our earlier blowjob session, too.
Please don't say that.
But, I...
I've been cummed in so many times,
that I.
That's good. Just cum as many times as you want to.
You never really came when doing it with him, right?
No, stop!
Oh? Did you get a boner from watching your erotic girlfriend?
Masa-kun, no way.
Your throat is gripping me very nicely.
Your lewd pussy's also on a roll.
Aren't you cumming soon?
Let me sync with you by cumming inside, too.
Stop, don't!
I don't want to cum.
I don't to cum in front of Masa-kun.
Impregnation, here I come!
Masa-kun... oh no, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Oh no, your love juices got stuck to my hand.
Now let me cum inside you as well.
It's deep inside me again.
I don't care what happens to me anymore.
Oh yes!
Be sure to let your boyfriend see your cumming expression.
You got this aroused from watching her fuck, huh?
All of your weird fluids are flowing out.
Oh no, Masa-kun's dick as become so big.
He's watching me as I get fucked.
Let me suck it all out for you, Mr. Boyfriend.
His thing is twitching as it gets sucked.
It's twitching hard and it's getting even bigger!
About to cum already?
Well then, why don't you cum as well?
No, please don't.
I beg of you, let me be already.
Don't fuck me so intensely!
Here it comes!
Such a waste.
Hey, you want to cum on her, too, right?
Has everyone had their fill yet?
See you then.
We'll just let you two do as you please.
Ain't that nice of us?
I'm sorry, Masa-kun.
I'm no longer.
I never thought you would call us back.
I can't hold back anymore.
It's not good enough with just the two of us.
My pussy's just craving for more.
R-Right now, I'm just the sluttiest, most perverted, bitch ever.
I beg of you.
Please punish my lewd pussy with all of your dicks.
Squirt all of your cum onto this bitch.