No, I really can't.
I really don't drink.
Oh god, what should I do?
What? C'mon, newbie, don't be such a killjoy.
The king's orders are...
...absolute!
That was our tennis circle's new member welcome party.
It didn't last very long.
If my kind and honest girlfriend was swayed
by the worst SEX group on this earth...
Alrighty then, Miu-chan,
what about this drink?
It's low on alcohol, so it should be easy to drink.
Okay?
Jun-san.
A-Alright.
I'll drink it.
I'll chug it.
H-Huh?
Oh, that was good!
Wh-What's going on? My head's all light and fluffy.
Alright, let's keep this party rolling!
Who's the king?
Come on, Miu-chan. You need to take one.
R-Right.
Numbers five and six will play the Pocky game!
Luck of the draw.
J-Jun-san.
I've never seen a Pocky stick this short.
Let's do it.
And it didn't get any better after that.
I kept getting ordered to drink more and more.
And everyone in the circle did really dirty things to me.
I had no idea that
they were a circle that did these kinds of things.
Alright next one's for six and eight.
Stand on top of the chair and strip down to your underwear.
I-I can't.
That's a little much.
It's fine, it's fine.
C'mon, it'll be like you're out on the beach wearin' a swimsuit.
Take it off! Take it off! Take it off! Take it off!
B-But...
Oh, what the heck.
S-Senpai?
Alright everyone, get a good look!
Come on, you need to strip too.
B-But, I...
Listen!
Can't you just go with the flow?
I'm older than you and I already stripped down.
I'm so sorry, senpai.
I-I'll do it. I'll strip too.
– Yeah take it off!
– What kind of underwear is she wearing?
Why... why did it come to this?
I-Is this enough?
Hot damn. I love how bashful she looks.
That's good.
Now then, how about we have the two of you
partake in a little cock-off?
You're gonna compete to see who can make us cum faster.
It's part of the rules of my circle.
N-No way!
When we play the King game, it's always like this.
Come on, I'm ready to go here!
Oh wow, it's so energetic.
What, have you really not fapped in that long?
Sh-She's really sucking on it.
Miu-chan? I need you over here.
Huh? Huh?
No, please don't push that any closer to me.
What are you saying?
If you don't hurry up and start sucking, you're gonna lose.
I'll lose?
I can't do something this embarrassing!
If you lose, you're gonna have to play a penalty game.
You want that?
P-Penalty game?
You know what's gonna happen to you if you lose, don't you?
Alrighty, let's make this a quickie.
I've never even done this to Masa-kun.
It smells awful. Do I really have to suck it?
I don't want to, but...
If you lose, it's not my problem. Come on!
That's not gonna work.
Gotta really go in there and suck it!
No! No!
It's so slimy in here!
I can't breathe. His dick is coming in so deep.
It's getting so hot. Are you really that turned on?
Shit, if you keep doing it like that, I'm gonna cum.
It's starting to twitch.
You're about to cum, aren't you?
So cute.
Oh no. At this rate, I'm gonna lose. What should I do?!
It's stuck! Oh wow, it's so tight! It feels so good!
I can't breathe.
But I need to endure.
It's hard, but I need to hang in there.
So does this mean it feels good for you too, Miu-chan?
Your eyes are showing it.
There's no way!
But why... why is my body getting so hot?
My mouth pussy over here's really wet
and feels so fucking good too.
I'm gonna cum.
Wait! I need to do something fast or else I'm gonna...
Do it.
Let it out. Cum whenever you want.
Please! Hurry up and cum!
Please end this already!
Please!
N-No!
I'm cumming!
Well that sucks, Miu.
Looks like you lost.
N-No way...
P-Please stop. I'm begging you!
I mean, you lost, so we gotta do your penalty game.
N-No! I have a boyfriend!
P-Please, anything but that!
Oh? You have a boyfriend?
I bet you guys go at it like rabbits.
We don't do it at all!
So please...
Oh wow, you're soaking wet.
There's no way I am.
Stop!
Doesn't look like your body wants me to, though.
It's a little looser now.
If you don't loosen up more, it's gonna hurt.
Please, take it out!
Don't be stupid. Why would I ever want to
stop doing something that feels so good?
I'll be sure to record you having sex for you, okay, Miu-chan?
N-No, stop! Don't!
Stop recording!
Why? You're such a cute and sexy college student.
I bet all the boys would be happy to see this.
N-No, stop. Delete it!
Please delete it!
This video is gonna be worth a lot.
Maybe I'll use it to make a little money for myself.
P-Please stop! You can't!
You're a perverted exhibitionist, aren't you?
Admit it. Look how wet you are.
Th-That's not... That's not true!
Let's add a little creampie to this video, huh?
No! No! No! You can't!
There's gonna be a lot coming your way.
Don't blame me if you get pregnant.
No!
Damn, you're gripping me hard.
I guess all of it's gonna go in your womb now.
See? The cum's not coming out.
I guess you're definitely getting pregnant.
Go home and have your boyfriend cum inside you.
At least that way he'll think it's his.
You don't got time to rest.
I still got more inside me.
No! Stop!
Oh, so you're showing me your sexy ass
because you want me to shove it in there, huh?
N-No...
Stop!
You don't need these anymore!
I can see your cute cum-filled pussy perfectly now.
No!
Don't look!
Come on, raise your ass more so
we can see your dirty pussy better!
Your cute pussy's coming in really well on video here.
No! This is so embarrassing! Stop!
Stop filming!
Alright then, let's start with a bang!
Holy shit it's tight. Your pussy is the best!
Stop! Please, let me go!
It's so slippery.
You're really quite the pervert, huh?
Somebody... Somebody, save me!
I don't know what's going on anymore!
It's getting even tighter now!
Holy shit.
Take in my thick cum too, okay?
No, stop! You can't cum inside!
I'm really gonna get pregnant!
Stop!
We're just getting started.
We're gonna fill you up with cum, Miu.
N-No... this isn't over yet?
Alright, who's next?
Masaya
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Masa-kun.
I did it! I got a point!
Do I really have to take it off?
Of course you do. Those are the rules.
I already stripped to give you a
handicap, so hurry up and take it off.
O-Okay.
Hey, that's a time violation, so two points.
H-Huh? That's not fair.
Arguing against the ref?
That's another point. Three points total.
O-Okay...
If you don't hurry up, you're gonna lose even more points!
Holy shit.
She's just rarin' to go!
You ready yet?
Hurry and serve already.
O-Okay.
Where's your sexy titty serve?
There's no such serve.
Ow. That's gonna bruise.
Isn't that a blatant act of violence?
That's another point, so take off something else.
H-Huh? That's not...
What? Got a problem?
N-No, I'm sorry.
If you get it, then take it off already!
O-Okay.
Oh, sorry, that was set point. Your loss, Miu.
Oh no. You lost, so that means it's
time for another penalty game.
Alright then, how about you get started now.
Do it just like I told you to.
O-Okay.
Hello, everyone. I... Miu lost, so I
will show you me m-masturbating.
You're doing it wrong!
Put your legs on top of the bench, spread your pussy wide
and shove your fingers deep into your pussy so we can see it!
O-Okay...
And don't forget your lines, okay?
Everyone, please look at Mius p-perverted pussy...
please take your time carefully looking at it deep inside.
Oh wow, her slutty pussy is making noises!
Why is this happening to me?
Why is everyone watching me masturbate?
Miu-chan, really? Is your pussy already this wet?
Yes. With everyone watching, I'm getting really turned on.
My pussy's already becoming an incredible wet mess.
Th-There's so much dirty juice coming out of me.
It's overflowing.
Tell me, Miu, think you can cum?
No!
Th-There's no way I could cum in front of you all.
Guess I got no choice then.
Then we're gonna help you cum.
P-Please, no!
You're already soaking wet.
Th-That's not true.
Oh wow, it's so slippery inside!
Why? I'm being forced to do this, but I...
It's getting so fucking tight.
My body's getting hotter.
Alright, I'll take point and give you the first load of the day.
What should I do?
I can feel myself getting lewder and lewder.
Them roughing me up is making me feel so good.
Holy shit, you're getting tight!
I'm gonna shoot one out too.
No! No!
Let me put mine in you too.
Your lips are so soft!
I'm gonna stick this straight down your throat!
Looks like you're getting in the mood now, huh, Miu-chan?
Your pussy's getting really good!
It feels so fucking good!
His dick is getting bigger and it's starting to twitch.
I'm gonna get filled up again!
I don't want this at all, but I feel like I'm gonna cum!
I think I'm gonna cum too!
I'm being squished so hard over here.
Oh no, I'm gonna cum!
Holy shit!
I'm cumming!
I can't anymore...
It feels so good...
Uh, this is a party for your circle, right?
Is it really okay for me to be a part of it?
Yeah, of course. No problem.
Anyway, how about a drink?
O-Oh, sure.
It'll be more fun if Miu-chan's boyfriend is there to party with us.
I'm sure she'll be happy too.
Sorry for the wait. I brought him here.
Miu!
Good timing.
Masa-kun, please don't look!
Don't look at me in this embarrassing position!
Stop it!
Show your boyfriend how you cum.
No! I'm gonna cum again!
Masa-kun's gonna see me... I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
I'm cumming!
Stop...
Come on, you gotta keep your eyes on your girlfriend.
Masa-kun, it's not what it looks like.
It really isn't!
They're forcing me to...
Stop lying. Your pussy's so wet right now.
That's not...
You really like deep throating now too, don't you?
Don't say that.
You guys just made me cum over and over again, now I...
Just go for it.
Cum as much as you want.
You haven't even had sex with that guy, right?
No! Stop!
What's this? You got really big from watching
your extremely slutty girlfriend, huh?
M-Masa-kun? No way!
Her throat's getting real tight now!
Her slutty pussy too.
Are you about to cum?
I'll cum inside you!
No! No! I don't want to cum!
I don't want to cum in front of him! No!
Here I cum!
No!
No, it's happening again! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Oh no, your pre-cum's getting all over my hand.
Let me cum inside you now.
It's going so deep!
I don't care what happens to me anymore. It feels so good!
Get a good look at Miu's face when she cums.
Your boyfriend's getting so turned on by watching you have sex.
He's getting really wet over here.
Oh my god. Masa-kun's dick is getting so big.
He's watching this really dirty scene in front of him.
Let me clean up your juices for you.
Masa-kun's dick is so hard and it's twitching so much.
Your dick's twitching and it's getting even bigger.
Are you about to cum?
Maybe he'll cum with Miu-chan then?
You're being too rough! Please stop being so rough!
He came!
What a waste.
You need to cum on your girlfriend.
Everyone feel good now?
Later.
You two can take it easy now.
Aren't we nice?
I'm sorry, Masa-kun.
I'm already...
I never thought you'd come to us first.
I can't resist anymore.
I just felt like I was so unfulfilled.
My pussy just kept getting hotter.
Oikawa Miu is a slut and the worst kind of pervert.
Please punish Miu's pussy with your dicks!
Cover the pervert, Miu, with your cum!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: ntro
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч