There's a men's room in every fertility clinic that is used to extract sperm from men. In other words, it's a masturbation room. Before entering the room, customers are handed a special cup, and they have to fill it to a certain degree by ejaculation into it. However, that amount is far greater than you might expect. Especially since many of the men who come in have performance issues. It is said that in some rare cases, a clinic will have a special nurse whose specialty is extraction of semen.
This is fiction
SEMEN ANALYSIS
Fap fap fap fap...
How long are you going to stroke it?
You don’t have any semen stored up at all.
We need about this much for our analysis.
I'll help you, to hang in there until the cup is full.
Okay, I'll have a look first, so hurry up and start.
Fap fap fap fap...
How long are you going to stroke it?
You don't have any semen storred up at all.
We need about this much for our analysis.
I'll help you, to hang in there until the cup is full.
Okay, I'll have a look first, so hurry up and start.
Hand
Job
Fella
tio
Now what should I do?
Maybe I should help you with my mouth.
Or maybe I'll help you with my hand?
Let me see when you ejaculate, okay?
Okay, here we go.
When you're about to come, press the ejaculation button, okay?
Make sure... you come a lot.
It's Good.
Okay, you're about to come.
It’s coming out... there's such a lot.
You sure came a lot.
Okay, you're about to come.
It's coming out... there's such a lot.
You sure came a lot.
Oh my, you’re rock hard.
Does this feel good?
It’s twitching.
I feel a little embarrassed.
It's twitching.
Come as much as you want.
This is great.
You sure came a lot.
Come as much as you want.
This is great.
You sure came a lot.
I don’t think this is enough yet.
Let's make sure you come some more, okay?
Maybe I'll give you some more service.
I don’t think this is enough yet.
Let's make sure you come some more, okay?
Maybe I'll give you some more service.
Tits
job
Inter
crural
sex
I wonder how your're going to ejaculate next?
You still have more sperm to give, don't you?
Do you want to ejaculate on my tits?
Do you think my tits are soft?
Does it feel good?
Don't hold back, come as much as you want.
You're about to come, aren't you?
Just keep going and ejaculate as much as you want.
Do you feel relaxed now?
You're about to come, aren't you?
Just keep going and ejaculate as much as you want.
Do you feel relaxed now?
Okay, so long as it's just my lap.
Hold on while I get in position.
Your cock is touching my thighs, it feels really warm.
Okay, so long as it's just my lap.
Hold on while I get in position.
Your cock is touching my thighs, it feels really warm.
It's twitching.
You’re about to come, aren’t you?
Just keep going and ejaculate as much as you want.
You came such a lot.
You’re about to come, aren’t you?
Just keep going and ejaculate as much as you want.
You came such a lot.
We’re almost there.
Let's both do our best, okay?
I’m starting to feel strange.
We’re almost there.
Let's both do our best, okay?
I’m starting to feel strange.
Onanie
Insert
You know we shouldn't do this.
Would you like to ejaculate your seed into my hole?
Are you about to come?
I'm going to come with you.
It's your fifth time already.
Can you still come?
Are you about to come?
I'm going to come with you.
It's your fifth time already.
Can you still come?
Woman
on top
Doggy
style
You say you don't have anything left?
Too bad, but I'm not going to let you go yet.
I want you to ejaculate one last time in this hole.
My pussy is so full.
You say you don't have anything left?
Too bad, but I'm not going to let you go yet.
I want you to ejaculate one last time in this hole.
My pussy is so full.
NEXT
I love your cock.
It's warm and feels so good...
Do you want to insert your cock into my pussy?
I want you to...
Ohhh.
This is amazing!
Do you want to insert your cock into my pussy?
I want you to...
This is amazing!
It’s so big.
NEXT
It's so rough, I’m going to come.
My pussy is going to come.
I'm coming!
You did a great job.
You made it to the finish line.
I'm going to take this to the lab.
I hope you'll come back again.