I spilled some juice on the carpet so...
Should I be worried?
Well, I'll just have to see it to tell.
Excuse me.
Uh, where's the stain at?
I can't seem to find it.
Right here.
I wonder if you can get the stain out from all this love juice.
This is...
You can't?
No, leave it to me.
It's alright if I do a special cleaning, right?
I'll let you do your job then.
All right.
You're really good.
You're spreading the stain out a lot.
All right, then let's start by getting this out of the way.
You really have an eye for cleaning.
Yeah... It's my job to clean things up.
No you don't.
Masayo-san.
Don't rush it.
Let's finish on the bed.
Masayo-san...
Young men really are better.
It's really smooth and hard.
There, right there.
Clean everything inside of me.
Now, harder...
Rougher...
Masayo-san, it feels so great inside you.
I can keep up with younger men.
So I'll show you what it feels like to really climax.
Masayo-san...
If you keep moving that way...
It'll get tighter and I'll--
You're young, so it's alright if you have to come.
Would it be easier for you this way?
I like it raw.
So...
Masayo-san...
It really is better raw...
I-I'm going to...
It's alright, go ahead and come inside.
Push your pure white soldiers inside me.
Masayo-san...
Come... Come inside me.
Young soldiers are bursting inside me.
My name is Shinji Oura.
I clean laundry part-time.
But then...
Shin-chan?
I have a few things, so could you come back?
Oh, sure.
Thanks.
Thank you, as always.
Yeah...
They all know me...
The launderer...
Shin-chan...
The Launderer
Shin-chan
Vol. 1
It's been a month since I took this job.
I'm one of the younger workers, so I'm really popular among the housewives.
But I still can't really clean that well.
I'm back from the job.
Good job.
It's hot out isn't it?
There's iced tea there, so take a rest.
Ever since I started working, I've been working with Sayaka.
Thank you very much.
After you change shirts, I'll wash that one for you.
And I'm not sure about the size, but feel free to use that shirt.
Oh, alright.
It's old, so I'm not sure if a younger guy like you will like it.
No, I'd be glad to take it.
Good to hear.
Right now, there's a huge stain in her heart because of her husband.
And I would like to clean her heart and body of that stain.
Sayaka-san...
No...
Don't, Shin-chan.
I appreciate how you feel but...
I'm still not over him.
It still feels like Yuutaro's alive.
Shin-chan...
That's not what your breasts are saying.
They're so stiff. You want it don't you?
Sayaka-san...
Forgive me, Yuutaro.
Wait...
Not there...
Do you remember how this feels?
It's not like you're doing better than what I want.
Let me touch this.
Sayaka, I...
Shin-chan...
I've been so alone, Shin-chan.
Hold me close.
I don't want to be alone anymore.
Then I'll do this for you as much as you want.
Anytime you want.
Don't let me go.
Hold me tighter, tighter.
So good.
I've wanted this for so long.
Harder, as hard as you want.
Make me forget all my pain.
Give me all that you've got.
Don't stop, Shin-chan.
Please, more, Shin-chan.
It's wonderful, Shin-chan.
Shin-chan...
Shin-chan?
Something wrong?
Oh, uh...
Does this make me look fat?
You're so funny, Shin-chan...
It looks really good on you.
Sayaka-san...
Here, can you take care of this, next?
Hey, uh...
I'm counting on you, Shin-chan.
Sayaka-san...
If I keep working with Sayaka...
I'll be too tempted.
But Sayaka's so alluring...
No, no, I couldn't do such a thing...
I should to keep my mind off her.
No, you should.
Your pants tell the truth.
Huh?
Marissa?
Marissa, this is, uh...
My goodness, Shin-chan...
Here, Shin-chan. This is your job.
Oh, my job... Right.
Marissa still doesn't know I only clean clothing...
Oh well...
How go things, Marissa?
Have you gotten used to Japan?
Moving to a foreign country must be rough for you.
Yeah, there are tons of things about Japan I don't get.
I see...
If I can help in any way, just ask.
I'm more than willing to.
Thank you, Shin-chan.
So, about what you saw in the car...
I'd like you to forget what you saw, but...
If anyone found out, then I'd--
I'm not sure about what they do in Japan...
But I definitely know about sex in Bangkok.
Wha..?
Wha--
Whaa--?
Shin-chan...
Slap me on the behind with that.
Well, even if you're smilling at me like that, Marissa...
I really don't think that in Bangkok--
Give it to me!
All right, Marissa...
Here I go.
Do it... hurry.
1... 2...
Oh... ouch.
Then, should I stop? Marissa?
It hurts, but it feels so good.
Marissa, if you keep making those noises while I hit you...
Shin-chan, if you're cock is getting so hard, then you want to do it with me, right?
Well, I, uh...
I don't mind one bit.
Let me see it.
A Japanese man's cock...
Your cock...
Marissa, I'd be glad to.
You got so hard just by hitting me.
We must really like each other.
This is really all new to me.
I really like your honesty.
Marissa...
Well? Does this feel good?
It's really good, Marissa.
Then I'll do this for you.
Marissa...
I didn't tell you to stop, Shin-chan...
Let's make each other feel good.
Marissa...
Marissa, it feels really tight, and so good inside your mouth.
Just shut up and keep hitting me!
Marissa... Marissa...
I can't take much more of this...
Marissa...
Shin-chan... Shin-chan...
Let's do that next.
It'll be really fun to use that, Shin-chan...
That, huh?
Shin-chan, hurry up!
It feels so good to be tied up...
My nipples are burning...
Marissa...
Put it on me, Shin-chan.
Anywhere! Put it anywhere!
Shin-chan...
Tease me by putting it on my clit.
Then it'll get really tight.
Marissa...
So good!
Put it in, right now!
Marissa...
Shin-chan's inside me...
I can't stop myself...
It's so deep...
This feels great, Marissa...
It's like my body is moving with you.
Shin-chan, I'm really glad that you're moving so violently inside me.
Shin-chan, do all that you can to me.
Marissa...
But, why are you doing this with me, when you have a husband?
You don't understand a woman's body.
It doesn't matter if it's with my husband or not...
a woman's body just has its needs.
It's the same in Bangkok too.
Shin-chan, your cock feels so good...
Marissa, I'm almost there...
I'm at my limit!
Go ahead, Shin-chan...
Do it with all that you've got.
Marissa...!!
Shin-chan!!!
Here you go, Shin-chan.
Thank you.
Since you're doing my laundry, I won't tell anyone that we had sex.
Well, if you would...
Shin-chan, come back soon...
A woman's body always needs a man's touch.
Shin-chan...
A woman's body always needs...
...a man's touch.
I need to get Sayaka out of my system.
Or at least, I should have...
I'm back from the job.
Huh? Sayaka-san?
Did she go out?
But leaving the place unattended wouldn't look good.
Well, she's probably using the bathroom or something.
Yeah, I'll just go through the back.
Huh?
Sayaka-san's... crying?
Then she...
She must still miss her husband, even now.
S-Sayaka-san!
She's not crying...
She's touching herself...
See, didn't I tell you?
A woman's body always needs a man's touch.
Shin-chan...
Your sweat has such a manly smell, so could you work for me even more?
I can't get enough of this smell.
That shirt...
Isn't that the one that Sayaka said she'd wash for me?
Shin-chan...
Sayaka-san...
Shin-chan's smell...
This...
I shouldn't. I'll ruin the clothes.
Shi -- Shin-chan...
Oh no...
Watch out!
Oww...
I'm sorry.
This is...
He's... hard?
Sayaka-san?
It's been so long since I've seen a man's cock.
So big... and so hot.
Ever since he died...
Sayaka-san!?
Oh, what am I...?
I'm sorry.
I got so weak when I finally smelled something from a man...
I just haven't had anything at all since my husband died...
So, when I got a hold of your shirt...
I couldn't help myself.
I couldn't bear it.
I am truly sorry.
Even though I know I shouldn't...
My body needs it...
Shin-chan!
Sayaka-san...
Now that I've gotten this far...
I can't help myself!
I'm getting the real thing!
It's getting really hard here.
Your cock... Shin-chan's cock...
That's not fair. You're the only one doing anything.
A want a taste of you too.
Go ahead.
Sayaka-san...
Please, give me the real thing, Shin-chan...
Don't make we wait anymore...
I want it right now, Shin-chan...
Alright.
This is Sayaka-san's...
It's so pink, it's gorgeous.
Shin-chan, there. Do it more, right there.
Shin-chan, no more, please.
Your cock... Put your cock inside me.
I want it too, Sayaka-san.
Shin-chan...
I'm so happy.
It's inside...
Oh, that feels so pleasant...
Then I'll make you feel it even more.
It's been so long since a man touched my breasts...
Do it more.
The real thing is really the best...
A real cock is really the best.
Shin-chan...
Please, mess me up all night tonight.
Sayaka-san...
It's good Shin-chan... Wonderful...
It's making squishing sounds.
Sayaka-san...
Sayaka-san.
Shin-chan, you have such good pacing.
Shin-chan... When we come, let's do it at the same time.
Sayaka-san...
Yes, give it to me harder.
Shin-chan...
A man's broad back...
I'm happy that you have a broad back.
Your cock is the best I've had.
Come all the way inside.
Good...
I can't take it.
Your insides are tightening up too much.
Come!
Come inside of me!
Shin-chan!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Sayaka-san...
Not yet...
I want to feel you inside of me, for just a while longer.
Shin-chan...
I still want you to do things inside me.