"Hey, do you want to have sex with me?"
With those words, I lost my virginity...
...and Hayase and I became sex friends... sex only.
Please, no...
You came watching us, didn't you?
Yes!
Now I want you to put your dick in me.
Yes! Oh yes!
She came already?
It's so deep inside me!
Yes! Yes!
Please, harder!
Can I come inside you?
Yes, come inside!
You shot such a hot load of come.
P-Please... I want you to come inside me too.
You have to take the vibrator out first.
Yes...
Takabe, please... I can't bear it anymore.
We've just started.
Which one do you like better? Me or her?
Ah, yes... Good, lick me harder!
Am I going to die like this?
Good morning!
H-Hey.
You were in the nurse's office yesterday, weren't you?
What? How do you know that?
I see... So it was you, huh?
Well, err...
Let me know in advance when you have sex with other girls.
I don't like to be stood up.
Okay, I'm sorry.
She isn't mad at the fact that I had sex with other girls...
I guess that's not strange... Hayase and I are just sex friends after all.
If you say it like that, then that thing is also the same as...
Hey, Takabe!
Yo.
Later, Kabu!
Taking a nap on the roof?
You're going to skip the afternoon classes, aren't you?
Shouldn't you go back to your classroom?
The teacher thinks you're cutting the class too.
I don't like the teacher of the next class that much...
I didn't know you would say a thing like that.
What do you mean by that?
What kind of girl do you think I am?
Just a horny girl.
You're right... I'm not wearing any underwear today.
Someone's coming!
Coming this way!
I wonder if she really isn't wearing any underwear...
With Hayase, it's surely possible... I should check and see...
Hey, what are you doing at a time like this?
Just a little... It will be fine if we keep quiet.
What are you...
You really aren't wearing any.
Stop it, please.
I wonder how this hole feels...
I guess I'll go with the hole I'm more familiar with...
Looks like you're already wet.
Then I should just use this finger to...
Now it's easier...
Please... I'm very sensitive there... I can't...
It's dripping wet.
Hayase... I can't believe you came so fast.
Takabe, you didn't come yet, right?
We don't have to do it now.
Why?
You must not be feeling good today.
Huh?
Because you came so fast.
Jerk!
Hayase.
Hayase is so cute today.
Go home if you're going to tease me like that.
Hayase, wait!
What is it?
I want to make it up to you.
Tickets for a movie? Two of them?
I got them in a lottery, you could take someone with you.
Okay then, I'll take you.
What? Me?
It's okay if you don't want to.
Of course I'll go!
But no sex for you today.
A date with Hayase...
I've never seen Hayase outside school...
What kind of clothes will she be wearing?
Jeans? Mini skirt? I bet she will wear a sexy tight skirt!
She's gotten careful, hasn't she?
Miss Taeko!
Don't you want to have Takabe only for yourself?
W-What are you saying?
Oh, it looks like your nipples have already gotten hard.
Ah, no...
How did it feel finally having sex with Takabe?
Don't you want him to do more naughty things to you?
Stop it... Please...
Your body seems to want Takabe's dick, doesn't it?
Yes, I want it. I want Takabe to...
Yes!
You have to be more lustful. That's how Takabe likes it.
Please... Please give it to me.
What a nice view, Kaori.
If you really want to make Takabe yours...
...you must show him how nasty Hayase really is. Then I'm sure he will...
Yes! Yes! So good!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Why am I so nervous?
I've had sex with her so many times...
Sorry I'm late.
H-Hey.
N-No, you aren't late, I just got here...
What? Do I have something on me?
N-No! It's just that you look so cute.
Don't stare at me like that! You're embarrassing me.
Uh, I'm sorry. Shall we?
I didn't realize that Hayase was so cute.
It's not that crowded. We can enjoy the movie without reserve.
Yeah.
I don't think I can really concentrate on the movie...
...with her next to me...
No, I can't concentrate...
Just a little bit... She's the one who wore such a short skirt...
Captain's log, Cosmo Year 50894 8'.
Something we've always been afraid of finally happened.
Why isn't Starfleet headquarters giving us the order to attack?
I suppose they didn't trust me enough to let me take care of this situation.
You can't do that in here.
At this rate, the subspace field will be destroyed!
I said no.
More power to the shields!
The pattern of the enemy's shields is rapidly changing.
Change course! We will go into the gas nebula.
You're gonna be like that, huh?
It's dangerous! We won't be able to use phasers in there!
Neither will they!
They're calling me, eh?
Chief! I'll put you in the charge of the bridge!
You're going to the spaceship by yourself? That's too dangerous!
I doubt they want to kill me...
Damage report!
Damage from deck 15 to deck 17.
Lieutenant, set a new course.
Captain, what is our destination?
Hey, do you want to go to...
Yeah, I can't hold it anymore either.
Earth!
Put it in, now.
Yes...
Hayase, it's so hot inside you.
Yes! Yes, Takabe!
I-I'm coming! Yes, Takabe!
Me too, I'm so close...
I'm coming! I'm coming!
It's still hot inside...
I'm going to put it in...
Oh, my god!
Takabe, harder!
I'm going to come!
Me too! I'm coming again!
Well, we did get to see the ending, at least.
It doesn't feel right to walk out of a movie theater...
...without seeing how it ends, you know?
Hayase, the back of your shirt got a little dirty.
What? Really?
It doesn't look that bad...
...but you want to come over to my house and wash it?
It's hot today, so it probably won't take too long to dry it.
Yeah, but what about your parents?
Don't worry, they've gone on a trip since yesterday.
So you're staying at home by yourself?
Yeah. Let's go, you won't be able to enjoy the date like that.
You're right.
May I come in?
Yes, go ahead.
I didn't expect that you would keep your room so tidy.
What do you mean you didn't expect it?
Here. It's my shirt, but it's better than just underwear.
I know you would rather want me to stay in my underwear, wouldn't you?
Hurry and change your clothes!
Okay.
Okay, I'm done.
Huh? Um...
Why did you take your underwear off too?
I want to thank you for the movie.
This gets you a little excited, doesn't it?
I-I'm going to put them in the washing machine!
Thank you.
She's too cute...
H-Hayase...
The breeze is nice.
Hayase, let's do it.
You really don't know how to set a mood.
Hayase... It feels good...
I'm coming, Hayase!
Lick mine too.
That's...
...your most sensitive part, right?
Please, don't put it in there.
Please Takabe.
Are you afraid that you're going to come fast in this hole?
No, please! Stop it!
It's too late!
N-No!
Hayase... it's getting so tight.
I'll make you feel so good...
Good! My God!
Yes!
I'm going to come!
You're amazing, Hayase! I'm coming!
Yes! Yes! I'm coming!
You really do come fast with this hole, don't you?
Was that your first time by any chance?
Yes. I've been licked and played with there before...
...but never the actual thing.
But you're the first, Takabe.
It was really great.
It was for me, too.
I wonder if I'm starting to really like Hayase...
Takabe!
Y-Yes?
Please break up with Hayase!
What is it all of sudden?
Hayase... All she wants is your body, and nothing else.
Well, I don't know what to tell you, but...
Oh? Am I interrupting something?
Yes, you are.
Takabe and I are talking about something very important right now.
Okay then. See ya.
Wait! She has nothing to do with me.
That's... That's horrible. I have nothing to do with you?
We can't be arguing like this here...
Please choose! Hayase or me, right here, right now.
I don't know how to answer, it's just too sudden...
Just pick one, then everything will be fine.
Takabe, do you like big breasts like hers?
Oh my.
She enjoys doing naughty things with anyone. She's just a horny slut.
Hey wait a minute!
Oh no! Stop it!
You have to help me too. I will show you how lewd she is.
I don't know if I like doing things like that.
Takabe, please stop it!
How is it? Doesn't this turn you on?
What? She's acting?
Oh no! Takabe! Please make her stop!
Um... Shut up and do whatever we tell you to do!
I beg of you, don't do such a horrible thing!
You're saying that now, but I'll see how horny you are!
Looks like you're already excited.
No...
You're getting wet too, Kaori.
Yes, good... Takabe.
I want to see you masturbate, Hayase.
Yes! Yes!
Takabe!
Takabe...
Now you put this inside you, okay?
Yes. I'll do whatever you say, Takabe.
Ah, yes!
Yes! Yes! I'm coming!
Takabe, deeper! Deep inside me! Yes! Yes! I'm coming!
Takabe, deeper! Deep inside me!
I'm going to come, Hayase!
Yes! Yes! Let's come together!
Takabe, you came with Hayase...
Don't let a small thing like that bother you.
Good!
Yes! Yes!
Now Kaori has finally become an adult.
Is something wrong?
Nothing is wrong, but I just feel strange.
So you do have something on your mind.
It's you that's on my mind, Hayase.
Huh?
I want to know what do you think of me.
I like you, Takabe. As a sex friend.
That's what I thought...
But she did say she likes me, so I guess that's progress.
Your face tells me you're thinking about something perverted.
Shut up.
Hey, do you want to have sex with me?
jugyouchuu sekkusu shitai
I wanna have sex during class.
totsuzen ni uzuite kichau
Suddenly it starts pulsing...
shitai toki wa shitai onna no komo
Even girls wanna do it when they wanna do it.
ferachio mo jishin aru no
I have confidence in my fellatio.
nameteru to kouhun shichau no
I get excited when I'm licking it.
kao ni kakete hoshii no kimi no koi no wo
I want to wear your love on my face.
aa ai nante dareka no kotoba yori
Ah... love isn't just someone's words;
aaahhh!
kimochi yokere ba ii no
It has to feel good...
sore wa suteki na koto da kara
...because it's a wonderful thing.
ima sugu watashi no asoko ni
Right now, in my special place...
kimi no atsui no wo
...your hot thing...
mou irete kurenakya iya
...I want you to stick it in already!
muzukashii kao shinai de yo ne
Don't make a difficult face, okay?
ima wo taisetsu ni
Let's make this moment count...
nee kimochi ii koto shiyo
...and do something that feels good!
You satisfied me!
jugyouchuu sekkusu shitai
I wanna have sex during class.
totsuzen ni uzuite kichau
Suddenly it starts pulsing...
shitai toki wa shitai onna no komo
Even girls wanna do it when they wanna do it.
ferachio mo jishin aru no
I have confidence in my fellatio.
nameteru to kouhun shichau no
I get excited when I'm licking it.
kao ni kakete hoshii no kimi no koi no wo
I want to wear your love on my face.
aa ai nante dareka no kotoba yori
Ah... love isn't just someone's words;
aaahhh!
kimochi yokere ba ii no
It has to feel good...
sore wa suteki na koto da kara
...because it's a wonderful thing.
ima sugu watashi no asoko ni
Right now, in my special place...
kimi no atsui no wo
...your hot thing...
mou irete kurenakya iya
...I want you to stick it in already!
muzukashii kao shinai de yo ne
Don't make a difficult face, okay?
ima wo taisetsu ni
Let's make this moment count...
nee kimochi ii koto shiyo
...and do something that feels good!