Excuse me... The library is closing now. Please wake up.
Oh, thank you for waking me up.
Y-You're welcome.
Ouch!
Shoot, she must have seen this...
Are you serious? You have got to be kidding me!
Stop it! Enough already!
Hayase?
Well, I didn't mean to...
Sorry, but you have to help me!
He is my new boyfriend. Do you understand?
Damn it!
I won't forget about you!
Thanks.
What was that all about?
Hey, Hayase, are you sure you wanted to break up with him like that?
You know... He might try to get revenge...
...by spreading rumors or something.
Takabe, come closer.
Hey, do you want to have sex with me?
What? What is it, all of sudden?
We have never even gone out or anything yet, and...
Let's go somewhere else!
What? But...
You have time, don't you?
Or are you saying I'm not good enough for you?
Oh, hello Nurse Taeko.
Yes?
May we come in?
Um, I'm not really...
Miss Hayase, I have to attend the teachers' meeting now.
Will you take over here for a while?
Yes.
You have the keys?
Yeah, I hold the keys sometimes.
Do you want to do it with our clothes on or off?
Um... Well...
Come on, you can touch my breasts.
Please be gentle, okay?
I don't want my clothes to get wrinkled.
Are you going to take your panties off first?
Why not? It's not going to make any difference what I take off first, is it?
Take your clothes off too.
Um, yeah.
You want to see it?
Can I?
Wow, this is how it looks...
Come on, touch it.
S-Sure.
It's getting wet...
Can I put my finger in?
Sure, go ahead.
H-Hayase... It's amazing...
Hayase, can I...?
Yes, you can put it in.
No, a little lower...
Y-Yes...
That's right, just lower your hip a little...
Um, well...
Was this your first time?
I see, you were a virgin...
Well, then it can't be helped, huh?
I'm sorry I came inside...
Everyone is like that his first time.
You'll do better tomorrow.
T-Tomorrow?
I'll wait for you in front of this nurse's room tomorrow after school.
I have nothing else to do.
O-Okay...
See you tomorrow!
Will you lock the door?
You want to see it?
What? Well...
You want to see it, don't you?
Will you take off your clothes?
Sure.
You have to take off my underwear.
Hayase...
It feels great, Hayase...
My turn.
Oh yes! Yes! Takabe!
Hayase, I can't hold it any longer!
So good! Takabe!
I'm going to come soon!
I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Hayase...
Hayase, show me how you do it by yourself.
What? How do I do it by myself?
I have never seen a girl masturbate...
...so I want to see how you do it.
Okay, but don't stare, okay?
It's so good, Takabe! I want it now!
You want me to put it in?
Yes, put it in!
Hey...
Takabe, hurry...
My God! Takabe, you're bigger than before!
So good! I'm going to come!
I'm going to come too!
You were yawning a lot during classes today. Didn't you get enough sleep?
No... Um, but it's not like I couldn't sleep thinking about you or anything...
How many times did you do it?
Um, three times.
Hurry up! The school gate will be closed soon!
Shoot!
Well, I'm free tomorrow too, so...
Of course, I'm free too!
I hope I can take a nap here for an hour...
No, please...
Please don't make me do this, Takabe!
What? Me?
No, not there.
Ah, forgive me, Takabe. I'll do whatever you say!
She's fantasizing about getting raped by me?
Ah, no. It's too big!
Takabe, please look at my wet pussy...
Ah, it feels good!
I-I'm coming, Takabe!
She came fantasizing about me...
Hayase isn't here yet... I guess I'll wait for her outside.
Oh, you're alone?
No, Um, well Hayase should be here soon.
What is the matter with your crotch? It seems very happy.
Uh, it's nothing.
Is it because you were thinking about Miss Hayase?
Or is it because you saw something at the library?
W-What? No! I don't know what you're talking about!
So you saw Kaori masturbating, didn't you?
H-How did you...?
Sometimes she cuts classes, and goes there to satisfy herself.
How do you know that?
I gave her a little advice on how and where to do it.
But you're a teacher...
I wonder who she was fantasizing about today...
Maybe it was you.
W-What are you...
How does it feel?
How do you like the technique of a mature woman?
It feels great... I'm about to...
I just started.
Aw, too bad.
If you had come back a little later, we could have had more fun.
You should stop trying to take other people's things.
It's a bad habit.
It doesn't bother me a bit, though.
I'm going to the teacher's meeting now.
You hold the fort while I'm gone, okay?
Okay.
Aren't you mad at me?
Not really. We aren't a couple, we're just sex friends.
It's better if we don't meddle in each other's sex lives.
I see... I guess we are sex friends.
So, did you want to have sex with Nurse Taeko?
Why do you say that?
I want to do it with you, Hayase!
That makes me a little happy.
Just a little?
What are you doing?
I can't hold it any longer!
You'll get wet so fast, we can do it...
Just be gentle, okay?
Take off your bra.
Yes! Yes! It's so good, Takabe!
It feels amazing, Hayase!
Yes! Yes! I'm coming!
Hayase, you came...
Hayase, can I do it with your breasts?
Hayase, I'm coming...
Come. I want to see you come.
Sex friends, huh?
Does it make me a pervert that I want to do it with her?
Does Hayase really think...
Take my bathing suit off.
You don't need to.
I'm putting it in, okay?
Yes! Yes!
Hey, pull your fingers out. I want you now.
Maybe I can put it in with my fingers in.
No, it's not going to fit!
It's inside you, Hayase.
N-No! Don't move your fingers!
It feels great! Takabe! Yes!
Yes! So great!
Yes! Yes, Takabe! I'm going to come!
I'm coming too, Hayase!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
I promised Kabu that I would go shopping with her after school, so I have to go.
Okay, see you.
That girl... at the library...
Takabe...
She's fantasizing about me again...
Like you told me, I'm not wearing any underwear today.
Takabe... I want you to tease me more...
T-Takabe... Please look at my pussy.
You want me to fuck you that badly?
Y-Yes...
If you put on a good show, I might grant your wish.
Takabe... Look at my naughty parts...
Please... I'm already so wet.
Okay, I'll do as you wish.
You know what you have to do, don't you?
Yes, Takabe...
Please let me suck your penis.
Come on, use your tongue more.
A dirty girl like you needs to be punished from behind.
Yes...
Please, put it in.
Yes! It feels so good!
Oh yeah? Just a little more...
Yes! Yes! I'm going to come!
What the hell? You came by yourself?
You came before I came, what do you think you're doing?
I'm sorry, Takabe...
I wonder if I want to have sex like this with Hayase...
Can I talk to you for a minute?
What is it?
Um, why are you locking the door?
Nurse Taeko! What are you doing?
I'm punishing her because she had fun all by herself.
She told me all about yesterday.
I can't forgive you for doing such a naughty thing only with her.
But...
I will show you how great a mature woman's body feels.
You have never done it in this hole yet, have you?
B-But...
That's right, it's my butt.
And you can do whatever you wish to do with it.
Looks like you're ready.
That's right, slowly...
It's very delicate, so be gentle.
That's right. You're doing good.
You're pretty good at it.
It feels amazing!
Yes, there... That feels good...
Can I put it into your butt?
Go ahead, you want to do it, right?
Oh, it's so big!
Yes! Yes!
Harder! Do it harder!
Yes! Yes! I'm going to come!
It's so tight! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
W-What?
I bet you have never used something like this either.
You should practice how to use it for your future girlfriend.
Please, no...
You came watching us, didn't you?
No!
Yes! Yes!
Now I want you to put your dick in me.
If Hayase sees this... what will she think of me?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Hey, do you want to have sex with me?
jugyouchuu sekkusu shitai
I wanna have sex during class.
totsuzen ni uzuite kichau
Suddenly it starts pulsing...
shitai toki wa shitai onna no komo
Even girls wanna do it when they wanna do it.
ferachio mo jishin aru no
I have confidence in my fellatio.
nameteru to kouhun shichau no
I get excited when I'm licking it.
kao ni kakete hoshii no kimi no koi no wo
I want to wear your love on my face.
aa ai nante dareka no kotoba yori
Ah... love isn't just someone's words;
aaahhh!
kimochi yokere ba ii no
It has to feel good...
sore wa suteki na koto da kara
...because it's a wonderful thing.
ima sugu watashi no asoko ni
Right now, in my special place...
kimi no atsui no wo
...your hot thing...
mou irete kurenakya iya
...I want you to stick it in already!
muzukashii kao shinai de yo ne
Don't make a difficult face, okay?
ima wo taisetsu ni
Let's make this moment count...
nee kimochi ii koto shiyo
...and do something that feels good!
You satisfied me!
jugyouchuu sekkusu shitai
I wanna have sex during class.
totsuzen ni uzuite kichau
Suddenly it starts pulsing...
shitai toki wa shitai onna no komo
Even girls wanna do it when they wanna do it.
ferachio mo jishin aru no
I have confidence in my fellatio.
nameteru to kouhun shichau no
I get excited when I'm licking it.
kao ni kakete hoshii no kimi no koi no wo
I want to wear your love on my face.
aa ai nante dareka no kotoba yori
Ah... love isn't just someone's words;
aaahhh!
kimochi yokere ba ii no
It has to feel good...
sore wa suteki na koto da kara
...because it's a wonderful thing.
ima sugu watashi no asoko ni
Right now, in my special place...
kimi no atsui no wo
...your hot thing...
mou irete kurenakya iya
...I want you to stick it in already!
muzukashii kao shinai de yo ne
Don't make a difficult face, okay?
ima wo taisetsu ni
Let's make this moment count...
nee kimochi ii koto shiyo
...and do something that feels good!