That all you can do! At this rate your belly fate aint going anywhere!
You've got 20 times more to go.
Come now, get on moving!
Oi oi. You're gonna muscle up and make your wife happy right?
Hey newface... it's your first day, right?
I'm Shoko, the trainer in charge of this time slot. Nice to meet you.
Yeah. Just like that. If you've got any questions, ask me okay?
How to use this? Alright. Watch carefully okay?
We've got a newcomer today so, everyone gather up.
This, you stick it in here...
And open your legs wide...
This is the position.
Take a clooooose look. This is how you do it.
Stop that. You want to see this, right?
The rule of bodybuilding... is to breathe out when you flex.
You've got to start off light and do the reps. No heavy stuff yet.
Do you understand?
Next it's your turn...
What an impressive dick...
So delicious...
Alright, yeah... just like that...
Ahhnn, that's amazing...
Oh wow, so much...
Bad boy... don't stop your hands...
You can still... cum some more, right?
Show me some more... of your cumming physique.
It's delicious...
Plunging in and out... you can see it, right?
More...
Move come more...
Yeah... go on and cummm... shoot out all that semen of yours...
Well done...
So you want to do it again huh...?
Ah... that spot is...
Oh no... that's not...
Amazing...
Oh yeah... so good... it feels... soooo good...
What's up...? Even though it's vacant, you're not going to enter?
I'm going to... go erazzzy...
No... Nooo... I'll cum... cnmmming... gonna CuUMmMMMMM!!!!
So warmmmm...
Hey, give me some more... you can still cum, right...?
Dickkk... diiiickkk...
Choose... where do you want to cum...?
In my pussy? Anus? Mouth?
Or maybe my titties?
Is it perhaps on my legs?
A big dick is...
Coming inside my pussy...
I'm goinnng crazzzzyyyy...
C'mon... ram your horny dicks inside my holes and blast your cum inside!!
I'm going to breakkk...
I'm gonna cummM! It's CuMmMINGG... CUMMMMINGGGG!!
Blast as much cum as you want inside my mouth...
So much cum...
You like breasts huh... Make sure to cum all over me
Amazing...
So much cum...
Wanting me to service you with my feet... What a pervert...
CummMMM... Cum alllllll over meee...
It's so warm...
After that... I continued to tempt the male members and have sex...
But, it wasn't long before the owner found out and I was fired...
Perhaps I should become a teacher next...
softsub – торрент иваниваныч