Here, how are your big sis' boobs?
Shall I give you a tit fuck?
Huh?!
Eh?
Any complaints?
No, well...
Nee-chan!
She's just too erotic!
This is a tit fuck.
This is, these are... Nee-chan's breasts!
It's getting big and stiff.
I'll make this thing into a great, adult dick.
Well?
How does Nee-chan's adult body feel?
Tit fucks are...
This is my first time experiencing this!
It feels so good!
Let's get your dick squeaky clean, okay?
My thing is completely enveloped by Nee-chan's breasts!
It feels really, really good!
Oh crap...!
I'm cumming!
Nee-chan!
It came out!
It's really... thick.
I'm sorry, it felt so good that I...
You sure came a lot.
Now, do you feel like throwing away your
virginity for your Nee-chan now?
Eh?!
Shall I listen to your carnal desires then?
Do it if you want.
Come over here.
Shuuichi.
Shabura
Rental
Rented
The slutty Nee-chan and the Super Erotic Lesson
Look, my insides are already like this.
So, what do you want to do?
I-I want to put it in.
Let's do it then.
You shall now experience...
Your first sexual act with me.
It's in.
I'm now inside you, Nee-chan,
So this is your dick, Shuuichi.
It feels hot... and good.
My pussy is being opened.
We're having sex right now, don't you agree?
Right?
We're doing something we shouldn't,
and yet I feel so excited.
N-Nee-chan...
Your dick is hitting my soft spots.
I planned on teaching you many things,
but looks Like all of it has been thrown out the window now.
It's deep inside...
No way...!
Nee-chan, don't...!
I'm, about to... cum!
I'm cumming!
Nanami nee-chan!
Ne-Nee-chan...
I can't hold back anymore!
Nee-chan...
Just cum...
Just cum wherever you want.
Wherever?
You can cum inside if you want to.
Oh yes... I'm about to cum.
My pussy is about to cum!
Me too, I'm about to cum too!
Nee-chan!
It feels hot.
Hot, and very nice.
I'm cumming with you right now.
Sorry for intruding, but can I speak to you two for a bit?
What in the world are you doing, Nanami?
Can we have an explanation?
Wh-What is this?
Well, um...
We're just taking a bat-
Or just having a good time with her brother's dick inside of her.
Good grief, I can't believe this.
Taking your brother into the female's dormitory bathroom,
and then having sex with him...
Hey,
at least let me put on some clothes first.
Nope, no can do.
You're going to have to reflect on your actions as you are.
You're Nanami’s younger brother, right?
I heard that you're still trying to get into college.
Th-That's right.
Nee-chan invited me here, saying there's a
great pilgrimage spot near the university.
I planned on spending summer vacation studying
while staying at a private lodge, but...
The place kind of burnt to the ground after
some meteorite fell on it though.
Oh, I've heard that rumor at the university.
So it was true then,
he doesn't have a place close enough to stay at,
so I thought of letting him hide out at my place for a while.
Please, it's just until summer vacation ends.
I"m asking for your cooperation.
Okay?
Well, if it's just that then,
I'm okay with it.
And if you're going to live here anyway,
I'm ready to give you some lessons.
Th-Thank you very much!
Well, each one of us have a different specialty.
We can probably set time aside for
some one-on-one study sessions.
In exchange, I also want you to call me onee-chan.
Wait, what's with that?
Nothing wrong with that, right?
I've always wanted a little brother.
Oh, I get what you're saying.
I think I remember when I was a kid and I asked
for a little brother as a Christmas present.
Hey, that actually happened to me as well.
I'm actually kind of envious.
Wh-What's with you three?
You're saying that you all have brother complexes?
Come now, try saying it once.
Say, Onee-chan.
I'm looking forward to this.
U-Umm...
Riko... nee-chan?
Wow, that wasn't bad at all!
Minato nee-chan?
Hey, that sounds kind of nice.
Manatsu nee-chan?
Whoa, now that's over the top.
Oh, you're suddenly quite popular.
I can't really say I'm too glad about it.
It's all settled then.
In exchange for tutoring,
we get to have our own personal little brother during your stay.
Now he seems like someone worth teaching.
I'm looking forward to this.
And so, he began his sojourn as everybody's
little brother during summer vacation.
shh~
Don't make a sound.
W-Wait, Riko-san!
It's gotten this big after just holding it in between for a while.
I'm going to finish this for you with my breasts.
It's twitching.... it seems very lively.
That actually kind of tickles, you know.
Riko-san.
No, you have to call me Riko nee-chan,
and if you do, I'm going to make this feel even better.
O-Okay.
O-Onee-chan.
Riko-neechan!
Nee-chan!
Your dick and my breasts are now drenched,
and it's become quite hot.
Do you really like my breasts that much?
Yes.
It seems my breasts are starting to get aroused as well.
If you keep getting aroused like this in front of me, then I'll also....!
I'm, already.... about to...!
Your dick reeks of lewdness.
You're about to cum, right?
A-Alright then.
Just squirt all of your white stuff onto
Riko onee-chan's lewd breasts.
Riko nee-chan...
I'm going to squeeze it out till the end, so just cum.
Cum, cum already!
Squirt it all on big sis!
Did you know?
Strong sexual stimuli can affect how memories are preserved.
R-Really?
Yes, that's why you should let us do something even more intense.
That's good, keep it up.
Really good.
Your dick is hitting all of my pleasurable spots.
My pussy is getting filled.
Riko nee-chan, you're gripping me really tightly.
Go deeper inside me.
Keep on pushing harder and harder!
It's rubbing...
Your dick is rubbing hard inside my pussy.
Oh no, if you do that I'll...
I'll be unable to hold back!
I'm about to cum.
Shuuichi, it feels really great!
Please, just keep on stirring me inside.
I'm already about to cum, so let's, let's...
Let's cum together, then do it some more!
Push it more...
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum again.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Not yet, we're not yet done here.
Then...
That's good, just keep it up.
Shabura Rental
That night,
the little brother decided to peek on my masturbation session.
Oh no,
I'm getting aroused more than usual.
My breasts are getting really aroused.
Hey, can you see it?
I'm masturbating right now.
Here, little brother,
I'm going to show you all of my lewd spots.
You wanted to see my pussy, right?
Oh no,
I can no longer stop at just masturbation.
I want to do more lewd things with my little brother.
H-Hey, you're peeking at me, right?
I already knew from the start.
I'm sorry, Manatsu-san.
I...
Can I touch it?
Yeah, okay.
What is this?
It's soft, and wet.
Shuuichi-kun,
should I caress your dick with my mouth and hands?
Come now, no need to be shy.
But,
it's okay.
I also didn't tell you that I knew you were peeping,
so to make up for it, I also want you to pleasure me a lot.
Okay.
Now I'm really getting into it.
Your dick, this dick, dick, dick....
Your dick is really good.
It's coming...
No, not there...
Manatsu nee-chan, your pussy is wet and twitching.
And it has a really erotic smell...
This is embarrassing...
Your dick is also already this big and hot.
You're about to cum, right?
I-I'm about to...
I'm about to cum.
Okay then.
Just cum. I'll drink it all.
Give me all of your sticky cum.
You came a lot.
Oh, it still looks lively.
Let's do it some more.
Ma...
Manatsu nee-chan!
It's really big.
My pussy feels really tight now.
Manatsu nee-chan, I...
I'll do my best to make you cum.
Okay, make me cum.
I'm...
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
It's gripping me so tightly!
My pussy is ejaculating...
B-But I just came....
No way...
I'm going to cum already.
Okay, then cum.
Cum whenever you want to!
Pump all of your hot cum inside me!
Release all of your cum.
Oh wow, it's pumping so much inside that it's overflowing.
It's okay.
My insides will squeeze out every last drop.
It all started,
with a gel that I concocted when I was in college.
It's a substance made from refined extracts,
and was supposed to be used as skin
lotion for beauty purposes, but...
Mi-Minato nee-chan, I...
I haven't done anything yet,
and it's already twitching wildly.
It looks as if it's in pain.
Sorry about that.
For making it go wild with my gel.
I'm going to to make it melt inside my slippery breasts, okay?
It's hot.
This, can you feel it?
My nipples are touching the tip.
I'm so hard already.
Even you, Minato nee-chan,
your face is starting to look like you're entranced.
My breasts are starting to feel tingly.
It's kind of like masturbating with a dick,
and I'm starting to feel really horny.
Th-This is amazing.
I think I'm going to cum soon if this continues.
You were worried about that?
No need to think of anything, just let it sink into my breasts,
as it cums.
Minato nee-chan...!
I'm going to let this dick cum as much as it wants to.
So let your big sis handle your dick.
I'm starting to get aroused as well.
I think I'm going to love tit fucks from now on.
Minato nee-chan!
Next, let's do something even more pleasurable.
Nee-chan's pussy is going take real good care of you.
Your dick feels hot, and slippery,
as I put it in.
Its like it's drowning inside my own pussy.
That gel is really amazing.
I'm starting to crave it more, and I'm unable to resist it.
Your dick is twitching inside me.
Okay, just go ahead and cum.
M-Me too, I'll... I'll...
I'll...!
I-I'm sorry.
No, it's alright.
Your dick is still big.
Just... keep on doing it until you're satisfied.
You can make a mess of my pussy however you want.
Make it even more drenched, even stickier!
Minato nee-chan.
Your hot stuff is pumping hard inside me.
It's okay.
Just, just keep on doing it!
Make me cum more!
Minato nee-chan,
I'm going to cum with you!
My pussy is trying to suck it in.
Cum, just cum!
Keep on pushing inside me.
Just release it all inside my lewd pussy!
Hey,
prepare for this night,
because you're about to enjoy an endless
sex session with Onee-chan till morning.
Wow!
This is great!
This is a private area that is considered part of the university,
so no one else can come here, and we can
treat it like our own private beach!
Well? Does it feel good?
Now,
let's play all day long.
Wait, Nanami nee-chan,
I'm still preparing for the next entrance exams!
No need to hold back now.
Nee-chan, it really feels good.
See, feels good, right?
A-Amazing...
It feels really soft.
Oh, it's gotten big.
It's really good for your studies to go out
once in a while to relax, you know.
Eh...
It's getting even bigger.
Go ahead, just cum.
Onee-chan...!
Ne-Nee-chan...
Nee-chan, your pussy is all mine and mine alone!
Wait... you're too intense!
No, don't....
Shuuichi,
it feels so good.
I'm going to cum with my brother's dick!
Your insides feel hot, and it's too good...
Your dick... it's rubbing so hard inside,
my love juices just won't stop.
Nee-chan, your pussy just feels too good.
No...
I'm cumming,
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm having lots of cum poured inside me!
We're not going to just let you hog him, Nanami.
Feeling good all by themselves, how terrible.
We also have the right to be pleasured.
Hey~!
Get away from Shuuichi!
This is terrible.
Let's all quell your dick's lust.
This feeling of freedom,
definitely feels great!
Oh wow, his dick feels good.
And with that,
our summer vacation with our little brother continues...