The kingdom has chosen several heroes to exterminate the demons.
One of them wields the power of flames and sword skills,
surpassing the other six heroes in demon-slaying.
This beautiful woman who possesses
a captivating allure contrary to her prowess is known as...
Blazing Flame Heroine: Eris Violet
This is the silly life story of an inept and beautiful heroine
smeared with sweat, tears, semen and love juice who fell from grace.
The Beautiful Blazing Flame Heroine: Eris Violet
She is one of the only seven individuals who are bestowed with the title of "hero".
Far from how she looks, Eris is acknowledged as the kingdom's strongest hero
for cutting down demons using her superior sword skills.
Due to her extreme diligence, she performs her duties as a heroine without a single time to rest.
Countless men want to hold her down into submission
and have their way on that body of hers.
However, countless men have also been
ruthlessly crushed by that strength of hers.
For a woman possessing such sheer strength,
never had she thought even in her dreams to go
through something like that against the demons.
A Scoundrel Who Became A Minister At A Young Age: Kiryuu Tanatsuki
Kiryuu is a minister in his early adulthood
who's in the position of managing the heroes under the kingdom.
He has enough power to talk down to the heroes that everyone admires.
Their own nation suffers for the absurdity
of having its fate being left to such a person.
Before long, he finally shows his own ambitions
and changed the very system of heroes itself.
He strengthened his own position for the sake of that ambition.
A Young Man Who Admires Eris: Keith
Keith is an upcoming hero candidate and junior of Eris Violet.
He is a young man who holds her in high regard,
admiring her strength and the way she carries herself.
Keith has a talent akin to Eris and is a young warrior with a promising future.
Eris is the beautiful blazing flame heroine that takes pride in her strength.
As one of the heroes of the kingdom, she always prioritizes her duty
of subjugating demons above anything else.
She keeps on training herself, as well as fulfilling missions more than anyone else
which further increased her record in subjugating demons.
As much as everyone is captivated by the beauty Eris possesses,
she is just as much hated for the strength she possesses.
She never takes the luxury of the position she currently has.
Today, she proudly embarks once again
to exterminate demons for the sake of her people.
At this particular day, The blazing flame heroine Eris goes to rescue a young girl
who seemed to have been attacked by demons at the outskirts of a town.
She searched at a secluded place where she suspects to encounter the demons.
And there she finds a nearby demon fort.
Although the best way would have been taking someone with her to raid the fort,
Eris misread the difficulty of the situation. She pressed alone onwards the fort.
However...
Original Animation
Shakuen no Eris
Blazing Flame Eris
The Beautiful and Inept Heroine Eris: Shockingly Disgraceful Ass
Miss Heroine!
Thank you, Eris-sama!
I want a piece of those tits and ass!
You fool!
If you make her angry, prepare to die!
It is an effortless subjugation.
You annihilated the demons with no sweat.
Just as I expected from one of the heroes.
Twelve villagers died, and the nearby
village was totally wiped out.
The way you speak is disrespectful
to those who fell victim.
It couldn't be helped. The nearby village
has already fallen when we got notified.
It's wrong to bring your emotions into this.
Then, what's my next mission?
Are you going already? You're an eager one.
Heroes have no time to rest.
He only gives orders somewhere safe.
Victims aren't simply written figures.
Look at the actual sites!
Senpai... Senpai!
What?
Th-Thank you for working hard at subjugation.
Oh, Keith. Are you about to do your training?
Yes, and I want to invite you as a partner.
It'll be a good opportunity
for an aspiring hero.
Alright, then. I need to let off
a little steam as well.
Your reflexes are slow! That's what
makes or breaks a warrior.
Never lose focus and act fast
at the right time, understood?
Yes, thank you.
You're the only one who
lasted this long against me.
I have high hopes for you.
Stop!
You jumped right into a
ten-thousand-strong enemy force.
You can't be too careless, Miss Heroine.
I don't mind sacrificing my subordinates!
Oh, you can't hear me...
We'll put you in an illusion of being fucked
by demons to slowly break you down.
Have a nice dream.
Stop!
What's happening here? It hurts...
I hate it, and yet it feels good!
No!
Stop!
I don't like this sensation!
This is bad!
It went deep into my belly!
I suddenly started feeling good!
But I shouldn't!
I'll never ever lose against a mere demon's cock!
Wow, I'm getting filled with cocks!
I'll never ever lose against mere demons!
You would've already been broken if you're
an ordinary human. That's a heroine for you!
How about this one, then?
This is a special cream extracted
from an orc's sperm.
This will drive you even crazier.
M-My body is...
That's a lovely orgasm you had there!
I'm sure that this will break you down now.
There are still more to come...
That was dangerous!
D-Don't you get your own position?
Aren't you the one who doesn't
know your own position?
I heard that it was a close call...
No, I'm alright.
U-Uhh, umm...
My handwritten report will be late.
Will that be alright?
Yes, I understand. That won't be a problem.
I'll be taking my leave, then.
Huh?
Oh...
Thank you for the other day.
I'd love to train with you again if it's okay...
Umm, I'm busy right now. Bye, then...
This is bad... If this goes on, I'm...
What's this? Shit... Why?
When Keith is around, I keep thinking about his cock!
Even though I shouldn't, this feels amazing!
But... But...
If this goes on...
Even though I'm a heroine,
but with this condition...
Huh?
Hey, Eris Violet.
What are you doing?
You won't get away from this
even if you're a minister!
I came to check your actual condition
as an authority in managing heroes,
and it gets mistaken for sexual harassment...
Please forgive my rudeness.
Follow me. We'll talk about that issue.
Y-You mean specifically?
B-But, you see... My body is...
You have the status of a heroine,
so you're setting a bad example
for being ambiguous.
I-I will explain in detail.
I, Eris Violet,
was put under an illusion spell by demons
in a battle several days ago.
The said spell was a sexual training
and was for body alteration as well.
A-A-A-And it made me sexually
excited as an aftereffect.
That won't be enough to be called a report.
Be more specific. How many times
did you do self-pleasure?
Self-pleasure!?
Yes, masturbation.
Shouldn't I make any judgment
based on objective data?
Th-There were three instances.
I can remember being engaged
in self-pleasure on the first two.
Will that be enough? I'm in an unusual condition!
I couldn't hold back so I also
did it in the toilet earlier...
That's how it is, so may I request for leave?
That only is a personal statement at most.
Try doing self-pleasure.
Try doing... You mean here?
Of course.
You'll convince me on how bad of a state
you're in for hero duties by doing it right here.
What is this man saying?
There's no way that I can do that here!
I ended up doing it!
Even though he's watching, I'm...
What a filthy cunt.
I'm doing it!
I'm teasing myself in such a place, but...
You certainly won't be able to fulfill
your duties as a heroine.
You'll have to take a break.
Th-Thank you very much...
You... Don't tell me that you're a virgin?
To think that a pervert like you is still a virgin!
I'm very sorry!
What the hell am I apologizing for?
Apologize to all our citizens!
I-I, Eris Violet, am a perverted
heroine who loses herself
in masturbation just from looking at men!
This is bad! I'm doing something
unbecoming of a hero,
but why am I feeling good?
Face this way.
Okay!
So, this is a cock...
Are they this huge? Are they
no different from the demons'?
You're a virgin so I guess
it's your first time to see one.
How about it? Want me to be your partner?
If you'll swear to keep me company as a blowpig
on or off your duties, then you can
suck me as much as you want.
B-Blowpig?
I-I'm...
I'll have to decline. I'm a heroine, you know!
Even if I'm off duty, I'll only make use
of myself for the people's sake!
That's amazing. I'd never think
that this is your first time.
Shit! Shit! This is what a cock is! This thing!
It's too big that I can't breathe,
but its firmness is amazing!
How is it? Do you feel like
being my partner now?
My virginity...
A blowpig... But that's...
Is it the "my virginity belongs to my love" thing?
Then, I'll leave your virginity alone.
But in exchange...
That's...
This thing that changed even you could become
a weapon or even a cure, depending on research.
We'll first test it in your mouth and ass.
This is your duty as a heroine
for the sake of our people.
That drug will be used on my body again.
I'm already this close to losing
my mind, and I'm here again...
I-If it will be for the sake of the people,
I'll gladly offer my body!
Wow, it's going into my mouth!
You're sucking my cock hard.
So, you really like it.
There's no way that I do!
This is for research purposes!
It has a lewd shape and it also smells awful!
It's going right to my head!
If that's so, then move your head more.
I don't want to lose against such a cock!
I'll go crazy! Having this much
done to me will turn me insane!
Make sure to drink it.
I'll drink your sperm...
It's going into my mouth!
This is what's called "sperm"...
It's thick and bitter,
but I might get hooked on it!
We got some good research data.
Alright, next is your asshole.
Were you waiting for it?
I'm not! It's for the experiment!
I couldn't help it!
I should see it for myself. Come on, stand up.
S-Shut up!
Having the entrance lightly
smeared with that felt incredible.
If he applies that inside me now...
What's this!? My ass feels hot!
Wow!
Don't! We can't do this!
Your cock is filling me up inside!
It feels so good that I'm lost right now!
We can't do the experiment like this.
Wow... This feels good!
I can't think about anything
else but your cock now!
You're like a child reporting.
But it feels hot in my ass,
and it's starting to take the shape of your cock!
P-Please forgive me!
I'm a heroine, but I'm wetting myself!
I made a mess...
A SakuraCircle project
Translated by: Tennouji
Next Time on Shakuen no Eris...
I, Eris Violet,
will become a blowpig!
I came!
I became a blowpig at a place that heroes use!
Here it is!
Th-The Blowpig Contract:
I am a blowpig and in charge of
cock semen disposal as well...
I am Kiryuu-sama's Blowpig #1!
Please tell me anything you wish
that comes to your mind.
Doing as he pleases...
Dammit... Father!
I'm sorry, I became a blowpig!
My ass! My ass!
Your cock is going deep inside!
You're filling up my ass! It's so huge!
Kiryuu-sama, your cock is
driving this blowpig crazy!
It's huge just as usual.
This cock turned me crazy! This thing!
You're a pervert, senpai!
Getting delighted from being abused...
I never knew that you're such a pig...
That's right, I'm a blowpig!
This Blowpig #1
is having a younger boy's cock
rape my mouth!
There, blowpig! To think that I've been
admiring someone like you...
Wow, I can't have enough of such a huge cock!
Don't be having fun by yourself,
Take care of this one too.
I'm having two huge cocks on each end!
I can't get enough of this!
I'm gonna lose against cocks!
I can't do this! Any more of this and I'll...