Wh-What?
What are you planning on doing to me?!
O-Ow!
That hurts!
I said that hurts!
Y-You're gonna rip it off!
You're gonna rip it off!
Please, stop!
Are you giving me orders?
You're gonna need a stronger purification.
You're kidding.
I'm sorry!
Please don't hurt me!
No!
No! Stop!
Domesticated Girlfriend
The Chains of an Angel
Thank god...
Now masturbate.
Okay...
You know what will happen
if you don't want to be purified, right?
Do you know what will happen if you don't?
I-I'll do it!
I'll do it for real now!
What's he doing white watching me?
Oh god, that's disgusting.
Why?
My right hand isn't stopping.
I-I'm already so wet, I...!
I'm gonna cum!
Good, you can stop that now. That is, if you can.
Why? Why can't I stop?
My right hand won't listen to me.
D-Does this mean that I enjoy this situation?
I'm getting off from this?
That can't... That can't be...
There's no way!
No! I can't stop! I can't stop!
My hands have a mind of their own!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
This is a purification drink created within my body.
I've been making it for a while.
Why? Why did I get turned on from that?
Am I going crazy?
This is cum, right?
He wants me to drink this?!
Shibata-san, will you still love me after all this?
You know what to do with that, don't you?
Purification failed.
MIRANO
NEWS
College Female Missing
She's not a girl who would just
skip work without saying anything.
I think she's been involved in some kind of incident!
Please, you need to save her now!
I'll do anything to make that happen!
That has nothing to do with you!
Keep your hands moving!
O-Okay.
Now that I think about it,
MIRANO
NEWS
College Female Missing
there was a very suspicious customer wearing
a hat who came into the store about a month ago.
He...
It's a little past its expiration date,
but that shouldn't have any effect on its purification strength.
Wh-Why are you putting that in my butthole?
It's not all gonna fit!
P-Please stop!
I can feel it starting to come back out!
You're kidding, right?!
There's no way!
That's not gonna happen!
There's no way that's going inside!
японская альтернативная реальность...
N-No! Stop!
Please!
Here.
Have a taste.
Here's the finishing touches.
This is a purification meal to return
you to the angel that you once were.
Eat it.
Eat it!
Okay.
It's so tasty.
So tasty.
This. This is so tasty, Sou-chan.
Eat all of it.
But... but...
But, you know, I think something's missing.
Something's missing.
Sou-chan, do you know what's missing?
Think about that yourself.
Hm...
Oh, I know!
Here we go.
This is what was missing!
Dressing!
Yeah, this is it!
I need the tasty milk that comes out of this dick.
Smooch. Smooch. Smooch.
So you've finally come to get it by your own will, huh?
Hurry up and let it out!
I want to drink it!
I wanna drink it!
Hurry up! Let me drink it!
Hurry! Hurry and let it out already!
Let it out!
Good girl.
Ow!
Sou-chan, what are you doing?
Ow! Ow!
Let me go.
Your spirit is too white right now.
You need some red inside you.
You're right. I want some red too.
This is my first time, but I'm giving it to you, okay?
Let's make some beautiful ketchup.
Sou-chan, here I go.
It's so tight!
It hurts, but I feel weird.
It hurts, but it feels good!
Yummy.
Sou-chan, is there still a demon inside of me?
Is there still a demon inside of me?
Good! So good!
It feels so good when you move!
It's moving so much inside me!
Good! So good! It feels so good!
It feels good! It feels too good!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Okay!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
So good...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч