Sou-chan? Is there still a demon inside of me?
Is there still a demon?
Good! Good! So good!
It feels so good when you move!
You're rubbing against my insides!
Good! Good! So good!
It feels so good.
It feels too good!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
Yes!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
The Chains of an Angel.
More! More!
Expel the demon from within yourself!
Take off your top.
Use it to wipe the floor.
Okay!
Heave ho.
Is this good? I got all of it!
Look up here and open your mouth.
I'm returning this purified substance back into your body.
Drink every last drop!
Lick what you spilled on the floor with your tongue.
You can have my dick later.
Okay.
We're here with some comments from the missing
girl's boss at the convenience store she worked at.
Female College
Student Missing
MIRANO
NEWS
How the hell has a month already passed
and there hasn't been any progress?!
If you have the luxury to interview me,
then find the guy with the red hat!
He's behind this!
The authorities have reviewed surveillance
footage from this store
and have begun looking into the man with the red hat,
– Sou-chan?
– looking into his whereabouts as well as
his connection to the missing girl...
– I feel weird.
– looking into his whereabouts as well as
his connection to the missing girl...
– My body feels so hot.
– looking into his whereabouts as well as
his connection to the missing girl...
– It's so hot...
– looking into his whereabouts as well as
his connection to the missing girl...
– It's so hot...
That feels good.
Rub it more.
That feels good!
That's tight.
Hey now I can't do what I wanted to do next!
Sou-chan?
That's not going to work.
You spread my pussy out too much.
It's still throbbing from you doing that.
It's coming! It's coming out!
It's so hot! It's so hot!!
Sou-chan... I love you.
Don't worry, mommy's going to give birth to you soon.
I was able to exorcise the demon from within her,
but now she's turned into some kind of monster.
I'm gonna buy some smokes.
What should we do while we wait?
Oh, this might be fun.
Let's take a picture.
Huh?
I'm sorry. I swear, I wasn't playing
around. I was dating her for real.
But my parents caused a traffic
accident and I needed money.
So I thought that maybe if I used these videos that
I secretly filmed, I could make some money.
It was an idea I got from Nac-chan.
But I ended up finding a job, so I ended up not
having to use it and end up hurting her.
I'll give it to you.
You can use it however you want.
So, please?
What's that?
The demon has been broken!
Everyone! Watch me!
This never gets old.
Oh my god.
That's hilarious.
No way! No way!
Natsuko
Natsuko... Natsuko?
Oh that loli with the big tits from the
convenience store that I flirted with.
Oh man, this brings back memories!
Okay, today I'll be using you.
And now on to our next story.
Around four o'clock on the sixth at
an apartment complex in A-1 City,
a completely naked woman jumped off the top
of a building, fatally injuring a man below.
A1C NEWS
The woman in question was a woman in her
twenties who lived in the neighboring city
and had been missing since last year.
She died immediately.
The other person involved in this incident
was a resident of the apartment complex,
– an unemployed man in his thirties. He's currently unconscious.
– Natsuko?! Wait that guy too?!
A1C
NEWS
The Convenience Store the Girl Worked At
After careful examination, it was determined that the
woman was pregnant and that the baby perished in the fall.
You're kidding.
On the phone that was clutching were various
videos that might link to other cases.
The authorities intend to investigate
both of these cases simultaneously.
Who is it?
Good evening. Is this the residence of a Mr. Shibata?
I'm with the police.
Would you mind sparing a moment of your time?
Welcome.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч