This is embarrassing...
Please forgive me...
Lift your skirt.
Spread your legs.
Wew! I worked hard today!
If I have this much food, I shouldn't have
to buy anything for at least three days.
It's Shibata-san's birthday next month,
so I need to make sure I don't spend so much!
I'll do my best to save up.
Domesticated Girlfriend
The Chains Of An Angel
Her name is Oominato Natsuko.
You might not be able to tell just from looking,
but she's actually in her twenties.
Thank you for your purchase.
She always has a smile on her face.
Be careful, okay?
She's always considerate,
and caring of the people around her.
Owie.
She's a bit clumsy, but...
Because of all that, everybody loves her.
The food she's carrying right now...
Is actually what the manager of
her workplace was going to throw out.
She usually walks home with her boyfriend,
Shibata, but she's alone today.
Why? Her boyfriend isn't feeling well, apparently.
Help me! Somebody help me!
Help me, Shibata-san! Help me!
Ow...
No! No!
Sh-Shibata-san, help me!
Help me!
N-No, you don't understand...
Shibata... secretly took pictures of you...
No! Stop! Please, leave me alone!
Are these... Did he...?
How does he know what I like?
Hell no, man. She's really uptight 'cuz she's still a virgin.
Yeah, yeah, but hey, how much are you gonna pay for them?
Welcome!
No, I didn't...
I didn't see anything! I promise!
No...
Just who is that guy?
Why did he kidnap me?
That aside...
I'm in a room with no natural light.
How many days has it been since he kidnapped me?
No SIM card detected
Shibata-san...
Please, come and save me, Shibata-san.
Shibata-san!
Wait, is this guy...
He came to the store all the time.
His name was...
What are you saying? You'll still be cute,
even if you put on a little weight!
Please, if I eat any more than this, it'll be a problem!
See? My stomach's already like this!
Oh, yeah! It's your birthday next month, right?
I'll see if I can get you a present, like sweets or something!
Really? There's actually something
I've really liked eating recently.
Have you heard of A1C's cream puffs?
There's a shop that sells them,
the cream is just so fluffy, and the filling is...
I apologize for that.
Thanks for coming here all the time!
Oh yeah, I need to check our inventory.
You're here to pick up a package, right?
Do you have anything that I can use
to check your name and address?
Uh, yeah, my health insurance.
Here you go.
You are Wakasa Souji, am I correct?
Y-Yeah...
Wakasa Souji?
No!
Why are you... trying to run away from me?
Please, I beg you. Let me call Shibata-san.
He must be worried sick about me!
You're Wakasa Souji, right?
If you could let me speak to Shibata-san,
I'd be able to prevent a police search.
Even if they're already looking for me,
I promise I won't say a word about you!
Please, I beg you!
Let me hear Shibata-san's voice.
Thank you.
I found a cute girl at the convenience store.
Yeah, the one we go to all the time.
Yep, and I made her my girlfriend,
which makes eight. These girls are so easy.
This girl looks like a middle schooler,
but her tits are pretty damn big.
She's practically begging somebody to fuck her.
I went to see her at work and asked if
I could have a pizza, and she turned red!
Isn't that so fucking cute?
I'm going to make her mine this week.
Ah, yeah. I kinda need money this month.
How about I sell you something nice?
Please, God, let this call connect!
Hello, is this the police?
I've been kidnapped, and am being
held against my will somewhere.
The culprit is a middle aged man, named Wakasa Souji.
Please, hurry and save me!
I'm calling from my boyfriends phone.
Please use it for GPS, and save me!
Hello? Hello? Can you hear me?
He's gonna kill me! Please hurry!
You were my angel.
How could you lie to me like that?!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
encoder: bakaproxy
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч