Domesticated Girlfriend
The Binding of an Angel
I found a cute girl at the convenience store.
Yeah, the one we go to all the time.
Yep, and I just made her my girlfriend.
That makes eight. Seriously, these girls are so easy.
She looks like she's in middle school, but her tits are huge.
It's like she's begging for someone to fuck her.
After I said "I'm lost, could you help me
find the G-spot?" She turned red!
That's so fucking cute, right?
I'm going to seal the deal with her this week.
I kinda need money this month.
How about I sell you something nice?
Please, God, let this call connect.
Hello, is this the police?
I've been kidnapped, and I'm being
held against my will somewhere.
The culprit is a middle aged man, named Wakasa Souji.
Please, please hurry and save me!
I'm using my boyfriend's phone.
Please use the GPS to locate me. Hurry!
Hello? Hello? Can you hear me?
He's gonna kill me! Please hurry!
You were my angel.
How could you lie to me like that?!
It's because she spent all that time with that demon.
It's all because of that demon,
that my angel was defiled and tainted!
It's fine. I still have time to purify her.
I can purify her.
I can expel the demon from within her. It'll be fine.
It'll be fine!
She can be saved. There's... Still time...
Shibata-san... Save me!
I'm going to expel the demons from within you.
I'm going to purify you.
Wear this.
You want me... to wear that?
Wh...
Why?! Why did you betray me?!
Why did you betray me?!
Why did you betray me?! Why did you betray me?!
You think I betrayed you? What did I do to you?
You beat me with a bat and are holding me prisoner!
Why wouldn't I call the police?!
Why do you trample all over my feelings, after I saved you?!
You're not even making any sense.
When did you ever save me?
That doesn't matter. Let me see Shibata-san!
Let me see him! Let me see Shibata-san!
Why?! Why don't you understand?!
I saved you! I saved you!
I saved you from him!
Purify the demon... Purify the demon!
By my hands...
This is embarrassing...
Please, forgive me.
Lift your skirt.
Spread your legs.
Okay.
I'll kill you.
No!
Wh-What?
Your pussy is wide open.
I'm going to expel the demon within you!
First, you're gonna get ready to be purified by yourself.
H-How am I supposed to do that?
Do it harder!
You're already starting to be purified.
I'll take the impure discharge from your body.
Shoot the impurities into my mouth.
Wh-What?
Please don't make me do this.
It's bad enough I have to spread my legs,
any more and I'll die from embarrassment!
I can't do any more than this!
Wait, does this mean that you hurt Shibata-san too?
Even in this situation,
it doesn't seem like you understand anything.
I... understand. Please, just don't hurt Shibata-san.
Please, stop already!
No!
Put your hands on the toilet and shove your ass this way.
B-But...
This isn't over yet?!
Shibata-san, forgive me. There's no other way!
W-Wait, that's...
Not there!
You're kidding!
Take it out! It hurts! It hurts!
You're gonna rip it! You're gonna rip it!
It's gonna... It's gonna...
No, stop! Take it out!
No, don't! Stop moving!
No! No!
Please...
I can't take it anymore! Please, stop!
Any more and I'll...
I'll break!
I'll inject my holy water directly into you!
Rejoice!
No!
No! No!
It's... It's going into me...
It's still not enough!
I can do more! More!
I'm going to purify her even further...
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupersent
typesetting: hyakupersent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч