Sitting diagonallyin front of me,
is Shiiba-san.
She's quiet and mysterious.
She's type of girl that'd make you think someone
like me would have no chance of talking to.
But I know...
The other side of Shiiba-san.
Sensei, allow me to pick up the eraser I dropped.
Oh, ok.
Close...
It's the first time I've looked at Shiiba-san
at such a close distance.
After school. The empty classroom
at the end of the hallway.
Meet me there.
The Other Side of Shiiba-san with Sister Lip.
Presented by Erobeat | http:/www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Why?
Could it be... she found out that I was peeking?
Do you have a girlfriend?
No... I don't...
Oh. Then what about someone you like?
No.
I see. That's good to hear.
Can I get you to do it with me?
Do what?
Sex.
What is going on? Am I daydreaming?
Did I go crazy from daydreaming too much?
Wait, wait a moment...
You're not going to blackmail me for money
or tell the whole class and make fun of me?
I won't do that...
I left a kiss-mark on you.
I'm taking off your pant, alright?
Wow... it's standing straight up.
It's a little different from what I’m used to...
So you can pull this back... interesting.
It's really sensitive between the foreskin and the tip...
The stimulation is way too strong...
Shiiba-san...
Don't grab. Hands behind your head.
Sh-Shiiba-san... don't... please be less rough...
I can't... I'm cumming! Cummingi
You want to cum, right?
You see, I want you to cum inside.
Inside?
Yeah. So, lie down.
Is this your first time?
Y-Yes.
I'll be taking your virginity then.
It looks like it's going to explode already.
Sorry...
It's fine. It's your first time putting it in, and you
were already at your limit from my mouth earlier.
It can't be helped.
But, I came just like that...
I...
Don't worry, I’m on the pill.
Oh, right... she let that guy cum inside as well.
Ah, you're still hard.
Does that mean... l can cum inside as much as I want?
So... so much is flowing out...
Hey...
It's fine... if you touch them...
You're getting even larger than before!
Why is this happening... and many other
questions should have been asked.
But I stopped caring about that
Not... my nipples...
Shiiba-san who I had no chance of reaching...
Is doing this with me...
Amazing, It's... twitching inside...
Cum whenever you want!
It's not like, I had a crush on her or anything.
I never even thought I'd get close to such a strange girl.
Um, um, we can still do this, right?
This isn't the last time, is it?
I won't tell anyone.
Good bye.
I guess... I'll see you around.
Like being poisoned, I was completely
absorbed by Shiiba-san.
The Other Side of Shiiba-san.
Will you introduce me to your
younger sister Miku already?
Maybe next time.
Hey!
I have a cute step-sister that everyone is jealous of.
To be honest, there are times when
I want to lay hands on her, too!
But she is... my sister...
What? It's from my room!
I remember this...
It's so hard...
Give me your sperm! Fill my mouth up!
Spray lots on my face!
Miku!
Step Sister
Ah, geez. Don't just come into my room and look at stuff.
I came to ask you to return the DVD I lent you before,
and when I was searching for it...
a lot of perverted stuff came out...
And I thought "oh, so Onii-chan looks at stuff
like this, too", and couldn't help but...
I get it, I get it Geez, I guess that can't be helped.
Don't tell mom or anything, ok?
So does Onii-chan... like that kind of stuff?
Huh?
Um... with the mouth...
That's not important!
I... couldn't take my eyes off the DVD and...
Before I realized, I had lots of drool in my mouth...
What are you saying...
I'd want to try it...
Sister Lip
H-Hey, hey, wait!
If Onii-chan likes that kind of stuff, then I...
What? Did she turn on some weird switch
from her first time watching an AV?
Even if we're doing it, I should shower!
This is bad... I got really, really excited.
True, Miku is cute, but... she my sister! My sister!
Onii-chan?
I took my clothes off in the room already.
You... don't just come in like that!
Amazing... it can really get this big...
Hey...
It's hot, and hard...
Oh, some fluid is coming out of the tip.
Can I lick Onii-chan’s penis?
This is bad... it’s really exciting...
Miku is so cute...
Threre, that's...
Mi Miku!
Ah, Onii-chan's penis is so hot!
It's pulsing inside my mouth...
I can't breathe...
It's painful... but my heart's beating so fast...
Mi-Miku... it's just too much excitement...
I'm going to cum...
I'm... Cumming!
That was incredibly good...
I just covered my cute sister with semen...
Onii-chan... amazing... so you can cum this much...
Let's shower together.
Uh, um...
I'll pass on the shower!
Hey Onii-chan! Put on clothes before you come out!
Huh? Wasn't it Miku who went it?
Geez, Onii-chan...
Come on... first thing in the morning!?
Well, Onii-chan always takes care of
it on his own every morning, right?
From today on, I'll do it for you.
Mi-Miku...
This is amazing...
Her tongue is rubbing on the back side...
and her soft lips are sucking hard!
I remembered... the taste of Onii-chan's
penis... and couldn't hold back and...
Onii-chan's penis is twitching again.
Let it out whenever you want
You're... really good at this...
After what happened yesterday, I went and
studied a lot of stuff from the internet.
Everyone was doing it with really perverted girls,
and they looked like they felt really good.
So I thought I wanted Onii-chan to feel real good, too.
This time, I want Onii-chan to spray
your sperm down my throat.
The tip is squeezed and rubbing with her throat...
Just a little... just a little deeper...
I think I'm getting addicted to Miku!
My who dick is inside Miku's mouth...
and wet from her drool...
Miku's mouth-pussy is really too erotic!
I... I'm gonna cum! Cumming!
W-Wait..
Drink it all...
That was great.
That's great to hear.
It's kinda bad to do this between siblings, but...
I guess it's fine if it's just fellatio.
Just think of it as like, masturbating.
Onii-chan's an... idiot!
Owwl
Sister Lip.
One day after school, I saw Shiiba-san on the streets.
She was with a man in his thirties.
A completely different expression, as if she
was different from the girl at school.
So different, I actually thought it was another person.
It was shocking, of course.
But moreover, my sense of superiority
of knowing her secret heightened.
Wanting to know more of the unknown Shiiba-san,
I followed them.
Where we ended up, was probably Shiiba-san's house.
I relaxed. They were merely a close father and daughter.
Dad...
Hey... wait until we go into the house...
Sorry, Dad, I just can't hold back.
Oh my, such a troublesome child.
Huh? You're soaked already.
Dad... the curtains are open...
It's fine. No one is watching.
I didn't have the choice of just leaving like that.
I wanted to see Shiiba-san's secret.
Shiiba-san's father was teasing her between
her legs however he wanted.
I expected it after see what they
did in front of the house,
but it’s actually happening in front of me...
Wow, your clitoris is hard before I even touch it.
Dad... not so many of my weak spots at once!
This is Shiiba-san's true self.
No... I'll cum right away!
No!
Shouko cums way too fast.
Try waiting until Dad says 'okay'.
Eh? No fair!
No! I can't!
Trying not to cum just makes it easier to cum!
No, I'm cummingi
I'm sorry...
Cumming, cumming...
Cumming! Cumming! Cumming!
Come to think of it, I haven't heard
much of Shiiba-san's voice.
The somewhat spoiled, crying voice, she moaned sweetly.
Shouko, make Dad cum, too.
Wow... your penis is so hard and big...
Fluid is already flowing from the tip of Dad's penis...
Dad’s is so big, you'll stretch my mouth!
Shouko, how slutty of you to touch yourself.
Dad... I'm at my limit... I...
I've only seen such scenes, in AVs before...
Inside Shiiba-san beautiful lips...
Forcing it in, and stirring up inside...
Shouko, I... I'm cummingl
So much, that even from here I could see,
the love juices dripping out.
Shiiba-san's been taught the taste of her father's semem,
so much that she can't get like this
from him cumming in her mouth.
Dad... put it in the mouth down here, too...
I can't hold back anymore...
Thrust me with Dad's lewd stick!
Shouko, you're making slutty noises.
Dad, you're so mean...
Be sure to enjoy it well...
So big...
It's inside!
It's hitting my womb and pushing up...
Shiiba-san is pretty and popular amongst the guys,
but everyone thought they had no chance at her.
No one dared to confessed, but only used her for fapping.
I, too...
As I try to burn the image of her right
now into my brain, I masturbated.
My womb is cumming again and again!
I know. It's been convulsing for a while now.
Shouko is a good girl, so I'll love your womb lots.
As if trying to show me, it's completely exposed.
Don't... Don't!
If you tease them all at once... I... I'll cum again!
Inside my womb! Dad's semen...
This has been going on for several days,
and I'm completely into it.
Shiiba-san... Shiiba-san I'm going to...
Your penis is twitching... you're about to cum, right?
Inside.,. I'll cum inside!
Amazing... so much... it's overflowing...
Shiiba-san... it’s about time I ask...
Huh?
Why did you ask to have sex with me?
I started have just the slightest expectations.
That Shiiba-san had special feelings for me.
I asked her, with no real readiness for what was coming.
Of everyone in class... you are
alone more often than anyone.
I thought you'd keep it quiet for me.
It wasn't unexpected.
That's all you chose me for?
That was great, wasn't it?
Thanks to living without standing out,
I became sex friends with such a beauty...
If you're just plain rough, it won't feel good...
Why am I so upset about it?
No, wait... not so sudden...
Like I thought, your womb is a weak spot.
Like you thought?
Not there... don't... I’ll cum! I'll cum!
Deep inside... I'll cum!
I'm losing my strength... please!
You're convulsing inside!
Are you cumming again, Shiiba-san?
I'll make you cum with your womb!
I'm letting it out. Cum, Shiiba-san!
Cum while you take my sperm with your womb!
Cumming, cumming!
Damn. Why are tears...
Why does that smile while she's with him... piss me off?
Are you okay?
Why... are tears...
Oh, I see.
I know. You wanted to become the special person for me.
Am I wrong?
Um... I...
I see. I did bad things, didn't I...
There, there...
I... fell in love with Shiiba-san.
By the way, what was your name again?