hanime.tv
Presents
You filthy creatures…
I will not forgive those who would
dare harm Ushiwaka.
Crap… Ushiwaka they're coming towards you.
I'm…
going to fight as well.
We've been chased all this time, even though
we're so far away from the capital.
Are you tired?
Looking from the sky,
I saw a post station that we'll reach soon.
Let's take a break there.
Welcome, welcome!
We have a bunch of goods brought
over from the capital!
Hey you, take a look!
Ooh, you guys even have books.
You can read?
Kinda.
This is "The Tale of Genji" that's
popular in the capital.
What a big post station.
With this many eyes,
they won't come even if they're still on us.
Shaga?
We should still be cautious.
We want to avoid being seen.
Let's keep moving and find an inn.
Okay.
(Random preachings)
A female dancer from the capital has come today.
Apparently she's from the capital.
Who would have thought such a pretty girl would
come to a country side post station like this.
This place isn't that removed.
I don't consider here the country side.
But…
It would appear that the remnants
of the Genji clan have taken refuge here.
How scary.
Remants of the Genji clan?
What's that?
Oh, you aren't aware?
Tell us more.
Not on the stage.
Come back over here.
Alright, let's stay here.
Here?
Excuse me!
Yes, here I am.
We want to get a room here.
Here is the head of the Genji clan,
and Yoshitomo's child, Ushiwaka…
Shaga…! You just revealed my identi…
Don't worry.
Your mother introduced this inn to me.
My mother…?
I see.
Son of a noble, the truth is I am
affiliated with the Genji clan.
This is my life right now, but I am very happy
to have the chance to be of your service.
Please rest and relax to your heart's content.
I will return this favor one day…
Don't think too much of it.
You'll let us do you…?
Yes.
Hold on a second.
Let s let him have first dibs.
I see, Sasuke huh.
He has no relatives in addition to being wimpy.
He still has no experience.
It's okay.
Eh?
Today will be the momentous
day you have your first time.
I'm very happy.
Come on, let's have fun.
I, I'll finally get to…
So big…
Heheh. You get to fuck such a nice bitch
your first time. You're lucky as hell.
Woah… Your nipples are erect…
You want to taste them too, don't you?
Ye-yes…
Oh my… it looks so congested. It must hurt.
Just kidding. I know that you're going
to shoot out a bunch from this.
So, where do you want to shoot it at?
Let… let me shoot it all out into you.
Very well…
Are you ready? Here it is.
That's right. Now move your
hips forward just like this.
It's so hot…
I'm going to break if you go so hard…
Sorry… but it feels so good
that my hips won't stop moving.
It's alright… I'm so happy that
you're trying so hard…
I'm… My name is Sasuke.
My name is Houzuki…
Houzuki… Houzuki, your insides feel so good.
You're very good too…
So good…
They way you move your hips is so good.
I feel more and more of you.
I can feel you wanting to let it all out inside me.
Houzuki… Houzuki… I'm going to…
So much hot stuff…
You let out so much hot stuff inside me…
Sasuke, you're a very fine man.
Sasuke, this time I'll do all the work.
How does it feel to have your mushroom
grinded on by my cunt?
Ahh… I can't think of anything…
It feels like heaven…
You're so honest…
Sasuke… It's ok to just let it out again.
Wait… I just came. It's too sensitive…
Are you sure? Your penis is saying
it wants to let out more.
It's twitching so much inside me too.
Tha-that's…
Holding yourself back is no good.
Cum until your penis goes limp and shrinks…
I'm, I'm…
You look like you're in agony.
Sorry for being so rough your first time…
I can be rough as well…
What are you…
Ah… you're being so rough.
I'm going to break at this rate…
Look at you go.
This guy is at the very least good at using his hips.
This isn't good…
Every time you thrust my pussy throbs…
I can't hold it in anymore…
I'm going to cum…
Houzuki…
Ah, so good.
Sasuke, I'm going to cum if you
keep going at this rate…
Houzuki… Me too…
Let's cum together…
Together, let's cum together…
Sasuke, I can't anymore…
If you go anymore…
Houzuki… become my woman.
I have become your woman already.
Houzuki… Houzuki…
Sasuke…
You don't have to be delirious.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're right Houzuki. I'm so happy right now…
Hot… so hot…
So much of your hot stuff…
You did well.
There, there. You're a very fine man.
Your amazing penis is pulling out…
It won't stop overflowing…
Next up is me!
No, me!
You guys must have so much saved up.
It's because we won't have another chance
to fuck such a nice bitch from the capital.
What's with this pussy…?
I've never felt something like this…
This suction… It feels like she's
going to suck everything out…
Geez… going after my nipples so much…
You must love breasts a lot.
No…! Let me rest.
If I keep cumming so much consecutively, I'm
going to be unable to go back to normal.
I'm going to take you to a place
you can't return from.
So keep feeling good as much as you want.
I… I'm cumming…
Agh… This is too good. Her entire pussy is
throbbing and clinging onto me so much…
I-I'm going to cum…
Me too…
I'm almost at my limit too…
Please, let's cum together…
I'm cumming…
Heheheh…
Look at the cum on your breasts flying off.
What a slut…
She might be a goddess that has
come to take us to paradise…
Bunch of monkeys…
How simple can human males be…
Now that I think about it…
I haven't had a human's cum in a while now.
Come on, you monkeys…
Huh?
Come on. What are you doing?
Hurry up and give me your cum.
Hey, don't stand there.
Hurry up and come warm yourself up inside me.
This hole is too good…
You filthy human…
You think you can do as you please with my body…
Get away from Houzuki.
Houzuki is my woman!
Houzuki, you're the best. You're the best!
Got it. I got it, tha-that's enough…
Houzuki, I'm cumming…
I'm going to cum inside you right now.
Stop talking so much you damn monkey…
A filthy creature such as yourself
has no right to cum inside me…
Houzuki… take in all my cum.
My stomach is so full…
On my face…!
Stop, you bastard!
It's fucking disgusting!
Houzuki's face is stained with my cum…
Die!
This goddamn insect.
I don't need this one.
You can eat him.
Understood.
Listen here, if you find the survivor of the Genji,
make sure to report it to me instantly!
Leave it to us!
Got it!
We're going to tear those guys apart
limb for limb for the sake of that person.
I see…
You were pursued by that much huh.
Yes.
That's right.
Why not go out with a different
appearance from yesterday's?
A disguise?
Rather than calling it a disguise,
right now is the season to change anyways.
Why not cut your hair, put on a cap,
and perform a coming of age ceremony?
Coming of age, huh.
Hello.
Another pursuer!?
Hello, you over there.
Do me a favor.
I want you to deliver a letter to that
lady in the detached room.
Eh?
Yeah her. Thank you.
Okay…
I've sent her a song several times, but she
won't respond to my messages at all.
Doesn't that mean she's not interested in you…
Nope. There's definitely something there.
I can tell.
But, you haven't even met her once right?
For a kid who hasn't come of age
yet, you probably can't tell…
Wait a second…
Even kids have a girl that they like, right?
You should be able to tell if she
has any feelings for you or not.
A girl that I like…
N-no…
Either way, here you go…
Can you go and get me a response?
I'm begging you.
You're a child so it's fine if you enter her room.
I don't feel anyone's presence inside.
Looks like something big…
She has a wound on her neck…
That's…
Hello…
Sorry.
Did you see?
What is it?
It had horns and looked like a cow.
Ushiwaka…
This is very embarrassing, but…
that monster is my daughter…
What…?
A cow-like appearance with horns…
Isn't that a half-human half-cow?
I beg of you to keep it a secret
what's living in that detached house.
Are you aware of the graveyard,
not far from this post station?
A half-human half-cow was born in the past
before, and the town was ravaged by a famine.
Are they a monster that brings about famine?
No. They have visions.
Most of their prophecies involve the coming of
devastating disaster such as famine or floods.
And their prophecies are said to be definite.
That's right.
And because of this, they are killed
the moment they are born.
But what parent in the world
can do in their own child.
I cut her throat so that she
couldn't make prophecies.
And raised her in secret.
Writing prophecies is also bad,
so she's forbidden to write anything.
Forbidden to write…
So, that's why…
Beyond her appearance and shape,
she's treated as if she doesn't exist at all.
She's a pitiful girl
that is doomed to hate the world
as her heart grows cold.
She has no chance of finding love
and living a happy, ordinary life.
How'd it go?
Um… there is no one in that detached house.
Wait, there's no way.
I'm sure there's a girl living there.
Hey, you.
If you've only come here recently,
the owner of this place has no daughter.
The reason why is…
That's not true. I received a folding
fan back from her once.
I had someone who was in contact with her.
Look.
Here it is.
There's some red mark…
Is it lipstick?
If this was her response, it makes sense
that you would think she's into you.
This isn't all I have.
She sent this mugwort on top
of the fan back together.
Do you know what that symbolizes?
A girl that is like a red flower that lives in an
neglected mansion, where mugwort grows thickly.
Imitating the character Suetsumuhana that
appears in the story, she is saying that she is ugly.
The Tale of Genji, Chapter 6.
Well?
There is no other female in this countryside
town with such charm as her.
I just sent her the song that was written to show
Genii's determination to meet
with Suetsumuhana.
If you really won't be surprised
no matter what she looks like,
I'll leave the back door open at night.
Is that supposed to mean it's fine for me to go in?
Woah. She's huge…
Horns…
Is it ok if go near you?
You're fine with it, right?
Answer me please.
Your throat…
Is that why you can't answer me?
But isn't it starting to heal already.
Let out your voice more.
I want your hot stuff…
I'm at my limit…
I can't anymore. It feels too good…
Kurenai…
You sounded like a beast.
Make that the both of us.
Thank you.
Thank you. It felt like heaven.
Whether you're a human or monster,
everyone in the end just wants
to be with the one they love.
We can't?
Is it because I'm a kid?
Do I have to come of age first?
Owner! Owner!
What's the ruckus about?
Owner, explain what's going on.
You left that monster alive!
That dreadful prophecy monster!
You were supposed to kill it!
You were harboring it!?
What's going on?
Wa-wait please!
It's that detached house. It should be there!
Over here!
Who the hell are you guys!
You filthy creature!
There it is!
Take her out!
The horns of a cow…
It's a half-human half-cow!
Strike it!
Kill it!
I won't let you!
Shaga, you cant!
They're just regular humans.
It's glowing…
A lance…?
Humans…?
They're doing something that makes
them even more wretched than monsters.
Go after the monster first!
Shaga!
It's not that they make frightful prophecies.
It's because you guys
do terrible things to them that they curse you!
That kid…
Isn't he the kid that the dancer was talking about?
The remnant of the Genji clan and that monster!
Don't leave them alive either!
Throw stones to kill them!
Ushiwaka…
You damn monster…
Wait!
You're in the way!
Kurenai…
Y-yo-you bastards…!
You bastards…
She spoke!
She's going to make a prophecy!
This town…!
Kurenai…
I'm going to destroy… this town…
Calm down…
I'll protect you.
You're going to live with me in happiness.
I…
am going to…
live with you in happiness…
I'm going to live with you in happiness…
Everyone! That's the prophecy this time.
She's going to live happily with this man.
Leave them be!
Ge-get out of here!
That's right! Hurry up and get the fuck out!
Get out of our sights!
So selfish…
We're going to leave this town.
Are you sure?
We'll be able to live happily anywhere.
Her prophecies all come true you know.
See you later.
Next up. You guys have to leave as well.
You are the remnant of the Genji clan and wanted.
We don't need any thing that could start trouble.
We just want to live in peace.
And that pretty much sums up my childhood.
Let me down here.
It s starting to get foggy.
I'm sure that the two of them will live very happily.
Shaga?
Shaga!
Humans are even scarier than monsters.
Those two will most likely never live
in a place with other people.
Unlike that man,
you're the son of a noble who will
rise to fame and lead people.
I can't be by your side…
Shaga, I'm going to perform my
coming of age ceremony.
You're going to protect me from monsters right?
In that case I…
I'm going to protect you from
other humans as a man.
Shaga…
Come with me.
Ushiwaka…
Hey, we're back.
Can we come in?
Such an impatient person.
About that Genji clan mate.
He left this town.
No need to worry anymore.
Well now.
Did I not tell you to report
to me if you found them?
They got away…
That's right…
It was easy to get close to Kiyomori and kill him.
But there is a large crow monster
that is with Ushiwaka.
A monster?
What do they think they're doing?
Those that would try to rule over man.
Those that could become king must be destroyed.
I am the one true existence
that shall rule over people and this world.
A good amount of time has passed
since Shaga traveled to Mount Kurama.
I wonder what she's doing.
This nation…
Oh, Yatagarasu!
Everything that happens
in this nation can be seen by these eyes.
In that case, what's Shaga doing?
Do you know?
Come on.
Yatagarasu always just disappears
when the sun sets.
Then that means the stuff that happens
during the night goes unobserved then.
Might as well go check on them.
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
Encoding: Dorans
QA: Dorans
Visit us at hanime.tv
Softsub: TFloater