Kurama... At the end of the 12th century.
It's been three hundred years...
Shaga of the Dark
It's gotten dark and we're all still separated.
Curses, we shouldn't have climbed the mountain this far.
There are rumors of monsters appearing here too.
Is that water I hear?
It's a dwelling! I'm saved!
Pardon?
Oh my, you're lost? That is quite the ordeal.
I haven't much, but please make yourself at home.
Oh, many thanks.
Do you live this deep on the mountain alone?
Yes, I live here by myself.
However, you must be troubled by food.
Oh no, I am fine in that regard.
Indeed. You do seem to not be lacking in nutrition.
I can't make much in the way of hospitality, but...
If you want to be hospitable, I have an idea!
You knew what was going to happen when you
took me in despite living by yourself, didn't you?
Please, no! Please don't!
Your breasts look so delicious!
How adorable you are! I'll do you well!
I'll take you back to my residence
and make sure you want for nothing!
You mustn't!
Why not? You could live a much better life than you are now.
Why? Because this will be the last time we meet.
A web?! I'm trapped!
The time is now the beginning of the Heian period.
In a certain village in the mountains,
they too were tormented by monsters.
Hiyomari-sama!
You siblings, come here.
I've got both wealth and strength.
I've got everything that would make my fatherland envious.
Everything in this world be it pleasure
or strength is mine, Kiyomori's!
Destroy anything that defies me.
Shaga-nee, are you going to the human realm again?
Oh, Ayame.
If one lives in a forest for three
hundred years, she will become bored.
You sure have interesting tastes.
Huh? Those are the hounds that Heike summoned.
What's going on with him?
Wait, Shaga-nee!
Another monster?
She changed into a human form?
They still seem to be coming.
Where were you trying to go to?
You're from Kuramad Temple are you not?
You need to get back to the temple before dark.
No.
I just saved your life.
I would've been fine without your help.
I can fight.
Hey!
I've no choice. Where do you wish to go? I'll take you there.
Let go of me! I'll get there with my own two feet!
Would you like me to drop you right here?
Then take me to... Ichijo... to my mother.
Mother!
Ushiwaka?
Is that you, Ushiwaka?
Mother!
It has been too long.
Ushiwaka!
Thank you for saving him from such a predicament.
This child's name is Ushiwaka and is the lost son of Genji.
He's constantly under the watch of the
Heike's and his very life is being targeted.
It is very unfortunate.
Ye monk that is named Shaga, I
have a favor that I must ask of you.
Please protect Ushiwaka and take him somewhere safe.
Could you see him to Europe?
Europe?
I beseech you. Take the child somewhere safe...
Mother...
What?! You're leaving the forest?
Indeed. I just couldn't find it in myself to decline.
This is all because you keep meddling in the human realm.
You've already used up one of your weapons. What a waste.
This is not something I can ignore.
Yatagarasu-sama.
Hear me, Shaga.
You may not be aware, but the reason you seek out
interaction with humans is because you desire a new path.
A new... path?
By avoiding others and living alone,
you invite darkness into your heart.
Shaga, my mother may have asked you
to accompany me, but you don't need to.
I can walk the earth by myself.
Not if you get attacked again.
I understand. You must be frightened of my non-human form.
N-No I'm not!
I need to hurry up and become a capable man like
my late father so I can take care of things by myself.
Shall I teach you the way of the sword?
Huh? Really?
Please! Teach me!
Then that means I'm coming with you on your journey.
Very well. I'll allow it.
Thanks to the medicine you've given
me, I am more virile than ever.
Oh dear, Kiyomori-sama, your penis is so splendid
that Yorhime cannot seem to get enough of it.
She's very tame, but this is good in its own way.
Oh, what a shame.
Please lick under the tip as well, Yorihime.
Yes.
Very good. And now stick your tongue inside.
This is quite amazing.
Alright, now raise your face.
Kiyomoro-sama...
You are quite the beauty.
And you're all mine.
Kiyomori-sama is taking you seriously.
You must do well to please him, Yorihime.
So cute.
How cute you are.
I'll let you have a good serving of me.
Are you satisfied?
Don't be foolish. I'm still virile due to the medicine.
In that case, please take your business over here.
Please give this Toyohime your depraved passion right here.
Nee-sama...
It's so perky. It's convulsing.
This is because it is frightened of the beast mounted on you.
Typically whenever I go inside this
devilish hole of yours, I lose myself,
but today, I will be the one to conquer it!
No! Not like this!
Not like this!
So strange. This is the first time I've heard you moan.
No composure at all... This new side of you is so fresh and cute!
Kiyomori-sama! You are reaching somewhere you mustn't!
I see. So I'm ramming on your gate now?
Then I'll...
No... No...
I... I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
We're not done yet!
Toyohime-sama, I...
It is fine. Come here.
Why is this? This is so frightening. So frightening.
Please leave it to us, Kiyomori-sama.
We will give you everything.
Nee-sama! Don't look! Nee... sama...
It is as you say. There is nothing to be frightened of.
I am this country's ruler.
And this is this world's greatest pleasure.
Mother...
Huh? You're gonna pass through that there mountain?
No way. Not happening.
There are rumors of terrible monsters
appearing on that mountain.
Many from this village have yet to return.
Just before, we found a kimono stained with blood
and the saddle from a horse flowing down the river.
Judging by the direction the stuff came from,
there's no doubt that there are monsters there.
We've no choice, Ushiwaka. Let's find another way.
I...
I want to be a great warrior though.
Can I really allow myself to run away?
Ushiwaka? What are you saying?
There are monsters terrorizing
people. If these people are troubled...
Then I'll defeat them!
Uh, the one defeating them would be me...
You there. Are you being serious?
Please! I beg you!
Please, the monsters...
He knows a woman who lives deep in the
mountains and it's got him mighty worried.
Huh? That woman's suspicious.
There's no way there's a safe place
on a mountain full of monsters!
Sh-She's not a monster!
But you have a point.
She never gave me a reason, but she always
tells me not to come on moonless nights.
There are parts of her story that don't add up.
What would you do if that woman is a monster?
Would it be okay to kill her?
Of course it would!
No matter how great the woman, a monster's a no go!
Y-Yeah...
O-Oh, if you're going to get rid of all the monsters,
you should stay the night in the village. We'll prepare a feast.
Oh, yeah!
Let's get ready!
Yeah!
Shaga, the man's running up the mountain.
We don't know what danger awaits. It's too dangerous.
We should go after him.
Why... Why did you come?
I told you to stay away when the moon isn't out.
I... I want to know what you truly look like!
Why are you hiding it from me?
Is it because you don't trust me?
Are you human?! Or are you a monster?!
That's...
I didn't want you of all people to know.
Let's run away.
I don't care what you are!
But there are people coming to kill you!
You... Are you saying that you don't mind me being a monster?
It doesn't matter!
Not at all.
After all, you're so cute.
Uh... Hey, Ushiwaka!!
Stop it. My true form is not cute at all...
They're completely different.
His hands are completely different than
any of the men who've come to me.
I've never felt hands like these before.
They're so hot and large.
They're completely different.
You're already so wet.
It doesn't look like I need to loosen you up.
No! Not there!
That's...
Why aren't you stopping even though I'm cumming?!
It's because it means that you're feeling really good.
It's because I want to see more of this side of you!
That is... That is what I want too!
Please leave it to me.
You know not how much it pleases me
to see you feel pleasure from my body!
Please cum! Please cum! I beg you! Please!
Wait! If I'm gonna cum, I want to do it with you!
No! Not this position! You can see everything like this!
I'll say it as many times... as many times as I must!
I want to see all of you!
I want to know all of you!
No, that's...
This is...
I told you!
I...
I can't face you.
I'm hideous.
You...
I want to love all of you.
That's...
That's my abdomen...
Your manly hand is inside me!
Let us climax together.
Our bodies are joining... they're molding together.
We're becoming one!
No! I'm going to cum! I am cumming! I am cumming!
No!
Ushiwaka!
I'll save you!
Not on my watch!
You idiot! What have you done?!
That man truly loved you!
She's hesitating.
Ushiwaka?!
What a tragic man. To be eaten by the woman he loved...
You think so? I think he was happy.
He was able to know every last part of her in the end.
Yes and she was a repulsive monster.
Don't change back.
I don't think you're repulsive in the least.
Ushiwa...
Even after three hundred years,
I've never thought that the world was this beautiful...
Ushi...
Oh, so you're that tired?
Such is man. Weak.
Even more so since you are but a child.
I will only be accompanying you until we reach Europe as well.
I don't remember half of last night, but...
Was... that real?
Ushiwaka?
Are you awake?
Shaga?
I found some chocolate-vine. Eat it then we'll depart.
Indeed.
Our pursuers may not be too far behind
us. I must deliver you quickly to Europe.
Well then, let us be on our way.
Yeah!
Just until Europe at least...
I'll let myself love this young man.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч