The
beginning
of the
12th
century
Horse
back
It's been 300 years, huh.
Episode 1
Contemplative
stream
Night has fallen since I was separated...
Darn! I shouldn't have gone hunting this deep into the mountains...
There's even rumors that monsters lurk around here...
Sound of water?
Signs of life! I'm saved!
Excuse me.
Oh my, that's why you're become lost? You must be in trouble.
My home's nothing but a shack, but please rest.
Right, thank you.
You're living by yourself this deep in the mountains?
Yes, I live here by myself.
You're not inconvenienced from the lack of foodstuffs?
No, that's not a problem.
I see, she does seem well nourished...
There's not much I can do for hospitality, but...
Hospitality?
If it's hospitality you're offering, then...!
You're asking for it, living by yourself and inviting me in!
P-Please, please do not put it in!
What a delicious looking body!
How cute! Don't worry, I'll treat you good!
I wouldn't mind you living in my mansion!
You can't do that!
Why? You'll be able to live comfortably.
Why not?
That because...
Today's going to be the last time we meet!
What the-?!
I-I'm trapped-!
The time is the Heian period.
During this age, whether it was in the mountains or populated towns,
monsters were running rampant on the land.
Oh my!
Kiyomori-sama...
Both of you, sisters. Come!
Wealth and power...
I'm the envy of the surrounding provinces.
I have all you can imagine!
All this power, isn't it wonderful?
It is all mine.
Crush all that oppose me!
Yes.
Shaga-nee, you're going to get involved with the humans again?
Oh it's you, Ayame.
Things gets boring, living 330 years in the same forest.
I see, you sure like humans.
Those are the Kamuro hounds of the House of Taira.
I wonder what that kid did?
Shaga-nee!
That's a monster...!
She changed to a humanoid form...
More seem to be on their way.
Where were you wanting go?
You're from Kurama Temple, no?
Go back before it gets dark.
I don't want to.
I just saved your life!
It's not like I needed help!
I was able to fight them myself...
Hey!
It can't be helped.
Where did you want to go? I'll carry you.
Let me go! I'll get there with my own two feet!
You want to be dropped off right now?
Then... Ichijou...
I want to go to Ichijou. Mother's place.
Mother!
Ushiwaka... Is it really you, Ushiwaka?
It's been a long time.
Ushiwaka...
Thank you very for saving him from danger.
This boy is Ushiwaka, an orphan.
He's kept under surveillance by the House of Taira
and unless he becomes a monk, the poor boy's life is in danger.
There is something I wish to ask of you, traveling monk Shaga.
Could I ask you to protect Ushiwaka and get him to the safe lands of Ooshu?
Ooshu?
Please.
Take him to safety...
Mother...
What?!
You're going to leave the forest, Shaga-nee?
Yes, I couldn't decline such request easily...
It's because you involved yourself with the humans...
You even used one of your rings; such a waste.
It's not everyday such things happen.
Yatagarasu-sama...
Shaga. You may not be aware why you're interested in human matters,
it is from wishing to find another way of life.
Wishing another way of life...
Help those in need and perform virtuous deeds.
Eventually you'll be granted the benevolence of God.
Shaga. Although Mother insisted, you need not come.
I will walk with my own to feet.
I bet he won't last long if he's attacked again.
I see, I bet my monster form is frightening too.
I'm not scared of that!
I want to become independent as soon as possible,
so I can become a proud man like my deceased Father.
Shall I teach you to use a sword?
What, really?
Please, please teach me!
Does that means I'm coming too?
Hmph, I'll allow it.
Because of your secret medicine, my crotch has...
Oh my, Kiyomori-sama.
It appears that your proud member is too much for Yorihime.
Let it be, she has a certain charm that her elder sister lacks.
Oh really, what a shame.
Yorihime, lick the shaft underneath.
Yes.
That's it, now stick your tongue into the tip.
This is great!
Alright. Next, lift your face.
Kiyomori-sama...
You really are beautiful...
And, you're all mine.
Kiyomori-sama is serious now.
You do your best too, Yorihime.
How cute...
Very cute...
I'll let you drink it soon!
Are you satisfied?
You surely jest! I'm still good to go because of the medicine!
If that's the case,
then please go here next.
Please give your affection to Toyohime, right here.
Nee-sama...
What an obscene display! It's twitching!
This is... It's just nervous about your proud member, Kiyomori-sama.
I'm going to thoroughly punish your obscene hole,
the mouth that'll instantly eat me up as soon as I put it in!
This-! It's too much!
It's too much!
How rare!
It's the first time I hear you scream!
There's no argument, you're definitely cute too!
Kiyomori-sama!
It's reaching to places where it mustn't!
I see, so this is your precious spot!
Take this!
No... No...!
I'm... I'm cumming! I'm gonna...!
So good-!
We're not done yet!
Toyohime-sama, where shall I...?
It's fine, come here.
What is this, it's frightening...
It's truly terrifying...
Leave it up to us, Kiyomori-sama.
We'll grant you everything.
Nee-sama, don't look!
That's right, there's no need to be worried.
I'm the supreme ruler of this country!
There's no need to be frightened; this place is paradise on Earth.
Mother...
What? You're going to cross that mountain right now?
That's impossible!
Rumor says horrifying monsters lurk in those mountains.
Some of us have never returned either!
There's even been blood-soaked clothing and a horse caucus that came down the river recently.
There must be some horrendous monster upstream, big enough to eat whole horses.
It can't be helped, Ushiwaka. Let us detour around the mountain.
I... I want to become a strong warrior. Is it okay for me to run away from this?
Ushiwaka, what are you saying?
If there's a terrifying monster that's troubling people...
I'll defeat it!
Wait, won't I be defeating it then...?
Young man, are you serious?
If it's true, then please...
The monster...!
He's worried about the woman living in the mountains all by herself.
She's the suspicious one!
If there are monsters, it's even more suspicious that she's safe!
S-She can't be...
Although she did say not to visit on cloudy nights without explaining why,
she's a mystery.
What will you do if she was in fact the monster?
Is it alright to kill her?
Of course it is!
Even if she's a nice woman, she's a monster!
Y-Yeah...
How about this?
If you're going to go defeat the monster, perhaps you could rest and enjoy a meal?
Sounds good!
Let's get it ready!
Shaga, that man is climbing the mountain.
It's dangerous for him to go without knowing anything.
Let's follow him.
Why... Why did you come?
I told you not to come on cloudy nights!
I... I want to know of your true self!
Why won't you tell me anything?
Is it because you don't trust me?
Are you a human, or a monster?!
It's something that I do not want anyone to know, especially you.
Hurry, get out of here.
I don't care if you're a monster or not!
There's people coming soon to kill you...
You, what did you just say?
Did you say that you don't care if I'm a monster?
It doesn't matter!
None of that matters...
Because, you're this cute...
Whoa! Um...!
Hey, Ushiwaka!
You mustn't! My true form isn't cute at all!
This is... it's completely different...
Of all the human hands that had reached out to me...
These hands are completely different... There's been none like it!
So big and warm, it's complete different...!
You're soaking wet down here...
Looks like there's no need for foreplay.
Not there, that's...!
Why? Why are you not stopping, even though I'm asking?
It's because I love it when I'm making you feel good.
It's because I want see you feeling good!
That...
That goes for me, too!
Let me show you...
Please understand how happy I am that you're feeling good from my body!
Please cum, cum all you want!
Please, please!
Wait! If I'm gonna cum, then let's both...!
We mustn't! If you do it like that, you'll see everything!
I've said it before...
I've said it countless times!
I want to see your everything...
I want to know everything about you!
That's... That's...!
Is this...?
Didn't I say to stop?!
I-I'm...!
I could never be with you,
being born this way...
You...
I want to love everything about you.
That's, that place is...!
Your burly arm, it's inside my body...!
Please, give it to me!
Our connected bodies...
It's melting, sticking together...
No! I'm cumming! I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming-!
Oh no!
Ushiwaka-!
I'll save you!
Not happening!
You idiot!
What have you done!
You killed the man you love!
The grip...
Ushiwaka!
What an unfortunate man.
Being devoured by the woman he loved.
Do you think so?
Maybe he was happy.
Being able to finally know the truth.
She was an ugly monster.
Don't transform back, yet.
I don't think you're an ugly monster, either.
Ushiwa-
Having lived 300 years...
Who would have thought the world was this beautiful?
Ushi-
Oh my, you must have been tired.
He's a weak, fragile human.
And still a child, at that.
Also, I can only be involved until we arrive in Ooshu.
I can only partially remember last night...
Did that really happen...?
Ushiwaka!
You're awake?
Oh, Shaga...
I found some chocolate vine.
Let's go after eating.
Of course.
We may have pursuers on our hands.
I have to take you to Ooshu with haste.
Okay, lets go.
Alright!
At least till Ooshu...
...I'll take care of him with love.
anatato issho ni sugosu shunkan
Every moment I spend with you
zenbu zenbu
every single one
takara mono da kira kira
it's a treasure, gleaming,
mabushi kute hokano koto ga mienaku nari souda
shining bright, blinding everything else
itsumo watashi no koto
You always can
egao ni suru
make me smile
mahou mitai da onegai
It's like a magic spell, oh please
tokenai de zutto zutto kono mama de itai wa
I wish for it to never end, for it to stay like this forever
Shikkoku no Shaga
hajimete te wo tsunaida ano hi mitai ni
Just like when we first held each others hand
kyou datte dokidoki shiteru no yo
even today, my heart is pounding fast
baka mitai
I'm helpless
warawanai de kono kimochi uso ja naii yo
Please don't laugh, these feelings aren't a lie
anata wo kaori de kanji rareru
This closeness, where I can sense you by your scent
kono kyori ga shiawase
our proximity, it's pure bliss
matadaku hoshi tachi ga
Until the twinkling stars above
yozora o watari oeru toki made
travels across the night sky
daai na ihanashi te
Speak to me
anata no koe
with your voice
watashi dake ni kikasete ite
let me be the only one who can hear it
anatato issho ni sugosu shunkan
Every moment I spend with you
zenbu zenbu
every single one
takara mono da kira kira
it's a treasure, gleaming,
mabushi kute hokano koto ga mienaku nari souda
shining bright, blinding everything else
itsumo watashi no koto
You always can
egao ni suru
make me smile
mahou mitai da onegai
it's like a magic spell, oh please
tokenai de zutto zutto kono mama de itai wa
I wish for it to never end, for it to stay like this forever
A good show deserves a good release, right? Hopefully we were able to do it some justice... - Shikkaku Fansubs
Fansub staff: Tax_Peace