My name is Kenta Fushimi. My folks
were into dubious and dangerous jobs...
...like ocean surveys and expeditions,
so they're already deceased.
I'm already alone.
Vowing to excel in a calmer area...
...I fell in love with a Japanese
painting I saw in a museum.
Resolved to apprentice
for that painter...
...I was prepared to bow to him or
sit in, but he accepted me right away.
Right now, I'm heading
to that painter's home.
I'm sorry...
No, it was my fault.
Don't worry about it.
Fleshdance
Episode 1
Wandering Body
Kyoto
This is the right place, right?
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm the master's
new student, Kenta Fushimi...
Oh, Ken!
Miku?
This brings me back!
You moved away in junior high, right?
You've grown so much!
You too, Miku.
Wait, Ken...
''The master's new student''... You're
doing classic Japanese dance?
Classic Japanese dance?
You can't!
I'm the number one student.
The only student
allowed to stay here is my...
Hold on.
This master's a classic Japanese
dancer, not a Japanese painter?
Oh, you're the master's student.
ls there company, Miku?
Oh, perfect timing.
Ask our housekeeper Momoko
about the rest. I'm in a hurry, so...
I see. So the master's wife is
an expert in classic Japanese dancing.
As opposed to being the mistress,
we've been friends since childhood...
...so when I helped to clean the house
and such, it became a live-in job.
It surprised me when the master,
who travels most of the year...
...said he was taking
a student under him.
And that it was Miku's
childhood friend is another surprise!
When is the master coming back?
Who knows?
Here's your room, Kenta.
Is there something wrong?
No, not really...
Momoko? Momoko!
Oh, Aoi's back.
Momoko, where are you?
Ouch!
A dream?
No, but her lap is my pillow.
I'm so lucky!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes.
I'm glad.
W-Where's Momoko?
Drawing a bath.
The long trip was tiring, right? Plus,
you fell and were covered in dust.
Go take a bath.
Okay.
Wow!
It's like a super-expensive
Japanese inn!
You're in that type of relationship
with Momoko already?
You've gotten aroused
looking at her naked body, huh?
You shouldn't dive into a bath.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
She knew Momoko was in here,
so that's why she offered?
Let me see.
Gosh, it's already this big.
I-I'm sorry...
There's nothing to apologize for.
Oh, again?
D-Don't rub it so hard...
How was Momoko?
Did she do it gentler?
No, she didn't go that far...
What am I to do?
Just stand up straight in front of me.
Let's continue the conversation.
Did Momoko do something like this too?
I said that we didn't do...
You can't... It's dirty!
Now, how far did
you go with Momoko?
She just saw my...
She didn't let you
do anything more than that?
R-Right...
You didn't get to touch her pussy?
Right...
I see.
Come on, lick it.
Come on!
Okay...
Open up your eyes
and use your mouth more.
That's right...
Yes, rougher...
Yes, right. That's good.
A little higher...
Right there!
Put your tongue in next.
Oh, right there!
It's so good!
It's gotten big again.
You have a wonderful thing.
Is that instinct?
I feel like I'm getting to my limit...
It doesn't seem that way to me.
I'm about to come...
Then come. No need to hold back.
All over my face this time.
I-I'm coming!
So hot...
Really... It's getting hard again.
D-Don't you want to feel good too?
That's for next time.
Amazing... Amazing... Amazing...
I'm about to come!
You can come...
You don't have to hold it in, so hurry!
It's still pouring
warmth inside my mouth...
Momoko?
Come on... More...
I-I can't get enough!
What huge boobs!
Her nipples and petals down
there are a beautiful pink colour!
Me first!
Me too!
No rush.
Everyone in order...
Man, I can't take her moving tongue!
It's like I'm melting...
I'm next!
I can't believe I'm allowed
to come inside her...
I'm next...
So good... So good...
Kenta...
W-Why didn't you call out for help?
Well, because it's not like I was
being assaulted, and I was asked to...
You shouldn't be doing that
except with someone you love.
Then let's do it.
You can do it with
someone you love, right?
I like you after all, Kenta.
I've wanted to do this with you
since the moment we met, Kenta.
No, don't...
It turns me on...
More... More...
It really turns me on... I-It's so good!
Be gentle, Kenta...
I-I'm embarrassed...
Give me yours too...
M-Momoko...
I can't hold it in any more...
It's okay. Let it out, Kenta.
Mine too, Kenta.
No, don't...
D-Don't stop...
More! More!
No! No! No!
Don't! Hurry!
Hurry and put it in all the way!
To Be Continued
The road used for travelling...
It's an everyday scene.
It changes gradually.
If I can find just one unchanging
thing, I would be saved.
Just stand there.
Tears come pouring out.
The sun goes down.
Stars start to shine.
My vision of younger days...
Everything just
shimmered in my eyes.
Let's go home honestly
like those days...
...while the sun is going down.
Without knowing any taint...