I-It's so good!
Fleshdance
Episode 2
Agony of Lust
See you.
Aoi!
So you two really were
in that kind of relationship.
What a player you are.
But if you make her cry,
that's not acceptable.
No, we're not
in that type of relationship!
I see.
I'm glad you're not
going out with Momoko.
Meaning...
Heart rates go up when you do
perverted things in the morning, right?
Come on, check mine too.
How is it? How does it feel?
V-Very soft.
It feels good.
How are my breasts?
T-They're nice.
Soft and really...
Aoi?
Oh, how amazing.
It's already so hard.
Let me see it more.
Doing this feels good?
Is it your first time
getting something like this?
Yes, it's my first time...
It's warm.
Aoi!
Why is it so hard?
You just came...
Aoi...
What's the matter?
You're not wearing underwear.
I don't wear any on strolls.
You're this wet...
You're such a perv, Kenta.
What's the matter?
I-I'm sorry. I'll put it in right now.
You can't.
I'm just glad you're not
going out with Momoko.
What does that mean?
It means I can still
tease you all I want.
In the end, I'm treated like a toy.
But one day I will
become that special guy to Aoi.
Are you about to come?
Hurry and do it.
I-I'm going to come...
Aoi!
Aoi...
If I'm remembering right,
that was left in the storage room...
You were tying to have sex
with Aoi and hide it from me.
N-Nothing!
Aoi isn't the type of person
you can lay your fingers on!
Listen carefully to what I say.
What's your relationship with Aoi?
S-She's just the wife of my master
who's letting me board here...
Don't lie! If that were true, you
wouldn't have been doing that stuff.
''That stuff"?
L-Like how you made her
put your thing in her mouth.
You took advantage of
her kindness, you beast!
That was something
she did to me...
There's no way she'd do that.
You must've coerced
her in some cowardly way!
S-She's not the type who'd be
coerced and broken by a guy like me!
You know that better than I do, right?
That's right. I know a lot
more about Aoi than you do.
Good things and bad things...
That's what makes
her attractive to me.
But you did those things...
I've held it in for so long.
Excuse me?
N-Never mind.
Could it be
you have feelings for Aoi?
There's no way it could!
That's right. I like Aoi!
That's why...
...I'm going to protect
Aoi from this filthy thing.
Um...
Hello?
Shut up!
Guys get weird ideas because
they get all pent up here, right?
If Aoi's going to get taken advantage
of by this, then I'll deal with it!
H-H-How'd it get this way?
Look, it's like this already.
M-Miku is sucking on my...
W-What the hell?
I-It's because you're like this
that I can't let you stay near Aoi.
I'll make it spit everything out.
I-It's inside...
It's inside you...
It's to save Aoi from
this violent thing of yours!
It's so hard...
Uh-oh...
It's so good... The best...
It feels so good!
Don't enjoy it...
If I don't suck it all out,
Aoi's going to be...
So good...
Miku, does it feel good?
It does...
...so not!
This is your...
Miku...
It's good...
That's right...
Yes, so good...
It's so deep...
My pussy is going to melt...
Are you about to come?
I'm... I'm already...
Miku, can I...
Can I come inside you?
You can! Come in me!
I'm going to...
Come... Come inside!
I-I'm coming!
Miku...
Are you getting hard again?
It's because your pussy
is squeezing me so much.
That's why I got hard so quickly.
Amazing... Even though
you came so many times...
You beast!
It's so good! l love it!
It feels so good!
Good... It feels good!
Feels so good...
Pound it in me more!
That's the way.
R-Right, I'm going to suck it
all up so you don't go near Aoi!
Come to think of it, Miku mentioned
that Aoi's birthday is tomorrow.
I'm not in a position
where I can have sex with Aoi.
How can I with her?
You want to do it with me that badly?
Aoi!
Seems kind of dangerous.
Here you go.
T-Thank you very much.
I was just thinking
out loud before, um...
Well, you've let it out
so many times today.
If you have the energy
to do it tomorrow morning...
...then I'll let you do me.
Are you serious?
So tomorrow.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Having sex of course.
S-Stop it, Miku.
Why? You enjoyed it
so much yesterday...
Well, there's a reason...
Who cares. I just want to do it.
I can't take this!
No, I have to keep
my promise with Aoi...
Promise with Aoi?
Miku, I'm sorry.
Ken...
I'm still this soaked...
I'm so lonely...
Aoi...
What good timing.
M-Momoko...
Today is Aoi's birthday,
so I was baking a cake.
Could you help me out?
I can, but... Momoko, your outfit...
Then here.
I'm sorry!
Oh no... It won't come off.
I'll clean it right away.
No, don't stop...
Hurry...
It's so slippery and feels so good...
It's so good...
S-So good...
S-So good... It feels so good...
So tomorrow.
O-Oh no.
No!
Don't go!
More! More!
I'm so tired from this morning.
How are you? Are you
all re-energized now?
Y-Yes.
I wonder if that's true.
I guess not.
P-Please kiss me.
If you do...
I've wanted...
I've wanted to do
this the whole time...
N-No...
I can't hold it in...
It's okay.
Let it out, Kenta.
Do it to me too, Kenta...
You're this big already...
Amazing...
So good...
No...
No, don't tease me.
Don't...
Please kiss me one more time, Aoi...
Amazing... You've gotten bigger...
You're youthful all right.
So big...
So hot...
Oh no...
It turns me on so much...
So hot...
I'll satisfy you.
Not yet... You can't come inside me.
No...
Turn around for me.
Like this?
No...
I don't want it there...
It hurts!
No!
So hot...
Take it out... Take it out...
Can I come in this one?
This is my first time...
So tight... It's getting tighter...
So good...
Aoi...
So good... I'm going to come...
I'm going to come...
I told you numerous times
not to come inside me...
I'm sorry...
It just felt so good...
It's okay,
since I enjoyed it to the fullest.
I finally became one
with the woman I admired.
And those days are still going on.
Do your best!
Dig faster!
That feels good.
I'm coming!
End
The road used for travelling...
It's an everyday scene.
It changes gradually.
If I can find just one unchanging
thing, I would be saved.
Just stand there.
Tears come pouring out.
The sun goes down.
Stars start to shine.
My vision of younger days...
Everything just
shimmered in my eyes.
Let's go home
honestly like those days...
...while the sun is going down.
Without knowing any taint...