It's my first time...
...so, take it easy on me.
Yuna...
You don't have to hold it in.
We're the only ones here.
Relax.
It's all right.
You're all wet.
Does it hurt?
I'm all right.
Keep going.
Your pussy...
It's starting to get very soft.
It's pulling me in.
My pussy's getting very hot...
I feel you, Takumi-san.
I'm really feeling you now!
So good.
It feels so good!
It's starting to feel so good!
So good!
You're tight...
Very tight.
Are you making it tight?
No.
My body just reacts naturally.
Look at you.
You're a very loose girl.
Don't say it like that.
I'm only doing this for you, Takumi-san.
Let's hold hands.
It's driving me crazy.
So good.
Harder, do me harder!
I'm so happy.
I never thought we would
be reunited like this.
Huh?
I guess you don't remember.
Takumi-san, you were working at
a convenience store, right?
When I was being picked on by a
drunk guy, you helped me out.
I don't remember.
If you don't remember, that's okay.
But I want you to
treasure me from now on.
Stop it.
I don't intend to treasure you.
What?
Someday Takumi-san will
look at me as a woman...
...and love me.
Good morning!
Well, it seems you're late, Tamura-kun.
Oh, I'm sorry. The train
was running a little slow.
Your train seems to
make a lot of stops, huh?
Well, something like that.
The line that Tamura's taking is the
same that runs the Sleazy Train.
Is he taking the Sleazy Train too?
Karin is my prize.
I brought her on this Sleazy Train.
If you bring a sacrificial
lamb you may board the train.
A sacrificial lamb?
You mean a guest?
That's right.
Those that don't bring guests...
...have paid large sums
of money to get on board.
You wanna do that, too?
I'm sorry, but I don't
have that intention.
What?
I didn't even say I
liked you or loved you.
You're right.
Well...
But...
If I bring an unsophisticated bitch
like her, she might call the cops.
She can't just be good-looking.
She can't just be loose either.
She has to be someone
who can amaze the crowd...
...and she must be an extraordinary
woman.
But she's so gorgeous, she
must have a boyfriend, right?
No, I don't think Kamijo-sensei has a boyfriend.
Are you for real?
Yeah, it's true all right.
I got the info from Eiji.
Ah, then it must be true.
So I guess...
Since she's so perfect,
her pride gets in the way.
Right?
Maybe she's a lesbian.
Don't you think?
Hey, don't say that!
Yeah.
If she's normal, maybe we have a chance.
She's a human being too, you
know, a woman to be more precise.
When her ripe body
can't take it anymore...
...she's gonna want to
do it with guys like us.
We have so much energy, so
we can do it whenever we want.
Stupid.
That's never gonna happen.
You're right.
Man, I really wanna do it.
Me too.
Right, right?
If she's got a body like that...
Well, Kamijo-sensei...
Good night.
Good night Azumi-kun, see you next week.
Is that her?
I've had my eyes on
her for a long time but...
...she's one tough cookie,
so you gotta be careful.
But a good operator like Tetsuo Amano...
...will have no problem
with a woman like her.
Amano?
You mean the legendary operator?
You're going to do it?
Yeah.
Stop doing that, or I'll scream.
You're not that type of woman, are you?
Besides, if I stop right now,
you're not gonna have any fun.
Do I look like I need
to be pleasured by a man?
Well?
Well if you're too good-looking,
most men are scared.
The same applies to you.
Me?
You're really wet.
It's a sign that you haven't
done this in a long time.
Am I right?
All right, I'll admit to that.
But not here.
Please.
All right.
Good, you're doing good!
Not bad.
Hey, stick it in here this time.
All right.
Turn around.
It feels...
...so good!
You actually enjoy this, but you
were just avoiding men in general.
You should just throw away your pride.
If I do that, will men let down their
guards and throw themselves at me?
I'm not afraid of you...
...but most men won't come near you.
There's a place where those
men can have their way with you.
Where is that place?
You wanna go there?
Take me there!
All right.
Now...
...let me come!
Go ahead!
Give me all you got!
I guess I'll go get two more.
It's not good for the
two of you to be fighting.
It's Maho's fault!
When the boys are near me, she gets
very jealous and starts to bother me!
I'm not jealous.
I'm just trying to
protect your chastity.
That is called jealousy.
That's not true.
Don't you know I'm trying to
look after my younger sister?
Older sister?
You were just born moments ahead of
me!
What did you say?
Now, now, take it easy, you two.
If you two lose your virginity
at the same time...
...your problems would be solved, right?
What? That's disgusting!
That's a pretty illogical jump!
What is the meaning of this?
Move your bags.
Sure.
No, don't!
I see.
Even though you're twins
you both feel differently.
Mizuho's very sensitive and loose.
Maho's frigid?
I'm not a loose girl!
I'm not frigid!
But the both of you get wet the same way.
This wetness is very uncommon.
Really?
Is that bad?
Not at all.
It just shows that you're a loose girl.
Mizuho seems to be enjoying it.
You can let yourself go too, Maho.
How about this?
Why did you stop?
We can't go any further.
Why?
It's my obligation
to support the passengers.
Obligation?
Passengers?
We'll continue with this tomorrow night.
But until then...
...maintain your glow and feel.
Sure.
That's good.
Listen up!
What I'm about to tell you...
...is going to be very important
for all of you in the near future.
So take this lesson very seriously!
Plus, we have female
students present today.
Boys, please be careful not to
make the girls uncomfortable...
...with what you say and do.
And do not disturb my lesson.
You got it?
Yes.
All right then.
Now, we shall begin by
explaining how babies are made.
Listen up, everyone.
In this society, they say that
the male-female relationship...
...involves indecent and
obscene acts to express love.
But that is all a lie.
You!
Did you forget what I
said at the very beginning?
I won't allow this kind of behavior!
But Sensei...
What?
It's your fault for
telling us such a lie.
A lie?
That's right.
Physical activity involving
love, is just a delusion?
That's...
I thought we could get actual
practice here today.
What are you saying?
We can't do that here.
How can you say that?
It's something you
personally do on your own.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
We can't do that.
Our lesson is not over yet.
That's right.
I'm getting very impatient.
You!
We're getting very impatient, too.
Both Mizuho-chan and Maho-chan have been
wanting it since yesterday.
Is that true?
Please!
Sensei!
What should we do first?
First you must prepare for insertion...
...by getting the vagina
wet through foreplay.
How do we do that?
You squeeze the breasts.
Like this?
Yes, just like that.
But it's better to stimulate
them directly, right?
I haven't taught you that yet!
We came very well prepared, you know.
That's right, we're not underachievers.
We can do things like this, too.
What do you think about that?
That's good.
Now gradually stimulate the genitalia.
Gradually...
You stick it inside, right?
That's right!
You're all excellent students!
Sensei!
I'm an excellent student, too!
Me too!
First, you prepare for insertion
by getting the male penis erect.
What? It's already hard!
There's plenty more
we need to do, Mizuho.
I got it, we make it
wet using our saliva!
That's good Mizuho, very good.
It's your turn, Maho-chan.
Sure.
Maho-chan, do mine first!
Oh, that's right.
You two are so wonderful!
I'm so proud to have wonderful students!
That's because your
teaching methods are great!
My teaching?
Now, Sensei.
We need you to teach us more.
I guess Mizuho's a loose girl...
...so does that mean she's
a better student than me?
That's not true.
You're a great student, too.
So go ahead and get busy!
Sensei...
I understand.
I'll follow what you say and get busy!
Wow, it's amazing!
Everyone, please enjoy
my wonderful body!
Hurry!
Yes, I'll do it!
Maho's doing pretty good.
I gotta do better!
I'm gonna come!
Who's next?
Please hurry!
You two are doing very well!
Keep up the good work!
Hey, keep going you guys!
Sure!
It's amazing!
Please, give me more!
I want to perform better than Maho!
So please do me more!
It's great!
You're all wonderful!
I'm very proud of you all!
Not yet, we're not through yet!
Please, I think we've had enough!
I don't think so.
If you don't do me more, I
won't give you a good grade!
No fair!
Wow, she's really something!
Incredible, I really admire her.
What are you people saying?
You guys can do so much more!
Come on, let's do more!
Yes!
Those are some fine guests.
You have really good taste.
Plus I bet you have a
good technique as well.
By the way...
Don't you think she's
having way too much fun?
No, not yet.
Don't stop now!
Give me more of that stinky
disgusting cock juice!
Not at all, we need to provide
as much as we can to these guests.
I see.
I'm glad to hear that.
Anyway...
I'm counting on you again.
Sure thing.
I'm officially a member
of the Sleazy Train.
I see.
That's it?
Aren't you at least
gonna congratulate me?
Is it that great to be on this train?
Great?
Well I guess it's not something
I can brag about in public.
But the guests I brought
satisfied those veteran passengers.
I feel real good about it.
Really?
Yo!
Welcome!
I'm done making this month's pamphlet.
Where's Kyoko-san?
I don't know.
She's not in her office.
You checking out some porn site?
Be quiet, get back to work!
All right.
It's a nice view from here.
Your cunt is drenched.
Director, please stop
staring at me like that!
No.
I like watching you get all dirty.
But I'll be nice and cover your asshole.
Thank you.
Now walk towards the window.
As you wish.
Take your hands away from your
breasts...
...and press your breasts
against the window.
But people are watching...
Just do it.
As you wish.
The way you move is very naughty.
You probably don't know
what to make of all this.
I don't blame you.
Your nipples are cold as ice...
...and your asshole is hot as fire.
There, keep on going.
The more agony you're in,
the more I get excited!
Yes, Director!
Wait!
He's your assistant right?
Yes.
I heard he became a recruiter.
Is he all right?
What?
I'm sorry, I wasn't supposed
to talk about the organization.
It's all right, it's not a big deal.
But don't worry, Director.
He was able to produce great results.
Really?
How delightful.
Well since we have so much time...
All right.
Great! Yes, there!
Give me more!