Sorry to have made you help me out with that.
No problem, I don't have much else to do.
It might be strange of me to say this now,
but I feel very relieved because you're here with us, Yuuji-san.
Yeah, I guess I can't tell her.
Happy to be here.
No, oji-san, if that doesn't work, everything will be over.
This is bad. We've been doing it for so long, but it's still so...
Yeah, that's perfect.
Oh, yeah, I think we can definitely use that.
It's going so deep! My mind's going blank!
If this keeps up, I'm gonna pee again!
No, I don't want to ever do
something that embarrassing again!
No! No! I don't want to pee myself!
So, should I finish up quickly?
If we don't stop soon, the hostess will find us out.
No, don't touch there again! You're being so rough!
Leave it alone!
No! Your dick is shooting that stuff out again!
There's so much going inside of me!
No... Why?! Stop!
You think I am?
Come on, I'm not that much of a child.
Girls these days are much more mature than you'd think.
So, who's not a child again?
I-If you just get close to someone like that,
anyone would be surprised.
Geez.
No, we're still going to have sex?
Please, just let me go already!
My body's going to become really weird!
Papa, please let me go!
Hey, we've only done it five times so far.
I just can't get enough of your body, Iori-chan.
Get ready to keep doing this until the sun rises.
No! If you cum in me that much,
I'm definitely going to get pregnant!
You're going to impregnate me!
My body just won't stop cumming!
Please, stop it!
If you keep making me cum,
you're going to make my body addicted to your dick!
Don't worry, I'll look after you for the
rest of my life. So just relax, Iori-chan.
No, that can't happen.
If you keep giving me this dick for the
rest of my life, I'm going to become a perv!
No, you're being so rough! You're gonna make me cum!
Oh no! My mind's going blank again!
He's basically had his dick inside of me since yesterday.
How can it still be so big?
Truth of the Secret Hot Spring
The constant frontal hesitation of the young hostesses Tsubaki and Iori.
Good evening.
Welcome to the Tachiragi Inn.
Please come this way.
Okay, Iori-chan, can you give them a tour of the inn?
Y-Yes. Well then, please follow me.
Around this time of year, it gets really bus...
Pardon me, my throat is a little itchy.
Ow!
Ow, that really hurt.
I'm sor...
Are you hurt, ma'am?
My apologies that you had
to see something so embarrassing.
I-I apologize, your room is right up here.
I can take this off now, right?
I can't do any work with this on.
If you can't even do that then, that means
that I won't be able to have sex with you either.
Yeah, I don't see anything wrong with that.
I'm not going to let you have sex with me anymore.
I don't even want to have sex.
Well, that doesn't really bother me.
I don't need that dick of yours.
You made quite the scene earlier,
but now you're coming onto me.
Does it feel good?
This is very great hospitality. This is just exquisite!
I'm going to go crazy if I keep doing this.
Chrysanthemum Room
No,
why would I do that?!
Just let me off the hook with your dick.
This is punishment for yesterday.
If you don't do as I say,
you'll have to take care of this as well.
F-Fine, I'll do it.
Please just cum whenever you like.
Don't worry. Just cum.
Wow, there's so much of your thick cum.
Are you serious?!
They sent in those people here?
Iori's just a child, but now he's making her do his bidding?
If I just got Chitose-san's help, this would've been so simple!
Come on, I already apologized.
I didn't get any of the documents.
Fine!
My last shred of hope...
I'll just have to pull out my last resort.
Are you satisfied?
This service is not included on your hotel bill,
so just contact me whenever you'd like it again.
Yuuji-san?
That was Iori-chan just now, wasn't it?
Yeah.
She's been acting strangely ever since she cut her hair.
Yuuji-san, did you do anything weird to her?
Huh? Did I do anything?
No, if anything, I've been...
Oh, is that so?
So that must mean that it's Fujikido-san.
Lately, they're just always together.
It feels that maybe she's sticking to him
because she never knew her father.
I know what a girl her age is curious about,
but I still think she's too young for...
Are you all right?
If I don't try to think of something different,
I just get so frightened.
I wonder if this is as far as a woman can go by herself.
Yuuji-san, I don't want to be alone tonight.
I'm sorry that it's happening like this.
I want to protect you forever, Tsubaki-san.
I want to make sure you and Iori are always safe.
Yuuji-san...
Yuuji-san, your hands are cupped around my breasts.
I'm being touched by...
I'm starting to feel strange.
I don't have any experience with this.
Don't worry, I'll be gentle.
Y-Your tongue is...
Your dick is so... so hot, and it's twitching.
So this will be going inside of me?
Tsubaki-san, you're getting so wet down here.
You can just call me Tsubaki. I'll also just call you Yuuji.
So this is going to go inside me?
Yuuji, let's do it. I'll give you my first time.
Finally.
Yuuji, your dick is going inside of me!
I can feel your dick slipping inside of me.
Please push it in all the way.
I can feel your dick pulsing inside of me.
I'm so glad that you're my first time.
Now I can finally... with him.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine. It hurt less than I thought.
I'm fine, you can move. Yuuji, make yourself feel good.
Ow.
I can feel you. When you move
around inside of me, it feels so good!
Your dick is stirring me up inside!
Yuuji! Stir my pussy up with your dick!
So intense! Yuuji, right there!
This position is so embarrassing.
You can see everything like this.
Yuuji, you're going even deeper than you were before!
This is amazing!
No! My pussy feels so good with your dick stuffing it!
Shit! Why is this happening?
Yuuji, you're being so rough!
You keep thrusting it so deep inside of me!
It's like you're lighting a fire deep in my body!
What happened? You're being more intense than before!
This is my first time, why does it feel so good?
My body is...
Yuuji!
Yuuji, I'm... I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna...
You're cumming inside of me!
I can feel your cum shooting out inside of me!
Your dick is pumping me full of your cum!
Wow, I never knew sex was this amazing.
You taught me something amazing today, Yuuji.
Huh? What's the matter Yuuji?
You got big again. What's going on?
Wait, does that mean we're going to have more sex?
No, if you keep doing it like that, I'm gonna...
You're being so rough that my hips are...
My insides are already so full with your cum!
I love it! Your dick is so big and fills up my pussy so perfectly!
I'm gonna lose it again at this rate!
My mind's going to go blank! I'm gonna cum!
Geez, Yuuji, you were just too good.
You know it was my first time, right?
What is it Yuuji? I kind of have work to do right now.
Yuuji? Are you hearing the words
coming out of my mouth, Yuuji?
Hey!
I know what's being done to you.
And I know the reason behind it too.
But you need to know that
your way won't solve anything.
Huh?
What are you saying?
Why do you think I've been enduring this?
If I keep things the way they are,
they promised not to do anything. That's why...
It's all a lie!
That's just the front they're using while they
launch their real scheme behind the scenes.
That's their ploy.
After you, they're going to go after Tsubaki-san.
And then after that, the inn will be theirs.
I've thought of a way to fight back though.
But for that I need your help.
Why are you telling this to me now? All this time, I've... I've...
You jerk!
That can't be true. Iori-chan did?
This is all my fault. I never thought
they'd send another one of their guys here.
They're being thorough.
I thought I was being pretty thorough
at the beginning too, but...
So what are you going to do?
I'm going to save Iori even if it means using force!
After I have all the steps in place,
I'll put my plan into motion.
Okay, I understand.
Iori?
What's the matter?
Sorry about earlier. I thought about it and I'll help you out.
It'd be a pretty big problem if this place went under.
Great, I'm so happy. All right then, Iori, let's...
But for me to help you, I have a few requirements of my own.
If you want to save me so badly,
you shouldn't be getting hard down here.
No, let go of me! Why are you doing this, Fujikido-san?
Stop!
Sorry, it's my job to keep you here.
You see, the young lady over there is a very fine woman.
She's one of the best women I've ever had.
So I'm not the best?
I've been trying so hard to become
your number one girl though, Papa.
You're still lacking in sexiness.
No, please, stop! Stop!
Why?!
It's useless. I know everything about you.
No, stop. You're being too...
You're seriously this hard already?
You really think you can save me when
you're like this? You're the lowest of the low.
No, stop! Don't touch there, that's...
You're pretty hard considering that
the person you love is getting raped.
So shameful.
You're such a shameful guy,
it's funny to think that you're my Papa.
Papa?! What are you...
Stop it, even if you do this...
Are you gonna cum while watching
the person you love being raped?
Just how much of a scumbag are you?
That was quick. Aren't you a little too aroused?
You're so pathetic, Papa.
I decided that I want to protect you too,
Iori, so please, untie me!
Seriously? You just came with my foot,
I don't think you're in any position to be making demands.
And look, you got big again.
Are you really even serious about saving me?
No, stop! This can't be happening, I'm...
Did that feel good?
You're quite the perverted hostess to have cum
while your boyfriend's watching you getting raped.
No, this is just disgusting to me!
Please, just stop!
You say that, but all this liquid
coming out of you says differently.
Why don't you just cum again?
No, Yuuji-san, don't look at me! No!
No, what's going on? No!
What's going on? What's wrong with my body?!
It's your own form of cum.
When you get turned on, it just pours out.
Judging by how much came out of you,
your body's going to be great to work with.
Iori-chan, what are you doing? We said we'd help you!
Oba-san, I heard about your past
and also what happened with my Papa.
Her past? Your Papa...
I heard that you were on bad terms with my Mama
and that both of you liked Yuuji. I heard everything.
You see, I've had a lot of time on my hands, so I was able
to get every last detail about you and all the related people.
You pretended to take care of me,
but what you were really doing was keeping me captive?
You never even told me where my Mama went.
Are you talking about when I used to live here?
The person I went out with back then was...
Yep, the child she got knocked up
with was me, your "Iori-chan".
That's right, I'm your daughter.
I'm the daughter of the pathetic guy who's getting
a hard-on from his daughter sucking his dick.
What are you talking about, Iori?!
I was wondering what would happen when you found out that your
daughter's sucking your dick, but you're pretty hard, aren't you?
No, this can't... It's too big!
No, it's so tight! What's going on? It's going so deep inside me!
If I'm already getting you to moan like that,
we must be really compatible.
Must run in the family.
No, I can't think straight!
You're just pathetic compared to my Papa over there.
You're smaller, faster, and there's nothing redeemable about you.
This'll be the last time we see each other.
I'll make sure I make it so that you
never forget about me though.
Wait, Iori, seriously, don't...
Look, your dick's about to go inside your daughter's pussy.
Your dick is fitting perfectly inside of me, Papa.
Your erect dick is going inside
your own flesh and blood daughter.
This perverted incestuous dick is so amazing!
This might be better than I thought.
It feels so good! Papa, your dick is so good!
No, stop! Yuuji-san! Iori-chan!
Hey, you don't have the time to worry about anything else.
This feels too good! Please, stop!
If you do this anymore, I'll...
No! My body's going to go crazy!
Let yourself feel more pleasure. I'll look after you.
It's so big, long, and hard!
If you keep doing me like this, I'm going to become addicted!
No, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
This... There's so much...
Oh my god! Papa, your dick feels so good!
I came without even realizing it.
This might be even better than I thought.
It might be smaller, but it's still really good!
Yes, the younger one is on top of him right now.
Yes. It was definitely very entertaining.
Your dick is coming so deep inside me!
It's making my pussy feel so good!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: akin
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч