Those are some fine guests.
You have really good taste.
By the way...
Don't you think she's
having way too much fun?
Not at all.
We need to provide as much
as we can to these guests.
I see.
I'm glad to hear that.
I guess it's only a matter of time
until I become the master of sleaze.
Hey, I'm gonna watch the monitor,
so can you take over for a bit?
You getting excited?
No, not really.
You liar.
He's really good, you know.
You want me to do you like that?
I don't know.
It's the best feeling ever!
This is why I can't leave you.
A love affair within the
organization is strictly prohibited.
Have you forgotten?
I remember.
Good.
But I want you to
treasure me from now on!
Stop it.
I don't intend to treasure you.
What?
Someday Takumi will
look at me as a woman...
...and love me.
Someday...
Well, look who it is at this time of day.
I guess doing you can make me sober.
Let's see how this body
of yours can satisfy me.
Are you ready for me?
No, if someone comes, they'll see us.
Let's go someplace else.
If a student at the
prestigious Anthreum University...
...is caught doing
this in the dormitory...
...she might get expelled.
What are you gonna do?
Hurry up and finish it.
Let me come.
Stupid!
You're too silly.
I'm not doing this for you.
It's not gonna end until
I'm completely satisfied!
If you make too much noise,
people are might come.
Is that what you want?
Don't stop!
Raise your ass up high.
I'll do you from behind!
Yes.
No, don't use that thing,
give me the real thing!
You just do whatever I tell you to do!
Your ass can take this
without any difficulty.
How is this possible?
I can't believe it's your first time!
It feels very weird.
Inside of my body is burning.
It feels so good.
Something hard is moving inside me.
Hot...
It's hot.
Takumi-san.
I want this instead.
This one might be one loose girl.
Put it inside me.
Do me with your big fat cock.
Which hole do you want it in?
In my ass, please.
All right.
Look the other way.
Yes.
This time it's the real thing.
It feels good!
Please give me more!
I don't plan on keeping up with your pace.
I'm gonna come soon.
You're not satisfied?
I said it before and I'll say it again.
I just wanted to get a quick workout.
Transit officer...
Full-time housewife.
She probably has no kids.
She goes out since she has lots of time.
She doesn't seem to have much money.
She ends up going to a department
store to buy tonight's side dish.
But her husband comes home
late so she eats by herself.
Her husband comes home tired, so
there's probably little or no sex.
This vicious cycle continues everyday,
and she's questioning her way of life.
She must be.
Please stop it.
Your ass is pretty huge, eh?
I'll scream out loud.
Then I'll stop.
Is that all right?
Don't worry, relax.
If you make a lot of noise,
they'll get more suspicious.
Anyway...
Put your hand over here.
How is it?
It's so hard.
Very hard.
That's right.
It's because your cunt is so wet.
No.
But you're still holding my cock.
It's all right, Miss.
Let's do it together.
Then let me suck on it.
What?
Miss?
I got you, pervert!
Thank you, Ayaka-san.
It was a fantastic performance.
It's nothing.
I'm sorry for making you the bait, but
that's the only way to catch a pervert.
Bait?
She was really enjoying it.
If that's true, then I
didn't do anything wrong.
It was consensual and it
can't be considered a crime...
Stop lying!
Why would I do such a
thing with a man like you?
But that feeling was definitely...
Right, Miss?
You can't get out of this mess,
you got caught red handed!
I'm calling the cops.
Prepare yourself!
Police?
Wait a minute!
Please wait!
I was on the same train as him,
and I saw him get caught.
It must've been some kind of mistake!
I work with
him, he's a really good guy.
This will never happen again.
So please don't go to the police.
Please!
I don't think so!
Perverts are a womans worst enemy,
it's the most embarrassing crime of all.
I won't let him go!
I'm begging you!
Nope!
Please! Please!
You're wasting your time!
Hey.
What is it?
Why don't you let him go?
He's apologizing this much.
I'm sure that guy learned his lesson.
But he's...
Punishment doesn't
prevent crimes, you know.
If that's what you want...
You saved me, Tamura. Thanks.
After seeing what
happened, I had to help out.
I owe you one.
Nah, it's all right.
I can't believe I was caught.
They made me look worse than
those middle-aged perverts!
Shit!
What's wrong?
Umm, you don't seem too happy.
It's nothing.
Will you be happy if you do me?
Don't sound conceited!
What kind of woman do you think you
are?
Are you all right?
Oh, yeah.
I'm all right.
I asked you to drink with me
to cheer up but I was the one...
...who ended up really drunk.
Silly me.
She can be real cute sometimes.
Sorry, Shindou-kun.
Good.
I'll just take her home and...
No, Shindou-kun.
I can't do this.
What are you talking about?
Now, let's go to your room.
No, I'm about to faint.
You're amazing, Shindou-kun.
Now it's my turn.
Please.
It feels good, Kyoko-senpai.
Good working women are good
at things like this, huh?
I'm very happy.
A man like you praising me like that.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Yeah, well, you were so great before...
So I have to try harder.
What do you think, Shindou-kun?
It feels so good, Kyoko-senpai.
Oh Shindou-kun!
I'm almost...
Do me with this one.
All right.
Takumi, it feels good...
So good!
Do me harder!
How is it?
It's perfect!
I want to ride on top of you.
Sure.
It's so wonderful!
I'm going to...
This woman...
She's good.
Kyoko-san, there's a place that
you might find amusing.
Are you interested?
What is this place of interest?
It's a sort of a sex orgy.
It's called the Sleazy Train.
What's wrong?
No, nothing.
Instead of keeping a close eye on
him, I became interested in his style.
Just when I thought I was having fun...
...he invites me to that Sleazy Train.
Sorry, but I'm really not
into that kind of stuff.
That's too bad.
I thought we could be really good
partners with a common ground.
She's late.
Shindou-kun, can you hear me?
I'm interested in that Sleazy
Train you told me about.
So I want you to do
me more from now on.
Maybe she went straight to the station.
Why?
Why are you giving me
this cruel treatment?
You have no idea?
No, I don't.
You let a recruiter into
your room, didn't you?
You obviously know what
happens to a person...
...who breaks the rules
of the organization right?
Don't bite.
I'll kill you if you bite!
Is this the punishment
given by the organization?
Shut up!
There, suck on that!
All right, I'll stick it down there.
No, please stop it!
What are you saying?
You came because you wanted it.
No!
Wow, I just love that shyness of yours!
Here we go!
Man, it's exciting!
I wonder what a married woman feels like.
What a view!
Let's see how it is.
Wow, it feels great!
There, there, there.
I'm embarrassed.
It hurts!
If you hurt me real bad, I'll have
my father give you lots of pain!
You're a prestigious girl at Anthreum.
But your father is nothing
but a bug compared to us.
That's right.
Plus if he finds out
what you've been up to...
...he'll have to quit his job
and become a nobody.
Then your father would
be less than a bug.
Even if he loses his
job, he'll be just fine.
He's not like you fools who
don't have a title or position.
You're a really interesting girl.
It's about time.
So many manly hands.
It's out of this world!
I guess my husband wasn't good
enough to satisfy my needs.
How much do you have to
squirt to be satisfied?
That's enough!
What, are you crazy?
We're not gonna be satisfied so easily.
Good!
I can't do this anymore!
No, no, I don't want to admit it!
But...
I'm very happy!
I guess she's not coming.
Tamura!
That woman isn't coming.
What?
I can't believe I have
to confront a recruiter.
What are you talking about?
I gave her plenty of punishment
on behalf of the organization.
Organization?
Now, we just need to
finish this between us!
Tamura...
When I woke up, I was
already in my room.
The number you have
dialed is no longer in service.
Sorry about yesterday.
I thought about what you said,
and I don't think I can do it.
Tamura tortured you, didn't he?
What?
What are you talking about?
You can't fool me.
You're seeing him, aren't you?
He's not coming today?
What do you mean?
I don't even know that person.
Stop playing games with me.
You see him everyday.
Good morning!
Ah, good morning.
You're late, Minegishi-kun.
Oh please, Kyoko-san.
I told you yesterday that I'm stopping
at the hospital before coming in.
Ah, that's right.
I totally forgot.
Please stay focused, Kyoko-san.
Sorry, sorry.
According to Kyoko-san, I've been
working for two years with this guy.
It's impossible that
Tamura doesn't exist.
Where did Tamura go?
There's just way too many
things I didn't understand.
I'm the recruiter?
Organization?
Is it the railroad company
that provides the Sleazy Train?
Then I'm just a puppet
of that organization?
Yes, everything is going as planned.
Yes, of course.
I'll keep a close eye on
him and make sure that...
...he can provide us with
great service as a recruiter.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, good day.