Your first present to me...
It made me so happy.
You know... I...
Su...zu... Suzu!
Suzu!
True Player
SHIN RINGETSU
Naoto-san... Don't...
No! It's so embarrassing...
Naoto-san, I'm going crazy!
Naoto-san, I can't take it anymore...
No!
Ayumi...
Naoto-san...
Ayumi... here.
Okay.
Naoto-san?
That ring...
Yes? Oh this...
It's a toy ring I found during my sister Suzu's wedding ceremony.
This, belongs to Suzu...
Nao-kun!
Ayumi? Ayumi!
It's Nao-kun!
Ayumi!?
Nao-kun... Who's this "Ayumi"?
Oh, this body belongs to Ayumi-chan...
Are you... Suzu?
Yup! I'm Suzune!
I see... So I've died already...
Hey! So, in order to create an heir for the family...
You did it with Ayumi-chan!
Well... that is...
All of Ayumi-chan's memories flowed into me.
Trying to hide it is pointless!
No matter what happens now, remain calm and composed.
Venerable Elder, please excuse the intrusion.
What!? It's me!
Didn't I die?
This is Suzune's body.
What is this... I don't even...
Her soul was absorbed!
By the bodily curse which has punished
our family for seven generations.
With some fragments of her soul remaining,
the body has somehow managed to stay alive.
But if that happens to run out...
She was alive!
Why did you hide something so important from me!?
A funeral was even held!
What reasons could there possibly be for
making me believe Suzu was dead!?
Nao-kun! Nao-kun, calm down, please!
You decided to have a baby with Ayumi-chan
because you attended my funeral, right?
So, the reason for hiding my body
was to help you make that choice.
Isn't that right, Onii-chan?
Is that true, brother Masa!?
It's ironic, but because of the curse,
everything except her soul is left unharmed.
That's why... If we could somehow secure a repository...
Then... This ring is...
Within the ring resides her mentality, although
the soul is a completely different matter...
But if her spirit was so strong that she could even
possess an entirely different person, then...
Then.. Suzu could come back to life?
Most likely.
Nao-kun... Please...
Suzu?
I'm... Ayumi...
I'm sorry!
Please hurry and go to her. Suzune-san
seemed so incredibly happy...
Forgive me.
Suzu...
Nao-kun!
Nao-kun...
Suzune...
My heart... It's beating so fast... Can you feel it?
Being together like this makes me so happy...
My heart's pounding and throbbing so hard...
We've finally reunited... I'm so happy... so happy...
Let's do it.
I want to have your baby.
That feels so good, Nao-kun!
It's like a dream come true, making love with you like this...
Suzune, I love you.
I love you too.
I love you... I love you! I love you so very much!
It feels so good down there... It's wonderful!
I love it! I can feel it...
I... I can't take it! I'm really...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
This time, it's my turn to pleasure you!
Lie down! That's it!
You've wanted to do this for a long time now, right Nao-kun?
Amazing... It's so hard...
I've fantasized about this so much.
How could I make him feel good?
Where are his pleasurable spots?
I thought about it and studied it a lot!
It's starting to feel really good, right?
I like this part so much! It's trembling a little.
Suzu, you don't have to say so much
just because you're so nervous.
I had a feeling you could tell.
But, I'm so happy... So very happy...
If I don't say something, I feel like my heart will burst!
Please be gentle with me...
Okay.
I'm okay... It doesn't hurt as much as I thought it would.
Keep going, Nao-kun.
You're going inside me! Your thing is going inside me!
I'm so happy... So happy! We've finally become one.
It's like my dream come true. To join together like this.
Keep moving, Nao-kun. It's okay. It doesn't hurt!
Also... it's starting to feel really good...
I feel so hot! I'm melting! If this keeps up, I'll...
So deep... It's hitting me so deep!
Nao-kun's... So deep!
Amazing!
More!
Nao-kun! I'll cum. I'm cumming. I'm...
Cumming!
Your warmth...
Your sperm is swarming in...
Our baby...
Nao-kun, from now on, we'll always be together, right?
Suzu, it's morning. Time to wake up.
What the? Hey! Suzu!
This can't be happening...
Someone help! Brother Masa!
I'm afraid what probably happened is that...
The power stored in the ring was exhausted.
There wasn't enough energy to last until her
consciousness and spirit fused back together.
It can't be...
Power must be gathered into the ring...
Please use my wife, Yuiko, for this task.
What?
When enjoying sex with another person, energy is gathered.
If such energies could be gathered from you,
whom Suzune loves, into the ring, then surely...
You musn't! Don't make Onee-chan do that!
You will not interfere in this!
Do you know what must be done to revive Suzune!?
I'll do it! I-I'll wear the ring... and do that with Naoto-san...
Ayumi?
Um... Naoto-san...
Let's do whatever's needed to bring back Suzune-san, okay?
I'm sorry, Shino-chan, Mizuna...
No... I have a different apartment on the
side ready for use if I need it, but...
I can't simply consent to this...
Just who are we talking about?
Naoto-san's fiancee.
What!? Didn't she die already!?
Suzu...
But still...
Are you sure it's okay?
If Rindo Naoto's fiancee were brought back to life...
She'll be together with Rindo Naoto...
Even though that was Ayumi-chari's place...
up until the day before yesterday...
No, that's not true Mizuna.
Since long before Naoto-san met me,
Suzune-san was always the one at his side.
It's not my place~
For more than 10 years, Suzune-san followed only Naoto-san.
When I was being possessed, Suzune-san's feelings
for him were so great I felt like I'd explode.
When Naoto-san found out Suzune-san
hadn't died, he looked so happy!
I... Someone like me... I couldn't...
Idiot...
In order to reach orgasm and quickly
gather energy into the ring...
I'll be cumming inside you, okay?
I hat would be the worst-case scenario, where
the ultimate purpose was to impregnate you.
The Rindo family only worries about finding an heir.
Any girl of the Hizuki family would have sufficed.
See, you hate this, don't you? You don't have to force yourself...
Suzu wouldn't want that for you either.
I'm happy... Does it really matter what
the other person is thinking?
No matter how we feel or what we think,
we have to try our best to save Suzune-san.
That's enough, isn't it? Right?
Thank you, Ayumi. Let's save Suzu no matter what!
Yes, Naoto-san.
I'll take it off myself so...
Um... Naoto-san?
There... That's! Don't... Don't!
That spot...
There? Not there... Don't!
Oh no... I'm going crazy!
No!
Don't! Don't! Don't!
I'll cum...
I'm cumming!
Naoto-san, please come to me.
I'm okay. Please continue.
Naoto-san...
Please... Please cum inside me!
Suzune-san, we'll save you no matter what!
Yes, we'll surely get Suzune back.
No! This is so embarrassing!
No!
This pose...
It's too embarrassing!
No, don't stare at my ass! Don't!
It can't be... It's only my second time, but this...
It feels good... It feels so good!
It's different...
It feels so different... Different than before!
Don't... Don't! I'm going crazy!
If you do it like that, I'll... Something's coming!
It's coming! I can't take it anymore! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!
Naoto-san...We didn't have to do it
here, we could've gone home and
No... Please! Wait until we get home!
No! We're at school...
Not there! I just got out of gym class,
you shouldn't lick me there! Don't!
Please, let me go!
No! Don't, don't, don't!
It's really dirty down there! No!
Please... stop this!
You're making a giant stain on my bloomers!
Don't! It's coming! I can't take it anymore! No!
You didn't even take my bloomers off all the way...
It's so messy and I'm so wet already!
Don't do it so hard!
I'll break! If you do it so rough...
You're going to tear me apart!
It feels so good... I'm cumming again!
So deep within me...
I'm scared... Doing it outside like this...
No! Naoto-san!
You're just teasing me, right, Naoto-san? Let's go home and...
No! That shouldn't feel so good!
Don't tease me so hard with your finger!
No! Not there!
Why am I feeling it so much?
It's coming! I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!!
I can't hold back any longer...
It's so deep...
You're going so deep all the way inside me...
I'm getting hit so hard inside!
I'm about to burst.
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum again!
I'm cumming!
So much is coming out!
Even though it's wrong to do it outside like this...
My insides are so warm and sticky with your semen...
Incredible.
Even though it's so embarrassing, my hips won't stop moving...
Please... Please cum already.
My body's going crazy.
It's so big and...
It's coming out... into my deepest crevices... You're...
Suzune-san... I... I...
Please don't look at me... This kind of pose...
No... I'm so embarrassed...
That... What is that, Naoto-san?
No! Naoto-san, stop it! Please stop it!
I didn't want to, but I couldn't help myself...
Don't tease me anymore... Please let me go...
It's going in!
It can't be! It's going go deep!
No, it's filling up my insides!
It's stirring me up inside!
It's so hot!
No, no! I'm going to go crazy!
No more! Naoto-san, please stop! Please stop it!
Ayumi, please do it with your breasts...
Okay...
But... how do I do it?
Put it between your breasts and then squeeze it.
Okay.
Please, help yourself.
It's kind of difficult.
You're getting so hard...
Please... I want to please you more.
I'll make you feel even better!
It's twitching and swelling up!
I'm so glad!
I know... This is the taste of your...
Are you going to cum?
Urn... Naoto-san... If you're going to
cum, then please cum inside me.
Your thickness is entering inside me!
Amazing! It's going so deep inside of me!
My body feels so good all over!
You're going into me!
I'm going to cum!
Naoto-san, Naoto-san! It feels so good!
Don't! It's amazing! It's too good! I'll cum!
Please cum lots inside me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Naoto-san! I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
It's coming out... Naoto-san...
Naoto-san... I love you.
Naoto-san... Naoto-san... Naoto-san...
Ayumi...
I'm sorry.
You're only having sex with me to bring Suzune-san back to life.
I'm sorry...
Please make me feel it Naoto-san.
Please make me feel all of your love for Suzune-san.
Please... Please, hurry!
Hurry and be happy with Suzune-san!
Please, hurry and return! Suzune-san... Suzune-san!
That spot feels so good! I love... I love it... I love you!
Right there! There! Naoto-san! I feel like cumming!
Naoto-san, please cum too!
Please cum all you can inside Ayumi!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out... Inside me... So much... So much...
Thank goodness... Suzune-san... Thank goodness!
Ayumi... Thank you.
I'm so glad things turned out okay.
Yes.
Ayumi...
No!
Suzune?
Where's Ayumi-chan!?
Ayumi is...
I remember it! This feeling...
It's the same as right before I got into that accident!
No! Ayumi-chan! Run!!
Suzune-san?
Stop! Please stop!
Naoto-san!