Royal Magic Academy - Library
Why...
Why are there tentacles in the library?
No!
Don't... don't suck my boobs so hard!
Wait...
Wait, wait a moment...
Something that large... won't fit!
No!
That's...
No there... you'll mess it all up!
No... no...
No... someone...
Someone come...
Please save me!
No!
I...
I was creampied by tentacles...
Stop... stop already...
If it goes on like this I'll break...
No, don't!
That's my butt...
Now... more...
Show me more of...
your lust...
My butt... and my pussy...
Don't rub so much inside...
No, no!
My, my horn...
Please don't touch my horn!
It feels so good... I can't think anymore!
I... crazy... I'll go crazy!
Tentacles... dicks...
What a smell...
Do you want to do lots of... perverted things with me?
You're about to cum, right?
It's alright, cum lots on Unico!
My boobs, too...
And my mouth...
There's so much of tentacle-san’s
semen... so wet... and warm...
It feels good...
My butt... and my small pussy...
Are both being dug out by thick tentacle dicks...
My mind is going blank...
I... I'm about to cum!
Please spray it on me!
Your white and sticky... thick semen...
Please bless my body with lots of it!
It’s coming out! Inside my pussy...
So much is coming out...
I'll cum! I'm cumming!
No!
I... again I got...
Violated so much...
What was that?
Unico!
I am sorry, girl with horn.
If I had saved you earlier, this wouldn't have happened...
A book is talking...
My name is Dante.
Although I look like this right now, I am a magician.
Young lady.
Would you... Would you lend me your power?
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
The Grimoire of Divine Melodies
A Girl with A Horn and the Mysterius Book
In fact, right now,
a book of sorcery that I had once
sealed inside a demon, Grimoire,
it's seal has been broken,
and the demon has returned to this world.
And it seems that someone is using its
powers for evil inside this Academy.
No way... do you mean a student is...
The Grimoire will always use a human summoner
as its intermediary to exert its power.
A person absorbed deep in their
desires who reads the evil book,
will become the "Grimoire Reader"
who brings disaster to the world.
I did it again... what's wrong with with me?
It's as if my mind is being clutched
and grabbed by this book...
No... not at a time and place like this...
My fingers won't stop...
What are you doing?
At a place like this...
If you're horny and frustrated, we'll help you.
Um, um...
This isn't what you think it is...
Young lady, seek after me.
No...
Please hurry and run!
Before I... before I lose myself!
Huh? What'd you say?
Expose all of yourself...
That is your true desire!
What's with this book!?
Now,
won't you do lots of things that feel good, with me?
I... I'm kissing a boy...
No... my body is out of control...
Put skin to skin, lose your mind in mating,
Drown completely in your desires.
That is your sin...
"Lust".
Wow...
My heart is pounding so hard...
I'm about to do perverted things...
Woah... her wet and soft tongue
is wrapping around me...
Is it really this girl's first time?
I'll make your pussy feel good, too!
Please rub it against my boobs...
Alright.
Can you tell? My nipples are really hard!
Right there, there, suck my dick harder.
I'm about to cum!
Yes... please...
Let out lots of thick semen on my boobs...
So this is a boy's semen...
It's thick and sticky...
What a lewd smell...
Such thick semen... what would
happen if it came in my pussy?
It's tight...
A penis... is inside!
It's went straight in all the way... it's so good!
This girl... she's shaking her hips on her own!
Amazing...
Such a thick penis is inside!
My hips... won't stop...
I'm... becoming more and more of a perverted girl...
Semen... is overflowing... but you're
still pulsing with energy...
What's with this girl?
She's so cute, how is she so perverted as well!?
More... I'll be sure to love you lots more with my dick!
Your penis... is still so energetic...
Please... thrust in my pussy more!
Wow... your insides are really hot!
The semen you creampied inside... is being mixed up...
My pussy is making... such erotic sounds!
It feels so good!
More... have more and more sex with me!
This position... my sensitive spot...
My clitoris is being rubbed...
There, there! Get pregnant with my child!
All the way inside... please thrust harder!
The rim of the tip is rubbing my pussy...
This is bad!
It's so wet, my hips won't stop!
Me too... my body... my pussy is so
hot... it won't stop twitching...
Here I go! I'm spraying semen all over you!
Yes!
In my pussy... everyone's... please spray
everyone's hot dick juice all over!
I... I can still have lots and lots of sex!!
Let's feel better and better together!
Let's release the desires in more and more people!
This pulse of magic...
A magic barrier is being set up in the school's temple!
Dante-san! Isn't there something we can do?
We have no time to waste.
Girl with horn! Open and read me!
Read?
Yes. I am a Grimoire.
With your magical powers you should be able to use me.
Girl with horn, please lend me your power!
That, that's...
I'm...
Unico!
Fumika-san!
There's serious trouble! The First Year's Division...
Shirley's class is...
Yes! More!
Amazing! Thrust your dick more!
It feels good!
It's coming all the way inside!
What... in the world is this?
Seems like they've been brainwashed by something.
They can't even hear us.
Every human holds lust... there is no exception in us.
All I'm doing is releasing those desires they've built up.
Shirley! Rayleigh!
As long as I have the power of this Grimoire,
everyone gets to feel very good.
You, you are...
My fellow library monitor, Patricia-san!?
If you plan to continue this...
I won't hold back, either!
I won't let you get in the way.
From now we'll be doing even better things.
No way, that's...
The magic of the sorcery book went
into Shirley and Rayleigh...
Oh! It's Unico-chan and Fumika-san!
Let's all get wet together...
and all feel good!
No!
No! Damn it!
Let's start with... Fumika-san!
I'll make you feel good.
Stop at once, you...
Fumika-san’s boobs are so pretty!
No, not there...
It'll start to feel weird...
Fumika-san...
Everyone is... my friends are being tortured...
But I can't do anything!?
Fumika-chan... use your mouth...
Do me with your mouth! C’mon...
Now...
More and more... be pulled into the vortex of lust.
You guys... will regret this!
It's amazing!
Fumika-san's pussy is squeezing so tightly... it's the best!
No... if you thrust me in this position like an animal...
I'll go crazy!
This is bad... this...
cock feels so good!
Fumika-chan... looks like you're all ready.
We’ll show you the true meaning of pleasure.
No, that's...
Not both at once... don't!
It's in!
Shirley and Rayleigh's futanari dicks...
They're violated me all the way inside!
Fumika-chan's butt feels good!
Your pussy... It's squeezing and wrapping around me...
And there's so much of slutty juices flowing!
Wow... Yes! It's so rough...
More... more!
Of course... we'll make you a slave of our dicks.
Your pussy and your ass are being
attacked at the same time...
and your clitoris is standing up so happily...
Wait! That place is sensitive!
Fumika-chan's insides are so warm...
it's like my dick will melt!
More... Violate all my good spots even more!
Lewd noises are coming out of my pussy and ass-pussy...
Amazing!
I can't take it anymore!
Are you cumming?
Fumika-chan... are you going to cum?
I get it...
Let's all... cum together!
Cumming!
If I have... the power to save everyone from this...
I don't want to give up!
What are you doing?
I'll try to stop them for as long as I can!
Meanwhile you run away!
Dante-san...
I...
I'll become a Grimoire Reader!
I've... always lived following someone
and listening to what they say.
Just like fledgling waiting for food in the nest.
But the day will definitely come,
When I have to fly!
To protect my friends... to protect everyone!
This is...
Unico-senpai's hidden magic is growing!
Please, everyone!
Return to your senses!
Everyone... have they return to normal?
Yes.
Unico-kun. Well done on finally being determined.
Truly...
Dante-san! That's...
It's the Grimoire of Lust!
Looks like it wasn't completely purified yet...
No!
Where is this place?
What happened to me?
No... it's embarrassing...
Please don't touch me so much...
Young lady...
Seek after me...
Your penis is...deep inside...
There is no way you can return to your life before.
You will be framed as a slut who went mad from lust...
and will be shamed for the rest of your life.
No, that's...
But have no fear...
If you stay with me... I promise the
wonderful future of your desire.
Yes... more... pleasure thrust more...
I'm going to cum... I'm cumming!
It's pulsing again...
Now... fall with me...
Into eternal darkness...
Thank you...
I... will always be beside you.
Patricia-san! Please get a hold of yourself!
If this goes on the Grimoire...
It'll rob you of everything and take over you!
Unico-senpai...
It's okay...
I fell down to Lust...
Is the atonement for my sins...
I don't have a place to go back to!
That’s not...
No...
It's thick... and nasty smelling sperm...
Unico-senpai...
You're covered in semen... it's so perverted!
Senpai... please let go of everything...
and fall into eternal pleasure with me...
As long as the human has its sexual desires...
The sin of lust will always follow you.
I'll carve that into your bodies so you remember!
I...
Until I save Patricia-san, I won't give up!
Why!?
There's nothing left to be save... what can you do!?
Even though you were possessed
by the powers of the book,
your heart kept fighting...
Those strong emotions will help you start over!
What are you jumbling about.
I'll seal all your holes with tentacles,
and violate you all the way to your brain with pleasure!
Deep inside...
again and again...
No! I'm cumming!
No...
Unico-senpai...
I... I feel too good...
No more...
Stop stirring up my pussy!
Unico-senpai...
My nipples... our nipples are rubbing...
It feels good!
My body is hot...
Every place is being violated by a tentacle dick...
No... no!
No more!
I can't... I'm cumming!
Sen... Senpai...
Patricia-san... your hand...
Give me your hand!
Unico-senpai... I...
I lied to myself.
I don't want to give up!
I want to be with Senpai and my friends!
Her heart has been freed!
This is the chance to purify Lust!
What, what you say...
You are definitely not alone!
If you have the power to fight...
If you want to return to your past self...
I... I'll become the wings you can fly with!
I'm... sorry!
I'm so sorry, Unico-senpai! I...
Light?
Looks like it still isn't over...
Dante-san... could it be that there
are other Grimoires out there?
Good thinking.
There are seven Grimoires in total.
No way...
They tune into the desires of humans, absorb
their magic and bring disaster to the world.
The only one that can fight them is the Grimore Reader,
only you.
I...
I... the Grimoire Reader...