Was that a dream?
It's been three months since then.
Right now, I'm helping out at a detective agency.
But... was that really a dream?
Shinshou
Genmukan
Epiloge.1
~Dream, Confession, and Straying~
Even though I say I'm helping out,
there's nothing much I can help out with.
But Kido-san says it's fine.
That's why I... I...
I really want to be of use to him some day.
As long as I can help Kido-san out,
I'll do whatever.
I'll try my best at whatever he wants me to do.
Please use me however you want.
You're doing fine, so don’t worry.
Moreover, I brought you in.
Oh, and what you did just then was a great way to wake me up.
Kido-san!
Speaking of that...
This is a bit sudden, but could you help me out with something?
It's morning, after all.
All right, I understand.
Is this okay?
Yeah, take it off slowly.
Okay.
Kido-san...
All right, I'm going to start moving.
I'm almost at my limit.
Okay.
Huh?
Sorry, I don't have time.
Yes, please do.
I can feel it.
I can feel...
...that you're now deep inside me.
Cood morning.
Oh, Kido-san.
You're up pretty early today.
Not bad.
Or did you pull an all-nighter?
Yeah, I had quite a bit to do.
Cood morning, Mei-san.
I'll go make some coffee right now.
Black coffee for Kido-san,
and extra milk with no sugar for you, Mei-san.
Just like usual, right?
Y-Yeah...
Right, extra milk...
Even though I'm always with you...
You idiot.
You idiot!
Kido Detective Agency
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't want to disturb you.
Disturb?
N-No, you have the wrong idea.
I wasn't really thinking about Kido-san. Well, uh...
Mei-san...
You're really beautiful.
W-Wait, stop.
I don't swing that way.
But look, it's already so...
No, not there...
It's wet.
It's embarrassing! Stop! You're–
No!
I'm still...
Oh, no!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
No way! With a girl?
I'm cumming!
Stop, please.
I'm... I'm still...
I'm still...
Don't worry. I won't be using that hole today.
Huh?
N-No, not there!
Please relax.
No!
It hurts! It hurts!
You're ripping a hole in my stomach.
You're so mean! How could you shove it up there?
Don't worry.
You'll feel good very soon.
It only hurts in the beginning.
It'll be over soon.
You can maintain your virginity while becoming a real woman.
Centler... Please be gentler.
All right.
I'm beginning... to feel a little better now.
All right, let's begin the next phase.
Phase?
That's...
We'll use this on your most sensitive spot.
Wh-What are you going to do?
This is the smallest place.
Yes! Yes!
No, please. Don't stop...
Open it up by yourself next.
Show it to the person you love.
Come on, say it.
Please... Please take a look inside me.
I've... I've been waiting for this moment.
Please, look at it more.
You're the ffirst one to see it.
More... More...
Call out his name.
Satoru-san!
Everyone sure is doing well.
What was that voice?
Don't tell me... That's impossible.
Kido Detective Agency
What?
W-Welcome back.
Wh-Why are you dressed like that?
I borrowed Nozomi-chan's spare outfit.
Is it strange?
No, it looks surprisingly good on you.
That's great.
Y-You can use me however you want today.
But you're...
I'm serious.
You...
You can do whatever you want to me tonight!
Mei, you...
I guess Kido-san and Mei-san are made for each other.
It's gonna hurt a little, so relax.
Is it in?
Only a little.
I-It's all in now
Your hot thing is throbbing inside me.
It's warm inside as well.
H-Hey, Kido-san, start moving.
But you're still...
I don't care.
I just want you to feel good.
Mei...
A-Amazing!
Y-You're churning up my insides!
You had sex with Nozomi-san this morning, right?
Well, uh...
It's okay. You don't have to hide it.
Nozomi-san is a good girl, and I didn't plan to disturb the two of you.
And someday, I might be fucked by some guy I don't know.
Hey, hey...
But, you know...
I just want to give my ffirst moment...
...to the person I truly love.
So don't get the wrong idea!
Don't take it out.
I want you to be the first!
So we need this.
Why the skirt?
It wouldn't feel like I was really fucking you without this.
Since you're not really a maid.
I'm so happy.
Cum inside me! Cum inside me!
Cum inside me for my ffirst time!
It's coming... It's coming out!
It's coming inside.
My insides are expanding!
Thank you. I'm so happy.
Manga Cafe
I've waited a long time for you to be alone.
That voice... Imada-san?
W-Wonderful...
Yes! More!
Kido-san, you're amazing!
Y-You've cum so many times, yet you're still...
I can keep going for the whole night.
N-No! I'll break...
I bet if we continue till morning, my cum will leak out of your tits.
Idiot, what are you saying?
Don't rub them so hard.
You're hitting deep... deep inside me!
More... More...
R-Right there!
Cum inside me, please!
It's too much.
I'm too tired to move.
Help me.
Ceez, I feel all weird now.
It's so hot inside.
I feel numb down there.
But fuck me harder, please!
All right.
It's... It's hitting there.
No way! There's no way!
I feel amazing.
You're hitting the right wall... the right!
As long as you feel good, I'm...
I'm cumming.
How many times has it been?
Your pussy wants it so much.
Excuse me, Imada-san?
What?
As long as I obey you, nothing will happen to Kido-san, right?
Yeah, I won't bother with that detective anymore.
F-Fine, then.
What a good girl.
I can't help him any other way.
That's not true.
I'm sure that was Lady Ayano's voice.
And this road leads to...
This is the underground tunnel that leads to the mansion.
It saved my life.
Hey, hey.
Don't think you can run away now.
You said that you'd obey me.
Yes.
Then quit talking and take your clothes off.
Right, what a good girl.
Let me fuck you.
Pretend that you're getting raped.
Okay.
Stop...
Don't do this!
Don't dirty my insides!
Please, Master!
Forgive me! I'll do whatever you want!
Just take it out!
S-Stop, please!
Right.
You're a woman who likes to get fucked hard.
N-No, I hate it!
You don't like it, huh?
Take this then.
No... No...
Take it out!
I'm going to cum.
No!
Then why are you squeezing me so tightly?
Nozomi isn't back yet.
Don't tell me she left because she cared about Mei?
Oh? A real maid, huh?
So this cute chick is gonna give us some fun, huh?
Aren't you happy that you've made some new friends?
Yes, Master.
Stupid bitch!
You're not only my fuck toy, you're also my hostage.
Spread it wider.
P-Please take a look.
This is my most important place, Master.
Look at this. It's gushing.
It can't be!
It's... It's not wet.
You make me want to fuck you so bad.
It hurts. It hurts! Stop, please!
So you want me to stop, huh?
No, I'm sorry.
I want you to tease my naughty breasts and nipples, Master.
No... No...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
I... don't want to cum because of this.
Am I...
Am I actually...
No!
Master... don't be so rough.
Or you'll get turned on even more?
N-No.
Then let's use this.
No! It's so big...
It's rubbing my insides. I'm gonna go crazy!
You mouth isn't doing anything.
Suck it harder!
Take care of mine as well.
According to her cellular GPS, she's gone to the mansion.
Because she has bad memories of that place,
I don't think she'd go back by herself.
So you mean something happened?
That's why we need to go confirm it.
And something's bothering me.
Please, forgive me.
Just let me take a little break.
No! I'm cumming again.
No... No...
Look, she's cumming again.
Well, she's been fucked for like half a day.
I guess it's normal for her to become like this.
Master, please forgive me.
I can't stand this any longer.
What are you doing?
Stop it already.
Then tell me where she went.
I know you want to take her away.
W-Well...
Look.
If you don't hurry, she'll die.
Very well.
I'll tell you, so stop.
That's not all that I want.
Very well, I'll give you some fun.
Well, well, are you sure?
My, you treat women as tools for sex,
but you're not very good at it.
What did you say?
So who's first?
Come on in.
I'll treat you with great care. Come on...
Can I go first?
Fuck you. I'm first!
Shit! Don't cum inside.
It's my turn next.
Oh, you're pretty powerful.
But should you really rush?
Oh shit, she's tight.
This is really awesome!
It's my first time experiencing such pleasure!
Don't rush.
Slow down, slow down.
But I'm already...
Move!
It's my turn!
Take this.
Power alone can't satisfy a woman.
Shut up and keep it down!
You're pretty energetic.
But come on, stick it in deeper.
This is...
No, don't cum yet.
I'll make you feel even better!
Don't worry about that.
Not bad, huh.
But what about this?
God dammit!
Hey, kid, my asshole is feeling pretty lonely.
Take this!
Wait, her asshole is mine.
Move!
Come on, don't rush.
Go ahead.
It feels so good to be penetrated by three cocks at once!
More!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
If you ever piss me off, I'll make you regret it.
Wait. Wait!
My, what happened to your enthusiasm earlier?
My, my. What a waste.
Jeez, why am I doing this, even though I'm the chairwoman?
Don't do that, or I'll get really turned on.
Quit talking and suck it. Hurry up.
Please, hurry up and cum already!
If I'm naked here and someone spies
on me, then they'll see everything.
My pussy will be all exposed.
Just a little more. Suck it a little harder.
H-Hang on a second!
Don't tell me he plans to cum inside my mouth! You're kidding!
Oh yes, that is the least you could do.
Since I'm lending you my precious car.
That's mean! Why did he cum inside my mouth?
That's not what he promised
Well then, you'd better swallow it all if you want to breathe.
This sucks!
All right, let's do the real thing.
That's right, turn around and–
I already said I'm sorry.
Would you let me go?
The job's over.
Who cares?
I'm just washing the taste away.
Thanks to you, he made it to the hospital.
You were a great help.
H-Hey, is Nozomi-chan really in danger?
Well, she may be.
Is this what's really bothering you?
Well, Nozomi wasn't there, but we found the body of a butler.
So you mean everyone's still alive?
Yeah, that leaves the question...
...where did Lady Ayano, who inherited everything, go?
W-We'll be rich as long as we can find her.
I guess it'd be natural to think that.
But no one knows where she is, right?
That's the problem.
No!
Mei, watch out!
Enclosed in darkness, your milky skin seems to melt away,
And the warmth of your breath seems to leave you.
I sense a burning passion in your eyes,
But it shimmers away as time flickers by.
I exist only to find the wings you have lost.
Without a heart,
I can only peer up at this fixed utopia.
At least let me embrace this love.