One day, a girl showed up at the detective
agency, with a request to make.
Excuse me...
Huh? Yayoi?
Oh, thank goodness.
It's been a long time, teacher!
Er, I'm not really your tutor or anything,
so you don't have to call me that...
But you'll always be a teacher to me!
You're pretty much an official detective
anyway, right? So in that case, I...
I'm still just an assistant.
The detectives are these two over here.
Karen, and...
I'm Rio. Nice to meet you.
So Yayoi, did you come here
today to see Masafumi?
Or do you have some sort of case for us?
Um... To be honest...
According to her story, a friend of hers
had gone to a relaxation salon.
While she was there, she suddenly
became sleepy, and they did horrible...
...things to her while taping it.
Threatened with the tapes,
she attempted suicide.
The girl was unable to tell the police,
so it seems Yayoi came to seek the
help of her old mentor, Masafumi.
Yayoi, we will certainly take your case.
We started looking into it right away...
...and over the course of the investigation,
an amazing clue fell in our laps.
We found trace amounts of
drugs in the blood and urine.
He seems to be the main culprit,
so from this point on, he's
the focus of our investigation.
He uses medicine to make it so they can't move,
then takes pictures of them
and blackmails them?
What a scumbag.
Rio...
We can't leave this creep
alone for one second longer!
We'll sneak into the salon, and
get some really irrefutable evidence!
So, these are our principal services.
The two of you are both quite beautiful.
However, as you both of course know,
stress is a terrible strain on a beautiful figure.
How would you like to try our Personal
Experience course today, free of charge?
And with that, Yayoi and I infiltrated the salon.
With this, we can take away
any swelling in your legs.
But...
What was that, just now...?
...we were caught in his trap,
and took the medicine.
We were videotaped as he raped us.
Ah, perfect!
Thanks to Karen's quick thinking, we
were able to escape the worst of it, but...
Yayoi could tell...
I have this feeling that, at the salon,
someone did something dirty to me.
I think... I think I was...
It was Masafu m I!
See, because of the medicine
you were really aroused,
so he did it to save you from yourself.
Masafumi did?
At this rate,
it doesn't seem likely that the damage
caused by this drug is going to decrease.
Somewhere in this city,
someone is doing the same thing
that was done back then...
Yes... The same thing happened to my
younger sister Aya, one rainy night...
Those bastards forced her
to take so much of the drug...
Tch, it's not working on this worthless girl...
This is bad, boss.
Yeah, let's go.
H-Hey, wait up!
Aya...
A... ya...
A'! N'.!
That man... I will never forgive him!
Whoa!
Look at that ass!
What a turn on.
And that's howl met Rio.
Rio's sister died when someone
forcefully injected her with narcotics.
The song from the music box she
left behind brought us together.
This song...
After hearing your story,
this song sounds so sad.
You investigate a lot of different
things when you're a private detective.
We had hoped additional information
leading to her sister's killer might turn up.
That's why we started the
Goddess Investigation Agency.
I don't want to upset Rio by making
her remember her sister like that...
...so you can't play this song at the office.
Venus File
Morning!
Morning? It's lunch time already.
You've let yourself sleep
in a little too often lately.
But...
...all the jobs recently have
been about cheating spouses,
more cheating spouses,
and even more cheating spouses!
Can't we ever get a job like solving a
murder in a perfectly sealed off room?
The investigation of cheating
spouses is work too you know.
But getting involved in other
people's affairs is just being nosy!
Fine.
Masafumi. Let's go be nosy together.
W-Wait!
See you later.
Rio, answer the phones will you?
What's that supposed to mean?!
Oh, I forgot.
Do you remember the incident
that happened awhile back?
The files detailing where the
narcotics came from that were used...
...in the "relaxation" sessions are on my desk.
If you're going to go investigate,
make sure you lock the door to the office.
Thanks Karen...
Guess who?
Y-You startled me!
Oh, it's you, Yayoi.
I'm the one who was startled.
You're such a scaredy-cat.
So this is where they have their affair?
Won't they see you if you're
spying on them from here?
This building is the tallest one in the area.
They can't see us if we're on the roof,
and we've got a perfect
view looking down on them.
Karen's strategy is perfect.
So where is Karen?
She went back to the office.
Then, we're alone and no one can see us.
Y... Yayoi! I can see your underwear!
How embarrassing!
Oops! You saw my panties!
I... I didn't see anything.
I didn't see anything at all!
Let's get back to work!
But you've already seen everything so...
Y... Yeah, but...
Plus, you're the one who made love to me...
...when I was high on that drug.
That's not true!
Rio made that story up to get
her through that moment.
But I can't remember anything that happened...
It's not fair that you're the
only one who can remember.
Fair? But...
Masafumi...
Y... Yayoi...
Masafumi, please...
Yayoi...
Masafumi... Please be more gentle...
Masafumi, make love to me...
Yayoi!
Masafumi!
Is it really okay for me to do that?
Masafumi...
Y-Yayoi ...
Masafumi, please...
Yayoi!
I'm back. How's it going?
F... Fine! Everything's fine!
Welcome back, Karen!
Oh, Yayoi, I didn't know you were coming.
Y... Yes! But I was just about to leave!
Good luck with the case!
Roof Closed
I was so close...
Did I come back a little too soon?
N... No, not at all!
What am I supposed to do about this...
Hey, I have a question.
There's supposedly a bar
called Lamia around here.
Do you know where it is?
Lamia? Why do you want to go there?
No, but I have heard of it...
It's in the next town over, though.
No way. Karen's information
isn't too reliable, I guess.
Thanks. Bye.
There's some broad looking for this place.
A woman?
That's not good. The game only just started.
I'm funding this operation and I can't
exactly have our connection public.
Was she hot?
You really like women, don't you?
Well?
She was exceptionally beautiful...
I see...
Then, there is no problem.
It's past ten... I wish they'd show up already.
I'm hungry...
Have some of mine.
I made it myself.
You went back to the office to make this?
Thanks for the food.
It's unexpectedly good.
What do you mean, "unexpectedly"?
It's three... I guess they're not coming tonight...
Our waiting paid off!
Masafumi, they're here.
I'm stuffed...
S&M sex!
Such a submissive girl...
Someone might see them by the window...
They're really daring...
No... They're doing it there for
the added excitement... I know...
...I used to be... No!
Masfumi's right here.
I'll revert to my old ways
again if I give in to my lust.
Bur...
They look like they're in such ecstasy...
She's being fucked by such a big cock...
She's addicted to sex... Just like I was...
Well? Does it feel good, Karen?
Yes, it feels great.
Masafumi, he's... He's awake...
He's pretending to be asleep
so he won't hurt my feelings.
I can still tum back.
I don't want to be like that again.
Bur...
It's so big...
You know you want it. Be honest, Karen.
Karen's sucking my dick...
His hot dirty cock is all the way in my mouth...
I love it so much!
It's getting harder...
He's going to cum soon. Cum! Cum lots!
It's throbbing so hard and it's pouring into me.
His thick cum is spreading all over my mouth...
I forgot... The smell, the taste,
the way it goes down my throat...
is it good, Karen?
Yes, it tastes good.
Masafumi, you're awake aren't you?
You haven't cum in a while.
I got excited because it's been so long.
K... Karen!
I have a favor...
Fuck me...
B... But...
Fine, if you're not going to put it in, I will.
It went in only a little bit and I came.
It's great! Your cock is...
Look at me, Masafumi.
I'm writhing in pleasure from your cock.
You can thrust it in me, Masafumi!
I musn't... Karen...
Don't say that.
Lick me. No, bite them... Bite my dirty nipples!
Yes! I want it to hurt! Yes!
I can't anymore! I can't hold it anymore!
M... Me too!
Did the milk surprise you?
That's what they did to my body...
You must hate me.
You must think I'm a perverted freak...
No... Of course not!
Of course not...
Thank you.
H... Huh?
Good morning!
It's noon already.
Masafumi, you're late!
Good morning, Masafumi.
Um, Karen...
Masafumi, you're acting weird...
Did something happen
between you two last night?
Did you...?
Of...Of...Of...Of...course...n...n...n...
Of course not.
That's for sure.
By the way Rio, how did it go?
Thanks to you, I was able to narrow it down.
There's a group of men distributing
narcotics underground and...
...now that Masafumi's here, there's some
things I want to check out on my own.
Excuse me... I have an urgent job.
I see...
So tell us about the case.
I want you to look for my friend.
You should just contact the police.
His father is in a critical condition.
I want him to see his father, just in
case he takes a turn for the worst.
Even if you only spend one
day looking for him! Please!
Well? What do you think?
What do I think?
Of course we're gonna do it!
Rio, check out where he works.
Masafumi will...
Masafumi and I will look for him together!
S... Sure...
I'm counting on you.
I'll search around his house with the client.
Call each other on your
cells if you get any leads.
Let's do it!
What are you talking about?!
I thought he was supposed to be
working at a bar around here!
I've never seen him.
I've seen the guy next to him though.
I'm not looking for him.
They used to go to a bar called Lamia
before it went out of business...
What?!
I've heard the guys who hang
out there will do anything.
Deal drugs, rape women...
There was even a rumor that they
pumped some poor girl full of drugs...
...so they could rape her, but she overdosed
and died before they got very far.
He really lives down here?
Yes, just a bit further down.
It's Rio.
Hello. Did you find him?
Karen! Be careful! The client might be...!
In you go!
What are you doing!
Sorry.
Karen! Karen!
Hey. Were you the one who
was sniffing around about us?
T-That voice...
I've never forgotten for a moment
what happened that day...
How dare you do that to my sister!
Sister?
A ya!
Oh, that's right.
You're her older sister.
Stop! Aya!
Sorry about that.
We were just trying to have
a good time with her, too.
Sis... We were just trying to
have a good time with her, too.
We were just trying to have
a good time with her, too.
How can you laugh and say that!
Don't worry.
I'll be more careful this time. I won't kill her.
Karen has nothing to do with this!
That's why it's so great.
You can imagine how much she's suffering.
Karen...
Karen, right? How do you like the rape wagon?
It's horrible.
Oh, come on. I'll show you how great it can be.
Nice pose. You're turning me on.
Excessively huge breasts and
nipples on such a thin body...
That look on your face...
It's going to be fun raping you.
I wonder how many minutes you'll last.
I can't wait.
You have sensitive nipples.
What about down here?
No!
Looks like you've been trained.
He's good...
I'm a well known sex trainer in the underground.
Let me see what you got.
Look... She's wet already and
it's dripping everywhere.
No!
She's tightening up.
Are you going to cum already? That was quick.
Awesome! Cum!
Whoa, even her nipples came!
I can tell... she's been trained before.
Interesting. If I give her to the Organization...
No... If I use her to get Rio as well,
I might even become a Kanbu.
Okay...
First I'll teach you who this body belongs to.
This is amazing...
Suck me off.
I can't hold it anymore... I'm gonna cum!
She's being raped and enjoying it.
What a pervert...
it's happy... My body... is happy it's being raped...
Let's get some fresh air in.
What's going on?
They're fucking in the car!
Are they shooting a porn video?
What's going on? What's going on?
Whoa! Look at that!
That's so dirty.
Come on. Show yourself off a bit.
No!
They're looking.
They're watching me.
Looking all the way inside me...
Come on. Let's finish it off!
I'm going to cum... I'm gonna cum!
You like it here right?
This woman... She came just
because she was being watched...
Looks like this is going to be a fun game...