What is this place?
There's nothing here.
I can't see anything here.
It's freezing.
I feel lonely.
Free me from this place.
Please.
http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
Yes. That should do it.
This goes here.
Just a bit more.
Youko!
Going home now?
We're heading to the station front for tea. Wanna join us?
I can't. I still have club activity.
I see. See ya.
Alright. Next, I just need to connect this.
See you tomorrow.
Carefully. Carefully.
Not again... Darn!
Takagi-sensei, please take a look.
He's set up a pretty huge firework display today.
Is that so?
This is not the first time. Can't you do anything about this?
Right. I'll think of something.
What are you laughing?
This place seems to be in tatters.
The door can't even open properly.
Can't you just knock?
Knocking it down is way faster!
You know I always do important experiments in here.
So making a bomb is an important experiment?
What did you say!?
This is far worse than I thought.
At least spare a thought for me, the Advisor for the Science club, here.
This makes it the third of this year.
The vice-president glares at me with white eyes every time an explosion goes off.
Sorry about that. It's her fault-
What! You're pushing everything to me?
It's the truth.
In any case, please clean after this place.
You can fight all you want after that.
Yes.
Me too?
Of course.
Are you really moving into that house?
Forget it.
Why now of all times?
The moving is tomorrow.
The rent there is really cheap.
The other areas can't even compare.
Is that your main reason?
That room has...
Has what?
Rumors have it that there are spirits.
Like I said, spirits.
Youko, what is this place?
The Science club room.
Me?
Science club president.
You?
Vice-president.
There you have it.
Believing in something you have never seen is a failure of a scientist.
My eyes will expose the truth of the universe.
Seeking out the guideposts to the evolution of mankind.
Sheesh. That's what you get for nonsense.
Where did I stop?
Forget about it.
There are no such thing as spirits.
What, are you afraid?
Just a little worried.
I'll be fine.
But...
The daughter of the landlord shouldn't say such things to the tenant.
Don't you worry.
Today's the best day to move.
That's right.
The luggages seem to have been moved.
This place will be my new starting point.
What! Are you still bothered by that rumor?
But...
Even if the rumors are true,
spirits that comes out at broad daylight now is nothing to be afraid of
because it's so stupid.
You really took your time.
Kotobuki.
Onii-chan!
You came specially to help?
I heard rumors about spirits, so I paid a special visit.
I'll have you pay an entrance fee if you take my apartment as a haunted house.
You occult fanatic.
This hardly packs anything coming from a mad scientist.
Hey now, the two of you.
It's getting late. Go and unpack your luggages.
You're right.
Little spirit, show yourself.
Let's have some fun.
A duel is fine by me.
Childish.
Hiroshi, where do I put this box?
The room next door.
Got it.
You still have lots to improve, Youko.
Wearing panties like that even though you're my sister, that's a joke.
You should consider wearing those with frills.
Hiroshi! You too!
Stop! That box is...
I'm leaving.
What's the meaning of this. I like it.
This suits you just fine, Hiroshi.
What did I do?
Well, don't be so mad.
With Youko gone, how about celebrating your moving in?
Kotobuki!
Let's have some beer.
Any cups here?
In that box.
Right on! Let's get the party started.
I'm fine with a party, but I should settle my luggages first.
That can wait.
It's pointless if you don't celebrate early.
That's a huge hole we have here.
What do we do about this?
Punching a hole immediately after moving in.
You'll probably get kicked out if the landlord finds out.
Kotobuki.
For a start, let's drink!
Drink up!
What are you doing?
Cheers! Drink more, you can do better.
Stop, Kotobuki.
Dad.
It's only a dream?
Don't worry, Dad.
I can manage fine by myself.
What?
Is this a continuation of the dream?
It's cold, and lonely.
Who's this?
Anybody here?
Free me from this place. Please.
A girl?
Mom?
It's a dream?
Did you have a nightmare?
My head hurts.
That's a hangover for you.
This is fantastic.
What's that?
That's a cute slipper you have there. Where did you get it?
Don't be a prick.
You going back?
There's a paranormal activity meetup this afternoon.
See ya.
Why is there a vase inside the hole?
This is just so strange.
Seriously.
Screaming in broad daylight, that kid.
My name is Ruri.
Ru...ri...
I'm Ruri.
Ruri?
Yes.
Where are you from?
You freed me from the vase.
This is bad. I'm totally having a hangover.
Hangover. Hangover.
COLD!
It hurts.
What's that for?
Your friend said hangover, and then he used water...
You saw that?
Yes, I saw from inside the vase.
Vase? You- Then, how did you get inside the vase in the first place?
Yes, it's because.
Because?
Well...
That's strange.
What?
I can't remember.
You don't remember?
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm seriously asking you here.
I'm equally serious.
Just that aside from my name, I only know myself to be a snow woman.
Snow woman?
Don't panic.
I'm Science club president. If I let a small thing like this affect...
Nothing. There's nothing here.
Which means she's floating in mid air?
This is impossible and shouldn't be happening.
The ten years I devoted myself to science.
What's happening.
Don't be alarmed, Hiroshi-sama.
You even know my name.
I heard your friend calling you that.
I'm thankful you released me from the vase.
Thank you really much.
N-No way...
W-What! Where's the sound coming from?
Hello.
I...
Youko!
Sorry about yesterday.
Is there someone hiding inside something so tiny?
Having thought over carefully,
I brought it upon myself.
So I have no right to be fuming at you.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I made breakfast. Egg sandwich.
Let's have them together. I'm walking over.
Should be there soon.
Got it.
I almost forgot! She's still here.
Ruri, hide.
Why?
Hurry!
This won't work, too.
Here...
Alright. Get in here.
In there?
No time to be picky.
Yes.
Do you understand?
She must not find you.
She's cold.
Your hands are hot.
A snow woman... no way...
I heard a girl's voice just now.
You sure are fast.
What? Anything wrong?
Maybe it's just me.
Have your sandwich.
I don't have an appetite.
Kotobuki and I celebrated after you left last night.
My head hurts from the hangover.
Geez, and I even made and brought over.
Sorry.
Let's unpack.
You're running late if you don't leave for school.
What are you saying? Won't you also be late.
I'm taking today off.
Do you feel unwell?
No, not that.
Just that...
You should hurry for school.
I'm right... He doesn't like me?
See ya.
Youko.
What's up with you, Youko?
Don't say anything.
So early in the morning...
I don't care.
What was that just now...
Wa- Hey!
I'm busted.
Hiroshi!
Well... you already found out.
Vanishing into thin air.
Flying in the sky.
Cold body temperature.
A snow woman...
What a joke.
It's true.
There, Youko.
But what happened just now.
Don't tell me you actually believe her?
The truth is before your every eyes.
You have to believe it.
Even Youko.
Man! This is a trap.
Someone must be trying to frame me.
Hey, Youko! You actually think this is funny?
I'm not.
I just thought it's been a while since I last saw you like this.
You're seeking joy from this.
Is it fun? That's great, then.
Hey!
I've understood the situation.
Hiroshi will take care of you from now on.
Huh?
Don't give me that. Got it? You have to look after her.
Wait a sec! Why are you deciding this on your own?
Ruri-san has nowhere to go.
You were the one who released her from the vase.
It's logical for you to be responsible.
What if something jappens?
No worries about that. You can't even touch her.
Lewd stuff is out of question.
I was not referring to that.
What if something happens to me?
Oh well...
This is a nightmare.
Hiroshi-sama, please take care of me.
Under my care?
To hell with everything!
Ouch....
Thank you, Hiroshi-sama.
What is Youko thinking?
And so this is how I began living together with the Snow woman, Ruri.
I wonder what's going to become of me from here on.