For now, resting will allow the patient to regain
consciousness with no complications.
She might even recover enough to be released tomorrow.
Really?
Thank goodness...
Rindo-san.
Yes?
The mother's physical health is fine, but...
Mother?
Yes, she is carrying a child right now.
Recently, with regards to the Rindo group,
this is the closest they've gotten to...
Ayumi is pregnant!?
Yes, she is indeed pregnant.
And unexpectedly, even though there shouldn't
have been any complications...
It can't be...
Ayumi-chan...
SHIN RINGETSU
True Oath
The baby can't be saved!?
Ayumi-chan's baby is in the same state I was, right?
If I explain it to you, you might regret it...
Even then, do you still want to hear it?
Tell me, Onii-chan.
Masakazu, you...
Venerable Elder, Suzune was able to recover of her own will.
Let's see what she can come up with.
The key... is that ring.
This ring?
Yes.
In order to gather energy for the fragments of your spirit...
Ayumi-chan wore that ring,
and became pregnant after making love.
Do you have memories of these events?
Yes, I remember it quite clearly.
Inside Ayumi-chan, there was so much love for Nao-kun.
Even then, she still brought me back from near death,
so Nao-kun and I could be together.
I could never be so selfless...
And at that time, didn't you feel another presence?
There... There was! A really small presence,
but very energetic, like a pair of them!
Those children, so they were Ayumi-chan's babies!
Two!
It could be that the consciousness of
those children are stored in the ring.
Then, if she puts on the ring, those babies will be saved!
I'm going now!
Wait a second!
Please wait a second, Suzune.
Your soul has successfully fused only recently.
The fusion might not complete, if you take the ring off now...
What will happen?
There is a strong likelihood that your soul will unravel...
If that happens... there might not be a second chance...
It's not for certain though, right?
If that's true, then I'm going to go save Ayumi-chan's babies.
Suzune...
I want to help Ayumi-chan. I can't ever thank
her enough for what she's done...
So it's my turn now!
I'll save Ayumi-chan's babies no matter what!
Ayumi-chan, let's save your babies no matter what!
Maybe we shouldn't. We only just brought you back...
Please, just worry about your own health.
So, it's okay if no one worries about the babies?
I know about your feelings.
How you steadily fell in love with Nao-kun,
it was all transmitted to me.
But still, I also felt a mysterious kind of emotion.
As you discovered more of Nao-kun's goodness,
and fell more and more in love with him...
I also felt so happy for you.
So please don't disregard children created
with someone you love like that...
Ayumi-chan, let me hear your true feelings.
I want to save them... my babies!
Naoto-san and my babies, I want to save them!
I really want to save them!
We'll save them. We'll surely save them!
Suzune-san...
It's fine. I won't die no matter what, so it's okay!
Okay.
Suzune-san!
I'm... okay... I'm okay.
Nothing happened?
Yeah! I think I'm okay!
Thank you so much...
Don't thank me yet.
Now it's your turn.
Okay.
Please. Naoto-san and my babies. Come back.
Please... Come back.
I hear it! The babies' voices!
Me too! I heard it too! Ayumi-chan's babies!
Suzune-san... Thank you so much... Thank you so much!
Congratulations, Ayumi-chan.
Thank you so much!
Please give birth to a healthy child.
Things are still okay this morning.
The babies' souls seem to have returned.
I'm amazed by your feat!
Brother, I'll be returning to the Hizuki estate tomorrow, okay?
What did you say!?
This is about Ayumi-chan, isn't it?
Yes, everyone's okay, and an heir is now on the way.
There's no problems, right?
But...
Ayumi-chan will surely bring happiness to Nao-kun.
And she'll give birth to a healthy child.
See? There's nothing wrong at all!
No... problems, right?
And Nao-kun really loves Ayumi-chan. He really loves her truly.
All right, but at least go get your health
checked by the doctors before leaving.
Masakazu, see to it.
Yes sir.
Nao-kun, I'll be going back home now, okay?
Ayumi-chan, I'll be leaving Nao-kun in your care, okay?
No. No. No!
What is this all of a sudden?
Well, I trust Ayumi-chan will bring happiness to Nao-kun so...
No way!
Ayumi-chan, even you though you
love Nao-kun, aren't you happy?
I'm not happy.
If it's not Suzune-san, how could Nao-kun possibly be happy?
At first, I felt like you had taken my place next
to Nao-kun away from me. I hate it.
But, when Ayumi-chan helped bring me back,
all of her feelings flowed through to me.
I couldn't let those hopes go unfulfilled...
Then... we're the same, aren't we?
I also felt all of Suzune-san's feelings for Naoto-san
and I couldn't let those go unfulfilled either.
Really?
Yes, that's why you can't just go home.
The two of us...
Maybe we worry too much about each other's
feelings and not enough about our own.
The inexpressible feelings that we kept deep within ourselves.
I love you so much right now!
Yes, I felt it. I love you too!
The two of you...
Nao-kun!
I'm not going home after all.
Instead the three of us will stay together forever!
Yes, I also want us all to be together.
Naoto-sama, please excuse the intrusion.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Please forgive the interruption of your talks.
But a matter demands immediate attention.
The latest check-up scans revealed that Suzune is also pregnant.
Congratulations!
If you give birth to a child, then there'll be five of us, right?
Thank you! This is so wild! I can't wait!
I know!
Um... Naoto-sama, what's going on here?
I don't get it either.
Nao-kun, congratulations on your success!
Congratulations!
Yup, thank you.
Wow... Nao-kun's is like this already...
Well, I'll let you take care of it.
Okay, let's begin!
Nao-kun, does that feel good?
Yes.
Come on, Ayumi-chan, you too!
But... that's...
Come on! You shouldn't be so bashful now.
Today is when we celebrate together with Nao-kun.
Um... that is...
All right. I'll do it first then.
Come on! Ayumi-chan come do it with me!
That feels really good, Ayumi.
I want some too...
Suzune-san... Here, let's do it together.
We'll always be together from now on, okay?
Naoto-san! Naoto-san!
Naoto-san's... there's so much!
We'll help clean it up, Nao-kun.
Amazing!
Do you want us to use our mouths again?
Nao-kun, you perv!
If it's with Ayumi-chan then it should be okay, I think.
You know what Nao-kun wants?
Yes?
Suzune-san!
Your pregnancy's made your breasts so big!
They're just throbbing to squirt aren't they?
It can't be!
Wait... Suzune-san!
Ayumi-chan is so cute. Her whole body is blushing.
No... Please don't say that!
It feels like it's about to come out.
Ayumi-chan, you feel it, right?
It'll soon be coming out from here, right?
No... No!
Nao-kun! Ayumi-chan's boobs are amazing!
Look how much came out!
No...
Go on, give some to Nao-kun, okay?
Okay...
So warm...
Nao-kun, you're getting really big again.
It feels so good... Ayumi-chan's breasts
and nipples are rubbing against mine.
It's big... and hard...
Naoto-san's is twitching a little. Are you going to cum soon?
Cum! Please cum on our breasts!
Nao-kun!
Naoto-san...
I can't stand it any more, please give it to me...
Naoto-san... me too...
Naoto-san, why are you having us get dressed again?
Nao-kun, I was surprised... This shirt is too tight for me now...
But that's because, Naoto-san's baby is inside you now, right?
Just like me, there's a healthy baby growing inside you!
I guess you're right
The baby's growing up strong and healthy without any problems.
Yup! That's why you had us get dressed, right? Naoto-san!
That's right. That's exactly why I said it.
I'll try really hard to give birth to a healthy baby.
Me too! I can't wait to hug my baby!
I know exactly what you mean. I can't wait!
But before then... Papa...
Let's make love.
Papa... me too...
No... This pose is too much...
Nao-kun, don't stare so hard...
It's embarrassing...
Nao-kun!
Th-There!
Nao-kun... hurry!
Naoto-san... please!
I see. So which one should I put it in?
You mean?
Ayumi, do you want it?
I... That is...
I really want you to answer me quickly.
I... I can't!
Suzu, what about you?
I want Nao-kun's...
Where do you want it?
Please put Nao-kun's right in here.
No... it's embarrassing! It's so embarrassing!
Nao-kun?
If I go in too deep, let me know.
Okay.
Nao-kun's is~
Nao-kun's went inside!
It feels good! It feels so good!
Suzune-san...
Nao-kun, that's...
Don't!
If you do it like that, I can't take it!
Nao-kun, cum! Please cum inside, deep inside me!
I'm going to cum. I'll cum. I'm cumming!
Nao-kun's semen is going inside me...
Naoto-san?
Now then, Ayumi, what is that you want?
That is... I want Naoto-san's thick thing inside me!
No! No!
This is amazing!
Naoto-san!
Ayumi-chan, you look like you're feeling so much pleasure.
Oh no! Suzune-san! No! Don't look!
Ayumi-chan, you also get turned on from others watching you?
That's not...
No!
Ayumi-chan, it looks like you're going to cum.
Suzune-san! Don't watch me!
I can't... I'm cumming. I'm going to cum!
Naoto-san's warmth is going near where the baby is...
As expected, I'm completely exhausted.
Nao-kun.
Umm... I want to do it again.
It's trembling!
And getting big again!
I'm putting it in...
My insides... Nao-kun's is filling me up again!
Nao-kun, it feels so good!
Don't! I'm cumming again!
Nao-kun, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's going so deep inside... I'm going to get pregnant again!
Naoto-san, it's painful to just watch.
W-Wait a second...
It's warm and squishy...
But, I can't hold back any longer.
I'm putting it in, okay?
It's wet! It's going in!
The leftover cum from just now...
It's so slippery and it feels so good!
It's amazing, it feels like my insides are stretching a bit.
It's bumping much deeper every time.
It's hard! It feels so good. Does it feel good inside me?
It's going to reach the baby! There... it feels so good!
I can't... My hips are moving on their own!
I'm going to cum. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Suzune?
Pee? Did your water break!?
Yes!
Oh yeah! Bring the old lady here to Suzune!
Okay!
Even as times flows by, nothing changes.
We can only keep waiting.
It's terrible!
What is it?
While Suzune was being attended to,
Ayumi-chan went into labour as well!
What did you say!?
"She's also going into labor pains," I think is what she said.
Is such a thing even possible I wonder?
Anyway, what's their current condition!?
Right. The two are too much for us to handle...
In any case, the medical team is on their way.
Our old lady refused to let them in?
Yes.
Well then, there should no problems here!
We can count on her.
They've been born?
Wait! There should be one more.
Now... There's two voices, right!?
Suzu! Ayumi!
Hey! Don't be so loud!
S-Sorry...
Nao-kun...
Naoto-san...
Look... It's Nao-kun's baby.
Such a healthy baby... Naoto-san.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
You've done so well.
We've started our family, right?
All together, there's five of us now.
I hope everyone gets along well and lives happily.
It's okay. It's Nao-kun, so he'll surely make us happy.
That's right! All of you, Suzu, Ayumi, and
the babies... I'll make all of you happy!
Shino-chan. Mizuna.
Thank you for coming. Let's talk more after, okay?
Are you happy now?
Yup! I'm very happy!
I see.
Well, congratulations.
Thank you.
Ayumi-chan is so beautiful.
Thank you, Mizuna.
Naoto-san! I want to be held too!
I don't really get it, but as long as they're
happy... I guess it's okay, right?
I've never seen Ayumi-chan so happy before.
I guess you're right.
Okay! All the preparations are done!
Brides and groom! It's ready!
Okay!
Let's go! Ayumi-chan!
Okay! Naoto-san, you too. Come on, let's hurry and go!
Kiss!
From now on, we'll be together forever, okay?