As for what happens to Ruri the self proclaimed Snow woman...
Good morning, Hiroshi-sama. Breakfast is ready.
She's still in my apartment.
http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
This is..
This is omelette made specially for you.
Omelette?
This?
Yes, and that's strawberry ice cream.
But it seems to have melt.
Are you serious!
But they look alike.
This isn't Miso soup.
That?
It's true they look alike.
And so, this is the start of my weird lifestyle living with Ruri.
It's spinning.
Hiroshi-sama, that's cruelty!
Packaging cute cats into boxes and selling them.
That's too much.
That's...
I'm getting you all out!
Ma'am!
How can they even fit inside those boxes.
Sorry.
Concealing yourself when the situation turned awry.
Just stay vanished and stop creating anymore trouble, you got that?
Yes...
I'm hungry. Let's get lunch.
Hiroshi-sama, I have caused trouble for you.
Geez.
Please take the umbrella, Hiroshi-sama.
I'm fine.
You'll cause me more trouble if you catch a cold.
Yes...
Hiroshi.
How's everything coming along?
No thanks to you.
You look like you can't wait.
How do I look like that?
Wait for me.
Thank you for coming.
You told me to take care of Ruri.
Honestly speaking, I have no idea how to treat her.
She's a Snow woman,
and is clueless about the world.
That's not the main issue, rather...
You can't help yourself to look at her like a girl?
I-Idiot! What are you saying?
Why would I treat a Snow woman like Ruri as a girl?
That's just lame.
Why are you so flustered?
I'm not.
A cold?
Probably because I walked in the rain yesterday.
You can treat Ruri-san as something like a family of sorts.
Like a little sister.
Little sister?
Right! A little sister!
Hiroshi-sama?
Hiroshi-sama? Hiroshi-sama!?
What should I do?
That's right. Youko-sama.
I've seen him talk to Youko-sama with this.
Youko-sama!
Why isn't she answering?
Hiroshi-sama, are you alright?
Hiroshi-sama.
Hey, Hiroshi!
What? You only just woke up?
You'll be late if you don't hurry.
Dad.
I'll be back a week later.
This is...
Dad!
Hiroshi-sama.
Hiroshi-sama...
It rained earlier than the weather report says.
Wait, you can't go!
Don't forget your umbrella.
Don't go! You can't go, Dad!
It's just like snow now...
A song?
Searching for that lost voice.
Stranded on the Plover mountains.
where the snow is falling now.
Putting on lipstick on this kid tomorrow
for her to take part in the village festival.
Are you awake?
How do you feel now?
My fever seems to have subsided.
That's great. Are you hungry?
I have no appetite.
That won't do. You need nutrients after recovering.
I'm in the midst of preparing porridge.
Was that a dream?
Hiroshi-sama, can you get up?
I can.
That instant.
That sensation on my forehead.
It was from Ruri's hand.
She scalded her hand because of me.
This...
I scalded myself while cooking just now.
It's nothing serious.
Let's eat.
My cooking has improved.
The porridge is a delicacy.
I see... I finally understood.
Ruri is this kind of girl.
You should hurry and eat, Hiroshi-sama.
How's it? Good?
What's the matter?
You mixed up the salt with sugar again, Ruri.
No way!
This isn't a laughing matter.
This is my first time eating sweet porridge.
You can used the prickles to adjust at this sort of time.
This won't change the taste.
Yes.
Hiroshi.
What do you think of this?
Isn't it too flashy?
Really? I thought it's rather fitting.
Youko-sama! Which of these do you think suits me most?
Let's see...
They all suit you.
Really? I'm taking them all.
Don't be silly! You're getting only one.
How about trying them before deciding?
Yes. I'll do that.
What occasion is it today?
What?
You ask me?
You were still fretting over how to treat her not long ago.
Now you're buying clothes for her.
It's nothing.
She only has a Kimono.
It's rather pitiful wearing like a Snow woman everyday.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Nothing.
This isn't too bad, don't you think?
Youko-sama.
I can't decide. Could you pick one for me?
No problem.
Sorry.
You look great, Ruri-san.
It's a reflection of your good taste, Youko-sama.
You think? I still feel the ones I chose earlier are better.
No. I want this.
Well.
What I mean is
It's your first time wearing western clothes.
That's why you can't tell which designs suit you better.
It's fine. I prefer this.
Suit yourself.
What a relief.
Hiroshi is gradually becoming who he used to be.
Right, Youko. You should teach Ruri to cook.
You have no idea. I eat shocking good daily.
What exactly is shocking about it?
Like what's inside Miso soup...
Stop that, Hiroshi-sama.
It's embarrassing Youko-sama learns of this.
So be it.
I said no!
Ouch...
What are you doing?
Youko-sama, is this all right?
Well, if it's too fine, the floor will get too sticky.
So this should be fine.
I'll go get the ingredients.
I'll whip something delicious!
OK!
Ruri-san!
Beware of the splattering oil.
Y-Yes.
That works I guess.
The radish is missing.
Are we making radish tempura?
No we're not. Grated radish as sauce makes it extra delicious.
I see.
Watch the fire while I buy it.
Sure.
The tempuras should almost be ready.
Youko! Ruri!
Where did they go? Can't be helped.
They don't know tempura tastes best when eaten hot.
Then I shall have a taste.
It's burning.
It's cold.
Sheesh.
I'm back!
Youko-sama?
Sorry, I decided to take a shower first.
W-W-Where did you go?
Shopping.
Right. Tempura goes well with radish.
Why are you so flustered?
But we love each other so much.
I love you! But we can't.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, what are you doing?
Weren't you yelling at me to wake up this morning?
So if you have this...
Then what?
Tell me what happens?
It's almost done. Just wait and see.
-Isn't it cute?
I thought it was something else.
That's mean! This is my voice. When did you record it?
When you wake me up every morning.
I tape recorded your voice in bed.
Dubbed: Ruri Alarm.
Hear it again.
It's morning. Hiroshi-sama.
Wake up! It's morning!
Geez, it's morning!
Since when do I yell this much?
Right. It's a ogre's voice that spares no one to sleep.
That's mean.
I asked Hiroshi to look after Ruri-san so that he becomes outgoing again.
He is definitely much happier now.
Full of vigor.
But.
But...
But the effect is too much.
I see it. It's the sea.
The sea during winter seems melancholic.
Melancholic?
Yeah, really.
Compared to the buzz during summer,
the sea during winter is almost deserted making it sad.
Idiot!
Stop flying, Ruri!
Ruri, don't float in midair. Come down!
Sheesh, look.
I  was careless.
Hey, Hiroshi-sama.
What would you do if I wasn't around.
Take for instance.
Let's see... relieve.
No one to disturb me in the mornings.
I won't eat strange cookings.
I don't have to care about others while watching films.
And... and...
Why am I a Snow woman?
I can't I have contact with people?
Why can't I touch the people I love?
Not even an embrace.
Ruri...
I hate the winter sea.
It's like looking at myself.
I hate it!
What's wrong, Ruri?
Ruri!
Ruri?
I can't move.
No!
Why? Why are you getting in my way?
No! Please leave Hiroshi-sama alone.
What? What happened, Ruri?
There's someone else in my body.
What?
I managed to suppress it.
Who knows when it'll come.
Ruri.
Your body is warm.
Hiroshi-sama, hug me. Please hug me.
I beg you. I'm afraid.
Please, Hiroshi-sama.
Ruri.
Hiroshi-sama.
Hiroshi-sama... I can't anymore...
It hurts!
Hiroshi-sama!
I'm so happy, Hiroshi-sama.
Hiroshi-sama.
Ruri.
I'm sorry, Hiroshi-sama.
Ruri?
I...
I want to be with you forever.
But I can't. I'm already at my limit.
Ruri.
Hiroshi-sama, don't forget about me.
Be happy.
I'll be fine as long as you're happy.
Farewell, Hiroshi-sama.
Ruri.
Ruri!
Ruri? Ruri?
Ruri...