Shinshou
Genmukan
Epiloge.2
~Love, Truth, and That Which Should Be Protected~
I'm so sorry.
It looks like you got caught up in this
mess because of me, Nozomi-chan.
Kaoru-san, where are Imada-san and the others?
It must've been an ordeal for you.
Just relax and try to have a nice time, if only for a little while.
Kaoru-san, your breasts pressed up against
my back are so nice and warm.
Thanks.
My body is... getting very warm.
It's so warm!
I feel so happy and it feels so good!
Does it hurt?
Just a little.
Those bastards.
Have they no respect for a woman's body?
I hope they go to hell.
Women are delicate and sensitive to touch.
If only they treated women more gently and softly,
the experience would be more enjoyable.
What lovely sounds you're making.
This feels wonderful!
You're so gentle.
All my bad feelings are disappearing.
You're very wet now, so everything should be fine.
Kaoru-san, why did Imada-san do such a thing?
Those bastards are after Ayano-san and the Nakakouji fortune.
So Lady Ayano is still alive?
Yes, she's alive.
Though because of special circumstances...
she's living in an obscure location for now.
U-Umm, Kaoru-san...
I don't care what happens to me...
but please protect Lady Ayano for me.
Thank you.
I thought I just heard Lady Ayano's voice.
Yes, I thought I heard it too.
In time, I'll have a chance to escape.
No, even if I do escape, I have no place to go.
I don't have a home.
O-Oh, no.
Why did I...
Kido-san didn't come to save me.
I'm sorry.
I made you wait, Nozomi.
Kido-san!
What horrible wounds!
Why? Why?
Why did you come to me when you're so badly wounded?
I... What should I say to you?
Please tell me, Kido-san!
He's so badly beaten up because of me, to tell the truth.
But where are Imada and the others right now?
Oh, those guys are knocked out over there.
Should we call an ambulance?
If you want to, go right ahead.
Kido-san, I sincerely thank you.
You've had a worse time than me.
You should rest.
I'm fine.
Please have your way with me.
I'm begging you.
Fill my body up with you, Kido-san!
Please, help me forget about everything!
Okay.
What's wrong?
Does it hurt?
No, it's just...
I... I don't have much experience with kisses.
Oh?
And even now, I feel like all you want is my body.
I see.
Then, in that case, I'll give you plenty of kisses from now on.
I see. I...
It's okay for me to be with Kido-san from now on.
Oh, Kido-san, how dare you!
How dare the two of them have all the fun!
And it's not like I can go interrupt Nozomi-chan.
Won't you kiss me now?
P-Please stop.
Go ahead, cum in my mouth.
I won't let it spill out.
No, I can't do that.
I want to cum inside you.
All right.
As you wish.
I'll reveal all of the embarrassing parts of my body to you.
Nozomi...
I don't mind.
As long as it brings you joy, I'll...
I'll do anything.
Don't lick there.
Not that deep! Your tongue...
So you're finally wet.
Yes, I'm sorry.
It was so tight before that I was scared.
But I don't mind.
I won't be jealous of your former partner.
I'm very... wet.
Kido-san, I... I can't... I can't...
Then, are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Please make use of my body.
Yes, right there.
I'm completely ready.
Inside. Come inside, please, Master!
It's coming inside.
So unbelievably big and thick...
It's filling me... filling me up!
"Master"?
You don't like it?
But from now on, you are my... my...
I don't mind.
If you want to call me "Master," you can.
Thank you, Master.
It feels good.
It feels so good!
You're so tight. It's wonderful!
Thank you very much.
Please cum inside me.
I'm almost...
Master!
No! Why?
Why did you do that?
I can't take it!
Please starting moving!
Please have mercy.
Don't leave me alone.
The thing about women is that they're
most sensitive just before they cum.
Amazing!
My head is going blank.
It probably would,
because your insides are having quite a ride.
I've never felt like this before.
So deep... To the deepest... deepest part of me.
I love this! I'll go all the way for you!
My body is entirely yours.
You're amazing!
Your insides are rubbing against me so tightly.
I'm hitting your cervix, too.
I feel like I'm going to burst!
I'm almost at my limit.
Yes! Me too!
Cum inside me!
It's coming... It's coming inside me.
So much! So much!
But still not enough.
Even though you just came, it's still so hard and strong!
Is there still more?
Yeah.
Your body wants more, doesn't it?
I didn't cum enough.
Even if you tell me to stop, I'll keep going.
What do you think?
If it pleases you, use my body as you wish.
That is my... my...
That is my duty to you, Master.
Okay, then. One more time...
I'll cum, not leaving a single drop behind..
Take it all!
Amazing. It's too good.
I feel like I've lost my mind
But... But...
Something this amazing is inside me?
I wonder if I'll get pregnant?
Showing off something so intense like that?
That would get anyone off.
No need to be embarrassed about it.
I feel the same way.
You're beautiful, my dear.
You're still so pure,
almost like you were a virgin until recently.
I wish I could be more gentle.
In that case, be more gentle!
This time, it's your turn.
Harder! Deeper, please!
Mess me up!
Tease me more, okay?
Damn it, you bitch!
You bitch!
You bitch...
You bitch! You bitch!
Yes! Yes!
Huh?
Sensei! It's urgent!
Ayano-san has begun to move.
Deeper... Yes!
Hurry...
I'm... cumming!
This is a big surprise.
Is this really Lady Ayano?
It surprised me as well.
But Ayano-san is actually 27 years old.
This might be the way she's supposed to look.
But, in just a few months?
Changing so much?
Three months ago, when I rescued her from the mansion,
she began to mature rapidly.
Looking back on it, it might be the result
of the fire or other psychological shock.
Nothing is really clear.
According to Kaoru-san's explanation,
Lady Ayano was unable to open her
eyes while her body was maturing.
But, even though her body has grown, she's still herself,
and she's very pretty.
Still, there don't seem to be any medical complications.
However, she keeps on sleeping.
I can hear everyone's voices.
Am I asleep?
Why can't I wake up?
According to Kaoru-san's explanation,
something traumatic happened to me recently.
Something that happened when Kido-san rescued Kaoru-san and me,
and we were staying at the hotel.
Yes, at that time...
As I thought...
This costume really does the trick.
Master, I'm... very happy.
It's hard like a rod.
I can feel the shape of it really well.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Let me cum!
Please? Please?
Please, you say?
I've been filled to the brim, but you'll give me more, won't you?
I’m losing my strength, could you please lift my leg?
Okay.
You're really tight.
That's right.
Rub them together.
Rub them more!
Okay.
How's this?
Nozomi, I'm cumming.
Yes! Please cum inside of me again and again!
Amazing!
There’s so much inside me!
Now that you mention it...
Lately, I've felt like I've been hearing Ayano's voice.
M-Me too!
At first, I thought I was just hearing things.
H-Huh? Wh-What does that mean?
I think it's a stupid theory,
but maybe it's a reaction to the elevated feelings
people experience at the mansion?
Even so, she's matured very beautifully.
Onii-chan!
Here.
Yes, put it in deeper.
More!
Lick my insides more.
Yes, like that. More!
Yes, more! Right there!
Yes!
Oh, no! No, no!
Don't tease me!
No, no, I was wrong.
Tease me! Tease me more!
Please!
Kido-san! Kido-san, are you listening?
Why are you getting hard here of all places?
She's hospitalized!
Still, it's a valid thought.
What about you? What are you doing?
I'm just making sure of things.
As I thought, she reacts to perverted thoughts.
Which means exactly what you think.
Why are we paired like this?
It's just wrong!
We're recreating the scene from before, so just enjoy it.
I'm sorry. I'm not wet at all.
It's a little tight.
I'll make myself ready right away,
so please be patient.
Right away. I'll be ready right away!
No! Not so fast!
Go slower.
Give me more time, please!
My pussy will break!
If the hospital finds out about this, what will they do to us?
But your body really seems to have taken a liking to this dildo!
No, it hasn't...
It doesn't like the...
Still, your body is so beautiful.
Master, it's so hard.
Not so fast. It hurts.
It's swirling and going crazy inside me.
All the way in deep... Tickling me...
It’s making my body feel like it's going to fall apart!
There's a reaction!
Yes!
Even so, this scene is really gorgeous.
If only I had some alcohol, I'd be the luckiest man alive.
Master, your firmness must be violating Lady Ayano instead of me.
So violently.
I know I mustn't be jealous,
but my feelings are confused.
I can't hold on!
I've reached my limit!
Lady Ayano's eyes have opened,
but her consciousness hasn't returned.
Not yet.
This time, we've decided to bond our bodies more closely,
so I think we're almost there.
Just a bit more, and we'll have her back.
Is it okay to do her like this?
We're doing this for her sake.
If it's our duty, I guess we'd better do it.
We don't exactly have a choice, do we?
She wants me?
Her skin is like a bisque doll.
See? See, Kido-san?
What cute breasts.
Now, let's get her all wet.
Kido-san, watch carefully.
Her skin is so pretty.
I'm starting to feel hot myself.
Very well.
Let's just thrust into it from the start.
What a body.
It feels like I'm falling apart.
Please fill her full of soft, warm juice.
Amazing.
From the top of my head... to the tips of my toes...
I'm... feeling... good... right now...
More.
I want this to continue, I think.
Rip me apart with your strong power.
My everything... Ravage it all. I don't mind.
Everyone...
Let's all... cum together.
Oni-chan...
Was I asleep the whole time?
My Lady!
And so, Lady Ayano opened her eyes.
I hope Kaoru-san becomes a doctor.
Not again!
Why does it have to be girl-on-girl?
I just barely gave up my virginity!
You're so young!
Women must experience undying pleasure!
So hot! So hot!
Yes, very nice!
I love this.
Master, please use my body as you wish!
Please... Please punish me. Then, cum inside!
I've always... I've always been waiting for you.
From now on, you'll stay with me, right?
You'll stay with me forever, won't you?
Hi, this is the Kido Detective Agency.
Kido Detective Agency
Yes, Kido is out on business right now.
Yes.
Oh, no. We have others.
A President, director, receptionist, maid, and a driver...
Besides myself, we have a staff that can assist you with any need.
So please look forward to our services.
Aw, give it back!
Enclosed in darkness, your milky slin seems to melt away,
And the warmth of your breath seems to leave you.
I sense a burning passion in your eyes,
But it shimmers away as time flickers by.
I exist only to find the wings you have lost.
Without a heart,
I can only peer up at this fixed utopia.
At least let me embrace this love.