You've gotten really good, Karen...
Thank you.
H! reward you.
What do you want me to do today?
I want you to fuck me from
behind while standing up please.
You're so adorable, Karen.
Master!
What a horrible dream...
Where am I?
That's right... I was captured and...
They raped me all night long...
I swore I wouldn't go back
to being like this again.
My body yearns for a man...
I won't lose. I won't go back to being like that.
Good morning, Karen.
What do you want me to do to you today?
Venus File
Part Z
Masafumi! Masafumi!
Masafumi!
What is it, Yayoi?
We should call the police!
It's useless.
The police won't listen.
How do you know that?
Because they didn't with my sister.
One of their accomplices controls the police!
They have that kind of power?
Rio, where are you going?
Where do you think? I'm going to look for Karen!
The guy who kidnapped
Karen killed my sister Aya!
Who knows what they'll do to her!
Rio!
Masafumi, what should we do...
There's no point in standing here.
I'm going to go talk to the police.
I need you to stay here and let us
know if any new information comes in.
Okay.
Karen... Aya...
Sis...
Aya, give me strength.
You're still glaring at me.
What a turn on.
Let go of me!
What? We had so much fun last night.
That's not me!
You think so?
Who was the one writhing in pleasure
from being fucked by multiple men?!
That hurts! Stop!
It hurts? I bet it feels good.
That's enough, Oguro.
Karen...
Karen, are you here?
Huh? ls anybody here?
Excuse me. Who are you?
Hello. I'm Karen's friend.
Is Karen out?
Karen... Karen...
She was kidnapped!
Tell me everything.
That's enough.
She's a valuable pawn for our game.
Besides, we still need her
as bait for our other pawn.
Who?
I know.
That's why I'm going to train her starting today.
Train me? You've got to be joking!
I won't submit to you no matter
how many times you rape me.
Even if you try, the training you've
received won't be easily forgotten.
Women will always submit if
you push the right buttons.
That's not true!
You want to bet?
Bet?
I'll only use your breasts.
You'll submit to me and the only
thing I'll touch will be your breasts.
If you're able to withstand that,
then I'll let you go.
Aren't we overconfident?
We'll just see if it goes your way.
We have an agreement then.
No matter how good he is, he can't
make me submit just with my breasts.
I swear I will resist!
I'll fondle you all over.
Look how hard you are.
Your nipples are like a man's cock.
I bet you jerk off your
nipples when you masturbate.
Whatever!
They're shaped like this because
you masturbated too hard.
You're wrong.
So you were born like this?
You're holding up pretty well.
Since it's just your breasts, I'm using some stuff.
No, it's cold!
What is this? Did you...?
It's just lotion.
That should be more than enough for you.
You love the suction.
Your moans are getting sweeter.
It's nice to just get your breasts fondled isn't it?
I'll make you cum from your breasts!
This can't be... I'm going to...
just from my breasts... I...
No! I'm going to cum!
This can't be... How can I cum from just
having my breasts fondled?
Well? Did you cum?
Not yet!
You squirted all that milk,
but you haven't cum yet?
Feel how hard I am.
Stop!
You want it?
Not in the least!
That's right.
Our bet is that you're going
to cum just with your breasts.
That hurts!
Ejaculation is the best when you
hold it back until the last second.
My breasts are filling up...
Your breasts are becoming
more sensitive, right?
No! I'm going to cum again...
You're twitching because
you want to squirt milk.
I'm not done with you yet.
My nipples are throbbing because I can't cum...
I think I'm going to explode.
Hey, stop rubbing against me like that.
You want me to fuck you?
You want me to thrust it all the way inside...
...and pound you hard, right Karen?
I can't anymore...
Don't hold it back... Please.
Please fondle me here as well.
I win...
You came the minute I stuck it in.
How is it Karen? Does it feel good?
Yes!
You scream in joy when you're raped.
That's the true you!
You're a masochistic slut
who can't live without sex!
This pleasure brings back so many memories.
Pleasure and sweet pain...
Hurt and sorrow, but happiness Hes beyond that,
along with a comfortable fatigue.
That's right.
I swore I would devote
everything to this pleasure.
I am your slave!
Yes! It's amazing.
It's all the way inside.
Harder! Fuck me harder!
More! More! I'm going to cum!
Okay! Cum all over the place!
It's like my nipples.
It throbs and pours lots of cum inside me.
That was a great cum, Karen.
Fuck me more... My nipples ache...
Fine, but before that...
I have a present for you.
Thank you.
Guess we didn't have to lure her after all.
There it is!
Finally, Karen's necklace has responded!
Wait for me, Karen! I'm on my way!
Police
It's no use. They won't listen.
Are they on the take, just like Rio said?
Hello? Rio?
I know where Karen is.
Really?
Yes, I'm following the tracking
device in Karen's necklace.
It only works within a limited
area, so it took me a while...
I see. I'm glad...
I'm going in.
What?
Wait! H! be right over!
There's no time.
I'll email you the location,
but don't contact me for a while.
New email
This is...
It's pretty far from here.
You must be Masafumi.
Yayoi told me about you.
You're...?
No one's calling.
I'm Yanagi. Karen's friend.
Karen's...?
We exchange information.
I've heard about Rio from Karen, too.
It's too dangerous to try
and save Karen by herself.
Yes. We need to get to their
hideout as soon as we can.
I know.
Damn!
I want to fuck her, too!
It's just our luck that we
have to be on guard tonight.
I can't take it anymore!
Maybe I should jerk off.
Stop! Don't do that here!
Hi!
Who the hell are you?
Be nice. I just brought you guys some stuff.
Are you Oguro's bitch?
What the hell?
It'll work better if you're wet!
Karen, wait for me!
Karen!
Karen! Get ahold of yourself!
They've drugged you!
No, we didn't.
You're...
Long time no see.
I've finally found you!
How dare you kill my sister Aya!
That was an accident.
It was just an aphrodisiac, but I guess it was bad.
We only use the good stuff now,
so any woman can take it.
Did you give that to Karen?
I already told you we didn't.
Karen already has the
foundations of a sex slave.
So much so that she doesn't
need any aphrodisiacs.
Foundations?
Was she hiding it from you?
W-What are you talking about?
Do you remember that
incident a few years back...
...when a sex slave trafficking ring
was busted deep in the mountains?
Tepes Headquarters Exposed
That's when we took Karen in.
Tepes Headquarters Exposed The girls were
trained and drugged in order to be sold.
The girls were trained and
drugged in order to be sold.
She was one of them...
So, that's what she was talking about...
So you knew about it...
Karen worked hard.
She fought off her sexual urges for months...
I helped her through her rehabilitation process.
Once Karen was able to live
a normal life, she met Rio.
In order to save others like her, she founded...
...the Goddess Investigation Agency
and tried to start her life over.
But if I work on her,
she'll be back to her old self in just two days.
Do you think I'm going to believe you?
Yeah, you'll find out for yourself.
K... Karen...
This must be it.
Are you sure you're going to be okay?
I'm a detective too!
Even if I'm just an apprentice...
Plus, I have this!
Yeah... But you still need
to have the motivation...
It'll be okay.
You see...
I understand. Please take care of Karen.
I will!
Let's see... I need to get ready, myself.
What should I get you for your birthday?
Sis, what do you want?
I can't afford that!
Oh, I know! You're terrible at waking up...
...so maybe I should get you
a really loud alarm clock.
Aya...
Where am I?
Welcome to Heaven.
Although there's no God here.
You're a lost sheep who will
be raped and trained here.
I'm not going to be trained by you!
Not me.
Karen...
Karen, no... You've got to snap out of it!
Rio, this is the true me.
Karen! No! Stop!
Your nipples are getting hard.
You're feeling it, aren't you Rio?
Look how wet you are...
Raise your ass.
No!
You're so wet!
Stop! Stop it, Karen!
Here, I'll make you cum.
Make your pleasure juice spew out!
No!
I... I'm going to... I'm going to cum...
My turn next.
I'm going to get you back for earlier.
It tastes like beer and cum.
I'll give you what you want.
This is awesome!
Her hot labia is sucking on to my dick!
You're such naughty boys...
Look how hard you are.
Fine.
I'll make everyone cum.
Come closer.
S-She's too good!
Look at her seductive look...
It's such a turn on!
Feels good, right?
You can cum whenever.
I... I'm gonna cum...
My breasts are gushy...
It's hot and yummy...
What? You're hard again?
Such naughty boys...
Be good and take turns fucking me, okay?
Yes!
What a view.
Yeah! Jerk it off!
Take that!
Harder! Fuck me more!
It's all the way inside!
No! Not my nipples!
Don't rub up against it!
What a dirty face, Rio.
K... Karen...
Karen, no!
Don't lie. Feel how wet you are down there.
Karen! No!
Your nipples are rubbing up against mine!
Karen's nipples are...
T-They're going inside!
Does it feel good?
It feels good, right Rio?
It feels so good, Karen!
Then I'll make you feel even better!
No!
Not you!
Stop!
How does it feel to be raped by the
man who killed your sister, Rio?
Is it despicable? Or does it feel good?
He's my sister's killer!
I'm being raped by...
Please fuck me, too.
Fine then.
It feels good master!
One more time Rio!
No!
It's hot! My pussy and nipples are throbbing!
Your nipples feel so good.
I'm going to cum with lots of milk.
Here I cum!
I'm going to cum... I'm going to
cum while being raped by him...
You guys are amazing.
I'll train you well so you guys will become...
...the best sex slaves no
matter where you're sold.
Who's there?! At a time like this...
This song may mean nothing to you,
but to two women, it means everything.
One swore to avenge the death of her sister.
The other vowed to start her life over.
What are you talking about?
Be careful... The Goddesses have awoken...
What?
You've come to your senses?
Yes, although this is the worst way to wake up.
I was with the other men and gave
them medicine that would suppress...
...their sexual desire.
But the medicine only helped a little.
It was their strong will...
...and Aya's melody that woke them up.
Then I'll just train them again!
You came to help, but you
can't do anything by yourself!
True.
By the way.
Haven't you wondered where
this song is coming from?
Hello?
This is the special operations team.
What?
No one move!
Take the women as hostages!
Y-Yes!
I'm on a roll!
If you go near them again I'll shoot you for real!
Y-You've got to be kidding me!
Run!
You'll get arrested for indecent
exposure if you go out like that.
Of course, the kidnapping,
sexual assault, abuse...
...and narcotics possession
charges will be a lot more severe.
This is the end, Oguro!
I really want to kill you myself, but...
...Aya... Sweet Aya would
have never wanted that.
You'll atone for your evil deeds in jail.
Atone my evil deeds, eh?
Are you all right, Karen?
You saved me again, Yanagi.
It was nothing.
I "just happened" to be passing by and...
..."just happened" to stumble
upon what was happening.
I guess you couldn't ignore what was going on,
even though someone might be pressuring you.
Thank you, Masafumi...
Not at all...
Damn that Yanagi!
She ignored Dad's threats
and mobilized the unit.
I don't have a choice...
Oguro...needs to disappear...
Watch out!
Is this...
This can't be...
The game's over, but it's okay.
If Oguro dies, I won't be exposed.
I wouldn't want to cause problems for Dad...
What game should I play next?
A few months later
Congratulations!
Thank you.
We'll be able to start work at the
Goddess Investigation Agency again.
Yes, though I'm still a little weak.
I see.
So Masafumi was taken down
every time you felt the urge!
Well, um...
You're not denying it.
I think I just heard something
that really bothers me!
To Karen leaving the hospital!
Cheers!
C... Cheers!
Are you guys are changing the subject?
Masafumi! What's going on?
Masafumi!
Well... Um...
Hey! Masafumi!
W-Wait! Yayoi!
Yeah! Do it!