New
Holy slut Academy
Hooker Diaries
Will this be all, ma'am?
Well then, please enjoy your...
Yes, that'll be all.
O-Okay.
P-Please enjoy your session.
Wait, you're not thinking that she's better than me, are you?
N-No...
Mister, you're not circumcised?
Well... Well, at least 70% of men in this country are the same.
I like it, you know.
Uncircumcised dicks.
Let's have a look at it now.
Let me see...
Ta-da!
Wow, it's still limp but it's already big!
I wonder how much bigger it will get.
Take this!
Rub, rub, rub, rub...
I'm not letting you off yet.
It's slowly starting to get harder.
I'll insert my finger here,
and twirl it around the tip.
I guess it's time to taste it already.
This is quite good.
Oh, it's grown quite big now.
It looks a lot livelier.
Oh wow, it's completely unsheathed now.
Now this is what I call a grown-up dick.
I'm rubbing it right now...
Rub the dick, rub, rub...
Rub the dick, rub, rub the unsheathed dick, rub, rub...
See? Feels good, doesn't it?
Rub, rub, rub, rub...
Now you're my hostage.
Just kidding, I'm just saving it.
Did you panic?
I'm actually collecting pictures of me sucking dicks.
Do you want to see?
From sheathed dicks, to unsheathed dicks,
there's red ones and black ones, there
are lots of interesting dicks to see!
No... thanks.
*Grip*
Mister, what shall we do with your big grown-up dick?
You don't plan on fucking my cute, little pussy with that are you?
Okay then, fuck me.
Totally make a mess of my pussy with your huge, grand dick.
You were expecting us to do it eventually right?
Because I'm student at that slut academy.
See? Your thing is already bulging.
I'm going to squeeze out every last drop that you can squirt okay?
These balls taste delicious.
Balls, balls, balls, balls...
Squirt, squirt, squirt, squirt already.
You usually cum when I do this right?
I really want to see it.
Rub, rub, rub
Rub, rub, rub the dick...
Rub, rub, rub the uncircumcised dick...
And go squirt, squirt!
Big dick go squirt, squirt!
Wow, your big dick is starting to get wet now!
Maybe I can tit fuck it without lotion with that!
Do you want me to rub your dick between
my soft and tender flesh?
I w-want to.
Well?
How are my boobs?
Now you really want to grind it in, right?
There, rub it more.
Rub it more inside my boob pussy.
Drill it into my boob pussy!
Dick, dick, dick...!
Make your uncircumcised dick cum!
Are you about to cum?
Is it about to cum?
Oh, it's about to come out!
Squirt it out then!
Squirt out that semen!
Squirt it all on my boob pussy!
Make your... Make your semen go squirt, squirt!
Release everything in your balls on me!
I'm cumming...
It came out! It squirted out!
It went squirt, squirt! The whiter thing went squirt, squirt!
Your uncircumcised dick is still twitching!
Excuse me.
Look, the one you noticed earlier is back.
U-Umm... Sorry for intruding!
No, you don't have to go.
Umm... ma'am, I would have to ask you to stop doing that here.
Eh? What do you mean? I don't understand.
Well... I mean having sex.
You mean putting this big, grown-up dick...
...inside my wet pussy,
and cumming afterwards?
D-Don't ask me!
Anyway, I meant whatever it is that you are doing right now!
Why?
Dicks fucking pussies,
is pretty normal you know.
You keep on using those weird excuses...
At the very least, it's normal not to in here!
Oh no, something's wrong Ms. Waitress!
This is bad, Ms. Waitress!
Come here and see quickly!
Y-Yes, what is it?
A-Are you alright?
Take this!
What the hell is this?
There, now there's cum milk all over you.
How was it?
Wanna do a threesome next?
Please, behave yourself already!
Does that feel good?
It feels great.
I... I never thought that you'd be so good at this.
No way, I'm technically a slut you know.
I love giving a handjob to your big, uncircumcised dick.
And I also love getting fucked by it.
Look, my slutty and already wet pussy, minus the panties.
Oh my, it already got really aroused with just that handjob.
Wanna see it?
My very wet and slutty pussy?
You want to see it right?
You're dick is even twitching at the
thought of looking under the Skirt,
of someone at an age that might seem like your daughter.
Oh well.
I'll give you a very special service.
Oh my, Mister you're looking at my hole too much.
Hey, don't just lick it!
Oh yeah, I have a good idea.
You see, I'm quite experienced at cheerleading.
I'll be cheering for you, so do your very best, okay?
Masturbation.
In other words, jacking off.
I want to see you jack off in front of me.
But...
I’ve gotten a little exhausted from all that rubbing, you know.
I knew you were good at this.
The way you do it just seem so different.
Go, rub, rub, rub!
Do you best now!
Rub, rub, rub, rub...
Your dick looks very lively as you continue rubbing it Mister.
It looks quite good.
Here, I'll give you some porn material to help you.
Can you see it?
You can look closer.
I'll also...
My pussy...
Look very carefully.
My pussy is already very wet and sticky.
Oh my, this is just too close.
Don't look at my pussy so much...
Oopsie.
Do you want to look at my pussy more?
Okay, you can look at it more closely now.
All that rub, rub, rub.
Your dick goes rub, rub, rub.
Just jacking off rub, rub, rub.
Your aroused dick is going rub, rub, rub.
Hi, ho!
Masturbating Mister!
Rub, rub, hi, ho!
Your uncircumcised dick!
Mister, you're rubbing your dick too much.
You really like that, eh?
T-The way you say it just...
Here, Mister.
You want that inserted into me badly right?
Look, my pussy's over here!
Can you see the lips opening and closing?
Oops, not just yet.
I want my ass to have a taste first.
You like that, right?
Ass rubbing I mean.
Oh wow.
Just by your big dick rubbing against my pussy and ass,
I'm already feeling very horny.
Your dick rubbing against my wet pussy feels great.
My ass feels great too, right?
You feel like cumming already,
with this dick rubbing against my ass, right?
Oh my, Mister what are you doing?
This is bad, your dick is rubbing inside, pushing into me!
It's completely inside now!
Oh no, my hips won't stop.
I just can't stop rubbing against your dick!
It's inside.
Your dick is inside!
It feels tight!
Move, move your dick.
Rub your dick into my pussy!
Your dick... Your dick feels great!
Your dick... is rubbing hard inside!
Fuck me while pinching both lips!
L-Like this?
That's good, that's good.
It feels really good!
Mister, it's so stiff as it rubs deep inside!
I’m starting to feel weak because of it!
I love this dick. I love this dick.
I love dicks!
I love your hard thrusting dick!
I love your uncircumcised dick!
Dicks, dicks, dicks.
Dicks feel good.
It's coming out.
It's cumming inside me.
It's pumping cum inside me.
And it keeps on pumping it inside.
I can feel it, how it pumps, how the cum flows deep inside me.
Squeeze everything out, everything out of those balls.
Squeeze every drop of thick cum out of it.
Huh? Mister, are you still alive?
l am, but my cum...
Let's stay like this for a bit longer.