Stop!
Please stop it!
You're so wet.
I wanna mess up your pussy real bad!
No!
Stop!
Look, you're soaking wet!
Now, it's time...
...for this.
Thank you very much!
Huh?
It was very interesting.
Oh, okay.
Please come again.
Yes.
She is very cute.
But even she is...
No, it's not the same.
Where in the hell is Karin Hisasaka?
I usually see her around this place...
Huh? Why?
Well...
After that experience, nothing
seems to be fun anymore.
If you want to ride again,
I suggest you bring a guest.
Ah, there she is!
It's Karin!
Such an innocent smile...
Hey!
What are you sneaking around here for?
It's nothing.
What, you see some
cute chick or something?
You know I'm not like you.
What is that supposed to mean?
You're using my secret
schoolgirl database too, right?
Hey!
I sort of got this special bonus.
Let's go for a drink tonight.
I got totally shitfaced the other
night and missed the last train.
I'll pass.
What?
That's not really a big deal.
Well, I was able to ride
something special as a result...
Come on, let's go!
Hey Tamura-kun!
There's nobody at the counter.
Hurry up and get back to work!
I'm really sorry.
I'm getting back to work.
What is it, Takumi-kun?
How come you're staring at me like that?
No, it's not like that...
Unbelievable...
Young boys like you are always
lacking in concentration.
What the heck?
Chicks like this are no fun at all.
But...
Get back to work.
You might be a guest one day...
Kyoko-senpai.
What? A guest?
That's right.
A special train after
the last train of the night?
Yes.
Do you have something like that?
We have one at the beginning of
the year and the end of the year.
No. Do you have anything else?
No, I'm afraid we don't.
I see.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
No luck here either.
I was able to exit from the
other side of the station, but...
I guess it was only for one time.
Hey you!
I know you!
If you're awake, get
your ass outta here!
You're getting in my way!
It's past 1:00 AM, but...
Oh shit!
There's plenty of empty seats!
Excuse me.
Oh man...
I feel sick.
Why is everyone standing?
Plus, they're all men...
Oh well.
I feel sick anyway...
I'm not getting any better.
It stopped.
Thank you for riding
the Midnight Sleazy Train.
Midnight Sleazy Train?
We're finally here!
What's going to happen?
We were waiting for you!
Hurry up and begin!
Thanks for coming, Karin.
Here, come on in.
Yes.
Karin?
Karin Hisasaka!
Now, come here.
Here we go!
We were waiting for you, Karin-chan.
We'll take good care of you again.
No, I don't want to do this anymore!
You don't have to hide it, Karin.
You're enjoying this as much as we are.
That's not true.
Well, let's find out
if it's true or not.
We want to see you get dirty again.
That's awful.
It's just awful!
What's wrong, Karin?
Are you crying with joy?
Karin-chan, you must really
love doing this, huh?
This can't be...
You're very cute, Karin-chan.
I just love it when
you look embarrassed.
Your cheeks are so soft.
Wait Karin-chan.
Don't leave us.
There!
The guest for tonight in the sixth car...
...is none other than Miss Karin
Hisasaka, a current student at...
...the prestigious Saint
Anthreum University.
I know her.
The girl from Anthreum!
What a hottie!
Stop! No!
Everyone, please enjoy the
show until you're satisfied!
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
No!
Oji-sama, help me!
That's right, crying out loud
is very important.
You sure know what to do, Karin.
What are you saying?
I really don't want this!
You sure about that?
Let's see if your cunt
is soaking wet, shall we?
Show it to us.
Like this!
All right, all right!
Spread those legs wide!
Hey, I can't see very well!
Let me pull up that skirt!
No!
Please stop it!
I'm scared!
There we go!
No, no!
Please don't touch me!
No!
Oh man, it's really the
school uniform of Anthreum!
Pull up her skirt!
N-No!
No!
What's going on?
I thought Karin was lustful and
enjoyed being treated this way.
No, no, no!
It hurts, it really hurts!
Wow, your nipples are really hard!
Your cunt is getting very moist.
Did you wet yourself?
That's not true!
Please let me go!
I don't want to do it anymore!
You mean...
All those guys are doing her?
So this is the Midnight Sleazy Train...
This kind of activity is
taking place in every car?
No, please!
More...
Fondle me more!
You're very honest!
That's right.
Women who are unwilling
to be pleasured are boring.
There, there!
It's a silk tie!
Feels very special, doesn't it?
This is an expensive
leather wallet full of money!
There, there, there!
Poor people can't enjoy
themselves like this, you know.
You really like rich people, don't you?
Yes, I really like rich people!
I don't like this!
You enjoy this more than we do!
No, no!
I don't enjoy this at all!
But your cunt is all sticky!
Let me take a look.
Wow, you're right!
Her body is saying yes, even
if her mind is saying no.
There, there, there, there!
There now, Karin-chan.
If you moan too much, everyone's
going to know you're a pervert.
These guys are good.
They pinpoint a woman's weakness
with accuracy and go for the attack.
I can do it much better than them.
Well look at that, it's really sticky.
It's flowing out like crazy!
It's almost time to
eat your favorite dish.
Here it is, Karin.
Your cunt is drooling so much!
No!
Here, lick it!
There.
Good, good, good.
How cute!
No matter how cruel we are, you
always end up wet and satisfied.
Hey, this way!
No! Please don't move!
What are you saying, Karin-chan?
If I don't move, then there's
no point in doing this.
Your cunt is real nice and tight!
Don't forget to service
the other men too!
Hey Karin-chan, grab my cock!
Mine too, Karin-chan!
Mine too!
Hey, Karin-chan!
Karin-chan!
Grab mine too!
Over here too!
Wow, it's amazing!
Karin-chan, you're such a dirty girl!
Karin, you're just happy to
receive this kind of pleasure.
You're a no-good bitch!
You're looking real good there.
Crying while sucking!
What an unbelievable bitch you are...
The more you cry, the
more your cunt tightens!
Even your asshole is getting tight!
No! It's hot!
It's really hot!
I don't really want this...
I don't really want this, but...
My cunt is very, very, very hot!
It's hot!
Now Karin...
Lick it!
Hey Karin-chan, take a look at this schlong!
She's really working those hips!
Wow, she's really naughty!
Karin-chan, you really like this.
Am I right?
Do you like it, Karin-chan?
I really like this!
That's really good...
The way you suck!
You're on a roll, Karin-chan!
I don't want this, but my
body moves automatically.
If I see a cock, I get very excited!
Hot!
It's really hot!
Everyone's hot and smelly cock juice...
Give me more!
Wow Karin-chan, you're covered
in lots of cock juice!
I'm ejaculating!
Me too!
What's wrong?
First time, huh?
I'm sure you're surprised but since
you're here on the Sleazy Train...
Why not give it a try?
No, I...
What is it?
I don't really feel good.
Karin-chan is my prize.
I brought her on this Sleazy Train.
You're ashamed, aren't you?
I was too, when I first started.
I know, I know.
True.
I'm ashamed of myself.
Doing some girl another guy has won
over means you're taking leftovers.
I will never accept that kind of thing!
I don't feel good.
I'm covered in cock juice and...
I'm very, very, very, very...
Nobody's here.
The floor's covered with semen.
I guess it wasn't a dream after all.
If you're awake, get
your ass outta here!
You're getting in my way!
I know what you seek but what are
you going to do after you find it?
Once more...
I want to ride that
Sleazy Train once more.
You seem to have talent.
But...
You know?
You know it, don't you?
Take it easy!
You really want to
ride the Sleazy Train?
Yes, of course.
I'll do anything to get on that train.
All right.
If you bring a sacrificial
lamb you may board the train.
A sacrificial lamb?
You mean a guest?
That's right.
A sacrificial lamb to provide
great pleasure to the other riders.
Bring the sacrifice
over to the Sleazy Train.
Your admission to the Sleazy Train
depends on your scouting ability.
I understand.
If you pick out a
sacrifice, come to me.
I'll always be here.
That's right.
I'll do it.
How can I be satisfied with doing a
girl that some guy has already won over?
If I have to bring a guest
to board that sleazy train...
Then I'll find the finest guest and
provide the best service to the riders!
Good morning!
I'll make it happen!