Mister Detective, you've noticed Iori-chan's
feelings, haven't you?
You're such a mean person.
Well, I'm just a guy renting a room here for work.
Besides, she's still a child.
If you say something like that...
Damn you...
Don't you dare make fun of me like that!
Geez. They're in a hurry, aren't they?
Hurry up and get out of here!
It's trouble for other customers, so please leave.
Customers?
I don't see any!
Cut it out.already. You're interfering out business.
I'll be back.
Are you okay, Tsubaki-san?
It took me a bit more time on the way...
Sorry for the trouble, Fujikito-san.
Don't worry about it. It's my job.
Don't push yourself too much, either, Young Hostess.
Oh, thanks for it every time.
They're too stiff for someone so young, Young Hostess.
Oh well, I'm not young anymore.
To me, you're just like a daughter.
Geez,
I have to help out while dressed like this...
How is it? Does it fit me well?
Ye-yeah...
Geez, you're so cold.
Even though I put so much effort into dressing as a hostess...
You idiot!
Iori-chan, Yuuji-san, this is Fujikito-san.
Starting today, we'll have him work as
the security guard over night as well.
Nice to meet you, I'm Iori.
I look forward to working with you.
Oh my, you're a very cute hostess.
Will you be the heir of Young Hostess?
She's my niece.
I'm getting her to help around a bit.
But she still has a lot to learn.
If you're this cute, you'll get popular right away.
You'll make the business prosperous!
You shouldn't say that,
she'll get too full of herself.
Well then, the Miss cute hostess,
good luck on the apprenticeship!
Yes, I'll work hard. Thank you.
Very promising there.
Welcome to the Tsubaki Manor!
Wow, you're cute!
Um, that's, right now it's...
Sir, sorry but she's not a spectacle or anything
so please keep your hands to yourself.
Hey, what are you fooling around about?
Well, this way please.
That was scary... Even though he brought a girlfriend he...
Haha, you're very popular, aren't you?
Geez, why didn't you save me there?
Even though you know I'm bad with stuff like that...
Are you a detective, Oji-san?
Do you know Oba-san? Hmm? Are you like a couple?
When we went to visit Obaa-chan, my mom
chased after some guy and left me...
Stuff like going after someone you just met
or love at first sight is just not possible!
Older than me? What, are you like a pedophile, Oji-san?
Well I guess it's fine. Barely, though.
Oji-san is the first person I can talk to easily.
I'm really shy.
Um, sorry, but I'm working right now... Um...
It's fine right? Go around for a walk with me.
Show me around and stuff, okay?
Eh? Um, what about your companion...
I'm just playing with her.
Isn't something like that very rude to your girlfriend!?
Oh really? Then I must get you to talk a bit more about that.
C'mon, let's go.
No, it's not something like that, um...
You'd better stop around there.
Ouch! Ou-ouch!
I'm just joking!
Sorry about that, Hostess-san.
Are you alright?
From now on I'll also be careful for you.
Yes.
True Visitation to the Secret Hot Spring
The schoolgirl-hostess Iori ~The Loosening Dress in Regret and Shame.
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Yeah, please work on the investigation, Kenko.
What's wrong, Tsubaki-san?
Oh, Yuuji-san.
I can't seem to find Iori-chan.
I'll go look for her. It's this late, after all.
Could you do that for me? She's not in her room, either.
I'm worried that something might've happened...
Yuu-san.
What are you doing?
Oh, so she was just peeking...
said you can't... Oji-san!
Why are you... so...
Miss Young Hostess is in really good shape down there.
Oji-san can't hold back.
I don't get it... Even if you say something like that...
Oji-san! Wait!
Students have become very erotic recently, haven't they?
You're taking me all in.
That's not true!
Why... is Oji-san... inside Iori...
If you let it out again and again like that... I'll get a baby...
It's fine. When that happens, Oji-san will take care of you.
That's not the point...
Oji-san don't! You can't let it out!
It feels really good when being creampied.
It's best that Miss Young Hostess remembers it, too.
Something like that is... a just lie!
I don't know anything like that!
You can't!
I didn't give you permission... and yet you're letting it out...
It's spurting and hitting inside...
I said you can't!
If someone else sees she could kill herself!
She could be serious about it, right?
If it's asking about something like that, it's best
for someone who's also a woman to do it.
Seems like Iori was sleeping because
she wasn't feeling very well.
So that's why!
It's great to know you found her.
I thought she left...
~Eight Hours Ago~
Oh? You're in a uniform today?
That's nice! Hostess wear, and school
uniform, I'd like to see others as well!
That guy is conveniently somewhere else as well...
Show me some other clothes in your room.
Um, no, sorry, I'm...
It's fine, it's fine!
Please, leave me alone!
Let's drink a bit of sake and have fun!
I can't!
Young Hostess, please go into the room ahead!
Be careful of what you do.
I-I'm sorry... I'll never...
Yuuji-san...
I scold him hard, so he won't come near you again.
It's all fine, okay?
Thank you.
I was scared...
Your shoulders are stiff, you must've been really nervous.
Yes.
Is it because I look like a woman that would easily follow him?
It's because Miss Young Hostess is too cute.
He wanted to invite you even though
he knew it was impossible.
Geez, that's all you say, Oji-san.
It's embarrassing.
Here, it for you from behind.
Oba-san said it as well... but Oji-san's
massages are really good...
It's fine as long as you get to know each other!
You're too full of yourself for a child.
It's dangerous if you don't know the
consideration adults need to make.
Then Yuuji can save me, right?
If you become a woman, I'll go save you.
Children are out of my range.
Geez, that's all you say...
No... I let out a strange voice...
Huh? Did I fall asleep?
Sorry, Oji-san. I'm fine now...
Did I wake you up, Young Hostess?
Stay still for a while, okay?
No, wait... Oji-san!
Please, wait!
C'mon, relax your body.
It's making nice sounds, right?
No, Oji-san, what are you doing?
Wait, there... that's not! No! Stop it!
I don't want this!
You have such a perverted body. It's very sensitive.
Don't joke around... wait, no!
You idiot! Stop, Oji-san!
Just leave it all to me.
I'll take care of you properly inside as well.
Don't! Oji-san, really!
Stop! I don't want this!
Instead of Oji-san, why don't you call me Papa?
What are you talking about!?
C'mon. please! Oji-san!
No way... Oji-san... you pervert... stop it already...
Please, Oji-san... Oji... Papa!
Miss Young Hostess's pussy is almost crying as well.
No. that's not!
That's...
It hurts!
It's hurts!
It only hurts at first, but it'll feel better
and better, please hold back.
You're lying!
This hurts!
Stop it!
Why are you doing this...
This shouldn't be happening...
You idiot!
Pervert!
It's alright.
have my dick inside Young Hostess's
pussy properly, so be at ease.
Shut up. You're horrible! Why... Even though I believed in you!
My bad, my bad.
In exchange, I'll teach you lots of things that feel good!
No way... This is my first kiss...
My first kiss is... this...
No! No more!
Stop it already... Please!
No... Such horrible things are being
done to me... why is my body...
It feels good here as well.
It's just disgusting!
You pervert!
No. It doesn't feel good... this isn't right...
Young Mistress is very wet inside.
You've finally gotten used to it.
There's no such thing!
Something like a perverted dick... Something like this...
No way! There's no such thing... my
insides aren't getting hotter...
There! No there!
No... What's this... It's amazing! This is bad...
Iori-chan's lewd face is really good to see...
No way!
No!
Am I making a lewd face?
It's coming again... No!
So much sticky stuff is flowing inside...
I'm crying in pleasure... from being creampied...
Seems like it felt good.
I'll teach you how to clean up now.
What... is this?
A tit fuck from Iori-chan is the best!
So it's called a tit fuck...
Something like this... really happens...
What was I expecting...
What the heck are you thinking about?
Something like kissing or sex, is to be
done between people in love, right?
Then what are you trying to do?
I was thinking of just giving you a kiss on the cheek.
Idiot. Pervert.
Don't joke around.
There's no way I'd show you.
Just a little bit is enough.
I don't want to wait awkwardly for too long.
C'mon. Let me see Miss Young Hostess smile.
If you do so I will stop doing weird things.
I promise.
I get it.
Nice smile there.
A highschool girl naked and smiling at the camera, huh.
Very nice.
What are you photographing there!?
Damn, there's too much noise. Cheap stuff...
Iori, what happened?
Hmm? Just a change of image.
It's kind of gloomy, too, if it gets long.
Did something happen?
Not really, I just kind of felt like it...
So Yuuji knows as well...
So Iori-chan likes older people?
Eh? That's not true...
Geez... But it's easy to overdo it when you just start.
Take care of yourself, okay?
Eh?
Yuu-san noticed...
It's just a change of mood.
C'mon, Yuuji should go back to work, too.
Doing so much... Even though I'm at work...
How's it going?
I'm alright.
You're doing it real rough with your
boyfriend, huh? I'm jealous.
Something like this?
Yeah, that's the way.
Young Hostess sure learns fast.
Bo-oss! What should I do?
If you don't give orders I can't move!
Boss, boss!
Chitose-san will go there.
Just take the files from that person, okay?
Oji-san, I can't take this anymore.
If you don't delete that photo.
I don't care if I have to stab you to take it back.
That's a very nice face.
Seems like you're very determined.
Great.
It's really great.
Oji-san, I'm serious.
I'm sorry for doing that much to Young Hostess... to Iori-chan.
I get it. I give up.
Is that all?
You haven't sent it to your computer or anything, right?
An old man like me doesn't know how to do those things.
Oji-san enjoyed it a lot right?
You should go to the stores for stuff like this.
Ouch!
You've got good determination, but carelessness is fatal.
No! Let go!
Breaking a good girl like you is very fun!
What are you... trying to...
My body is... no... right away...
Even though I'm being played with...
What's wrong?
Why are you pressing your butt against me?
You don't want it, do you?
Even though I don't want it, I can't stop!
I don't need stuff like this... anymore!
What are you doing to do? Do it by yourself?
Or ask him to do it with you?
I won't do it... on my own, and I won't... do it with him... either!
Something like this is...
My pussy is... overflowing...
Very nice, how good it feels is reaching your whole body.
No! Not there!
Something like this will never feel good!
It's definitely not true!
It's not true... something like this...
Just a bit more. No, no, no, the Hostess is...
Yes.
Iori...
Even if Iori's insides... are being stirred by a dick...
There's no way this can feel good!
I will never admit it!
My body is getting wet!
Iori-chan's body is knows about everything now.
Be reassured and just feel good.
I said it doesn't feel good!
Even if I'm being stirred by a dick, it won't do!
I'm not holding back!
I don't know anything about the pleasure of sex with Papa!
It doesn't feel go even if such a
thick dick is sticking in and out!
Yes... Well done...
You sound energetic.
I'll leave cleaning up to you.
I'll contact you again about the other one. Yes.
It's all Papa's fault!
Even if I get creampied and get a baby, this is wrong!
Are you done?
Just the kid.
Does it concern you?
Yes...
N-No...
Is it because it is similar to the Inn you have at home?
Should I say they are similar...
It's more like they have the same smell...