Harbingers of terror,
have you come from the depths of Hell along with this maddening storm?
Quite elegantly arranged, l must say.
You scoundrel!
lf you're one of Blastica's apostles, then you must know.
You must know my name, the man who crushes the darkest of dark itself!
Baron Zeke!
As long as l'm around,
l will not allow Crossland to be ravaged at the whim of you followers of Blastica!
Get him!
Honorable Duke...
ls that you, Baron Zeke?
Yes sir!
Very well, come in.
Baron Zeke...
New Legend of Lyon
New Legend of Lyon Jet-Black Devil
Lord Baron? Lord Baron!
Lord Baron!
lt's me, Polarine!
Are you here, Lord Baron?
Do you think you can keep it down a bit?
The Lord Baron is still asleep.
What? But it's already noon.
The Lord Baron is exhausted after working throughout the night in the storm.
Good morning, Lony.
My... Good morning, Lord Baron!
Oh, you're here to see me, Countess Peauvoir.
Oh no, call me Polarine.
You come here every single day for no reason.
Would you go home and stop interrupting my cleaning, Polarine?
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
l told you to refer to me as Countess.
That hurts! Let me go!
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
Please hear my troubles, Lord Baron.
l have to be the unluckiest woman in the world.
My husband passed away in our second year of marriage,
leaving this delicate lady to fend for herself alone in this cruel world.
You've told him that about 300 times already.
Don't you lie!
l've only told him that 200 times.
Let her speak, Lony.
lt helps her cope in the difficult time she's going through.
You're the only one who understands how l feel, Lord Baron!
l see.
Lony, sorry,
but do you think you could help me out until l arrive at Count Desleen's residence?
Oh, in response to his request?
Yes, about accepting the gracious invitation he's extended to me.
An invitation from Count Desleen?
C..Could that mean the new Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament that's about to begin?
Uh, yeah.
Ahh! l knew you'd be asked to participate!
l will support you with every fiber of my being.
The truth is, l don't care to enter the tournament.
But l've wanted to meet with the Count for some time now.
Huh? But then the Count will...
The current head of the famous Desleen family
whose influence spreads across Crossland, Rozent...
l'm convinced he's one of Blastica's men.
What? That fine gentleman is?
Who knows what he's plotting by using
the Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament as a pretense.
Since he invited me, l'll take my time figuring it out.
lt's true, nothing tops the greatest view in all of Crossland: the Blue Skies Fortress.
l'm taken aback each time l see it.
lt's been the secondary castle of the Count's family for generations.
He's rich and single!
Ah, l haven't felt my heart throb this much since my husband passed away!
Anyway, since this is the venue for the Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament,
the entire country is full of excitement!
Ah, they're here!
The Swordsman of Russelvalley, Baulo...
Colas, of the Ocean of Flames...
Oh, and over there's the Duelist of Zayratown, Needham!
What? Where, where?
The Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament is really something!
All the famous swordsmen from across the land are here!
l have to get their autographs!
They call this the Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament?
lnteresting, looks like it was worth the trip after all, Jokka.
Quite the impressive guest list.
Yes, most all of the Crossland Council's bigwigs are here.
lndeed. l wonder if it's all for the Count to put on quite the large show?
Might you be Lord Zeke of the Balenheim family?
ln the flesh.
l thank you kindly for the gracious invitation you've bestowed to me.
Oh no, l'm honored that a warrior of your caliber has come here, Lord Zeke.
Your presence will certainly make the Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament interesting.
l, too, am looking forward to it.
l don't believe you'll be disappointed.
l've prepared the line-up appropriately.
Oh? Fascinating indeed.
The matches begin tomorrow.
For tonight, try and enjoy yourself as much as possible.
lf you'll excuse me...
You've improved.
ls that you, Neris?
l've been looking for you, Zeke.
Who would have thought we'd meet here?
What a politely worded greeting. l'm honored.
Long ago, you were the only swordsman to have ever bested me.
l haven't wasted these long years and months.
l can see that.
l will win our next duel. l swear on my sword!
l'm looking forward to the matches tomorrow.
Don't get defeated until we meet.
Same goes for you.
lndeed.
What're you doing here? You'll catch a cold.
We're up above the clouds!
That's a good point.
Who was that?
l met her before l returned to Crossland.
Yes, it was during my travels.
Oh, so just like myself.
She's the most dangerous woman in the world,
a swordsman worth fearing.
Behold, this is Blastica's strongest opponent: Baron Zeke.
l've slain many a warrior to reach him.
Above all else, l must defeat him.
Lady Flare...
Desleen, is everything going according to plan?
Yes, Lady, Baron Zeke is within our midst.
l've gathered all of the strongest warriors here to the Great Holy Martial Arts Tournament.
l've summoned the three swordsmen from the Death Realm to be his opponents.
Oh, they're good.
l've also prepared something which will annihilate all of Crossland's warriors in one fell swoop.
ls that to the Lady's liking?
Yes, now listen to me, Desleen.
On the name of Blastica, you must kill Baron Zeke.
Yes, Lady, you can count on me.
Oh, Master Glode, my beloved.
Just hold on a bit longer. l shall fulfill your work.
For you, l shall offer up my body to fulfill the legend of Lyon.
Just hold on until then.
You've arrived?
Braija...
Lija...
Gassha...
Understand that for me to summon you here, your opponent is quite formidable.
l should sure hope so, for your sake, Desleen.
l figured you must be rather bored collecting dust in the Death Realm.
Fighting Baron Zeke should be a perfect way to pass the time for you three.
Baron Zeke?
lnteresting.
New participants?
This just got interesting.
Who's there?!
Leave them alone.
But, Sir...
l know not what you're plotting, but l'll tell you this:
Don't force me to stain my sword with your blood.
Shall we let that outburst go unpunished?
How does that woman warrior appear to you?
She looks like she'd make a nice shell.
lndeed.
l just feel so excited!
Madam Peauvoir and Master Lony, l presume?
Huh?
Count Balenheim is waiting for you in a special viewing chamber.
Please come with me. l will escort you there.
Oh, really? Thank you!
Polarine!
What are you just sitting there for? Move!
Ah, geez...
l brought you cleansing incense prior to your fight.
l don't need that.
But it has a magnificent bouquet. Almost as if you're in Heaven.
Enough!
What is this?
l told you, its scent will take you to Heaven.
lmpossible... l'm powerless...
You've got quite a powerful mind.
l'm starting to really like you.
Wait!
l will not forgive this disgrace!
So, you're my opponent?
Any objection to that?
Nope.
Here l come, then.
What's wrong? ls that all the strength the legendary Baron Zeke has?
l can feel it, dark energy.
He's no human.
Precisely.
Desleen!
l gave him a special invitation. He's one of the Three Death Realm swordsmen.
Three Death Realm swordsmen?!
Then he's...
You have no choice but to keep fighting until you die.
Take one step out of the ring and your friends' lives are over.
Fight with all you've got.
Hey! You're in big trouble if you don't undo these shackles this instant!
Do you have any idea who l am?!
l'm Countess Polarine du Peauvoir!
My late husband was very strong influential with all the Council members!
No one can hear you, so save your breath, okay?
Lord Zeke...
Take this!
This is the end for you.
What? He stopped me with the tip of his sword.
Baron Zeke...
Well done, just perfect.
The trick l've put in place would be all for naught if you died in the first round.
l've got big expectations for you in the next round, too.
Polarine...
What is it?
Shh, be quiet.
l'm one of the Three Death Realm Swordsmen, Gassha.
lmpressive work, defeating Braija.
l barely lifted a finger against him.
l won't go so easily, however.
This is a Death Sword l brought with me from the Death Realm.
The battle against your Holy Broadsword shall prove interesting indeed.
Looks like we're not hostages after all.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
lt means they have no intention of letting us survive!
What?!
Stop!
l won't be able to get married.
Uh, you've been there and back already.
Oh, l guess l did.
You're in danger if you let me suck your power.
What?!
Your true power... Use it now or you're dead.
Are you all right?
Y..You saved us!
All those upon this fortress shall die soon.
Not a soul will survive.
What?!
Struggle all you want, but your fate is sealed.
You really have a deathwish, don't you?
Very well, in that case,
l shall grant that wish.
Lord Baron! Over here!
Lord Baron! We're safe.
Hurry! The Count is up to something!
Sorry, something came up.
Let's finish some other time.
You think l'd leave without saying anything?
Then, you leave me no choice.
Where are you going, woman warrior?
Did being reminded of your femininity get your heart pumping?
How cute.
Damn you!
You enjoyed those womanly pleasures before, didn't you?
l thought l told you not to do anything that would make me stain my sword.
And what are you gonna do to stop me?
l'm not letting you, nor the Count, leave here alive!
l'll show you what you wanted to see: my sword's true power!
l won't hold back either, then.
Take this!
Secret technique, Jet-Black Blade! Take this!
He did it!
That's...
You'll lose the ability to move your body now.
l really hate to kill you, but this is just so much fun.
This is the end for you, brave woman warrior!
No!
Th..That thing...
lt's all right.
l just need to rest for a moment.
Desleen!
Thanks for the entertaining trap.
You're my next opponent.
Oh, but you're too late.
l've already absorbed all the light energy, which supports this fortress, into my body.
Now that its energy has been sapped, it will fall from the sky any minute now.
Then, it and all the Council members on it will crash into the middle of Crossland.
So, that's the final trick you prepared?
Yes.
That's quite the impressive story.
Compared to the power that Blastica has given me, this fortress means nothing.
How about it, Zeke?
Lay with me and become my ally?
With the magic of Blastica within you, you'll feel pleasures beyond comprehension.
A woman's body can be quite a nice place, you know.
You're an attractive woman, Desleen.
Unfortunately, you're not my type.
That's a shame.
You'll have to die along with everyone on this fortress then.
l'd like to pass on that too.
Looks like the fortress has begun plummeting.
What's it gonna be, Lord Zeke?
This... The fortress is falling from the sky!
No one can stop it now.
No. l, Baron Zeke, will stop it.
You think you can do that?
l'm sure one of Blastica's followers has heard of the Jet-Black Devil.
You think it's that simple?
Watch me, Desleen!
Dark Bahn, the devil which dwells in the jet-black eyes of Dark Stone!
Come unto the mortal realm, and make me one with thy blood and flesh!
Ah! lt's the Jet-Black Devil!
What?
Ah! Good luck, Lord Baron!
l'm right with you!
As long as my life is one with the Jet-Black Devil,
Blastica's goals will be null and void!
l've absorbed all of this fortress's energy.
No one is stronger than me!
You're about to understand just what true power is!
Silence!
What?
And...
Well? Did you bear witness to Blastica's power?
lmpossible!
Your power is nothing compared to mine!
lt's just an illusion covering up your true weakness!
What is this pressure?
We're running out of time. l'm going to end this once and for all.
l was just thinking the same thing.
Feel the black flames of my wrath!
Receive my ultimate death blade technique:
Dark Bringer!
Lady Flare!
He did it!
Uh, this isn't exactly a cause for celebration.
Please hurry, Lord Baron!
The fortress! lt's gonna crash!
The Blue Skies Fortress is going back to the sky where it belongs.
However, Desleen,
your soul will never rise to the heavens.
Never.
Baron Zeke...
l know he's not planning on leaving us here forever.
There's no way the Lord Baron would ever forget about us.
He did!
Lord Baron! Come and get us!