At that time...
My sister and I literally had nothing.
What is it that you seek? I shall grant it.
You.
What you is that you want to happen?
I want it.
I want everything.
Wealth, fame,
and...
...my freedom.
After forming a contract with the
grimoire on that day my sister...
Changed completely.
Just wait... nee-san!
You mustn't!
This isn't...
It's starting to get even bigger.
You're aroused by being teased like this?
Here... how's this?
I can keep on sucking this dick with my lewd tongue, you know.
Please, nee-san!
Faster...
I want you to suck my dick faster!
Nope.
This is enough for your bulging thing over here.
My oh my, what's wrong?
Getting it all lively like this while having my feet play with it...
Nee-san...
I-It feels good!
Is that so?
I'll rub it more, then.
I'm about to cum already.
It's alright, squirt it all out.
Now my beautiful legs are soiled with your cum, Adam.
Nee-san,
I'm sorry.
But I just can't hold it in.
Can I pleasure myself inside you, nee-san?
Alright.
You're such a spoiled kid, Adam.
Nee-san, your pussy is trying to suck
me in, and it feels very good!
That's good, Adam.
Nee-san!
It feels so warm and soft, it pleasures me so much!
Here, just keep fucking me as long as you want to.
Nee-san, nee-san!
You dick is hitting my womb.
Kissing it every time it hits.
Just keep on fucking me!
This is amazing, nee-san.
My hips, my hips are starting to feel weak.
It's alright, Adam.
Just stir my pussy more and more!
I'm about to cum.
Nee-chan, here I go!
Just go, Adam!
Just cum lots of your thick seed into my pussy!
Cum it all!
My torn heart...
Was saved by this grimoire... by Master Mamon.
It granted every singly wish I had.
Which is why this time, I must obtain whatever
it is that Master Mamon wants.
Do you understand?
Adam?
Nee-san...
The Grimoire of Divine Comedy.
The Order of the Library Knights?
Correct.
Also known as the Guardians.
It was an organization established
specifically against the grimoire.
I am the Order's commander, Miolinde Bloom.
I am pleased to meet you.
I'm the library representative, Uniko.
I order you to cleanse those who are
under the influence of the grimoire.
We need your powers, as the master of all the grimoires.
We will have you cooperate with us.
Alright.
But I've just achieved this state not too long ago.
I still have no idea what exactly I should do.
Actually, during one of our investigations,
We found one man of suspicious interest.
His name is Adam.
One of the students of this school.
I'm... a perverted woman who loves sex.
More... please fuck me with your dick more!
I'm about to cum!
Okay, just cum.
Please cum lots inside my wet and dripping pussy!
Such a slutty bitch.
Hey, I'm gonna call my buddies next time.
We'll mess you up completely each turn.
*sigh*
I'm getting tired of this acting shit.
What?!
It'd be bothersome for me...
...if I get too popular so suddenly.
You're... a man?!
You just had sex with a man.
Don't you think it'd be too embarrassing
to talk about it with your friends?
Here, it's snugly inside now.
A boy's ass can feel just as good as a girl's pussy, right?
No way, this can't be!
You really were a girl just a while earlier...!
Your dick looks like it's having the time of its life.
I think I'm about to get aroused too.
This ain't true.
No way...
I see, so as long as it feels good any hole will do, huh.
You're such a pervert.
You're rubbing my ass so hard,
and it feels great!
I'm about to cum too!
I'm about to release it all just like the way you did it earlier.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
If you're still okay with me,
I can still play with you.
I see.
It's a surprise for you to use a feminine
disguise as a method to collect mana.
Whoa!
You just suddenly tried to slash me.
That could be dangerous.
His wounds are healing?
You were trailing me the whole time, right?
I know.
You...
Just who are you?
You see, I'm..
I'm a homunculus. An artificial human.
Artificial human?
Then why are you able to channel the grimoire's power?
I'll do whatever my sister asks me to.
Because she's my dear family.
What's going on?
You still don't know?
My sister's objective,
is the Grimoire Master of that library.
Well,
it's probably too late letting you know at this point, anyway.
Good heavens!
Grimoire Master!
This grimoire is now mine.
This is...
The Grimoire of Greed's power?
Just who are you?
Let me go!
And give back Dante!
We desire but one thing:
the great power bestowed upon you as the Grimoire Master.
Such an innocent and cute face.
I shall now siphon every last drop of your power.
You seem to have nice and fair skin, I see.
Not as fair as mine, however.
What...?
I'm getting all slimy.
My oh my, your cute pink nipples are already very stiff.
You're feeling horny, correct?
Stop!
Stop rubbing my nipples!
In order to extract the mana of another person,
I must first make contact with the person
physically, and be one with her.
No...
I don't want this.
What should I do?
My body is starting to get really hot.
Is this the effect of that ointment?
What did you just...?
Did you just insert something in my ass?
I'm going to extract lots and lots of your mana.
My belly is...!
It just keeps on bulging!
What? Something's moving inside!
My oh my, such an amazing sight.
It's as if you're pregnant.
No, no!
Don't push it.
I-It hurts!
Don't you just want to do it already?
You can't help but want to release that
which is inside you already, right?
No, stop...
Stop... don't!
If you keep stimulating my ass like that, I'll!...!
I'll..!
It's alright.
No need to hold it in.
Just let it all out.
I can't hold anymore...
NO, no...!
S-Stop!
Don't look!
I won't stop.
It's coming, it's still coming out!
Feels good, right?
The sensation of the slime slithering out of your ass.
No...
This is so embarrassing.
And yet... and yet it feels terribly good.
I'm getting aroused.
Now I'm starting to feel horny as well.
What is that?
What is that gigantic thing?
A magical creature born through alchemy.
It's a wonderful creature that can transmit
to me exactly how it feels.
Now then, unite with me.
And let us sing the rhapsody of your own mana!
This can't be...
No... stop!
It's big!
Your pussy's so wet that I just slipped all the way inside.
You really are a slut, aren't you?
No, I'm not!
This is just...!
No!
Stop... don't move!
Oh yes.
This is way better than all the mana I have extracted before.
Your pussy absolutely feels the best!
What is this?
It feels nothing like a tentacle, or even a dick.
And it's rubbing hard inside my pussy.
No...
It feels good.
I don't want this, and yet...
You're feeling all horny while I rape you, I see.
It's squeezing me really tightly.
I'm about to cum as well.
No way.
Are you going to cum?
No, stop!
Oh yes...
I feel the mana filling me.
I beg of you.
Stop this already.
My oh my.
Do you really think I was satisfied with that?
It was just a sliver of a thought earlier, but
after seeing you excrete that much slime...
So you're actually 'trained' in that already.
N-No way...
I'm actually aroused in my ass?
My body has slowly become a lot more lewd.
What should I do?
Your ass is starting to squeeze me even tighter.
S-Stop!
It you continue to push that hard,
my ass, my ass might turn itself inside out!
But it really feels good to be raped hard in your ass, right?
Oh look, your pussy is starting to drip with your love juices.
I-It feels so good.
The insides of my ass are starting to feel very hot.
It's hitting me very deeper.
I think I'm about to cum.
Take every drop as a precious gift from me.
I'm going to cum too.
I'm going to cum while being pleasured in my ass!
I-I'm cumming!
For me to fall for a mere decoy...
How is it, Master Mamon?
How is her mana?
Was it good enough to you liking?
N-Nee-san,
will this be really okay?
Is this the world you really wanted?
Adam.
You seem to have been tailed.
Master of the Grimoire of Greed.
Eva Paracelsus, I presume?
Just what are you trying to do?
N-No way.
Why?
There's supposed to be a barrier surrounding the area.
That explains it.
A Reflector, huh.
Quite an interesting item you have there.
Any form of barrier or mana-based attacks will not work on me.
What?
Master Mamon!
This is bad!
My Reflector!
So this is Master Mamon's true form.
How wonderful!
Nee-san, watch out!
Adam?
N-Nee-san...
I'm just a mere homunculus,
but I think of you dearly as my family.
Th-That's...!
Adam!
Master Mamon, what in the world does this mean?
We desire, Eva.
We deisire for your flesh, and blood.
No, no!
Master Mamon, please stop!
Stop!
Curses.
How could this have happened?
Now, become one with me.
Become one with this penis... forever!
This can't be...
For me to do it wit this monstrous entity...
It's sucking it very deeply.
Such a greedy female.
I'm being stirred!
These perverted tentacles are penetrating me so deeply!
Squealing like a little child.
Is it all because of my caressing?
Don't rub it so vigorously in me!
Your clitoris is completely bulging.
It feels as if it's taking you to heaven, is it not?
Eva!
Is this really what you desire?
It's of no use.
Witness the debauchery before your eyes.
This woman is nothing more than a squealing pig now.
Oh no, I can't take this anymore.
I'm about to cum!
Homunculi... what is it?
No!
Stop.
Stop at once!
A pig like you shall be best paired with these.
Can't you hear me?
Let me go!
Get those filthy hands off me!
D-Don't suck my nipples like that.
Stop, stop!
Your words have no power here.
Homunculi are but mere dolls devoid of souls.
You of all beings should understand this the most.
Th-That's not true.
If it was him...
If it was Adam...
He would never do something as forced as this.
S-Stop!
That's not where you're supposed to put it!
In my ass...?
Please... don't rub my asshole that hard.
I be of you!
There is absolutely no reason why I should hold back.
For I shall penetrate you, regardless of which opening I take!
It's so deep...
These dicks are pushing wildly inside me!
So hot, it feels so hot!
Eva.
From my point of view, you're just the same as them.
Only a doll filled to the brim with folly and stupidity!
True.
I truly am a fool.
I did something that can no longer be taken back.
Adam...!
But, every single thing is just...
...is just too late it seems.
This is the punishment for all the other humans I've violated.
Being drenched in semen.
No matter how much I become defiled,
I shall take it all.
Eva!
Isn't what you really want,
the love of a dear family member?
Don't let Adam's will be in vain!
He's... your one and only family, right?
N-Nee-san...
I'm just a mere homunculus,
but I think of you dearly as my family.
Dearly as family?
Utter rubbish.
The heart can never feel fulfilled by such intangible things.
It's nothing but a fantasy.
You're wrong.
Adam and I were always together.
When we eat, when we sleep.
It's all because Adam was with me...
...that I was able to endure such isolation.
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I was...
...never alone!
What is this?
She broke free from his grasp?
Mio-san?
Did you save us?
I'll tell you all about it later.
You still have to cleanse that thing!
Okay!
Wh-Why you...!
I won't let you!
Why?
Why give everything, every single thing
that this woman ever wanted!
The one thing that I truly desire,
is something that can never be granted
by a demon such as you.
Eva-san!
Let's do this together!
I shall stretch out my hand,
for the sake of the ones I truly hold dear!
Hey there, Mio-san and Uniko-san!
Sorry about the trouble I caused the other day.
A-Adam!
Wh-Why...
Us homunculus can completely recover
regardless of physical damage,
as long as our preservation vessel remains intact.
Is that so? So that's what happened.
That's quite good, right, Mio-san?
E-Enough about that!
I'm not really... it's not that I...
Have you had a change of heart?
I decided to broaden my knowledge in magic studies.
I actually plan to tour the library at least once.
From now on, it won't be mana,
for I shall gather knowledge instead.
Every single book will become part of my repertoire!
That's amazing, nee-san!
I shall assist you once again in this endeavor.
So that personality wasn't due to the grimoire.
They really are such close siblings, right?