On the other hand... we need to discipline Tomoe.
Really, I wonder why the siblings are so different.
That Tomoe...
[Keiai School of Fine Arts] AM 0:15
On the other hand... we need to discipline Tomoe.
Really, I wonder why the siblings are so different.
[Keiai School of Fine Arts] Dormitory AM 0:32
Every year there are people who run away from school...
...because they're grown tired of the strict rules or became homesick.
Are you like them, I wonder...
Misaki... Tomoe-san?
It's ok if you don't want to talk.
It's late, please return to your room.
It's alright...
I won't tell anyone about what happened tonight.
I am Komatsusaki Rie.
You're always welcome to come to me with your problems.
Ok.
HQH@EFnet
New Century Cream Lemon
subtitles: Miketsu, Turvy
timing: Miketsu
encoding: Silencer
graphics: Silencer, Miketsu
ESCALATION
Love
[Keiai School of Fine Arts] AM 8:00
Ah, Komatsusaki Rie, the student representative?
She's got excellent grades and wins every piano contest.
It's as if she was a real princess.
Tsudou Akane-san.
Yes.
Yamamura Aisa-san.
You have broken the rules by going out without permission.
Therefore, tonight, you are ordered to reflect on your behaviour.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Then, you are excused.
Hi, it's the mail service.
Thank you!
Hey, is there any mail for Misaki?
I'm sorry. It looks like no mail came for you today.
What are you saying?
It's not something that you have to apologize for.
It's all right.
Because my talented brother is at home.
Father and mother don't care what happens to me.
On the other hand... we need to discipline Tomoe.
Really, I wonder why the siblings are so different.
Reuegefühl - German for 'Remorsefulness'
A single student's mistake is every student's offense.
As the representative of those students,
I will care out your punishments.
Prepare yourself!
Is... Is that true?
Oh.
Misaki-san, didn't you know?
People who repeatedly break the school rules are sent...
...directly to the student representative to be spanked.
I was so surprised when I first heard about it.
She looks like such a gentle person... It can't be...
Note: German is being taught here
(Ich bin noch jung. ??? und rühre mich nicht an!)
I...
Why am I so disgusting...
I'm such a slut...
I'm such a disgusting person...
That's why I can't make any friends and...
...my parents hate me.
Surely it must be like that.
Tomoe-san?
You're always alone, aren't you?
U... Um...
I'd like to thank you for that night.
You are talking about that time, right?
You still can't bring yourself to liking this school?
Let me introduce you.
This is my friend, Oomori Midori-san.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Misaki Tomoe. Nice to meet you too.
Midori-san is the tennis captain.
She is good at sports and anything that involves moving her body.
It's all right. We don't play that intensely here.
So come try it and see.
Yes.
Wow. You look cute.
I did it!
Komatsusaki-senpai, that Tomoe-san seems to have a crush on you.
I wonder if she doesn't know that
Rie-senpai and Midori-senpai are a couple.
Hey what are you saying.
Hey Midori-senpai.
You lost to her on purpose just now, didn't you?
You would never really lose to that person.
That's not nice. If you say that in front of Tomoe...
If this helps Tomoe-san keep her confidence, then it's OK...
...right, Rie?
Really, I wonder why the siblings are so different.
Misaki-san?
I'm staying on purpose!
If I go back home during the winter holiday,
my parents will make me study during my free time.
I don't like it.
Yukari, hurry up!
Yes.
Well then... take care.
Misaki-san?
Senpai!
If you're just going to cry, I won't know what's wrong.
If something happened, then please tell me.
I...
I am a bad person...
that's why Mother, Father, and everyone...
...wouldn't love me!
Mama, Papa, listen, listen! I won first place in the "My papa and mama" writing contest!
The teacher even praised me!
Wow that's great, Masato! You're the top of the mock exam!
It's nothing special.
So there's no mistake about you studying Linguistics right, Masato?
Let's have a party tonight!
Hold it, it's too soon!
Is that so?
On the other hand... we need to discipline Tomoe.
Really, I wonder why the siblings are so different.
Tomoe-san.
What do you want from me?
Can I tell you the truth?
Sure.
Will you think that it's strange?
No I won't.
I...
I like you, Rie-senpai.
I love you.
That's why... I want to be abused by you.
I really want to be abused by you.
Fine, I will show you the real me.
I will take you to the villa of my respected sister, Naomi-sama.
Yes.
So you are Misaki Tomoe-san.
Rie has told me about you.
Do you really like her that much?
Yes.
But you see...
Mi... Midori-senpai!
Rie isn't the person you think she is.
Look at her.
Rie-senpai!
Rie, likes to do it this way.
You're done already... you are a really disgusting girl.
How is it, Rie?
It... It feels good, big sister.
Mi... Midori-senpai!
Tomoe-chan, this pleasure comes from watching that cinema.
Look at Rie.
If you don't get off like that,
you can't achieve any satisfaction.
Is that OK with you?
Tomoe-chan, you saw it didn't you? This is the real me.
The student representative, Komatsusaki Rie,
that you long after is just a surface appearance.
No matter what I see, My feelings will not change!
I really want to be abused by you.
I want to be played with like a toy.
Otherwise...
I... I...
Take off your clothes.
Yes.
Note: a 'sow' is a female pig
You disgusting sow!
I will now give you what you desire. Prepare yourself!
Yes... senpai...
Some... Somehow...
please forgive me...
Could you answer me something?
Getting so excited when I do these things.
You really are a disgusting sow, aren't you?
Let me look at you touch yourself with your own fingers.
The way you always do it.
Yes.
That's right.
You did it so willingly. You disgusting sow!
Nobody would love you. You repulsive piece of junk.
But...
I will love you.
Senpai!
Se... Senpai?
Tomoe-chan, Let us become one.
No... not like that!
Let's cum together...
You know, a year ago, Rie...
Midori, you!
Since Rie became the student representative,
her eyes were opened to the world of S&M.
Big sister!
Rie, you will be graduating soon. From now on, love Tomoe.
Yes, big sister.