Ruri.
Who are you?
Sorry, you resemble a girl I'm looking for.
What a terrible pick up line.
Christmas~ Christmas~
Are you well, Hiroshi?
This insolent voice is...
None other than Kotobuki-sama for you.
I always thought you were a jinx.
I didn't think you'll look for me on your own. What a nice guy.
I am a nice guy to begin with.
Right, on Christmas Eve morning the day after.
We have an event as per custom.
Do you wanna come?
You're referring to a Christmas party, right?
I've spent quite long looking for you.
You're looking for me because of this?
It's nice to just let loose and enjoy yourself once in a while.
That's true.
It's gonna be fun.
Our Paranormal Investigation Association will have a show of hidden talent.
Any news since then?
Nope.
It's been a week.
Aren't you going to look?
She left on her own.
Why should I.
I don't even know where to start looking.
http://wakusubs.wordpress.com
Ruri.
Youko.
Welcome back, Hiroshi.
Welcome back? What are you doing here?
Cleaning.
You haven't been cleaning for the entire week.
So...
It's fine. I will do my own cleaning.
Don't just barge in.
Sorry for giving you a wrong idea.
Wait. You don't have to leave in a hurry.
But...
What are you saying? No one's misunderstanding.
The flowers are beautiful. Arigatou!
Now where's the vase...
I just happen to find a perfect replacement.
I'll add some water.
But the vase is filthy.
How does Ruri stay in there?
I've been cooking and scaled myself slightly.
I'm fine.
It looks great, Ruri-san.
It's all thanks to you, Youko-san.
I can see the sea.
What?
You pickles! Are you trying to kill me!?
Who?
No idea.
Where's Ruri Onee-chan?
Ruri Onee-chan?
You're her sister?
What's your name?
Ruri.
Ruri is my name.
Where's Ruri Onee-chan?
She's gone.
Where?
She...
Well, I mean Ruri your sister... dear...
It's messed up.
Can I call you by another name?
Name?
Yeah, right.
Right. Koruri. (Means Little Ruri)
No way!
What a cute name.
Cute?
I guess so.
Her attitude towards Youko and me is different.
Koruri-chan.
You address Ruri Onee-chan. Are you her sister?
I think we can't say for sure.
That's absolutely right. I'm her sister.
Really? Then I hope you'll tell me more.
I don't wanna.
I don't even know what this place is.
What do you mean by you don't wanna?
I'm sleeping!
What a huge futon.
Wait, that's...
We are not done talking.
It's fine, just let her be.
She doesn't want to talk anyway.
But where do I sleep...
There's somewhere you can sleep over there.
Thank you for today.
See you at the party the day after.
Hiroshi.
It's nothing.
I'll leave Koruri-chan to you.
Koruri?
Did she go out?
Well then, I'll take a bath.
Warm water is great.
A bath has to be hot.
Why are you in the bath?
I should be asking you that!
Scram!
Ouch...
How's the water?
Not too bad.
Ouch...
What's there to be pain about, you pickle!
Peeping on girls bathing.
It wasn't on purpose.
I just stumbled onto you.
You said you were bathing?
Don't think you can smoke your way through.
Ouch...
You said you were bathing.
Bathing in hot water?
Of course. You bathe with hot water.
That means you know how to adjust your body temperature?
Of course.
I'm a Snow woman.
Ruri didn't know how.
What?
What's that supposed to mean?
Ruri... she's...
What about Ruri Onee-chan?
I'm Ruri.
I only know I'm a Snow woman and my name.
Snow woman?
Why am I a Snow woman?
Why can't I touch humans.
Why can't I touch someone I like?
Ruri?
Why?
Why do you get in my way?
No!
Leave Hiroshi-sama alone!
Why? What happened? Ruri.
I have someone else in my body.
Then Ruri subsequently disappeared that night.
What exactly happened?
What do you know?
Hiroshi-sama! Please embrace me, embrace me.
Please, I'm scared.
Farewell, Hiroshi-sama.
Don't go, Ruri. Ruri!
Don't go! Ruri! Ruri!
Ruri...
Koruri, where are you going?
I'm going to look at society.
To understand the current world.
I see.
Why am I a Snow woman?
Why can't I touch humans?
I can't even kiss someone I love most.
Ruri.
Hiroshi-sama, kiss me.
But.
What, it's only you, Koruri.
Do you want to date me?
You tend to do incomprehensible stuff.
Who?
It's a Taimashi. (退魔師 Exorcist of sorts)
Taimashi?
They are beings that seeks to destroy us non-humans.
She must have detected my aura.
Exterminate is... to kill, right?
This must be a lie.
Move aside.
I can't do that.
Do you know what she is?
She is a Snow woman.
But she's not an evil  existence.
Please spare her.
No way.
But...
She didn't do anything bad.
Why?
Because this is my mission.
Mission?
Move aside!
Koruri, run!
It's dark. Where am I?
It wasn't intentional.
Where's Koruri?
She escaped.
I see.
Sorry.
But she's really not a bad person.
Though she can be quite the bully.
But she's not bad by nature.
So please don't kill her.
I'll take responsibility.
Please!
I'll observe for the moment.
Thanks.
I'm Ayaka.
I reside in the Miyama Shrine.
I got it.
I'm Manabu Hiroshi.
I'll be sure to notify you if something happens.
Why do I have to sleep in the Kotatsu.
You...
What? Not asleep yet?
I have something to ask you.
Sure, go ahead.
Regarding Ruri.
You said she was unable to adjust her body temperature.
Yeah, that's why Ruri was unable to touch anyone.
She will scald herself.
So she bathes in cold water daily.
How do you know it's cold.
Because...
You saw, didn't you?
Like I said...
You said?
Sorry, I did see.
But it was a coincidence.
Well, it's fine.
Ruri...
I can gradually understand why Ruri chose to vanish.
She seems to have taken a liking to you.
So she left.
Why leave when she's smitten.
How do you know she likes me anyway?
Tell me why?
Koruri?
I can understand.
Because I think I...
What?
Could you embrace me?
Don't be silly.
Do you hate me?
It's reasonable after how I bullied you.
No, I don't hate you.
You...
are crying?
Koruri.
It's too intense.
Please be more gentle.
Koruri.
Hey, Koruri.
Are we not attending the party together?
You really OK?
Enjoy yourself. Don't worry about me.
I see.
Merry Christmas! Congratulations!
Cheers!
Aoyama's special moves.
Right on, Aoyama.
Nomura, your turn.
Nomura's special moves.
Having fun, Hiroshi?
It's the best.
Hiroshi...
Hiroshi!
Youko.
When are you going to stop being so indecisive?
Indecisive?
You actually didn't want to come today.
No, you shouldn't have come.
What are you saying.
I got invited...
Why won't you look for Ruri-san?
You like her, don't you?
She left on her own accord.
I don't have any reason to look for her.
How could you not understand Ruri-san's true feelings.
Your feelings are what's the problem.
You like her, don't you?
If you can't understand her feelings,
just let your heart lead the way.
If you truly love her,
you should look for her.
Youko.
Living according to your own will.
Didn't you use to be like this?
Because...
That's the reason I fell for you.
Youko, I'm sorry.
You're too kind-hearted.
Making the guy you love ditch you on purpose.
Let's make immediate preparations.
It's gonna be busy.
You can't bear to leave him on his own, right?
We should go, too.
Ayaka-san!
You're...
I didn't mention to you.
There's actually another Snow woman.
But she's..
She's a very precious woman to me.
You located Koruri because you managed to sense her aura, didn't you?
I beg you, please tell me.
That girl...
The whereabouts of Ruri.
I believe you will know, Ayaka-san.
The foot of Mt. Fuji.
There's been an unbelievable aura at that place recently.
And it's getting stronger.
Koruri, I'm leaving.
Koruri?
I'm going to find Ruri.
Don't look for me.
Koruri.