Shion, a Single Figure sent from another dimension,
to hunt and kill Geist-infected humans was rescued by Hiroki.
To keep an eye on Hiroki, who himself was infected with a Geist,
Shion created an alter-ego for herself at his school.
She sensed an uneasy presence on the school grounds, however,
and appearing before them just as they were
about to get to the bottom of things,
was Odawara, a boy infected with the Slug Geist.
Hiroki suffered a mortal wound,
and Shion was filled with venomous semen.
Shion's life and sanity were both in danger.
But then, coming to her rescue,
was a Geist who should have been her enemy.
As Shion lost consciousness
in the mysterious Geist's arms, she whispered,
"Miko... The leader of the Geists."
Wolf Geist...
I don't know who you are, but you're dead meat!
I don't like you, so it's time to die!
He vanished?
Where did he run off to?
He's too strong.
Could you be... No way...
Are you Asaki-kun!?
So you became a Geist just like me?
As your best friend, I'm so proud of you!
Hiroki...
Vol.03   The Subordinate Angels
Jamming detected.
Scanning Phase initiated.
Two Geist presences detected.
A Doll's presence detected.
Number 7.
Code name, Shion.
Aptitude of current Geist undeterminable.
Shall we continue the Scanning Phase?
Infinity-sama.
No. Don't bother.
The Geists will be altered to our presence if we continue.
What do we know about the two Geist presences thus far?
One has been destroyed.
The other is still alive.
But we cannot determine his aptitude or type.
Let us leave that detail to 7.
We will step back and continue with our search for Miko.
Yes, my Lord.
Assuming the form of a wild wolf and
unleashing the wrath of the heavens... they say.
Hiroki, thanks for saving me.
What's wrong?
Why are you silent?
I just remembered.
The feelings I just had...
The sensation of slicing Odawara into pieces...
I still feel it in my fingertips.
I see.
But that is not something you can control.
That's not what I mean!
When I did that, deep inside I was enjoying it.
And also...
And also, what?
After I killed Odawara... I... well...
I wanted to... How should I put it...
Violate me.
You wanted to violate me, didn't you.
Your Geist personality.
My Geist personality?
A Geist has no physical presence.
When a human takes on his Geist form, he is consumed
with desires for destruction and sex.
I see...
I was able to hold them back last time.
Hiroki, do you want to violate me even now?
Dolls are made to be desirable to Geists.
It is recommended that a Doll not be a virgin
to be able to better withstand their violation.
But I am still pure.
So... if you still want to violate me,
I don't mind.
Shion!
Does this feel good?
The venom the Slug Geist infected me with is still working.
Shion, your nipples are so hard.
No! Not that!
Don't!
No!
If you do that, I'll... No!
Don't... It's too intense.
Shion!
Hiroki...
D-Don't suck so hard.
Do your boobs feel nice?
Yes.
Shion, you're so pretty.
Hiroki, do you like my boobs?
Yes, I love them.
They're so big and soft.
Rub them harder.
Like this?
Yes!
My boobs feel great!
Because of you, Hiroki.
Because you're rubbing them.
I'm cumming!
I feel ashamed... to be like this.
Your pussy is so pretty, Shion.
Sexy juice is spilling out.
That's because...
Because what?
Because I just came earlier.
Then I'll help you cum again.
But if you do it that strong...
If I do it that strong, what?
Hiroki! No! Oh my god!
Don't!
Does it feel good?
Very good.
Hiroki, your tongue is so...
Shion, it's really big.
Hiroki, stop it.
You're embarrassing me.
Shion, your pussy smells so good.
The scent is enticing.
Impossible. It can't "entice" you.
Your pussy is so wet.
Listen to the sounds it makes.
Stop it!
You're embarrassing me!
Don't!
You're so noisy.
Because it's so slippery.
Please, stop teasing me.
Your pussy feels so great it's crying. Say it.
No. That's embarrassing.
I won't keep it up unless you say it.
Fine, I will.
My pussy feels so great, it's crying.
If you keep moving like that, I'll cum again!
Then cum, Shion.
Cum a lot!
You taste so good.
No!
I-I'm cumming!
What is this?
I am your master now.
My master?
Here we go.
Shion, it's all inside.
I'm moving now.
Shion, this feels amazing.
Hiroki! You're inside of me.
I feel you.
You're inside of me!
You're moving!
You're going crazy inside of me!
Shion, you're really nasty.
Don't say that!
Does this feel good?
It feels great!
Hiroki!
Amazing!
You're getting bigger inside of me!
Don't! Don't get so big! I'll get torn apart!
If you get much bigger, I'll cum!
Shion.
Hiroki!
I'm cumming!
My dick is huge.
Even though I just came, it's already hard again.
I wonder if it's because of the Geist?
Shion, can I put it in again?
Yes, you can.
Put it in me a lot.
It's so thick!
Shion!
Hiroki, stop!
I can't have anything much bigger inside of me!
Shion, this feels too good.
I can't stop.
No! Don't hit so deep inside of me!
Hiroki!
Shion.
I want to hurt you.
I want to slash you to pieces.
Then do it.
Do what you want to me.
How horrible. Not this.
Your butthole is all squishy too.
You probably loved it when the slug fucked you there.
You loved it.
You like anal, don't you.
Ah, stop it. Don't tease me.
Not in there. Stop it.
You're embarrassing me.
Do you love me?
Then you'd better say so!
I love you.
I love you, Hiroki.
Now, say you love my dick.
I love your dick, Hiroki.
Say it more!
I love your dick, Hiroki!
Go in deeper!
Deeper, please!
Then say you're my slave.
Say you're my sex slave!
I am your sex slave.
Does that make you happy?
Yes, it makes me happy.
I'm your sex slave.
I'm cumming.
You're getting bigger again.
Getting bigger inside my hole!
I'm cumming!
Huh? Shion, you're awake?
No. I was watching you the whole time.
I couldn't sleep.
You couldn't sleep?
Last night was amazing.
Was it?
I am your sex slave, Hiroki.
Did I say that?
You did.
So what are you to me?
Me?
Let me see...
I guess I belong to you, Shion.
The reason I was able to turn back into a human...
...is thanks to you, I think.
You're very important to me, Shion.
I love you, Shion.
I see.
So you belong only to me.
Then...
Again?
We'll be late to school, though.
But you love it, don't you?
Hiroki!
Does this feel good?
Sh-Shion...
Hiroki!
Hey, hey, did you hear?
Odawara-kun went missing last night!
Is that true?
It's true!
I heard he was last spotted walking
towards the old school building too!
Oh god! Then could it have been the ghosts?
Freaking scary!
You don't need to trouble yourself.
He was no longer human.
Asaki!
Misuzu-sensei is calling you.
Misuzu-sensei?
What's up with that, Hiroki?
Why are you the only one she ever calls?
Yeah, why?
Wait, are you guys dating or something?
What... No way, you dumbass!
Excuse me.
You scared me.
You're late!
Asaki-kun, you silly.
Sorry!
What do you want though?
What do I want?
Isn't it obvious?
Your test results from yesterday came back.
Really?
So? What did they say?
You want to know?
Before that...
You see, we were interrupted yesterday,
and I've been left unsatisfied this whole time.
So first let's continue.
You belong only to me, Hiroki.
We can't!
Oh, why not?
We just can't.
I can't do this with you anymore.
You can't?
Is it because you started having sex with Shion?
How did you know?
Aww, I was right?
It was only a hunch.
You're too honest for your own good.
You can have fun with both of us though.
I don't mind at all.
Ouch!
Misuzu-sensei, did you just bite me?
Yes, I did.
You will become a complete Geist 24 hours from now.
Geist?
How did you know about the Geists?
Oh dear.
Did it already work?
Then listen to me.
I am actually one of you.
My name is Snake Geist.
So let's make nice, Wolf Geist.
Snake Geist? You're...
Hebi.
In Japanese, it's "Hebi".
and my Geist power is venom.
I can manipulate the entire bodily fluids of someone with my mouth.
Don't you think that's amazing?
By the way, I just injected you with a Geist awakening venom.
Why?
Because you are Miko.
I got a clear glimpse of that last night by the old school building.
Miko?
What's that?
The Geist leader of the Geists.
He stands as the alpha male of the Geists.
Taking the form of a wild wolf and
unleashing the wrath of the heavens.
It's a legend among the Geists.
But that is all we know about Miko.
No one knows anything beyond that.
Even though you were infected by a Geist, your
reaction was different from the other humans.
So I had a hunch you might be Miko.
You think I'm... Miko?
Probably.
Oh, I forgot to tell you.
There's another component to the venom I just injected you with.
When you transform into a full Geist, you will be under my control.
Wh-Why are you doing this?
Sh-Shion...
Now, Wolf Geist.
Let's create a new world together.
What?
Damn, you thought you could control me with this weak venom?
What a pitiful joke.
Wh-What are you doing?
I can't move.
Your eyes!
My body is hot!
So this is Miko's power.
Oh no!
My hands... My hands won't stop!
You want me that badly?
Then I'll let you have me.
I'll let you have all of me.
He's late!
I feel weird.
My chest hurts.
What is this feeling?
Misuzu-sensei!
She always oozes sexuality all over the male students.
Don't tell me she and Hiroki are...
Hiroki belongs to me.
He told me that.
Your dick is yummy.
I've never had a dick this yummy.
That's great Sensei.
Feels great.
I remember, you really like this, don't you?
Yes!
I'm cumming!
That felt good.
It was very yummy.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh Sensei, I have to go pee.
Can I go in your mouth?
You want to drink it, don't you?
Your pee... My throat is dry.
Why is that? Do I want to drink your pee?
Yes, I do! I want it!
Fill my mouth with your pee.
Please.
Then here I go, Sensei.
Asaki-kun's pee is in my mouth.
It's so warm and yummy.
Hey, drink it faster or it'll spill.
Ah, what a relief.
Time to go all the way now.
What's this?
What do you intend to do?
Seeing you in that position really gets me off.
Stop kidding around.
Those eyes... Please stop it. Please!
I can't take anymore.
Tease me!
Please. Tease me lots!
Wow...
Sensei, your pussy juice is bitter and yummy.
It feels great. It feels so great!
More!
Wait are you... That's my butt.
I haven't done that yet.
Oh, so you're an anal virgin.
Then...
What?
No, stop it!
No!
I can't take it!
What? I feel it!
My butt feels great.
I can't hold back anymore.
Please! Give me your dick in there.
Even though it's your first time, you already want my dick in there?
Yes, please.
I want it anally.
Please, gimme anal! Gimme anal!
Well, well, well... You're a really dirty pig, aren't you?
You're right.
I'm a dirty pig.
I want your dick!
I want it!
Oh well, then.
I'll thrust it in for you.
Please. Hurry.
That hurts!
So tight!
It's going deep inside!
This is great.
Your hole is so tight.
My butt loves it.
No way.
Please, more...
Hey, Sensei, which hole do you want my semen in?
In both!
In my butt and pussy.
I want them both drowned in your semen!
Please, do both!
Please!
Really? Both?
You're so greedy.
If you want both, then swear that you are my slave.
I will. I'm your slave.
So do with me as you wish.
Control me.
Use me, tease me.
I'll give all of myself to you.
So, please... Give it all to me.
Fill me with your semen!
Then I'll give it to you.
My thick semen.
More! Move more!
Hurry! More, more, please!
Your dick is getting bigger.
So much... So much bigger!
Harder, harder!
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels great!
I love your thick dick.
Bang me harder, Master.
Harder, Master!
I'm cumming.
Cum! Hurry!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Well then.
Next up, I'll shove it in your pussy.
I'm so happy!
My Master...
Where are you?
What?
This room is jammed.
What's going on?
Oh my. Welcome.
Look.
My pussy and ass are all messed up and sticky with his cum.
Looks like I underestimated him.
What are you talking about?
I am his slave.
My body can only be satisfied by him now.
That's the face.
So you must be his slave, too.
Even though you're just a Doll.
Stupid bitch.
You bitch!
What have you done?
He will become a full Geist 24 hours frorm now,
and then he will belong to me.
Which will make him your enemy.
So you'd better make the most of the time you have left with him.
I'll allow you that much.
After all you're a fellow slave.
You bitch!
I'll find you and I'll kill you.
I'll fucking kill you!
I'll fucking destroy you!
I'll kill you until there's nothing left!
What's going on?
What happened?
Sh-Shion!?
Good morning.
Wh-Why are you here... I wonder?
Never mind that. Put on some clothes.
Good idea.
Oh, that's it!
Misuzu-sensei is a Geist!
She put venom in my body too...
I know.
I scanned your body just now.
It's filled with a special liquid.
Y-Yeah!
At this rate, I'll turn into a Geist!
I'll capture that Geist who did this to you
and make an antidote out of her venom.
That's my only option.
Be my sex slave...
You say that to all the girls, don't you?
No... Well, I... Maybe she misheard me.
She heard "slave", but I probably said "sleeve" or "shave".
Even her ass.
Ah, well that was just...
Huh?
Shion, are you jealous?
D-Dolls have no feelings.
So we have no jealousy.
I merely asked you to remove my virgin disadvantage and you did.
Thanks for you help.
You look pretty jealous to me.
I'm not!
Stop it!
Good grief.
You two, cut out the chick flick, will ya!?
Did you just hear a voice?
Someone's out there.
Where are you!?
Right here, right here.
Can't ya see me?
Stupid bug...
You trying to kill me!?
This bug is talking!
How fucking gross!
Seems like his body is a manifestation of his whiny voice.
I've heard that voice before...
It's me, Odawara!
Odawara?
The disgusting namekuji? Why are you here?
Stop calling me a namekuji!
You're a rude bitch as always, I see.
Never mind that.
Aren't you supposed to be dead?
Heh, sorry about that.
You only destroyed my body, not my voice.
So I was able to get a new body and come back to life.
I can fix that. I'll burn you to death right now.
Wait just a minute!
Don't ya want to know where Misuzu-sensei went?
How would you know that?
How do I know it's not a trap?
Well, I know things.
So just rest at ease.
I'm on your side now.
Now that I've learned my best friend is actually
Miko, I need to follow my alpha.
I'm still not convinced I should trust you.
Well, tell us anyway!
Where did Misuzu-sensei go?
It's pretty obvious.
She went to the old school building.
The old school building.
I got it.
We'd better go there right away.
I don't see her at all.
Are you sure she went here?
Hmm, that's strange.
I thought for sure she was in here.
Oh my... You kiddies.
This place is condemned you know.
Mikuriyagawa-sensei!
Why are you here?
You went missing a month ago!
Be careful!
He's no longer a human!
You bastard... You're a Geist, aren't you?
Correct!
I see.
So you're the Single Figure who came here with the Doll.
13... Where is she?
I can't tell ya that for free.
But... If you defeat me, you'll know.
I don't need memories,
omoide wa iranai
friendship or bonds.
yuujou mo kizuna mo
I won't miss it if I throw it all away.
subete nage dashite mo oshiku wa nai
I have unforgivable feelings,
yurusarenu omoi mo
but if I live for your sake,
anata no tame nara ba
I believe I can pierce through those feelings.
tsuranuite yukeru to shinjirareta
I was within my grasp,
kono te no naka ni
but the dreams slip through my fingers.
tsukanda hazu no yume ga kieteku
as if they're floating to a land long ago.
maru de hakanai utakata no you ni
Just the mere fact that I love you
anata o aishite iru koto dake ga
is proof enough that I lived.
watashi no ikita akashi
My last wish is one and only one.
saigo no negai wa tada hitotsu dake
Please don't ever forget that I loved you.
ai shita koto zettai ni wasurenai de