What lovely breasts.
As expected from the health club.
Eh?
Hey~ You're peeping underwater again!
Shiofuki Mermaid
Exercise on the Pool Side
Geez, where are you looking at?!
Well, if you ask me something like that...
Maybe I was looking at your fabulous body.
Just do your job properly, why do you think you're here for?
Sure, I will!
Geez...
What a perfect proportion!
What's more is that she's pretty!
Did you hear what your senpai said?!
I-It's not what you think, Hinako-san!
Um... Are you okay?
Yes, thank you.
If you like, I can teach you how to swim...
Leave it to me, I'll make sure you can swim faster than ever!
W-Wait... What are you saying, Makoto?
Is that really true? The truth is that I can't swim...
I'll be glad if you would teach me.
Don't you worry about it, I'm the perfect one to teach you how to swim in this place.
Yes, I'll be in your care.
Okay then, I'll leave the responsibility of her in your hands.
Of course, then, shall we begin right now?
Thank you so much.
My name is Hongou Marina.
You're Marina-san...
My name is Makoto, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Then, let's start with the walking exercise.
Yes.
When I look closely...Those breasts are really beautiful,
it's obviously too big.
Um... coach?
No... no... I should resist myself.
Is something wrong?
No... No... there's nothing.
Then shall we walk-
I'm sorry.
Co... Coach, is this...
No... this isn't...
Did that happen because you were looking at me?
S-She found out!
I'm gonna be killed by Hinako-san.
Um... coach?
Y-Yes.
Would you want to go somewhere, just the two of us?
There's something I need you to help me with.
I-Is it okay for me to feel this happiness?
Isn't this something I shouldn't do?
W-What should I do right now?
I've...
I've been married, but my husband is indifferent to me.
So I've been unsatisfied my whole life.
When I look at your healthy penis, I just can't hold it anymore.
I-Is that so?
Let me lick this sturdy penis of yours.
M-Marina-san...
It's great, Marina-san.
Please coach, please make me feel good, too.
T-That's...
It's good... more...
Please... more...
Marina-san, you really feel it, don't you?
Yes, it feels good.
Please coach...
M-Make me cum...
It's... It's so good...
Coach... Coach...
Quickly, come inside~!
Please give me your penis.
It's hot... His hot thing has come inside of me.
The inside of Marina-san is so hot.
Rougher... I want you to be more rough!
Good... It's good...
Coach's penis is really good, I feel so good...
I-I feel so good, too.
It's the best.
Rougher...
I want more of it!
I want it to come out!
Marina-san.
I can hold it anymore!
It's okay.
I can't hold it either!
Please, cum together with me.
The two of us cumming together.
I... I'm cumming...
Coach-
C-Coach!
Did you know... I'm gonna lose myself!
It's hot-
It's coming-
I'm cumming!
It's great...
Inside of me...
It feels good!
It's good... good...
It's... been a while for me...
to feel this good.
Good!
My breasts, too...
It feels good!
More... More of it, coach.
It's great... It's big and hard...
It's... good... cumming... I'm gonna cum!
I never thought that it was gonna be this good!
Marina-san, I-I'm gonna come inside again-
Coach's semen is gonna come inside me again...
My stomach is full of it.
It's good to be young again...
You made me cum a lot...
Cumming-
I'm really gonna cum again!
No...
I'm cum again!
It's hot...
Yesterday was fun~
I can't believe that I'm having sex with such
a gorgeous & big breasted wife.
It hurts!
What are you doing, Hinako-san?!
Don't slack off in here, you pervert!
No... I'm not, I'm doing my job right now.
Anyway, be serious with Hongou-san's swimming lessons.
Don't look at her with those perverted eyes, okay?
O-Of course I won't...
Hmph...!
If you really want to look at women's body,
there's one over here...
Eh? Hinako-san, did you say something?
I-I didn't say anything!
There, back to work!
It's strange though...
Besides that,
why is she always mad at me?
Does she really hate me?
Marina-san.
You're truly an unsatisfied wife, aren't you?
I-It's not like that.
I just can't think of anyone but you.
Good...
Coach's penis is really good.
Coach, please touch it!
Please, hurry up and touch me!
Marina-san's breasts are the best!
My breasts...
and pussy feels good!
Good... It's good...
Marina-san...
I...
Can't... hold...
It's fine... You can let it out inside of me.
I can't...
It's hot!
His hot stuff is flowing inside of my stomach.
Fill me... I want you to fill me up more...
It's so good...!
Marina-san, you're more indecent than I thought.
Yes... I'm...
I'm... I'm... truly an indecent woman!
I can feel the coach's penis inside my pussy right now.
Cumming... I'm going to cum, coach!
Is it okay to let it out inside?
It's okay, please give me your semen.
Please give me your hot thing!
I'm cumming~!
Eh? Coach, that's...
It's okay, I'll make you feel good.
No... You can't!
You can't do it in there!
It's great.
Even though it's my first time...
It feels so good with coach!
Good... I'm...
gonna cum with my ass!
I-I'm...
It's gonna come out!
I'm gonna cum again...
Marina-san's asshole is really narrow,
it's really tight for me.
Great, I want you to be more rough.
Coach...
I can't hold it... I'm gonna cum... I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum from my ass and clitoris.
I-It's cumming!
Coach, you're the best!
Hey, did something happen with Hongou-san?
Eh?
W-What do you mean?
She's gonna let you to be her swimming coach again
and you seem happy about it.
T-That's not true, besides, it doesn't concern you at all.
O-Of course it's gonna be my concern!
Wha-
The truth is...
There's something I wanna talk to you about, wait for me
at this pool tonight.
I-I got it.
Then, I'll see you later...
Hinako-san, what do you wanna talk about?
Um...
That... The truth is... I like you.
Eh?
It really made me happy when you said that you liked my swimsuit.
But recently, it makes me sad when I saw you look at other
women's swimsuit or when you're peeping underwater.
T-That's...
But I'm really surprised... I didn't think that
you would like someone like me.
You hate me?
No, not at all.
Hey, do you really like me?
I like you, Hinako-san.
Hinako-san, is it okay?
If you want, please be gentle with me.
Hinako-san, you're so cute.
I-Idiot, don't say something like that, it's embarrassing.
It's really wet.
No... Don't say that...
Your finger is great!
Please touch it more!
I'm cumming!
Hinako-san, please bear with this a little longer.
It's... good... It feels so good!
S-Something's gonna come out!
Hinako-san...
I'm coming in.
Are you okay, Hinako-san?
Is it possible that you're virgin?
I-It's okay... go on.
O-Okay.
It's inside!
Hinako-san, I'm gonna start moving.
Sure.
Hinako-san, does it feel good?
It hurts...
But, I'll try my best.
It feels strange...
It's rubbing inside...
Hinako-san, you're so cute... I really like you.
I-It's intense!
I... I really like you too, Makoto!
It feels good!
Makoto's penis feels really good inside of me...
Hinako-san!
More, I want you to feel more of it.
If you're doing it that way...
I'm... gonna go crazy from that!
It's great... I'm gonna... gonna cum!
Cumming!
Hinako-san, are you okay?
It's your first time, but it's already this intense...
You're gonna take responsibility for this, right?
Eh?
Should I raise your part-time schedule?
Eh?!
In exchange of that... would be...
I'm gonna let you have sex with me more often.
I-Is that true?
That's true.
Your penis is healthy once again.
Of course it will be, since you're saying it like that.
With Hinako-san's mouth...
Huh?
Would you do it with your mouth?
Do it with my mouth?
Sure, I'll do it.
There's something sour coming out from the tip of your penis.
Hinako-san, please take it all the way in.
Hinako-san, I'm going to cum soon!
D-Don't do that.
Hinako-san, please take it with your mouth!
You can't!
If you touch it with your finger...
I'm sure I'm gonna go crazy!
It feels good.
It's great.
It feels too good.
I feel good too... Please cum again, Hinako-san.
Cumming... I'm gonna cum...
I'm gonna cum many times for you!
A-Again...
I'm cumming.
Cumming!
Please hold me once more!
I can't do that, I'm not gonna have sex
with another woman again!
N-No.. I've been forced to do it, even though
I already have Hinako-san.
Hongou-san?
Eh?!
Are you in there?
N-Negishi-san, what do you want with me?
No, the lesson's gonna start soon, but I can't seem to find him.
I'm worried about him.
Ah... Yes, I just feel sick right now.
I'm sure that the coach is gonna be back soon,
did you check his locker room yet?
Yes, I wonder where he is...
Beside's that, I'm worried about your condition.
Is it okay if I'm going inside?
You can't, I'm sure I'll be fine soon after this.
Hongou-san, are you sure with your condition?
Yes, I'll be just fine in here.
Are you okay? Should I take you to the infirmary?
Fine... Fine... Fine... I'll be just fine... I'm sorry to make you worry about me.
It's fine for now.
Um, Coach Negishi?
Yes?
Even though we're both women here, I'm sure it's embarrassing to look at each other's naked body.
Would you please...
Ah... I'm sorry about that, I hope you get well soon.
If you need something, just go to the infirmary, okay?
Sure... I'm gonna come!
Cumming...
I'm really getting excited with this thing...
Good~
I want you to be strong and hard with it!
Good... Good!
Great... Great... It's great!
Good-
Cum... I'm gonna cum!
Cumming!
I'm have sex with Marina-san again!
What's more, is that I couldn't hold it when Hinako-san came over that time.
It's from Hinako-san!
Good work.
Are you free this Sunday?
If you'd like, maybe we can somewhere together?
It would be good if you can go.
I'm sorry.