One night,
in an abandoned school building at Kitanoseifu Academy,
a woman with a sword attacked a being called a "Geist".
Her attacks were countered however, and she fell victim.
Meanwhile, Hiroki was hit by a truck while walking to school.
But he escaped without a scratch.
To verify that there was nothing abnormal about his body,
Yukiko-sensei, the school's nurse, gave him a full body exam.
However, no abnormalities in his body were found.
Lydia, captured by the Geists,
had her body violated in several locations by the Tentacle Geist.
And by the hypnotic words of the Cat Ceist,
she acquired feelings that are not Doll-like.
She was also tricked by the Cat Ceist into revealing her Doll comrade.
On his way home from school, Hiroki ran into a creepy man in the park.
When he tried to escape,
a mysterious beautiful girl stood in his way.
Who are you?
In light of the heinous crimes with the Geists,
I hereby release you now.
You release me?
So you're helping me?
My target is you. Ridium rake.
Wait, is it me you're targeting?
You've got the wrong guy! He's the bad one!
Oh no. l'm dead!
Vol.02   The Magical Girl's Predicament
Lizard Geist.
Is he protecting me?
Or is he protecting her?
I mean, this guy's not human!
Leave this to me.
What do you mean?
So you came to face me in your true form.
You've got courage.
And what's more, you're glowing...
I see! You're a released Doll!
Imagine running into a Single Figure - it's my lucky day!
Okay!
I'm your opponent!
Die!
Too slow!
I did it!
Have you learned your lesson?
How dare you thwart me!
What the hell is this?
This is just like an anime!
Is she dead?
She's alive!
At a better glance, she's really cute too!
I guess I shouldn't just leave her here...
No, no!
She tried to kill me.
I'm not sure what she'll try to do once she wakes up.
So see if I care!
Stupid bitch!
There's no way in hell I'd help you!
What've you been staring at lately?
I was just remembering what it was like when I first met you,
and wondering how we got to sitting across
from each other at the cafeteria.
It's all in the past now.
It doesn't concern me.
Come on, don't say that!
I'm the one who should be concerned.
Me.
I carried your unconscious body home and took care of you
after you tried to kill me.
I see...
But I no longer intend to kill you.
At least not now.
I decided instead that I would borrow your body and research you...
...for a while.
Of course you did.
It's a miracle that I'm not dead by now.
Though I wish you wouldn't use the word "borrow".
Well?
So you think the reason my taste in food
changed is because a Geist infected me?
Yes.
Exactly...
Shion, at least stop eating curry when you're talking.
You're a lady, aren't ya?
Don't patronize curry.
Curry has a good balance of meat and vegetables.
I never tire of it plate after plate, either.
Don't change the subject like that!
You really are strangely bossy.
You needn't compliment me so.
No!
I wasn't complimenting you!
But anyway, I was really bummed when I found
out I was sorta buddies with that lizard guy.
You're lying, right?
Tell me you were lying!
Geists are wanderers in the dimension in which we live.
Ordinarily, they possess no physical presence,
but occasionally they slip though.
They come to life via the lifeforce of human hosts.
Those humans who are infected acquire
special mental and physical powers,
taking on the tasks their parasite Geists wish of them.
That is why I must kill you.
What's more, you have not changed completely into a Geist,
but you seem to have powers that surpass those of the Geists.
This is a first for me.
So I find it very intriguing.
So that's why you want to research me.
Shion, who are you...
I am a Doll.
My codename is "Shion".
Using your words, I am an existence that
teleported here from a different dimension.
We Dolls were created to exterminate
humans who have been infected by Geists.
We are manufactured bodies.
Then why are you dressed in my school's uniform following me around?
To eat curry.
Yeah, not that...
Oh, I see.
You mean in the long term.
To keep close watch on you.
If you show signs of further transformation
into a Geist, I will slit your throat.
I will twist your head.
Then I will slash your head off.
You don't need to be so explicit...
You would most certainly die.
Even if you were to survive, you wouldn't
be able to do much without a head.
So I will take your remains with me back to my world.
Ah, I see.
Well, I didn't see you around all morning.
Don't tell me you'll be "absent" from swimming class this afternoon?
Swimming is in the afternoon?
"Swimming"?
Swimming...
Swimsuit?
Jeez.
Shion sure is hot!
She's got the perfect body, and her boobs are so huge!
Why didn't I notice her sooner?
I've been wasting my time.
Of course you didn't notice her sooner.
Shion only started going to school here today.
Is she really your cousin?
I can't imagine you two sharing any DNA.
That's another bone I have to pick with Shion.
Picking an alibi without consulting me first.
Pushy bitch.
Shion!
How did your boobs get so big?
Aw, cut it out Miho.
What kind of reaction is that?
Doesn't she have any feelings?
What a freakish chick.
She's got everyone wrapped around her finger.
– She's already the most popular person here.
– All right everyone,
it's time for class.
Sensei... Fucking sexy as usual!
And her mouth was on my...
Cum!
Cum real thick! Fill up my mouth!
Shoot your semen deep down my throat!
Drown my mouth full of your semen...
Hey.
Your expression looks strange.
Are you already starting to awaken?
If you're changing into a Geist, I'll kill you now.
I-It's nothing!
Oh my...
You two sure are close.
Huh? Are you a student in this class? I don't remember you.
Sensei, she's Asaki Shion!
She's Asaki-kun's cousin.
Oh... Is that who she is?
Nevertheless, you've got a great body.
Very much so.
Really?
But having a great body is not all it takes to be a great woman.
You need a little more of that thing called "pheromones".
You mean, like this?
Th-Then, how about this?
And then... this.
You mean, like this?
Hey, cut it out already.
What are you all doing!?
Misuzu-sensei, doesn't it embarrass you as a teacher
to be exhibiting such a lascivious posture?
And who are you?
Not a student at this academy, I see.
What're you talking about?
She's Asaki Shion.
That old bag actually forgot about Shion?
So I guess never getting married does fuck with your memory.
She needs to get laid.
Be quiet!
I have never seen this girl before.
Leave this place at once.
Now she's done it again.
She used that spray to fool everyone else.
More importantly though, where does she hide that spray?
Ah, Shion-san!
Lovely as always, I see.
Anyway,
Misuzu-sensei, please begin your instructions right away.
Hey.
Forget about that.
I want you to come to the old school building with me after school.
The old school building?
No way, I don't wanna go to that gross place.
People say it's haunted.
That's exactly why I want to go.
Okay, kids.
Let's start class.
Everyone dive in.
Yahoo!
Diving!
Take me there after school.
What is she thinking of?
So cold!
Excellent!
What a lovely scene.
Do you like being so full?
You are sure a lucky one getting dinner for free.
Fill yourself full of lovely nutrients and birth me some cute little babies.
They're born!
Now you've become a Geist mommy!
Well then.
I'll have you give birth to more and more of them for me, meow.
Yes.
I will fill you up with my semen, too.
Let's go!
Even though you just gave birth to a baby, you're very tight!
You're very tres bien!
You sure are a meaty Doll.
Marvelous!
Yahoo!
I'm cumming!
By the time the next kid is born, the first kid will have grown up.
Then the Tentacle Geist you gave birth to will fuck you.
Isn't it a beautiful cycle?
You will truly be a part of the Tentacle Geist's life.
I look forward to it!
Hey. Tell me why people think it's haunted.
I don't wanna.
I suck at that sort of thing.
How did you hear about the ghosts anyway?
During swimming class, Kodaka-san told me.
Explain the details to me.
About a month ago, a senior girl and the music
teacher went missing at the same time.
There were rumors that the two were dating anyway.
And since the music teacher had a wife and
kids, people thought they just eloped.
But then their clothes were found in the forest nearby.
They were torn to shreds and there were some
sort of strange bodily fluids on them.
Knowing it was serious, we called the police
and they investigated the scene.
But they couldn't find any bodies or any evidence of where they'd gone.
On these grounds, there's an old school building from the
Meiji era that was used during the Second World War.
Lots of old schools have them, I hear.
There's alway been rumors that the souls of those who
died in the war haunt the old school building, too.
So in the end,
people decided that the couple went to the old school
building to hide and were killed by the ghosts.
What a ridiculous story.
Certainly.
By the way, why are you so emotionless when you talk to me?
Because there is no need to mask my true identity around you.
Is this the old school building?
Yeah.
It's my first time here,
and it's just as creepy as I thought it'd be.
This place is also jammed.
I can't pick up any Geist signals here.
Come on, let's just leave.
Several days ago, Geist readings were picked up in this town.
Another Doll and myself came here to investigate.
But she disappeared suddenly and was imprisoned here.
So my reason behind coming to this
school was not only to observe you.
I get it.
So that's why you were gone all morning.
I've been meaning to ask...
Why did you rescue me that night?
Why are you asking that now?
Well, I'm not sure.
Maybe because I thought you were cute.
"Cute?"
You've got a knockout body.
A swimsuit and school uniform both look good on you.
I wish I could date someone like you.
I-Is that so...
Huh? Are you blushing?
Of course I'm not!
I don't have feelings!
Yo, my best friend!
How lucky I am to run into you here!
Otahara... What're you doing out here?
Well, I...
It's because he was following us.
Just as I had hoped.
And thanks to you, my suspicions have been confirmed.
Well, now you've said it.
But I think I should also be thanking you.
Battle Program, emergency activation.
Two-level process,
A-5 through C-8 opened.
Z-1 as well.
2-C launched.
ACU.
491.
007.
Shion.
Shion!
Oh, I see.
So it's just as my friend told me.
Your friend?
So you have an accomplice?
Who is he?
Tell me.
I cannot do that.
I will, however, show you my true form.
Transformation in progress.
Geist infection detected.
I will release you.
Ridium Rake.
O-Otahara!
Do you like my beautiful form?
It is my body's rebirth!
Fucking gross!
Really?
Wh-What are you saying?
Slug Geist.
The years of ugliness in his heart have
manifested into his outward appearance.
Horrible. That thing is the worst.
You thought I'd be your friend?
Try evaluating yourself from time to time, you monster.
What did you say!?
I offered you such friendship and you
betray me with arrogant scolding?
You have a Geist in you too, you know!
Namekuji, I have one final question for you.
Namekuji? How dare you translate my name into Japanese!
It's slug, you hear? Slug!
This is why I hate Dolls.
Don't you have any manners?
Now, ask me again properly.
So, Namekuji, who is controlling you?
If you tell us, I will ease your passing.
Aw, man...
No!
Hey, don't take it out on me!
Sh-Shion! Are you okay?
No! Don't touch that!
You protected him, just as I thought.
My scheme was a success.
That arrow would have killed a human, however
I suppose it's just a nasty poison dart for a Doll.
Hiroki, don't mind me.
Just escape.
Oh, Shion!
You just called me "Hiroki", didn't you?
I don't think that's relevant now...
Hiroki!
Yes. Listen to your Dolly.
You don't have time for chit-chat.
What the... No way...
Hiroki!
Foolish boy!
Now do you appreciate the situation you are in?
Now, Doll, while the poison is still working,
there's one last thing I want from you.
I'll have plenty of fun with you.
I can completely suppress my pleasure circuits.
That is because Single Figures have stronger
programming than standard Dolls.
Will you be able to say such noble things
once this has had its way with you?
That's...
Ouch!
What did you inject me with?
It's a special Doll serum.
Filling a Doll's body with this will allow
me to manipulate her pleasure center.
With this in your system, your body will
feel everything with intense senses.
There's no stopping it.
I don't know why, but...
My body... is hot...
You're getting turned on already?
Stop it.
Now, I'll let you go if you tell me.
Why haven't you killed that Geist infected boy yet?
What do you expect to get out of him?
I'll never tell you...
It doesn't concern you.
Don't tell me, that pitiful little human dick gets you hot?
But I haven't...
Done anything like that...
So you're still a virgin?
I get to have my way with a virgin who's
also a Single Figure? I'm so lucky!
You'll never break me...
Impudent bitch.
Then maybe I should be more rough with you.
What're you planning on doing?
I've already got you under some extra strong drugs,
but I'll inject you with the highest dose.
Stop it!
With this, you'll be able to experience
sexual pleasures like never before.
My breasts... What... is this sensation?
Oh, my. This is so great I can't stand it.
You're going to lose your mind from the good sensations.
These sensations... I've never felt before...
Then tell me!
Why have you not yet killed that pathetic boy?
Stop it... No more...
Stop touching my breasts...
Answer me!
Stop it.
Tell me!
I'm cumming...
So even the all-mighty Single Figure is no
match for my venomous bodily fluids.
I'm so proud I could kiss myself!
Hiroki...
Seeing you so pained makes me want to do more!
This time, let's thrust this guy into you!
You're a monster.
Resistance is futile.
Wh-What's this?
Now that's more like it.
A Single Figure's throat sure feels good!
This feels amazing!
Very good! Very good!
Hiroki...
And now it's time to violate the most important part.
You're still continuing?
Now it's time to tweak your clitoris.
You won't be able to resist me now.
I won't stop until you tell me what I want to know.
Do as you wish.
I've already been violated.
So no matter what you do to me, I won't feel anything.
Then I'll violate you some more!
I'll tear both your body and your heart to shreds!
Hiroki!
I won't lose to him!
No!
Stop it...
Stop it!
Stop it. No!
You want me?
You want my penises in you?
I won't ever forgive you. Never.
Then let's finish this off.
Violating your real hole is the most proper.
I vow... that you will not get away with this. I will kill you.
An "emotionless" Doll tells me this?
Sounds like you're angry.
How amusing!
I look forward to hearing more.
Oh, your butthole is so soft.
I had no idea a Single Figure was so soft down there.
Stop it! I'll break!
No...
Your virgin hole is so amazing!
If I go in there, I'll probably cum right away.
This feels great!
Beg me for more.
Beg me for more of my mighty Geist dick!
Hiroki... Hiroki, help me!
I'm cumming!
No!
Now it's time to take the vanilla.
Huh? I sense something strange.
What? He's gone?
Where did he go?
You! Who are you!?
Miko... The leader of the Geists.
I don't need memories,
omoide wa iranai
friendship or bonds.
yuujou mo kizuna mo
I won't miss it if I throw it all away.
subete nage dashite mo oshiku wa nai
I have unforgivable feelings,
yurusarenu omoi mo
but if I live for your sake,
anata no tame nara ba
I believe I can pierce through those feelings.
tsuranuite yukeru to shinjirareta
It was within my grasp,
kono te no naka ni
but the dreams slip through my fingers,
tsukanda hazu no yume ga kieteku
as if they're floating to a land long ago.
maru de hakanai utakata no you ni
Just the mere fact that I love you
anata o aishite iru koto dake ga
is proof enough that I lived.
watashi no ikita akashi
My last wish is one and only one.
saigo no negai wa tada hitotsu dake
Please don't ever forget that I loved you.
ai shita koto zettai ni wasurenai de