St-Stay away from me!
I'm a teacher!
I'm a teacher here at this academy!
You're not even a student here.
Yet you intend to kill me?
The form you currently assume is fake.
You are no teacher.
So neither of us belong at this school.
Fear not.
I will be swift.
Just stay still.
So you stepped into our trap.
I tried to warn you when I said, "Stay away from me."
That's what you get for disobeying your teacher.
Resistance is futile.
Even your kind cannot cut through those wires.
There is no escape for you.
This is our victory!
Allow me to introduce you.
This is a Thunder Geist.
His name is Ura-chan.
When I told him of the plan to trap you, he insisted on helping out.
Sorry. Any last words?
Please kill me.
Oh great!
What marvelous resolve you have!
But alas,
I've grown tired of tormenting human females all the time.
And more so, I had difficulty figuring it out when
you were disguised as a human student,
but you've got a really hot body.
I just can't let it go to waste.
I hear that your kind have very high levels of pride.
I wonder how much of my abuse you can tolerate.
Vol. 01   The Angel with Cruel Magic
Woah!
Oh shit. I'm late!
I guess eating steak first thing in the
morning isn't such a great idea after all.
If I take a shortcut here, maybe I'll make it...
So your homeroom teacher didn't believe you.
Infirmary
Yes.
And he told me I'd better think of a more
creative excuse next time I'm late.
This day just sucked!
The truck that hit me drove away.
But wouldn't you ordinarily die?
A truck hit you, and you didn't even get a scratch?
Even I don't believe it!
I thought I fell head first into the street.
But it's true!
Shit.
Here I thought you of all people would believe me, Misuzu-sensei.
By the way, Asaki-kun,
about what you were saying earlier...
You ate steak for breakfast?
Yes.
And I used to hate meat.
But suddenly, I really crave it.
So your taste in food changed suddenly.
I see.
But I do believe what you're saying.
I know you're not the type of boy who lies.
Really? You believe me?
You've never lied to me all the other times you came to talk.
What a relief!
I knew I could count on you!
But we should still examine you a little just in case.
Can you take off your clothes for me?
Okay!
Seems all normal to me.
Misuzu-sensei is looking at me naked!
Makes me feel kinda funny.
Ah... She smells so good!
Are you sure nothing hurts at all?
There are some cases where pain doesn't show up until after the fact.
Ah... I'm such a horndog!
I wanna bury my face in those huge tits!
Looks like your head is okay.
Woah, so squishy!
Oh shit. My dick's getting hard.
Well, let's begin the next exam.
Misuzu-sensei... What're you doing?
What am I doing?
Taking a semen sample, of course.
Semen?
I've never heard of a school nurse giving that kind of exam.
What're you saying?
Haven't you heard?
It's been recognized nationally as a very
thorough method of checking for illness.
Huh? Is that true?
Of course it's true.
A lot of things can be learned from analyzing someone's semen.
Even I'm a little embarrassed to perform the exam.
But it's my job. I have to do it.
I believed your story, but you won't believe mine?
That makes me sad.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
As long as you believe me, it's okay.
Now, let's begin.
You've got a major hard-on.
Ah, Sensei not there!
So this is your precum.
Very thick.
How nasty.
What were you thinking about...
while I was talking to you?
Nothing!
I wasn't thinking about anything!
Are you sure?
Weren't you thinking about my tits?
Didn't you want to bury your face in my chest?
And that's not all, is it?
You wanted me to suck your dick.
Or you wanted me to jerk you off with my boobs.
You were fantasizing about that, weren't you.
No, I wasn't!
Oh dear. Lots of nasty juice has come out now.
You sure are honest.
I must reward honest boys.
Sensei... don't...
Your dick is so firm... You're nasty.
Sensei, please stop this.
We shouldn't...
It's still so firm and springy.
Where does such virility come from?
I'm so proud you grew up into such a big man.
Sensei, we shouldn't...
This is school.
But this is a medical exam.
It's a well trusted extraction method of your semen.
But are you sure you have to suck it out with your mouth?
Since we have to do it anyway, we might as well have a little fun with it.
I don't mind.
Ah, your dick is so thick it fits perfectly into my mouth.
More juice is steadily flowing out.
It's so warm, thick and yummy...
Sensei, this feels great!
Then let yourself enjoy it.
More semen will come out that way.
The more sample I can collect, the more
accurate your test results will be.
Oh no!
My balls...
I wonder if that's a little too intense for someone so young?
More juice is flowing from your dick.
So much.
I can't let it go to waste.
Sensei!
It's so yummy.
Squeeze more out.
I want to drink more.
Your juice tastes so good.
Let me drink more.
Sensei!
Is this your first time?
How do my boobs feel?
Oh, you're so hot.
So much is flowing into my mouth now.
It's so delicious!
More. Give me more!
I can't... That's dirty, Sensei.
I love dirty things.
Make me dirtier.
Cover me in your filth.
I want my tits drenched in your cum.
So more... shoot more out!
Sensei... You don't mind getting dirty?
Make me dirty!
Make me your slave with your dripping cum.
I'm a dirty teacher. Punish me by making me your slave!
Make you my slave?
Doesn't it turn you on to see your teacher looking so naughty?
That's perfectly normal.
It's okay, get more turned on.
You can do whatever you want to me.
This is great.
Sensei... You're so dirty!
More came out.
Yes, that's it.
Shoot out more cum.
Soak me through the skin with your smelly cum.
Make me even more sticky and dirty.
I'm losing my mind.
Getting doused in your semen is making me lose my mind.
More.
I want more of you, Asaki-kun!
Sensei, yes!
Wow!
My dick and balls...
Unreal!
Good!
Give me more to drink.
Shoot out more cum.
I want you to drown my entire mouth in your wonderful semen.
Sensei.
I'll suck you harder.
Everything's inside your mouth!
Hurry.
Give me all your juice.
Amazing!
This is the first time so much has come out.
And yours is so delicious.
I won't let a drop go to waste.
I'm sucking it all up.
Sensei! Yes!
You're shoving your dick so deep inside.
You're fucking your teacher's throat, you know.
This feels great!
Your dick is filling me up...
I want to make you dirtier.
I want to make you even dirtier.
I wanna fuck you up.
I can't breathe... it's so much...
I want to break you.
I want to break the inside of your mouth.
How is this?
It's pushing so far inside that I can it breathe.
Is it delicious?
Sensei, does my dick taste good?
Yes... very... delicious...
Does it feel good?
Does it feel good having your throat fucked?
Yes. It feels very good... so good...
Having my throat fucked feels so good!
My whole throat is filled up!
You want it, don't you?
You want my semen, don't you?
Yes, I want it!
Gimme your semen.
Fill up my whole body with your semen!
Here I go!
I'm dousing you with more semen!
I'm scared!
I think I might drown with all your cum inside of me.
But I want it. Fill me up.
I need your cum.
Cum now.
Fill me up so full.
I want to drown in your cum.
Punish me for being such a dirty teacher!
I'm getting so full... I can't breathe... it's choking me...
This is the first time anyone has cum so much on me.
So delicious!
Why are you so delicious?
I'm so proud.
You've grown into such a delicious man.
Sensei, let me see the inside of your mouth.
Are you satisfied?
Yes. I'm so very happy.
That's strange.
Misuzu-sensei is always in her office this time of day.
Oh well.
I'm coming in.
Ah, my best friend, so you were here?
You mustn't hog our school's Madonna, Misuzu-sensei, though.
All the boys here will hate you.
I didn't ask for your advice.
Well, see you later, Misuzu-sensei.
You're leaving already?
Never mind him, Otahara-kun.
What business did you have with me?
Hold that thought.
I'll be right back, Sensei.
Wait up, my best friend.
What is it?
You're already done with her?
That was fast.
Oh, and one more thing,
I am not your best friend.
Stop making decisions on your own.
It's your snappy attitude that I like so much.
You really creep me out.
Should you really speak to me that way?
I had something really awesome to share with you today.
Bro, bro, I acquired a very nice "thing" today.
After all, today is a Magical Girl Ai day.
Magical Girl?
I... I don't really wanna see that shit.
I prefer the real thing.
But the sequel is so much better than the original.
I'd like to get your opinion on it.
It's even better than the first!?
W-Well... I guess if you really want my opinion on it, I'll have to watch it.
Just like last time, I hid it in the social studies room in the same place.
I got it.
Wow, today sure was my lucky day!
First I survive getting hit by a truck,
then I get to fuck my teacher.
And now I get to watch the sequel to Magical Girl Ai?
I guess this episode will have even more crazy stuff!
Well then, Doll-chan.
It seems like your sister is coming this way.
Is that true?
Kill me.
Oh dear.
Quiet as usual, you girls are.
Just like a doll.
That really makes me a sick cat.
Kill me at once!
But I can't kill ya that easily.
We're just getting into the main event.
It's show time!
Come, my little children.
Put this little Doll-chan here in a special happy mood.
Te-Tentacle Geists?
Yes.
But these little ones are a special version that I have created.
They're engineered specially to suit the body of a Doll.
I'm sure you'll enjoy them.
We Dolls have no feelings.
This sort of intimidation will not work on us.
You have no feelings?
Is that true?
I thought you Dolls were created with the same
materials as the females on this planet.
So you surely have receptors for pleasure and pain.
You also have sexual capacity.
Just by having your nipples tweaked, you're feeling it, huh?
I'm not feeling anything...
I'm not feeling...
I know you're feeling it.
You're very sensitive.
How about this one next?
Thunder.
What did you just do?
A human nervous system can be enhanced by electric shock.
You know?
This boy is called "Thunder Geist" because
he can summon electricity from anywhere.
Just by pumping a little electricity into your tits...
Your senses are overloaded with
electricity and you get totally turned on!
That make you happy?
S-Stop it.
Now, my cute little Tentacle Geists, don't let Uracha upstage you.
Let that little Doll-chan have some more fun.
Stop it.
My boobs are so...
How impossible!
How is this happening?
You're falling apart!
Finish her off, Thunder!
I'm... cumming...
Oh my.
You're just too sensitive, my little Doll-chan.
You cum just from having your boobs tickled a little?
It's over too fast and now I'm bored.
Then kill me.
What was that!?
You mustn't! You must let me enjoy you a little more!
Okay. The next phase is right here...
D-Don't.
Stop it!
Not there...
Oh dear, oh dear.
The emotionless Doll-chan is upset?
What a strange world.
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
Are you frightened, Doll-chan?
Have we hit the spot?
Shall my little children thrust themselves into your happy spot?
Stop it!
Don't!
No!
Don't...
Stop... it...
No... Stop it!
It's ripping!
S-Stop... No!
I'll break!
It's tight!
It's all inside my uterus.
My uterus walls are... expanding.
No! Don't move!
Please, stop!
What you're doing... will not be forgiven.
Never.
My uterus!
Oh no!
Please.
Stop this!
Her belly's getting all swollen from my little children.
You must be feeling it well now.
I'll kill you, god dammit.
I swear I'll kill you!
Meow! I'm scared!
You're so vicious!
And who was the one who said you had no feelings?
What is it?
You don't like being scolded, it seems.
But there's more to come.
No!
It's too much!
Please stop... it won't work!
Go to heaven!
I'm cumming!
Mew!
This is their fifth time and they're still going!
Dollies sure are horny, aren't they.
This is wearing me out.
I need to catch another one of you.
I may be a Doll, but I'm number 13.
It means you shouldn't underestimate me.
I'm much more different from Single.
Single, eh?
So you fell for it.
So the other one of you is Single?
I don't know.
I m... I'm cumming!
Again?
Invite Single over here.
I refuse.
You damn doll.
Thunder.
I'm... I'm cumming!
Please... stop.
Kill me, please.
Just... kill me.
My pretty little children, please violate that little Dolly's asshole next.
Stop it.
Not there.
I haven't yet...
That's the reaction!
So you haven't experienced anything anal yet.
I look forward to seeing your reaction.
Little children, please tear open her hole.
No!
That hurts!
Not my butt!
Stop! No...
I've never even had one thing inside there.
If all of them come in at once, my butthole will rip open!
That hurts!
I'm losing it!
No!
Call Single's Doll to me.
If you do, then I will ease your passing.
It won't work.
Torture me all you want, I will never do your bidding.
You still have the energy to act tough!
Well then, we'd better punish you some more.
No!
Don't!
Does it feel that good?
Dolly's sexual lust sure is something.
How very amusing.
Well, well take you to the finish.
Thunder?
I'm... I'm cumming!
Go!
I'm cumming... cumming...
Go! Go!
It's no good.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
Again!
I'm cumming... It's still continuing?
Finish.
I'm cumming... I can't take it!
I'm cumming!
Oh, what a pity.
Well, shall we get her final answer?
Okay, Thunder?
Well, this is my stop.
See ya later then. Bye-bye.
See ya later, Hiroki.
Be careful in this park. I hear something
really creepy happened here years ago.
Hey, hey, stop scaring me.
It's not like I want to go home this way.
See ya!
It's so late.
It's not like I want to walk home in the dark.
What was that noise?
Who's that?
I'm your friend.
Wh-Who are you?
I don't need memories,
omoide wa iranai
friendship or bonds.
yuujou mo kizuna mo
I won't miss it if I throw it all away.
subete nage dashite mo oshiku wa nai
I have unforgivable feelings,
yurusarenu omoi mo
but if I live for your sake,
anata no tame nara ba
I believe I can pierce through those feelings.
tsuranuite yukeru to shinjirareta
It was within my grasp,
kono te no naka ni
but the dreams slip through my fingers,
tsukanda hazu no yume ga kieteku
as if they're floating to a land long ago.
maru de hakanai utakata no you ni
Just the mere fact that I love you
anata o aishite iru koto dake ga
is proof enough that I lived.
watashi no ikita akashi
My last wish is one and only one.
saigo no negai wa tada hitotsu dake
Please don't ever forget that I loved you.
ai shita koto zettai ni wasurenai de