Bonus Video
What are you doing, Hiroki?
Tying me up with my own swimsuit...
Perv!
Hey!
Hiroki!
Cut it out already!
Just st...
If you use your Doll powers, you can untie yourself easily.
You try and protest with your mouth, but your pussy says otherwise.
No, not there!
Time to go.
But I'm not wet enough yet.
That's fine with me.
Oh my. Looks like you're having fun.
Misuzu-sensei!
You guys left me out again.
Inexcusable!
Out of the way.
Move it, move it.
See?
Now you make me feel good...
Butt out!
I don't see the problem.
Keeping him all to yourself is mean.
Who do you think saved your life?
I want to have fun with him, too.
Don't steal him from me!
Deep throating is a special snake trick.
I'm cumming!
Hiroki! You just came...
You're so strong.
I'm putting it in, Shion.
You're so cute, Shion.
Don't say that.
This feels great. Your insides are great.
It's my turn next, so cum already.
Your swimsuit is great.
Hiroki, you cheater!
Shion, if you move like that I'll...
I'm cumming!
It's my turn next!
In this beautiful paradise...
I'm never going back to Japan!