Those who possess human bodies to take life in this dimension,
Geists are violent life forms who have traveled from another dimension.
During her battle with Slug Geist,
Shion, a Doll, was rescued by the legendary leader of the Geists.
Wolf Geist was created from the possession of Asaki Hiroki,
an ordinary high school student.
Though he was transforming into the Geist,
Hiroki still maintained his human heart.
Shion started to fall in love with him,
and that night, Shion gave herself to Hiroki, body and soul.
The next day Hiroki was called into the infirmary by Misuzu-sensei,
and was injected with a venom
that would fully transform him into Geist form in 24 hours.
Yukiko turned out to be a Geist.
Will Hiroki turn completely into a Geist?
And who are the mysterious group of people who arrived on the scene?
The mysteiy-filled story is now reaching its climax.
It's you, right?
You're the Single Figure who came to this dimension with that Doll.
"That Doll"?
I see.
It's you, isn't it?
You're the one who raped 13.
Where is she!?
I will not give you the answer for free.
However... If you defeat me, you will know!
Dammit!
You got caught!
Shit.
That must sting.
However I'm not finished yet.
I need to show you a really fun time.
Very nice, very nice.
Feel more pain.
That must hurt.
I'll put you in the same position as that other Doll.
Something's not right...
H-Hiroki?
Hiroki... You're still Hiroki?
13!
Vol.04   The Fallen Demon Angel
Lilium!
13...
7...
Shion...
I understand.
Don't tell me you're gonna kill your friend?
Don't do that!
She's been violated so much...
Her rejuvenation program won't work.
Shion, hurry.
Thank you, Shion.
Hey Shion, what are you doing?
I will trade my armor with her now. It has been damaged.
You can't... Doesn't that mean anything to you?
We were created to destroy Geists.
We must use any means necessary to do so.
Shion.
You're crying.
I'm just washing the dirt from my eye.
I can't have my lenses soiled.
Shion...
Wow, that was fabulous.
You truly are a pro.
Misuzu-sensei?
You bastard... Lilium!
Not so fast.
If you kill me now, you won't be able to prevent
Asaki-kun from turning fully into a Geist.
Hand over the antidote at once.
If you do, I will give you an easy death.
Do you say that line out of professionalism?
Or out of jealousy?
Misuzu-sensei?
Why are you doing this?
Hiroki! What are you doing?
What am I doing?
She came at me!
Now, just stay quiet.
Misuzu-sensei, what're you...
Hiroki!
I won't forgive you.
I'll kill the two of you now!
Wait a minute.
That wasn't my fault.
Doing such an act in front of me...
Unforgivable!
Like I said, Misuzu-sensei was...
I will punish you at once!
I just injected his body with the antidote.
He'll be fine.
She's right...
The venom that my scanner was picking up is gone now.
You bitch.
What are you up to now?
I'm not up to anything.
I just gave up.
Gave up?
Witnessing that last battle gave me an understanding.
Understanding of the fact that even if you turn into a
full-fledged Geist, I wouldn't be able to control you.
That's why I changed my mind and decided to release you.
What do you mean by that?
Good question...
I think I'll live as his slave from now on.
That way seems more appealing anyway.
I see.
Good for you, Hiroki.
Yeah, but that's... How shall I put it...
Oh, but won't you come along too?
I'm a Doll.
I couldn't...
Putting on airs is useless.
Your cheeks are telling me you can't live without Hiroki.
That's not...
Oh? So Dolls can make that expression.
Well, let's get along well as fellow slaves.
Misuzu-sensei!
What?
Could it be...!
What's happening this time?
Infinity.
Infinity?
You know him?
He stands at the top of all the Dolls.
He is our Master.
Your Master?
7, you surprised me.
I never thought a Geist would poison your judgement.
Wait.
Hiroki may have been infected by a Geist, but his heart is still human!
He is different from the other Geists!
Oh, I see.
So even Single Figures can be deceived.
Is that the power the leader of the Geists has?
However...
Stop it!
Don't!
Shion!
What's this?
My body won't... move...
Stop it.
Infinity.
7, we will reinvestigate your case later.
Stop it!
Shit!
Don't resist me.
This barrier was created from a sample of your own power.
The stronger you struggle, the stronger the barrier will become.
7, I want you to get a good look at this Geist's death.
Please stop this.
Shion.
Infinity... Stop this.
Shion!
Don't worry about me.
Hiroki!
You need to go home.
To your own world.
Hiroki!
When the Geist infected me, my number was already up.
Yes. I was meant to die here.
However you don't have to die.
So live for me!
I see.
So your heart is still human.
But we were programmed with the mission to
exterminate humans who have been infected by Geists.
No, don't... Hiroki... No!
Farewell, Leader of the Geists.
Goodbye, Shion.
No!!
What's this? Shion?
7... Why?
Was my controlling program... ineffective on you?
Where did that power come from?
I'm sorry, Infinity.
Emergency command sequence initiated.
Shion!
Emergency program initiated.
Phase two initiated.
Shion, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why did you do this?
I came to a realization.
On what?
Please. Just hold me without saying anything.
Shion!
Oh my, that makes me jealous.
Misuzu-sensei!
You're still alive?
I guess so.
Just as I was pierced, I injected my own body with a healing venom.
I was pretty close to dying, though.
However you... You betrayed your friends to protect a Geist, didn't you?
I don't regret it.
As long as Hiroki is safe.
Shion, I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
However since you've both already gone this far, I'll
need to request your assistance in helping me fight.
As fellow slaves of Asaki-kun, let's have some fun.
I feel the same way!
I'll help, too, so let me join in!
I don't need your help.
That was fast.
A month passed after that.
Everything remained normal at school.
As usual, rumors were circulating about the old school building,
so everyone stayed away from it.
So naturally, that gave me plenty of opportunities to have
some secret playtime with Misuzu-sensei and Shion.
Please. Let me join in.
No. You must watch us from there.
No!
I can't hold back.
Please!
This is embarrassing!
But it feels good, doesn't it?
Your pussy is soaking wet!
No, don't say that!
No, don't...
Shion, your nipples are so firm.
So nasty.
Ah, don't say...
Don't... No, if you do it like that...
No!
That'll turn me on too much!
Oh no.
Just watching makes me too hot!
Then, shall I do something even more pleasurable?
Hiroki, what are you going to do?
Something that will make you feel even hotter.
Here I go.
Well? Does it feel good?
Wow!
Please! Do it to me too, please!
Amazing, Shion.
Oh no!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
You're horrible, Hiroki.
Not this...
It felt good, though, didn't it?
I wanna feel good too!
Let me join in!
Move it.
You're so mean, my best friend!
If just this much makes you that hot though,
I wonder how you'll react to what's next?
Hiroki... what's next?
I will show you my new form, given to me by my Geist powers.
Hiroki... What's this?
These little beasts will keep you occupied, Shion.
Oh, gimme!
I want them too!
Please!
What... They're so slippery.
So slippery... Hiroki!
My nipples... No!
What's wrong, Shion? Doesn't it feel good?
I feel it...
My nipples are so hard.
I feel it... I'm feeling it!
Hiroki... Hiroki...
It feels so intense!
So intense...
This is... Oh no, I can't take much more!
Yes!
I'm cumming!
Please! L-Let me join in!
Please!
Not yet, Misuzu-sensei.
I'm busy with Shion right now.
Hiroki, I can't keep it up.
You should stop cumming just from
having your boobs played with, Shion.
We're just barely getting to the good stuff.
What?
No!
Hiroki!
Not this... Hiroki!
Here we, go Shion.
It's inside... of me...
Hiroki!
Do you like it, Shion?
I like it.
I love it.
I love it so much I can't stand it!
I smell your pussy, Shion.
It smells really nasty.
I love it!
Shion.
Yes... I'm cumming!
Then cum, Shion.
I'm cumming!
Misuzu-sensei, do you want it too?
Yes! Yes! Please!
Tease me lots!
Harder! Suck harder!
Make me lose consciousness!
Ah, my nipples...
More!
It's going in my pussy?
Yes, right there! That is my pussy. Go in there already!
It's inside...
What? In my ass too?
You're coming in there, right?
In my ass too, right?
Yes!
Sensei.
Next, I'll fuck the inside of your body plenty.
Yes!
Does it feel good?
Hiroki! I want it!
Like this?
So big! Hiroki! Hiroki!
Shion, does it feel good?
Does it feel good for you, Hiroki?
Yeah. Feels fucking good.
That makes me happy.
Shion!
Inside of me...
I feel you, inside of me...
Shion, you're naughty.
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does!
You feel great!
Shion!
You're getting bigger inside of me, Hiroki!
You'll tear me apart!
It's so intense!
Shion!
Yes. I'm cumming... Hiroki!
I'm cumming!
Yes!
Give it to me too!
Your dick... Give me your dick!
You want it that badly?
Then, I guess I'll let you have it.
You both look great.
Gets me going.
Yes!
Hiroki, what are we doing this time?
You both want my dick?
Yes!
I want it!
Hurry up and thrust it in!
Thrust it over and over again!
What about you, Shion?
I can't say it... It's too embarrassing.
Then you'll go without it.
Hiroki... No...
Sensei, your pussy juice is so bitter and yummy.
It feels so good! More!
I-I feel it. My butt loves this!
Ah, I can't stand it anymore.
I want your dick. Gimme your dick!
Hiroki...
What? I couldn't hear you.
Please... Me too...
I can't hear you at all.
Hiroki, you meanie.
Unless you speak loud and dear, I can't hear you.
I know!
Gimme!
Louder, please.
I want your dick, Hiroki!
Gimme!
Give it to me now!
Damn, Shion, now you're a total pig, too.
Well, because... You made me this way, Hiroki.
Is that so?
Then I'll thrust it in.
Hiroki... You're coming in.
Hurry! Do both!
So tight!
So many inside of me!
Yes!
Your asses and pussies are so tight.
This feels so intense!
Please, more!
I feel the penises!
Hiroki, you're...
This feels great!
This is...
So many!
So many penises... they won't fit!
Come in! More and more, come inside!
Oh no. Not so many. They won't fit.
The penises are amazing!
I love this!
Hiroki... you're coming in too deep...
Come in deeper!
All the way!
More, more, faster, faster!
Hurry! Give me more!
The penises... are in so deep...
Does it feel good?
Yes, it feels great!
Hiroki!
The penises feel so good, Master!
Give me more!
Here I go!
Yes! Harder, please!
This is amazing!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, cumming!
Hiroki sure is late.
He didn't have to carry that stupid
teacher all the way up to the infirmary.
Well... though I guess that's one of Hiroki's good points.
Besides, when we get home, we can have
a great time with no interruptions.
I guess I'll let it go.
It's been a month now...
I hope this happy life continues forever.
Wh-What?
I don't need memories,
omoide wa iranai
friendship or bonds.
yuujou mo kizuna mo
I won't miss it if I throw it all away.
subete nage dashite mo oshiku wa nai
– Infinity...
– Nee-san.
I have unforgivable feeling,
yurusarenu omoi mo
– It's been a while.
anata no tame nara ba
– How do you feel?
but if I live for your sake,
– Are you surprised I survived?
I believe I can pierce through those feelings.
tsuranuite yukeru to shinjirareta
It was within my grasp,
kono te no naka ni
– I was built to aid the rebirth of the Wolf Geist.
but the dreams slip through my fingers,
tsukanda hazu no yume ga kieteku
as if they're floating to a land long ago.
maru de hakanai utakata no you ni
– So until that happens, I cannot die.
Just the mere fact that I love you
anata o aishite iru koto dake ga
is proof enough that I lived.
watashi no ikita akashi
My last wish is one and only one.
saigo no negai wa tada hitotsu dake
– Too bad for you.
– That you lost your happiness.
Please don't even forget that I loved you.
ai shita koto zettai ni wasurenai de
– Did you want to say something, Nee-san?
Our love is being tom apart and hidden by the darkness.
kurayami de mienai hikisakareru ai ni
Even if we search for an exit, we will not find one.
deguchi o sagashitara ari wa shinai
– What is it, Nee-san?
As if to mock us as we search for each other,
motome au futari o azawarau ka you ni
the wheel of fate begins to spin again.
unmei no wa ga mata mawari dashita
– Hiroki...
The arms that once guided me
yasashii ude ni tsurarete ita
– I will kill him immediately.
are left behind by time,
toki wa sugita no
and there is nothing left for me now.
watashi ni wa mou nani mo nai kara
– Does that make you sad, Nee-san?
I'll keep my unattainable vow locked in my heart,
kanawanai chikai kokoro ni himete
and let go of my future.
ashita sae tebanashite
– You useless Doll.
Even if it's a fight I have no right in winning,
kateru sube nado nai tatakai demo
fasing it head on is the only choice I have.
tachimukau shika mou michi wa nai yo
– Nee-san. I won't deliver the final blow.
The world is ending.
owaru sekai ni
– Traitors should die slowly and painfully.
– Farewell, Nee-san.
I put my faith in us,
futari o kakeru ga
but the whiteness is all that reaches to us.
shiroku sashinoberu
– Hiroki... I'm sorry...
– I can't be... with you anymore...
For now...
ima wa
– I... will... disappear... so...
– So...
Just the mere fact that I love you
anata o aishite iru koto dake ga
– Just the mere fact that I love you...
is proof enough that I lived.
watashi no ikita akashi
– ...is proof enough that I lived.
– My last wish is one and only one.
My last wish is one and only one.
saigo no negai wa tada hitotsu dake
Please don't ever forget that I loved you.
ai shita koto zettai ni wasurenai de
– Please don't ever forget that I loved you.
Just the mere fact that I love you
anata o aishite iru koto dake ga
is proof enough that I lived.
watashi no ikita akashi
My last wish is one and only one.
saigo no negai wa tada hitotsu dake
Please don't ever forget that I loved you.
ai shita koto zettai ni wasurenai de