Hey there, guys!
Don't bring such books at school!
You don't have to be so strict, Class Rep.
Put it in your bag already!
Huh?
Yeah, yeah...
Alright.
Let's read it together!
Pervert! I really hate people like you!
I'm gonna beat you up next time!
Puberty SEX
Episode 1: Puberty Sex
I wonder why guys like those stuff.
I saw something disturbing!
Huh?
Whoa! Who the hell left this thing here?
What should I do?
Students commute this way
so I can't just leave it here...
I don't want to touch it, but it can't be helped.
I flipped it open!
I need to put it out of people's sight!
Why did I bring that back home?
B-But maybe I should take a look for a bit.
Huh?
I-It's inside!
This is stupid! I'm going home.
I-I got an amazing one today!
So, this is what they call a di...
Ahh, gosh!
I know it's wrong, but I can't help thinking about it!
Here's the porn book!
I'll take a page home again for today!
Huh?
Class Rep? What is she doing?
I got a lot of them now.
How long am I going to do this?
Or rather, I wonder if I have
the same one that as well.
That hole...
Alright, I'm gonna check it out!
Oh? There it is!
So this is how it looks like.
I wonder if my finger will fit inside.
I-It should, right? That thing goes in this, after all.
Wh-What did just happen!?
I'll have to take the book home to make sure!
The guys are talking about lewd stuff again!
They're the worst!
Tell them off, Class Rep!
Yeah, she's right!
O-Okay...
The girls hate it, so stop doing that!
Yeah, yeah... I gotcha.
Gosh, you really are a perv...
Sheesh, she's treating me like stupid...
She's a cutie if she shuts up, though!
Thanks, Class Rep!
You think so!?
Guys are such pervs, right?
Yeah, you said it!
Thank goodness, it's still here!
Class Rep!
O-Okazaki...
You tell us off like we're perverts,
but aren't you one as well?
Y-You're wrong!
No, I'm not!
Tell me that you've masturbated!
Or else, I'll tell this to everyone!
I-I masturbated...
I touched myself while looking
at it through a mirror...
T-Touch where?
I can't tell you that!
I'll tell everyone about you!
M-My pussy...
Let me see you masturbate.
No way! D-Don't get carried away!
Are you sure? I'll tell this to everyone.
B-But...
I won't be moving from here, okay?
Don't tell everyone about this, alright?
Hurry up and show me.
Just wait for a moment!
W-Will this do?
So, this is Class Rep's...
Don't stare too much!
Try playing with it.
Class Rep...
D-Didn't you say you won't get close?
I can't hold myself back anymore.
Aren't you feeling horny too?
I-I'm not...
Then, tell me what that is.
Th-This is...
Just be honest.
You're cute when you're lewd.
Huh... Huh!?
Th-Then, what if I told you
to show me your dick...
Will you?
Of course, I will!
Whoa!
It's an actual dick...
It looks like an alien!
It feels hard and warm...
This part is squishy and soft, huh?
This is kind of fun!
Class Rep, show me your tits.
O-Okay...
Don't laugh at me, alright?
Oh!
Do you hate huge ones?
I love them so much!
I'm glad...
Your tits are pressing hard on me!
It's like my tits are devouring his dick!
I can feel it twitching from
being engulfed with my tits!
This ejaculation thing is amazing!
I wonder what will happen if this goes inside me.
Class Rep, do you know what a blowjob is?
It's that thing they do in comics!
Isn't it like this?
I have to gobble it down, right?
I'm coming again!
It tastes weird, but it's making me feel dizzy!
Class Rep...
Huh?
I want to put it in your pussy!
F-Finally!
Try to ask for it by yourself.
Huh? No way!
It's because you're cute when being bashful...
Okazaki, your dick...
W-Will you put it inside my pussy?
It went deep inside!
Class Rep, it feels soft and warm inside you!
No way, stop describing it!
But you're squeezing me hard!
No... Don't move all of a sudden!
My breasts started to feel sensitive!
Class Rep...
You're so slippery and squishy all over down there.
Stop saying such embarrassing stuff!
S-So rough... Y-You're being reckless now!
I'm having sex with a guy from my class!
And worse, it's my first time
and we're doing it outdoors!
It's making very lewd sounds.
You're so lewd, Class Rep!
Th-That's because...
D-Don't be so rough on me!
M-My legs are gonna...
My hips gave out...
Then, you should sit down.
Here, sit above me.
D-Do I have to put it in myself?
Wow, you're sopping wet down there!
What's with this? It feels way better
than my own fingers!
Class Rep...  Put it in already!
M-Maybe like this...
It went inside!
Try moving.
O-Okay...
It's so deep!
You're fully exposed, Class Rep!
S-Stop staring...
You're so cute when you're lewd!
You got even harder than before!
It goes in and out of me...
Sex is such an amazing thing!
It's rubbing against several places inside!
I can't think of anything else anymore!
I can only think of sex and nothing else now!
What should I do? My hips won't stop!
I-It feels so good that it's driving me nuts!
The same thing in comics is being done to me!
It feels so good when you touch me!
Class Rep...
Huh?
Let's keep feeling good!
The force will reach deep inside
when you're that intense!
You'll shake my womb!
Your dick is going wild inside me!
No, you're so intense... If you do it that much...
I-I'm gonna come!
Because of my classmate's dick...
I'm coming!
My classmate's semen is flowing into me...
So, the rain stopped.
We should be able to walk home now.
I'll lend you a porn book next time.
Thanks...
But rather than that...
I'd love to learn more about sex.
That's why...
...we should do it again.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization