Swimsuits everywhere!
Huh? Rina's not here. Where's Rina?
What!? She went to rescue Ibuki, who's been raped!?
Sit tight, Rina!
Shishunki Shoujo Kari Kari
Translation: Voldemort Timing: PlasticYakuza Editing: Collectr Typeset & Encode: ShocWave QC: Chaosrains
Hey,
lie down on this table, ass facing me!
That's enough! Did you forget our bargain?
Oh! Nice smell.
I love that salty, sweaty smell!
Don't talk like that.
My butt is being stared at...
After all, she's unexpectedly good at giving head.
How horrible.
Take a look. Her butthole is so cute.
No! Stop it! S-Stop looking at me like that!
A school uniform plus a swimsuit.
Gotta make the most out of this.
I feel so embarrassed. I can't stand it!
Oh, you're such a dirty girl.
I can't take this anymore! Don't touch me down there!
Shall I enjoy the feel of your
swimsuit with my bare balls?
No! This is gross!
There's something between my butt cheeks.
What a lovely firm ass!
No! Not there! Don't put your dick in there!
No! Don't!
It's touching my pussy. It's hot... touching it!
I'm cumming!
Why? Why? No more cum!
No...
It's on my butt... Hot stuff on my butt.
That was fast. I'm up next.
No! Let go! Let go! Let go of me!
Haven't you heard of a swimsuit fetish?
What guy wouldn't do it?
No! It's slipping. No...
It's all slippery. No! Stop it! Stop it!
Not my butt!
Even though it's just over my swimsuit...
I still feel that dick.
It's sliding over me.
What's this feeling?
Stop it! Stop it!
You're gasping for air. Are you enjoying it too?
I'm not. How could I?
Oh no, I'm moaning.
Even though I'm not enjoying it.
Oh, no!
I hate this! Why!?
Hot stuff on me again. I can't take it anymore.
Okay, I'm next in line.
Stop it! Not there!
Don't!
Well?
Doesn't it feel good to have a
cock so close to your pussy?
That's not...
Why? Why is my body getting hot?
I'm about to let it out.
You're cumming again? No! Stop it!
O-Oh, no...
I'm hot down there.
Okay, guys. Take a break.
I'm tired of screwing around.
Stop it! Don't touch me! Take your hands off me!
Not there!
I-It's slipping into my pussy. No!
Not that!
My swimsuit is sliding up my
pussy. I'm feeling strange.
Your fingers are spreading me apart.
Oh, no! My head's going blank!
What a pretty pussy.
How nice.
Not your fingers! They're going in... my pussy.
It hurts!
Just one finger hurts her?
That's a virgin pussy for you.
No! Don't lick my dirty place!
That's where I pee! Don't lick it!
You're always holding back, aren't you?
I'll make you feel better than you've ever felt before.
Now you're higher up. No, not up there.
This bitch is pissing.
No, I can't take it anymore.
What's happening to me?
It's no use. My mind has gone blank.
I can't think of anything.
If you're this wet, you're probably ready.
After I'm finished, you guys can do whatever you want.
Don't do it. Please, not that!
It's futile. No one's gonna save you.
Just lie back and take it.
Here I come, Rina.
No! Don't put it. Don't put it in!
You assholes. How dare you hurt Rina!?
Let her go!
Kumi... You...
Rina, sit tight. I'll fucking kill them.
Asshole! Give it back!
Kumi, you really want your ass kicked that bad?
You have a choice:
You can get fucked either gently
or brutally. Your choice.
What a horrible smell, but I can't stop.
This is perfect. If you wanna go home, suck it dry.
What's with that defiant stare? Follow Rina's example.
Rina.
She's a virgin, yet she's doing this to save you.
And even though I didn't order her to,
she's using her hands and her mouth.
For my sake, she's doing something so gross.
Rina...
That's right. That's a good girl.
It's really... hot.
Why? I can't stop. I'm throbbing down there.
Very good, you two.
Take it on your faces.
What a horrible smell. Wow.
There's a lot on Rina's face, too.
Rina... Rina...
She's all soggy.
Stop it!
Seems like their cocks have revived.
Kumi!
Now, this time for sure I'll take away your virginity.
No... Stop...
Oh, no. I have no strength left.
You may say you don't want it,
but look at this. Look at all this juice.
No! No!
Why? I don't want to do this, but I can't resist him.
No!
It's moving... It's going in!
My turn next.
No...
Come on, suck it nicely.
K-Kumi...
Time for you to become a woman, Rina.
N-No!
No, no! Not there. Not there. No! No!
First, to break your hymen.
No!
Help me! Koizumi-kun!
Rina, time to thrust it into your pussy.
Wow, it's so tight! Now that's a virgin vagina!
Feels like you're squeezing me.
Wait a minute. It feels a little too tight.
And it really feels like she's "squeezing" me.
Hey, raise your ass!
Wh-What the fuck? You're Koizumi!?
Now that was close. Don't move.
Unless you want your dick pulverized, stay still.
K-Koizumi-kun.
Rina!
Anyone who hurts Rina is on my shit list!
Let go!
Whoa, I was just grabbing a guy's cock.
Smelly!
Are you fucking retarded?
Letting go was your final mistake!
You may have beat an entire gang or whatever,
but you can't beat me.
By the time you wake up,
Rina's pussy will be all slashed and bloody.
Hey, not so fast!
What the fuck did you just say!?
Don't play dumb, you fucking punk!
Hey! Rina's pussy belongs to me!
Don't touch it again.
Got it!?
They're... They're running away.
Gangs like that are weak once
you get rid of the leader.
You're pretty good.
Huh?
So that last whack finally kicked in now?
Are you okay? Koizumi-kun!
Koizumi-kun! Koizumi-kun!
Where... am I?
Wh-Why are you dressed like...
A-And this room...
Could this be... a love hotel?
But I was in the shed. Where's Kumi?
After that, Kumi and I carried you here.
After we tended to your wounds,
Kumi made me take a shower.
And then...
She left this.
Rina, I'm gonna go to the hospital.
Since Koizumi got hurt rescuing you,
you'd better thank him!
And also, be more honest about your feelings!
Get naked. That's the kind of place you're in.
You're supposed to be naked with the one you love.
Good luck! Bye, Kumi.
What the hell was she thinking?
Anyway, I guess we should leave this place.
R-Rina?
I need to be brave.
I...
Koizumi-kun, do you still love me?
Of course I do.
In that case, don't say anything.
Just accept my feelings.
Put it in! Stick it inside me!
I'm inside of you now, Rina. We're finally...
It hurts that much?
I guess it hurts, Rina.
We can stop if you want.
No, don't stop.
No. If I stop now...
I'm fine. I'm perfectly fine, so...
It does hurt a little.
But I'm hot crying because of that.
Rina...
Today was filled with horrible things.
But you came to rescue me.
And now, my happiest time has come.
Thinking of this makes my heart
so full, I could just cry.
So don't worry. Keep going.
Rina.
Koizumi-kun...
So deep...
Koizumi-kun!
Oh, you're in so deep!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
Hey, Koizumi-kun.
I live at a karate dojo.
I've learned karate since an early age.
Every day after school, I had to practice.
My parents made me.
But something didn't feel right.
After I started high school,
I found I wanted to go to karaoke with everyone.
To go on dates with a boyfriend.
And just when I was thinking that...
W-Will you be my girlfriend?
It was so sudden. I was surprised.
You were the first boy who asked me out.
It was then that I started noticing you more.
Feeling nervous around you.
But I wasn't brave enough to give you an answer.
I guess we're kind of similar.
I spent all my time fighting and never had a girlfriend.
So when I started high school,
I began to want a girlfriend and to go on dates.
I wanted to have a normal high school life.
Then...
I saw you at the entrance ceremony.
I was struck with Cupid's arrow that day.
After two weeks, I finally got brave
enough to ask you out.
You're right. We're very similar.
I guess we're two peas in a pod.
Well, we really had sex, didn't we?
The phone?
Looks like we're out of time. Oh well, let's leave.
Hey, Koizumi-kun.
I still want to be with you more.
Rina...
So, let's not leave.
That uniform...
I was wearing a swimsuit,
so I don't have another change of clothes.
Does it look weird?
N-No! You're hellaciously cute!
Really? I'm so glad.
You're licking me. You're licking me.
Not there!
Don't lick my clit!
It's too intense!
Oh, no!
Oops, don't close your legs.
But...
Your clit is all erect.
Not there!
You're mean, Koizumi-kun.
I-It's all about you.
It's already hard!
And also...
It's also very wet.
Wow. It's throbbing.
Th-That feels great!
Right here? Then I'll lick it.
What an amazing smell. It's throbbing.
I-I'm cumming!
Th-This position is really lewd.
He's staring at it again.
He's so close.
Wow. His dick is so big.
Koizumi-kun, I can't hold out anymore.
I want you.
Yeah. Me too.
L-Like this?
He's here, right before my eyes.
I'm coming in.
Your dick is inside me!
I feel strange.
It's my second time, but it feels more intense!
That's okay. I don't mind losing my mind.
Wow.
It's so deep inside of me.
It's hitting deep inside!
No! Not so rough!
It's hitting... deep...
No... I'm gonna cum. I'm gonna cum!
I'm...
I'm cumming!
I promise.
I'll never cheat on you.
You're all I want, Rina!
And then, forever...
he promised he'd love only me.
How embarrassing!
Don't get carried away.
By the way, Kumi!
Yeah, they said I'm not pregnant.
But I won't be able to have sex
or masturbate for a while.
Oh, no.
But that's good news.
If something happened to you, I couldn't...
Thanks.
By the way, did you talk to your dad?
Yeah. He asked me to bring him home for dinner.
I'm happy for you, Rina.
Thanks!
Hey, stupid, stop it!
You're actually happy about it!
I'm not happy! Let go of me! I've got Rina!
It's not what you think!
She jumped me!
How dare you cheat on me!
You liar!
But I still promise!
My cock is only for your pussy!