It's pink!
And cream!
Idiot! They'll hear you!
I can totally see everything.
I'm so glad I go to this school. Right?
Yeah.
What the hell are you guys doing?
You must've been peeping.
You perverts.
Ah! Ibuki Kumi!
And to top things off, next to her is...
my dream girl Nagase Rina.
Koizumi Junzo, when you asked Rina out,
you told her you "had eyes for no one else", right?
But that's hard to believe when
you stare up other girls' skirts.
Uh, well that was just...
This doesn't matter. Let's go, Kumi.
W-Wait, don't go, Nagase-san!
Right before my eyes... P-Panties!
My balls.
My balls...
W-Wait, Nagase-san.
You haven't given me an answer yet...
Don't you know when to give up?
Isn't it obvious?
I despise you!
This sucks!
Shishunki Shoujo Kari Kari
Translation: Voldemort Timing: PlasticYakuza Editing: Collectr Typeset & Encode: ShocWave QC: Chaosrains
Washroom
So Nagase Rina hates me, eh?
But even though it was an accident,
I still got to see... her panties!
I can't get it out of my brain!
Whoa, I'm cumming.
Of course I'm not coming, you shitheads!
I already broke up with him.
But that's not what Katsumi-kun says.
He told us to come get you.
Shit. Now they're yelling...
Give Katsumi a message from me:
"If you get lonely, stroke your own dick."
Hey, don't give me shit, you stupid bitch!
Maybe if we rough her up a bit,
she'll learn some manners.
Good idea.
Hey, you guys, if you do weird things
to me, even Katsumi won't approve.
He'll turn a blind eye.
Hey!
What the fuck are you guys trying to do,
luring a girl into our bathroom?
Can't a guy get off in the boy's bathroom
anymore without a stupid girl around?
Koizumi Junzo!
What? Did you say "Koizumi"?
It's him?
He's got a dumb brain, but he's a great fighter
There's a rumor going around that
he beat up an entire gang single-handedly.
I had no idea he went to our school!
Huh? You talking shit about me?
You wanna get your ass kicked too?
Stop this coffee klatch and just fuck off!
Shit. This isn't over.
Hmm?
So you're famous.
That's not true.
These stinking, crumpled up pieces of toilet paper...
You really were jerking off in there, weren't you?
I'm begging you!
Please don't tell Nagase-san about this!
Please!
If it's really been that long for you, then...
Does it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
You've really been holding back.
You're getting it all over the toilet and floor.
But I mean, are you okay with this?
I don't mind. You saved me, after all.
And besides, it's not like you're
Rina's boyfriend or anything.
Nothing wrong with it.
I guess so...
Say, how about I give you head?
H-Head?
Looks yummy.
I... I...
You're gonna cum, right?
That's fine. Shoot it all into my mouth.
It's coming!
See? A lot came out.
Well!
Let's go for the feature presentation!
What!?
By "feature presentation", you mean...
Why are you acting so surprised?
Thanks to you, I'm all hot now.
Help me out, will you?
A live pussy before my very eyes.
Hey. Hey, hurry up.
What the?
Hey, don't get distracted.
Hit me with that thick thing.
Yes. Thrust it in now.
It's in!
Koizumi!
Hey! That's too rough all of a sudden!
No, I like it.
I... I'm cumming!
Me too!
There's so much cum on my butt.
You've still got some left I see.
Let's try this way now.
I like this too!
Deep in... It's deep inside!
Koizumi, up here...
Up here...
Play with my boobs.
Oh, no!
Don't bite!
Be more gentle.
Yes. Yes, I like that.
Harder.
Push your dick in harder.
Oh, no, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
Your insides feel too good.
That’s okay. Release it. Release it inside me.
Flood my pussy with your cum!
Your cum. Your cum. Fill me with your cum!
Fill me with it!
I'm cumming!
I did it. And inside of her too.
I think that's the best sex I've had in a while.
Ibuki...
At first, I thought...
it was something you do with the person you like.
You can't escape.
That stupid asshole won't find you here.
Katsumi-kun said we could do
whatever we wanted to you.
Should we do it here?
If you really wanna fuck me so bad, I'll let you fuck me.
You understand your place well, I see.
But in exchange,
you'd better not be too rough and ruin my beauty.
I'll lower their guard, then I'll have my chance.
You guys have got pretty nice dicks.
I may not look it, but I'm really dirty.
I'll make sure we'll all have a great time.
Hang in there. I need to wait for my chance to escape.
I've had enough of your hand.
Get it in your mouth already!
Yuck, it's rubbing up against my cheek!
That jerk. He's moving his hips!
His dick is hitting the back of my throat.
I'd better make them cum quickly so I can get control.
Oh, crap. I'm cumming. I'm gonna cum!
Me too!
All right. Let's all go at once!
I'm cumming!
This sucks.
This much cum on my face at once?
This smell is nauseating. It stinks.
Come lick up my cum.
Come on. Open your mouth.
Who the fuck would voluntarily
suck your filthy dicks anyway?
I've been waiting for this chance.
Time to bite!
What the fuck?
Don't get jealous, dear.
This time, I'm breaking your shitty dicks.
You think I could live with myself
if you guys fucked me?
There's the exit!
I figured that would happen.
K-Katsumi.
You're breaking up with me?
Pissing me off comes with a big penalty, Kumi.
Stupid bitch.
I'll let my monkeys punish you all they want.
No!
I wonder what's wrong with Kumi?
She didn't tell me she was going to skip class today.
It's Kumi!
Hello, Kumi?
Kumi?
Wh-Who's there?
It's me, Katsumi.
Kumi's here with me.
Katsumi? Why do you have her phone?
I've got something fun to show you.
I'll mail it over in a bit.
Got it?
What's he talking about?
Eh? What?
No way!
But Koizumi, swimming's for girls.
Stupid ass! You can stare at girls in swimsuits for free!
Who cares if guys don't take swimming class?
It's their fucking loss!
Kumi!
Where's Kumi!?
Give her back to me!
Don't worry. Kumi's here, as promised.
Presenting her!
Take a good look.
That cock's tight inside.
I got lots inside. So much it's falling out.
Oh, no.
Kumi...
Next up...
it's your turn.
You're all dead.
How dare you do this to Kumi!
You guys are all fucking dead!
You're not bad, Rina.
Oops.
Oh, shit...
Your girly fighting doesn't work on me.
Now you get it, right?
I could control you by force.
But I'm not a devil.
I'll make a deal with you to get Kumi back.
A deal?
If you don't want to be raped, then suck our cocks.
If every one of us gets to cum,
we'll let you leave with your pretty body intact.
Your... You can't!
What a cute face.
Her cheeks are bright red.
Why is this happening?
Well then, Rina-chan, here's your cock.
Well then, Rina-chan, here’s your cock.
No way!
This is... So this is...
It's so scary... and big... and so close.
Come on, use your hands and tug on it.
W-With my hands?
Even though this is to help Kumi...
I'm touching a boy's dick.
I can't believe it.
Come on, squeeze harder.
Then stick it in here.
No! I can't!
Let go!
Come on, come on.
No!
Cumming!
What's... this?
C-Cum?
Next, suck me off.
Choose your favorite cock first.
B-But I can't do something so lewd!
Stop playing innocent! Come on and suck it!
No! I don't want to do this!
– Rina!
Didn't you want to save Kumi?
If we fuck her any more, I don't think
she'll have much of a future.
She'll get pregnant for sure.
Please stop it! Don't hurt Kumi anymore!
Then hurry up, will ya?
Use your whole tongue.
Kumi told me about this.
It's called "fellatio".
Not just the tip.
The underside and the top, too.
Some fluid's coming out...
and it's gotten harder.
This dick... is feeling me.
For a first-timer, you're pretty good.
Licking such a hard, hot dick...
It's starting to make me feel weird.
I'm almost there!
Oh, no! It's inside my mouth!
Drink it all up.
This hurts.
I drank it.
This time, try two at once.
Very good. Get them in deeper.
I'm gonna cum. Turn your face this way.
Good. Wanna drink more?
Answer me!
Yes.
Very good. Gulp it down.
And lick the remaining stuff clean.
This cum is so disgusting.
But if I satisfy them, then we'll be free.
That's a nice expression,
Rina-chan.
We're all very satisfied. Thank you.
Th-These guys... are happy.
In that case...
She's wearing a swimsuit under her uniform!
How'd she know we were into that!?
I had swim practice today, so...
– Oh man,
I can't stand it! So soft!
No! Don't touch me!
You ejaculated, right?
Keep your end of the bargain!
But when you're dressed like that, we can't hold back.
N-No!
Should we take off her swimsuit next?
No! Let go of me!
No!
D-Don't!
No! Not that! Absolutely not!
No! No!
No...
No!
Don't...
No.
Someone... help me!