Umm...
Today's health lesson is about the bodies of adults.
An Adult
• Male
• Female
All of you will also undergo through
these changes as you grow up.
A few examples are the development of breasts,
and growing pubic hair for early birds.
Hmm?
Each one naturally develops
at different rates so don't worry.
Let's meet at my place today!
Puberty SEX
Episode 2: Let's Meet at My Place Today!
Looks like everyone started to grow theirs.
Y-Yeah...
What's with that reply?
Kenta, you already got some?
N-Not yet...
Really?
You still didn't have them the last time
we took a bath together...
I'm not lying.
Hmm?
Hey, no one's home at my place today...
Show it to me there.
Huh? No way!
Eh... How mean!
Hey, won't it be okay?
I'll do everything you want!
Then if you'll show yours too, Hana-chan...
Then, we'll be showing each other!
Come here right after taking your bag home!
Hey... Hurry up and show me!
Hana's Room
You're still talking about that?
I'll let you borrow my comics, so show me!
Then you go first, Hana-chan.
Huh!? I'll show mine first?
The one who suggested it should do it first!
O-Okay...
Oh, you're wearing a bra!
Of course, I'm not a child anymore...
Take it off, hurry!
I-I know...
Whoa! Your boobs are puffing out!
Don't stare too much!
Can I touch them?
No, you can't!
Hey, why are you touching... No!
Th-They're soft!
Stop, that tickles...
H-Huh!? Why are you sucking it?
Don't babies suck like this?
You need to practice.
Don't suck it like that...
No!
I think I'm starting to feel weird...
My groin started to feel itchy...
Hey, please...
I'm home!
Oh? So Kenta-kun is here...
I'm coming in.
I bought some cream puffs.
Welcome back.
Good afternoon.
Pardon my intrusion...
Good afternoon. How are you, Kenta-kun?
I-I'm fine...
Make yourself at home.
Thank you...
penis
testicles
produces sperm
Our lesson today is about
the male reproductive system.
When stimulated and becoming
aroused, its changes shape.
This is called an "erection".
Hmm?
It happens when blood accumulates in the penis.
Let's go to the girls' restroom
on the third floor!! Immediately!
The increase of pressure inside enlarges it.
I don't want to! It's embarrassing!
Shush! What would we do
if somebody came in?
I've shown you mine before.
B-But...
Come on, our break time will be over.
A-Alright, I'll do it myself...
This should be fine, right?
Whoa! It's a little bit different
than the one we saw in our lesson!
Hey, show me how you pee.
Huh!?
I-It can't be helped...
I'm peeing in front of a girl...
Wh-Whoa...
She's watching me intently...
Whoa! The shape changed! Is that a boner?
You're aroused...
I-I'm not!
But sensei said that you'll get a boner
when you're aroused or it's stimulated!
Don't touch it right now!
Kenta, your thing feels so hard and hot!
H-Hana-chan... D-Don't!
Hey, how does it feel?
It feels good... I never felt like this before!
Some fluid oozed out!
Whoa... It's slippery!
Whoa! I feel something coming!
Huh? Whoa!
S-Sorry...
Is this sperm?
Maybe...
Are there any tadpoles?
Umm...
And what should I do about my clothes?
Let's study about the female
reproductive system for today.
Let's go to the restroom during the recess!!
There's a female organ called the uterus.
It is where an infant develops.
How is it? Is your pee about to come out?
Uhh... Yeah...
That's amazing...
You don't even have a dick,
but your pee is still coming out!
Th-This is embarrassing...
Show me the inside as well.
O-Okay...
C-Can you see it?
Yeah, it's squinching like some sort of creature!
Your breath tickles...
There really is a hole here!
Whoa... It feels warm and soft!
Something slippery is starting to drip out...
There's something that's like
a little dick attached here.
Ahh! That's...
Huh!?
That felt so good...
Let's study like this again, okay?
Well then. Let's begin with our health lesson.
Does everyone know how children are conceived?
It is by having the penis go
into the vagina like this.
This lets the sperm meet the ovum.
This kind of turned into something incredible...
When the sperm finds the ovum,
the sperm will fuse with it. And this...
B-But it looks like it'll feel good...
Hana's Room
K-Kenta, your thing got even
harder than the last time.
Hana-chan, yours is so slippery as well...
You shouldn't suddenly insert your finger.
H-Hana-chan!
Th-That tickles...
H-Hey...
Let's try putting it in already!
Okay!
Do it slowly, okay?
H-Huh? It won't go in...
Huh!? Hmm?
Ah... That's not the right place!
Ahh... It won't go in...
But it feels good when I rub it against your belly!
You're rubbing it against my groin...
It's making me feel weird!
If you stimulate me there too much...
It's coming out!
No!
That's amazing! One more!
Let's do it one more time!
Okay...
I wonder if it'll go in easily if I do this...
I think this will do.
It's going in!
Whoa! This is incredible!
Hey, don't suddenly go hard on me!
It feels so good that I can't stop myself!
W-Wait, stop moving!
I-I haven't braced myself for this yet!
Stopping now would be impossible!
Dumbass! No!
Your dick is going in and out of my belly!
You're amazing, Hana-chan!
I never felt anything like this before!
Something squishy is squeezing my dick!
I think it's gonna come out again!
No! Stop stimulating me any further!
The tingling at my groin is getting stronger!
It felt so good that I can't move...
Hana-chan, I want to do it again.
Huh?
You're being too rough... Go slower!
It's so slippery and warm!
I can't stop myself anymore!
Stop rubbing it deep inside me!
My mind is going blank...
No—!
I-I'm gonna die—!
No!
Ahh!
Ahh—!
Ahh...
Hana-chan... Are you alright?
I'm alright...
H-Health lessons are wonderful...
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji