www.SubDESU-H.net
Ladies Changing Room
What’s the matter, Baito-kun? Don't be so shy.
Why are you so stiff?
I-I am sorry.
Hurry up and sit down.
Okay.
I hope you like everything in today's lunch.
W-What's this?
So cruel...
Who would pull such a prank?
What the hell is this?
It stinks.
No! No!!
My face! My face! It’s burning!
Miwako-san...
Baito-kun...
Help me...
Miwako-san is....
Miwako-san is...
Dead.
W
Body Wash
「Sex Demon」
This is pretty tight.
Don't stain my work place.
The reacting pheromone and semen medicine emits an odor.
Always makes me feel sick.
Kaburagi-san.... I...
How is it, Saiki-san?
How does it feel to come back to life?
No time for sleeping.
That Yasaka Seiji is in quite a bad state.
No, I can't anymore...
Seiji-kun.
It's almost time for your medicine.
No, you can't do this.
Oh, Seiji-kun...
I didn't know you wanted this so bad.
Cute... You're so adorable.
More! More! Go deeper!
I guess no one is here.
All right. With this, I'm ready whenever.
You're a monster now.
Looks like it’s completed.
It’s Kaburagi.
Come in.
Did you call me?
I left it behind as requested.
I see.
Kaburagi-kun, let’s celebrate together.
A celebration?
Yes.
For completing that.
I’ll have you take care of me all night.
Miwako-san...
Why did you have to die?
Why? Why!?
I will wash you clean right now. Don't need don't worry.
I see. So Sanada Miwako went missing.
That's fine. She said she didn't feel well and was going to leave early.
Yeah. I gave her the permission.
Yeah. That’s how it, is so don’t worry.
This is so thrilling.
Kaburagi-kun, this is the best day of our lives.
He went beyond our expectations.
Yes... A lot harder!
Can't hold back any more?
I can't believe you're doing it by yourself.
How pitiful!
Try shoving it in her mouth!
I don't mind the nether mouth either.
What's the matter? Have you given up already?
Such a coward.
You're scared of tainting her, aren't you?
I like it pure.
Miwako-san...
I am... I...
Yuuki-senpai!
Seiji-kun left the washing room again.
I see.
What do you mean...?
I know.
He is in the cellar.
Mao-san...
Don't worry. I will be back shortly.
Let's get married.
All we have to do is to get married.
Then you don't have to decay.
You won't get dissected.
Wonderful...
Why didn't I notice until now?
Hey... It's okay, right?
I-I have a request...
Miwako-san...
I... I...
Let me put it inside you...
It's about to start.
We can see him change into a beast.
So he will be able to indulge as much as he pleases.
Yes! I can finally see my production.
I am putting it in, Miwako-san.
Please stop, Seiji-san...
O-Ouch!
What are you doing, Baito-kun?!
Miwako-san, don't move!
I will soon be deep inside you.
Ouch! What are you doing?!
Miwako-san...
No! I don't want this! Stop it!
Stop it!
Stop it! What are you doing to a specimen like me?
Why are you tainting me?
Don't stain me!
Seiji-san, you idiot!
Stop it!
Do you know what you're doing!?
Drugging Miwako-san and then trying to rape her...
You're the worst! I've misjudged you!
You're already here to take her...
Miwako-san isn't a specimen.
I won't let you dissect her!
Ouch!
What are you doing!?
Why don't you become the specimen instead of Miwako-san?
W-Why would you do something like this? I am not a specimen.
Specimens don't talk.
Specimen? I am alive!
I see. I haven't washed you yet.
I see. So that's how it is...
Wash? No!
Seiji-kun, I don't think one bitch will satisfy you.
Hurry up... Hurry up and put it in.
I will put it in, too.
It's in!
It feels good!
Seiji-kun too. Hurry up and put it in.
Here. You like this, don't you?
I don't want this!
You don't like it?
When you were alive, you seemed to enjoy licking my dick with your tongue.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
I don't want to have sex with someone who doesn't love me.
Don't fuck with me!
You came to interfere with my marriage with Miwako-san!
You should... You should take her place!
Hey, get your ass out.
How does it feel to have it inside?
I will wash out all the dirt inside you body.
Please! Stop! I beg you! My stomach hurts!
You have no choice.
You're going to be a specimen from now on. I have to wash all your dirt out.
Stop! Please, stop!
Oops! I need to plug it.
No, please stop!
I have to put my white soap in, too.
Something that big won't fit! I will break apart!
You don't need to worry. I will release a lot inside you.
It hurts! It hurts! Please, don't move!
Please!
It's rubbing me inside. Please stop!
It hurts!
No, stop! It will damage me! It will tear me inside!
It feels so good!
Seiji-kun!
I'm about to cum!
Yes! Yes!
I'm cumming!
It's in! It's in! So big!
It hurts!
Why am I cumming?
Even though I am being raped... Why am I cumming!?
It feels so good.
It feels like the world is breaking apart.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming! I can't hold on much longer!
It's agonizing. Hurry up and clean me thoroughly. Please!
People live to die, and die to live.
I think I understand that saying now.
They want to continue to shine.
That's why they want to be clean and shiny even after they die.
Kaburagi-kun, I'm cumming!
Go on. Spray it all inside my womb!
Clean me with your sperm!
Well then, I will take the offer.
I'm cumming! Cumming! Please, cum inside me. Hurry!
Why? Even though I hate you...
No! Why are you moving again!?
I just came! Wait a bit!
Please, stop it!
Miwako-san... Miwako-san, I love you!
No, I am not her!
Miwako-san, I only want you! I only want you!
No! I am about to cum again!
Seiji-kun, you idiot!
I love you so much, but why do you treat me like trash?
I... hate you!
I hate you!
I am going to die... Die. I am going to die...
I'm cumming. Cumming!
I am cumming!!
It's coming out! So much hot semen inside me...
I wonder if this hole is clean yet...
I am not done.
Medicine... I need it!
To be continued
www.SubDESU-H.net
Eien no yume ga naze sameta no darou?
Why did I wake from the eternal dream?
Rakuen wa kataku tobira mo tozashita
Paradise has now slammed its doors on me.
Itai hodo sosogu hikari no senrei
The diminishing rays of light are hurting me.
Tenjou no kao ga kanashimu kirei
The face in my ceiling is sad and beautiful.
Dareka oshiete yo
Someone, please tell me.
Watashi wa ikite iru no?
Am I still alive?
Kimi o sagashite kimi o sagashite
I search for you. I search for you.
Sakende to
And I scream.
Tadareru ashi ni tada mitsuku no wa
But all my wandering feet find...
Fuai shitai ni
... is a grim, dead body.
Filled with anger my heart weeps.
You that I want to kill...
and you that I love.
Lost reality and a world of delusion.
These empty people started craving for a medicine that would save them.
Body Wash, Case 3: Sex Drug.
I offer my body in the name of medical research.
「Sex Drug」