www.SubDESU-H.net
Who am I?
What is it that I want to do?
Is this the medicine that you wanted?
Yeah, that's it. That's the one. Now just...
Don't be so hasty. I will properly give it to you now.
I see. So you want to be washed, too.
First, I will clean you with my white soap.
Lower your panties and move your ass towards me.
Hurry up!
I will soon put this soap inside you.
Just wait a little bit.
Do you want it now?
If you want it, then beg for it!
Say it properly!
Give it to me, please. Give me your white soap!
Good. I'll go ahead and put it in.
It's hot! It's so big and hot!
S-Seiji-san?
I don't even know why I did that.
I cannot escape from that person.
I don't have the courage to correct my wrongdoings, and I am scared to truly love somebody.
Who am I?
What is it that I want to do?
I only have one wish.
W
Body Wash
「Sex Drug」
Are you finished yet, Baito-kun?
Baito-kun...
I don't think you should take different medications.
The specimens... I can hear them laughing.
Why are you laughing? Why!?
I am sorry for calling you out at this time.
The medicine!
Make me a promise. After you take the last one, please leave the hospital.
Why would you do such a thing!?
The antidote I got for you...
Your name is not Midou Yuuki.
Your real name is...
Stop!
Don't you have a relative that went insane?
You're a victim, aren't you?
He was giving you the same medicine like mine, wasn't he?
Stop! Stop!!
Please don't make me remember it!
You're also insane, aren't you?
You're wrong!
I cannot run from that person.
I can't help but be bothered by what she says and does.
What do I want to do exactly?
My wish is...
Yes. To become a specimen...
You're a victim so it shouldn't matter.
Stop! Please stop!
Stop!!
What's the matter?
Why don't you want to be washed?
You want to be cleaned, don't you?
That's only because I want to save this person!
Thats a lie. You're lying.
Wrong! You're wrong!
You're so mean, Yuuki-senpai!
You called him out to this place and seduced him, didn't you!?
Mao-chan, please trust me!
That wasn't my intention!
Who would believe you!?
You're in the way!
Always watching me!
You thief!
Why did you do something like this to my Baito-kun?
I won't forgive you! I won't forgive you! You really should become a specimen!
Become a specimen! Become a specimen! Become a specimen!
Become a specimen!!
You're wrong! Please believe me!
Come on, clean it up.
Clean it with your mouth.
I will wash it...
Why? Why can't I stop?
It's delicious.
I never knew your sperm was this delicious.
More, let me drink more!
I will do my best to give you a blowjob.
Just let more sperm out!
Please give me more, a lot more inside my mouth!
Let me drink it all.
This is the first time since I was born I have ever tasted something this good.
To fail it is easy.
The hard part is to get back up.
Miwako-san, were you waiting? I'm finished, so you can use it now.
Miwako-san?
The medicine you gave us the other day...
We ran out of it, so could you please give us more?
O-Okay.
Miwako-san!
Yes! This is the Nurse Station.
M-Mao-chan?
Miwako-san just fainted in the shower room!
Find Kaburagi-sensei and bring him here!
Yes, understood.
You heard what she said, Kaburagi-sensei.
I'm in a fix. I have to go search for Kaburagi-sensei.
I will go after another round.
Miwako san... Where is my Miwako-san?
In such a place...
You shouldn't be doing that here.
Miwako-san, where were you?
I have to hurry and put soap into you.
I understand.
Let's go to the hospital room.
It looks like your penis is also having a good time.
No. It's nothing like that since I am your dog.
It's too big for a dog.
If you use this on any woman, she will become your slave.
Just a moment ago, I left a woman named Sanada Miwako in my room.
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Do as you like. Just like Saiki Mao.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, do you mind if I ejaculate?
No!
I will have you fuck me while we watch a show in the hospital room.
Just hold on a bit longer.
It irritates me.
The fact that Baito-kun likes you.
Later, you should just get fucked by Kaburagi-san!
Looks like it's just about to start.
Why aren't we watching it from your private room?
It's a lot more thrilling to watch it from the next room.
Seiji-san, does it feel good?
Thats enough. Next, I am going to put it in from behind.
Stand up!
Yes.
Take off what you're wearing.
Stop right there!
Just like that. Come over here and face the other way.
Yes.
I understand.
Just like this?
Stick your ass out more!
Yes.
Now, I will check what your body fluids taste like.
T-That hole is...!
No, you...! That's wrong!
Would you like me to stop?
Do not stop! Continue!
It feels so good!
More! Do it much harder!
Yes!
Yes!!
I can't resist. I want to hurry and put your cock in.
Alright, put it in yourself.
That hurts! That's the wrong hole!
Its amazing!
Kaburagi-kun, use your big dick and pierce my asshole!
I have been waiting for this.
It got a lot bigger so...
I'm not sure if it will even fit.
I got it in all the way.
I am going to start moving.
Wait!
Put this in my pussy first.
Please!
Yes. I will insert one more.
It's good tight pussy.
Try squeezing tighter.
If you do that, I will cum in you.
Good, just a little longer!
It's amazing!
Kaburagi-kun, cum inside me, too!
Cum a lot!
Is this how you like it, Vice President?
I can ejaculate at anytime now.
Hurry! Hurry!!
Give it to me!
Understood.
I will remove my belt now.
Its coming out.
It's so hot. It feels like my stomach is burning.
You can't do that right now!
Vice President, you're urinating.
Kaburagi-kun, fill my pussy, too, with your cum.
I created a new medicine.
First, Kaburagi-kun, try and test it.
Yes, I understand.
N-No...
I didn't want to be fucked by Yasaka-kun.
The one who made Yasaka-kun like this was...
Who could it be?
You are lying to yourself.
The truth is you are the one who would've done this to any male.
Didn't you make him drink the same medicine as you?
You're wrong! I...
You're just a perverted girl.
N-No!
Even now, you're being fucked by an insane man and enjoying it, aren't you?
The real me.
Yes. The real you is...
Just like that woman. You just love hot semen.
Yes... I...
I'm just a woman who loves hot semen.
Seiji-san, give me more! Please wash me!
She is about to give birth.
Just for today, I will specifically take this. Kaburagi-kun, you take care of Chigusa.
Yes.
Let us begin.
Mao-san, turn the switch on.
Yes.
Congratulations, Miwako-san!
You are about to have a baby.
It's because you always let him cum inside.
Vice President, Chigusa's reaction is too extreme.
If it's too much, there will be a problem.
For revenge, let's make it smaller.
Chigusa's full of that man's semen.
I will remove next one.
Please!
Save me! Mao-san!
It's delicious, Miwako-san.
It tastes like Baito-kun's sperm.
Right? Isn't it the smell of Baito-kun's semen?
It's about time to take the baby out.
Wasn't Yasaka-kun's sperm tasty?
Looks like your stomach is about to burst.
Kaburagi-kun, open her stomach, too.
Such a healthy baby.
I have to wash her.
Wash me.
I will wash.
I am going to wash again tonight.
www.SubDESU-H.net
Eien no yume ga naze sameta no darou?
Why did I wake from the eternal dream?
Rakuen wa kataku tobira mo tozashita
Paradise has now slammed its doors on me.
Itai hodo sosogu hikari no senrei
The diminishing rays of light are hurting me.
Tenjou no kao ga kanashimu kirei
The face in my ceiling is sad and beautiful.
Dareka oshiete yo
Someone, please tell me.
Watashi wa ikite iru no?
Am I still alive?
Kimi o sagashite kimi o sagashite
I search for you. I search for you.
Sakende to
And I scream.
Tadareru ashi ni tada mitsuku no wa
But all my wandering feet find...
Fuai shitai ni
... is a grim, dead body.
The ten bodies of unknown identities that were found at the Sougou University Associate Hospital
were discovered to have their organs missing and bodies covered in a strange fluid,
according to the results of the preliminary autopsy.
Formerly a center for researching experimental drugs, the hospital is being suspected of human experimentations
as per an inside report.
In order for the main investigation team to start making headway in this case,
they are rigorously tracking any connections related to
the currently missing Vice-President of the hospital, Suusaki Chigusa.
Also, according to the primary investigation team,
the structure built beside the hospital
contain a considerable number of hidden rooms and seem to be connected like a labyrinth.
However, as to why these rooms were built...
Yasaka Seiji-san, it's time to take the medicine and cleanse the toxin from your body.
First drink this medicine.
Next, I'll be extracting the toxins, okay?
Wash...