www.SubDESU-H.net
Five minutes late, aren't we?
You can't do this work with that kind of attitude.
Especially if you can't arrive on time.
This is your contract. Check it and sign it please.
Though it doesn't matter anymore, but...
this job carries a confidentiality clause.
Are you scared?
If you want to quit then you still have time.
N-No... I think I should get used to this if I want to succeed as a doctor.
What you are about to do, see, are going to do and what you are asked to do,
is not to be told to anyone. Not your family, not your friends – no one.
Yasaka Seiji
Is that understood?
Do you understand, Yasaka Seiji-san?
Yes.
Now then, after you're done changing please come outside.
Kaburagi-san will take care of the rest.
Okay.
There is no going back anymore.
From today forth, I will be washing vessels in which human souls once existed.
W
Body Wash
「Sex Death」
You're late.
Did you get scared?
No. Sorry I am late.
You got told off by the nurse, Midou Yuki, didn't you?
She is too detailed and has an annoying mouth.
Hey! Change into your cleaning uniform.
Okay.
Hey, looks like you're in luck.
We have a young beautiful female today.
A rare sight of a beautiful naked body.
Doesn't it make you happy?
No way.
Eh? So you aren't happy?
Don't tell me you haven't seen a woman naked before.
Oh wow, do you even know any woman at all?
You're one weird guy.
Sorry.
Something came up to the pool surface accompanied with a weird aura.
A vessel in the shape of a human.
Eyes that will never open, and a face that will never be seen smiling again.
She requested that her body be donated to science after she had died.
So we are going to wash her body before we fulfill her final wishes.
Hey, get the legs!
Err...
Don't "Err" me, hurry up!
Okay!
Hey what's the matter? Don't get frightened just by this.
Seriously, I wonder why the vice president chose someone as weak willed as you?
It's beyond my understanding.
You are letting a guy like this do that  job?
Are you sure, Vice President?
I don't mind.
It was decided a long time ago.
I see.
Well then if you say so.
I don't mind either.
Then so it is.
You can leave now, Kaburagi-kun.
Understood. Well then.
Yasaka-kun.
Come here.
Okay.
Not there.
Come here.
Do you dislike this job?
No, it’s not like that.
I think this will be a fantastic experience for someone who wants to be a doctor.
Yes.
Hey now, don't make a face like you're being victimized.
You have to be more perky, you know?
O-Okay.
It’s not that we abandoned you.
This is a chance.
To save enough money for your university expenses.
I-I understand.
Are you sure?
V-Vice President?
Call me Chigusa.
There is no one else here apart from us.
Umm...
You showed courage and accepted it, so...
I shall reward you for it.
What are you...?
Look how hard you're already.
What are you so scared about?
W-What did you...?
A medicine that will make you less scared of women.
Let’s observe if it works or not.
Wow, it’s so big.
Well isn't that a waste.
It’s so big and yet you never had it inside a woman.
P-Please stop.
Don't talk like a girl.
Your dick is splendid and manly.
If you move it so fast..
Are you about to cum? It's okay, go ahead.
So? How does it feel to be masturbated by a woman?
Don’t you want to have sex now?
Please stop... if you go on any further.
Nope, I can’t let you off the hook now.
This is kinda getting me horny too.
I can’t believe I am about to see you cum.
Erm, why are you doing this?
Because you're a virgin.
They say you don't forget your first woman.
That's why I am going to carve myself into your memory.
Go on, imagine it.
Me opening my legs up to you naked.
Can you see it?
My pussy.
Isn't my pussy beautiful?
Don’t you want to put your big penis inside?
Say it.
Say that you want to put your dick inside my pussy.
Say that you want to shove it in!
You want to put it in, don't you?
You want to ejaculate inside, don't you?
Then it’s okay. Cum!
Cum as much as you want in me.
It came out.
Such thick cum.
Go on. Cum some more!
Don't stop. You can still cum, right?
So much is coming out!
You had a lot stored in, didn't you?
It won’t stop.
Yes... Go on, cum more! More!
Doesn't it feel good?
Look!
Stop... please stop.
I can’t take anymore...!
If you do any more than that...
I... I...
You can cum. You can cum a lot more!
Don't be shy and let it all out.
Go on!
So, how does it feel to see a woman naked for the first time?
What? You don’t like girls or something?
But this is work, so watch carefully.
U-um...
What?
Is it okay to do it so roughly?
Huh?
Um... don't you think it hurts?
You serious?
Are you okay?
This one is dead now.
Dead.
Already dead.
Not a human anymore.
Can't treat this thing as a human anymore.
She is dead.
Wash her.
You will be doing this alone from tomorrow on.
Get used to it.
Erm, where should I start from?
Well let’s see.
First of all wash from her shoulder to her arms.
Then wash her chest to abdomen.
Okay.
Put more force into it.
Otherwise you won't be able to properly clean it.
Okay!
This is...
The first time I’m touching a...
All right, the upper body is clean enough.
Do her genitals next.
Why are you getting surprise now?
You're obviously going to have to wash that part as well.
Open her legs and wash it properly.
Because it is an easy place to get dirty.
I am sorry.
I am really sorry.
I...
For the first time...
You can't wash it if you don't look at it properly.
Hey! Don't look away!
Eh... Okay.
I am sorry.
For putting you in such an embarrassing position.
I am going to wash it.
Even though I didn’t want to see it.
I saw it.
I finished my work.
I would like you to check the documents.
It seems like...
You threw up during work.
I-I am sorry.
Why don't you just give up?
Pardon my frankness, but...
I don't think you are suited to be a doctor.
What's the matter?
You don't seem well Baito-kun.
TL Note:  ”Baito =part-time job”, so Baito-kun is a nickname she's given him.
Miwako-san.
I heard that you switched departments.
You seriously don't look well.
Your face looks pale.
Are you eating enough nutritious food?
Yeah.
Well with that look it doesn't look like you're eating well.
All right! Just for today, as a special treat I will share my lunch with you!
This is a SubDESU-H release, visit our website @ www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Come here.
I hope there is something you like in there.
Open it.
You don't like them?
Does it look bad?
No, it’s not like that.
Really? Then you can have it all.
What about you?
I have this so I am fine.
Don't worry about me.
I am on a diet at the moment.
So I can't really eat much.
I see.
Then I will take you up on the offer.
Go on, eat it!
How is it?
It's delicious.
Really?! I am glad.
Hey, shall I bring some tomorrow too?
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's fine!
Because I am on a diet now.
Ah, I guess that's not related though.
I am begging you.
Please stop this.
Why?
Because...
Could it be that you have someone you like?
So you do have one.
Who is she?
Tell me her name.
No it’s not like that.
I don't have anyone...
Don't try to fool me.
I can easily tell when you're lying.
And I was just about to give you your first experience...
But we will put it on hold for today.
Your sperm that lust's over another woman.
I will suck them all out.
I don't know which woman you're lusting over but,
I am not handing over your virginity to anyone.
It’s no use. I... I can't...
Miwako-san.
W..wait!
Miwako-san wait!
People live to die.
They die to live.
I will wash another soulless vessel today.
I am sorry for being such a mess.
Miwako-san.
I am tainted.
I am no longer who you think I am.
Here it comes.
Your dirty juices.
So much love juice.
I can't stand by and let any other woman take it away.
Stop... not there.
It’s okay, let it out.
You can spread more on my face.
Exam Room 1
Saeki-san.
What were you doing?
It’s time for work.
Yuuki-senpai was searching for you.
Sorry, I will go to her right away.
Hey.
You smell.
You smell like after-sex.
Oh no. Why did I say something that would make him hate me?
Hello, this is the nurse station.
Ah, Kaburagi-san.
Eh?
Yes, I understand. We will search for him right away.
What’s the matter, Yuuki-senpai?
Yasaka-san ran away.
What’s the matter? Everyone is worried sick about you.
Weird... I am weird.
Weird?
I am sure something is wrong with my body.
What do you mean.
Hey, what do you mean by weird?
I am no longer normal. I can't stop!
Seriously... What can't you stop?
Delicious.
I am sure Baito-kun will be joyous after eating this.
Its fine. I will always help you out like this.
Cum all you want.
Miwako-san.
I am... breaking apart.
Please forgive me.
Farewell... please... live well.
She is dead?
Why is Miwako-san dead? Why?
So delicious.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Stop, stop!
I told you to fucking stop!
Didn't I tell you?
I won’t let any other woman have you.
You're my toy.
Use that short life of yours for my sake only.
Understood?
Life... death?
Specimen.
Dead.
Already dead.
I am already dead.
Excellent. Let me drink more!
Everyone is dead.
I have to wash them. I have to wash the specimens.
What the fuck do you think you are doing, you mere specimen!
It hurts. What are you doing, Seiji-kun?
Shut the fuck up. Specimens don’t talk!
W-Wait. Why so suddenly?
What kind of joke is this?
Wait!
No!
Please stop.
A specimen disobeying me?
Even though I was going to wash you.
I will make you clean so make me release my white cleanser!
Isn’t that what you want?
Answer me!
Yes... I want it.
I want it, please.
Seiji-kun please hit me more.
I love being hit by someone... Give me more.
Then give me a tit job.
Like this?
Use your tongue too!
How is it, master?
More! I need more.
I can go more!
W-What are you...?
I have to wash and make this place clean too.
Geez... you're so rough.
This is a success. I can't believe the medicine would work this much.
Wait for it.
I will spray white cleanser all over it.
So good.
Ouch! It hurts!
How are you feeling pain when you're just a specimen?
It hurts, it hurts, stop! Please stop!
I beg you.
No!
Stop it!
Please stop it.
It hurts.
I don't want this. How many times are you gonna cum?!
I am not done yet.
I can't satisfy myself with just this.
This feels good.
Yes, I wanna see that face.
That's it.
The face that fears death.
I wanted to see that face.
Fear of death.
You understand?
To be continued
www.SubDESU-H.net
Eien no yume ga naze sameta no darou?
Why did I wake from the eternal dream?
Rakuen wa kataku tobira mo tozashita
Paradise has now slammed its doors on me.
Itai hodo sosogu hikari no senrei
The diminishing rays of light are hurting me.
Tenjou no kao ga kanashimu kirei
The face in my ceiling is sad and beautiful.
Dareka oshiete yo
Someone, please tell me.
Watashi wa ikite iru no?
Am I still alive?
Kimi o sagashite kimi o sagashite
I search for you. I search for you.
Sakende to
And I scream.
Tadareru ashi ni tada mitsuku no wa
But all my wandering feet find...
Fuai shitai ni
... is a grim, dead body.
Beneath the water...
My imprisoned body... awaits for the light of hope.
Who will be the one to wash me?
Lured by awakening,
seeking insane nectar.
The time...stops.
Body Washing, Case 2: Sex Demon.
Please wash me.
「Sex Demon」