AKEMI PRIVATE COLLEGE
So your father's a murderer?
You think it's all right for a murderer's
daughter to just casually come to school?
Dad!
Dad, why are you...?
Nanase, this is some kind of
mistake. l'll be back home soon.
The charge was murder.
The murder victim was my father's
classmate back when he was a student.
Apparently, people witnessed
the two arguing right before the
murder, so my father was arrested.
CLASSROOM OF ATONEMENT
EPISODE 1
My father didn't murder anyone!
Yes he did! l know it!
How would you know something like that?
l said l know it!!
Unfortunately, your father's
fate belongs to the law now.
So now, the only thing we can do is
judge you, a girl who has the blood of
a murderer running through her veins.
You have a responsibility to
atone for the sins with your body!
A responsibility?
This is for your own atonement!
No!
What are you doing?
Stop!
No!
Help me!
No!!
This is awesome.
This is the woman's clit
l've been waiting to see!
You're...
You dumped me three months
ago. l'm Kuroda from Class B.
Damn bitch.
You didn't even think about how
l felt when you dumped me.
Damn it! Damn it! l wanted to
have sex with you as lovers!
Stop...
Look. She's acting like she doesn't
want it, but look at how wet she is.
Yeah. She's the daughter of
a murderer, so she's a slut!
l bet she's a huge pervert!
l can't wait to find out!
She's so tight. This bitch is awesome!
l can't. l'm about to cum.
Don't hold back, just cum in her. Who
cares, she's the daughter of a murderer.
B-but...
Well, if you say so.
No!
OK. Me next!
lt feels good, right? Make some noise.
Suck it.
Who's he? Why is he just watching?
Atonement... What is there to atone?
Why do l have to get raped because
my father's a murder suspect?
Plus, there's no way a kind person like my
father could commit murder. lt's all a lie!
Nanase, you're still here. Are you
done? Let's go home together.
Sure.
Huh? Are you feeling all right?
Oh, it's nothing. l'm OK.
l see.
Oh and by the way, my brother
is really happy that he gets to
see you on the morning train.
He hasn't said anything, but
l bet my brother likes you.
Nanase? Are you listening?
Satsuki... l was just...
Huh?
l can't tell her that l was raped.
Even if l made a big fuss out of it, since
l'm the daughter of a murderer suspect,
no one would pay any attention.
What's wrong?
l'm sorry. l lost my train of thought.
Oh, Nanase! You're too young to go senile!
l'll go get my bag.
Nanase.
Madoka.
This is going around.
Do you know about it?
Huh?
Atonement!!
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
This Atonement Newspaper is being
published to bring important news
about our school to the student body.
Today's important news is about Nanase
Hiramatsu, second year, classroom A.
Me!?
Yesterday afternoon, Nanase
Hiramatsu was summoned by a
number of male students in her class.
She was subjected to sexual assault and
bullying in a certain classroom on campus.
She probably could have predicted
how it would affect her after she
was sexually assaulted, but...
...instead, she raised her rear for more.
Could this be because of the
perverse disposition Nanase
Hiramatsu was born with?
This can't be!!
To add to the story, her father, who was
arrested for murder the other day...
...had raped one of his students
when he was an educator, thus
leading to his swift resignation.
The sexual assault on Nanase Hiramatsu.
Did it happen in order to make
up for her father's crimes?
This can't be! My father didn't
rape his students! lt's a lie!
Don't let an article like this get to you.
Who could have written such terrible lies!
l wonder what kind of sick
kick they get out of this?
Nanase, cheer up.
Your father will be proven innocent,
and he'll be released in no time.
Yeah. Thanks Madoka.
Now is the time when she's
really going to need my help...
We're friends.
l can't let that newspaper get to me.
Yes?
lt's like a dream come true, that l get
to do something like this to Nanase.
S-stop.
You have no right to refuse.
Just shut up and take
whatever we do to you.
Whoa! lt keeps going in further and further.
Wow, it looks like it's alive.
She's twitching. She's such a slut.
Her juice is pouring out, too.
lt's getting so wet. This is awesome.
She's feeling it, but she's trying to hide it.
lt's okay, you can moan as loud
as you want. You're a perverted
slut who likes to get fucked.
No! That's not true!
Then why are you so wet? Huh?
You're getting fucked.
Might as well enjoy it.
Let's try another one.
Should we use some lube?
Who cares. Just shove it in.
Well, if you say so.
lt hurts!
Kuroda, you're a sick fuck too.
Maybe you caught her pervert virus!
lt's because l haven't forgotten
how she dumped me.
Give me some service over here, too.
Don't forget about us.
There's no point resisting anymore.
l'm starting to go numb, and l can't tell
if it hurts or if it's pleasurable anymore.
Am l a slut like they say? Am l a pervert?
l'm gonna cum!
Me too.
The best is yet to come.
She's getting used to it. She's
starting to moan out loud.
But this is starting to get lame.
Were you expecting someone?
lt's a brainiac woman
who looks like a student.
lt's probably her tutor. Tuesday
is when you have your private
tutoring, right Nanase?
How'd you know that?
Were you stalking Nanase?
A private tutor...
Huh?
We're Nanase's classmates. We
were doing homework together.
We'll be leaving soon. Please come
in, she's waiting for you in her room.
Ok. Then l'll go see her there.
Hello...
Nice to meet you, Miss Tutor.
We're all really good friends.
When school is out, we go over to
someone's house to have a party.
We'll invite you today as our special guest.
No.
An older woman even smells different.
Come on, Miss Tutor. Let's have some fun.
S-stop.
Stop! l'll have sex with all of you,
just please let the Professor go!
How many times have l told you?
You have absolutely no say whatsoever.
You're the daughter of a murderer.
No!!
You feel great, Professor. l'd love to get
private lessons from a tutor like you.
She had nothing to do with it.
She hadn't done anything wrong.
lt's all my fault that
Professor Yuka was raped...
l'm such a sinful woman.
ls that why?
ls that why l have to atone for my
sins? For being such a wicked woman?
ls that why? Someone, please tell me...
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
ln light of recent events, we reported
Nanase Hiramatsu being sexually
assaulted in our last article.
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
We will now report the
details of the incident.
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
The incident happened yesterday.
Nanase Hiramatsu was again sexually
assaulted by five men in her home.
On campus it's understandable,
but this time, she had invited
the men into her home.
With this factor involved, how can
we say she was unwillingly raped?
Can we conclude Nanase Hiramatsu is
a slut that cannot live without a man?
Unfortunately, there was a distressing
occurrence during yesterday's incident.
Nanase Hiramatsu's private tutor, Yuka
Gotoh, was caught up in the assault...
...and was raped by several
of the students at our school.
Does this unfortunate incident stem from
Nanase Hiramatsu's sinful bloodline?
ln our last article, we reported about
the rape incident Nanase's father
had committed in the past.
ln our investigation, we have
discovered further shocking evidence.
Nanase Hiramatu's father was
the ringleader of a group of
thugs when he was a student.
He and his friends reportedly had
raped fellow classmates and female
professors on a regular basis.
The school, with their anti-scandal
policy, had stifled the truth...
...and the incident was never
reported to the authorities.
Ordinarily the culprits of a heinous
crime of this magnitude would
have been sentenced to prison...
No! Stop! Please!
You like this? You like this?
Cry! Scream!
Even if someone comes to help you, the
fact that you got raped won't change!
You won't forget about this
for the rest of your life.
My father was a rapist?
l don't want to believe an article like that!
But, what they wrote
about me is accurate...
To say that my father really
did rape a lot of women...
Did my father really murder his classmate?
Please, tell me the truth. Dad...
Dad...
l wonder where Nanase is?
Normally she's always on this train, but...
There she is!
But, something's strange.
Maybe she's not feeling well.
lt's so crowded, l can't move.
l wonder if she's ok?
Good girl, Nanase. You actually came
without underwear on like we told you to.
She's a true whore.
She can't wait to get fucked.
This is such a turn on!
She's getting wet with all these
people around her. What a woman!
You can raise your voice.
Say ''lt feels good.'' ''l'm really feeling it.''
lf it feels good... lf it's pleasurable,
it'll lose it's meaning as atonement.
l can't. That wouldn't be right.
But what is it? What is atonement?
l can't take it anymore. l'm so hard.
Don't just stand there and
enjoy it. lt's your turn.
Can you hear me, Nanase?
There's a while until our stop.
Make everyone cum by then.
lf you don't, we'll just have to pull
in an innocent bystander again.
Are you going to commit another crime?
No!
Don't dirty the train. You better
take whatever comes out.
l want to cum a different
way than everyone else.
l was hurt when she dumped me.
You can at least do that for me, right?
We're so lucky to have a
slut like her in our school.
Tell me about it. lf we did this to
a normal girl, we'd get arrested.
Man, l'm hard again. Shit, we're
almost there. l'll just have
to wait until after classes.
This is like two lovers making
out on the way to school.
l've been dreaming of doing
something like this with you!
Nanase, change out of your dirty
uniform in the bathroom at the station.
l've readied another outfit
for you, so don't worry.
They're doing something terrible to
me. But why does it feel so good?
l want to moan out loud. l
want to scream out loud!
l'm gonna cum!
ls this my atonement, too?
Nanase!
What!? What are you staring
at? You're all terrible!
Nanase. What happened?
Talk to me. l'll help you.
lt's nothing. l'm fine.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
lt's a lie. She's lying! Something
terrible is happening to Nanase.
l have to protect her.
l'm her friend!
Nanase has a secret.
The secret she's hiding from me has to
be the reason for her sudden change.
What's the most popular
girl on campus doing here?
ls there something
interesting going on inside?
lt's nothing.
Nothing, you say? That's
a bit of a problem.
Because you're going to
be the star attraction.
Huh?
Madoka!
You're such a sinful woman. You
dragged in someone who has
nothing to do with this again.
No! Don't do this!
You have no right to talk back!
This is for your own atonement!