ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
Today, l would like to bring
you more important news.
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
Nanase Hiramatsu has once again brought
an ill fate to another innocent woman.
The victim this time was Madoka Yuki,
who is known throughout campus
for her beauty and intelligence.
Madoka Yuki...
...had noticed her friend, Nanase
Hiramatsu, was acting strangely.
The victim tried to determine what the
problem was by following Nanase.
But unfortunately...
...the victim had walked in
on the scene of the bullying.
CLASSROOM OF ATONEMENT
EPISODE 2
Madoka!
You're such a sinful woman.
You've brought misfortune to
another innocent bystander!
N-no! Stop!
Don't talk back to me! This
is all for your atonement!
No!
As expected of an honor student.
Even your pussy feels different.
lt's my fault that Madoka got raped.
What am l... What am l supposed to do?
Stop, please!
l'll shoot a load in you like l did in Nanase.
Now...
Let's have you two star in an orgy.
Nice view.
l'm going to cum.
Me too.
Not me! l'm not done here yet.
l'm sorry, Madoka.
lt's my fault.
lt's OK. l'm with you. l can deal with this.
Thank you.
Well, would you look at this
beautiful female friendship!?
Yeah, how tender.
Madoka, it's a lot easier if you
just let your mind and body go.
You don't want to suffer, right?
Just relax, like me.
l'm with Nanase.
l'm enjoying this.
This is to atone for my sins, so l
shouldn't be feeling good, but...
...but to ease innocent Madoka's
pain, l can't let her see me suffering.
M...more. Fuck me harder.
lt feels so good. Fuck me harder!
l want more... l want more...
What kind of honor student is she? She's
probably more of a pervert than Nanase!
She's smart and likes to get
fucked! That's great! lt's awesome!
Yeah, but once a guy cums he's satisfied.
We can't really do much, even
if they're asking for more.
Let's have them make out and give us
a lesbian show. That'll be interesting!
Did you hear that, you two?
lsn't it a great idea?
The guys are going to take a break.
Entertain us.
You guys have a strong friendship, right?
Just think of this as a way to
acknowledge how strong it is.
l'm okay with it...
Madoka.
Madoka, does it feel good?
Yes...
lt feels really good.
l'm so happy, Madoka.
Your pussy tastes so good.
lt's embarrassing.
Oh yes...
lt feels so good.
lt's so good.
Your pussy is beautiful.
And it tastes so good.
l'm so happy. Nanase
is going down on me.
This is pretty nice, watching
two girls make out.
Watching them makes me excited.
Nanase, do you love me?
l love you so much!
l've been in love with you for so long.
lt feels good, Madoka.
Nanase, l want you to touch mine too.
OK.
Yes. Nanase, pet me more.
Nanase, l love you.
l've always wanted to do this with you.
Me too.
...love...
...you...
...too.
l'm a wicked woman.
l got Madoka involved in
something so terrible.
My precious Madoka has been scarred.
She's been defiled...
The least l can do is minimize the
damage done to her mental state.
l have to make her feel as happy as l can.
Dad...
CHEMISTRY PREP ROOM
Professor, you got it? One
hour, one hundred bucks.
Yeah. l'll pay you later.
Oh, and just a reminder about
our chemistry grades...
All right. Will you shut up already?
Atonement...
This what l must do...
My all...
Nanase.
Masami.
l've been waiting for you.
l haven't seen you lately.
Nanase.
Make love to me.
Huh?
Don't ask me any questions, just hold me.
Masami...
l never knew sex with someone
you love was so comforting.
Whatever happens, you'll always have me.
There's nothing to worry about.
l'm so happy.
lt feels so good.
Yes. lt feels really good.
lt feels like there's a fire inside me.
You're beautiful, Nanase, l love you.
Me too.
l can't anymore... l'm going to cum.
Cum on me.
You were fast asleep. Did
you have a good dream?
Oh no... l...
lt's all right. Stay in bed
until we have to check out.
l'm sorry, l didn't mean to fall asleep here.
You must have been really tired.
l'm wet...but l just had multiple orgasms.
Masami was being considerate to
me. He was taking care of me.
l've never met anyone like him.
Masami...
Masami, it's OK. You can
fuck me all you want.
l came here with those intentions.
No, that's enough for today.
Why?
l feel like l'm taking advantage of you.
l love you, but l don't think
that's right for me to do.
Yeah. l shouldn't!
l'll wait until the day you open
your body and your heart to me.
ls that ok?
Yes.
Masami... He's such a wonderful guy.
l'm too tainted to become lovers with him.
l can't... He's out of my reach.
l'll only bring him misfortune.
And the next news.
Koji Hiramatsu, who was arrested
for the murder of Takahiro Nishino...
...has committed suicide by
hanging himself in the prison
bathroom this afternoon.
ln an investigation of Koji
Hiramatsu's suicide...
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
Today, l would like to report
further important news.
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
Nanase Hiramatsu, who has already
been sexually assaulted continuously
over the last few days...
Nanase Hiramatsu, who has already
been sexually assaulted continuously
over the last few days...
...spent several hours in a hotel yesterday
afternoon with another male student
who seems to be her boyfriend.
lsn't this incriminating evidence to prove
Nanase Hiramatsu's sexual thirst?
And at the same time, her father,
suspected of murder, hung
himself in the prison bathroom.
Granted she did not know, but at a
time like this, she was spending her
time in a hotel with another man.
Perhaps the hussy Nanase Hiramatsu
was born under a dark, cursed star?
Thus, we can conclude there
is even more need for Nanase
Hiramatsu to atone for her sins.
What are we going to do from now on?
Who cares if her dad's dead?
lf he committed suicide, that
means he was the murderer.
lt just proves that Nanase Hiramatsu
is the daughter of a murderer.
Then, does that mean we can do
what we want to her even more?
That's awesome! Then l guess we're
going ahead with today's plan?
ls that all right with you, Ohbari?
Hey, Ohbari!
Huh?
Are we going ahead with the plan?
Damn right we are.
Did you see this?
What?
What? What?
''Events concerning Nanase
Hiramatsu: AII participants must
assembIe at the gym this afternoon.''
No! lt's not me! lt's not me!
Please! Stop!!
Satsuki!
Nanase, haven't you pulled
enough innocent people into this?
l'm sorry, Satsuki... And your brother
has been so kind to me, too...
How am l going to be able to
make this up to both of you?
l am such a wicked woman...
Satsuki.
Don't come near me!
lt's all your fault...
Huh? ''Atonement memo''?
''Drags Madoka Yuki in at the infirmary.''
''Sold for a hundred dollars an
hour in the Chemistry Prep Room.''
What is this!?
l'm so happy you came
to visit me at my house.
Where's Satsuki?
She's been in her room since she
came home, and won't come out.
l think something might
have happened at school.
Nanase, do you know anything?
No...
Oh...
Oh, this...
lt's my homework. lt's a research paper.
l'll go make some tea. Wait here.
ATONEMENT NEWSPAPER
Atonement Newspaper...
You and your sister were writing it.
Yup.
You've hit the nail right on the head.
Why did you write a paper like that? Why
did you put in the fact that l've been raped?
You want to know why?
Of course l do!
Our father's name...
...is Takahiro Nishino.
My father and your father, Koji
Hiramatsu, were classmates.
At that time, the Atonement Newspaper
was circulating the school secretly.
My father wrote and circulated it.
My father couldn't bring himself
to do the abominable things
that your father was doing.
So instead, he disclosed the truth, and
enjoyed watching your father panic.
My father was laid off from his company
a year ago, and he needed money.
With this economy, he
couldn't find another job.
lt got to the point that we were
struggling just to pay our living
expenses and the mortgage.
WEEKLY RESOURCE
SPECIAL REPORT: THE REVOLUTIONARIES
OF THE EDUCATION WORLD
WEEKLY RESOURCE
SPECIAL REPORT: THE REVOLUTIONARIES
OF THE EDUCATION WORLD
And he just happened to find out
about Koji, after about ten years.
WEEKLY RESOURCE
SPECIAL REPORT: THE REVOLUTIONARIES
OF THE EDUCATION WORLD
He had succeeded in running
his own Cram School, and was
getting noticed by the media.
WEEKLY RESOURCE/SPECIAL REPORT: THE
REVOLUTIONARIES OF THE EDUCATION WORLD
HOW IS HE GOING TO CHANGE
JAPAN'S FUTURE!? - AKAWA
MEDIA TAKES NOTICE: KOJI HIRAMATSU
THE THREAT OF THE EDUCATIONAL
SYSTEM'S COLLAPSE. SOMETHING
MUST CHANGE! - YAMAMOTO
He had succeeded in running
his own Cram School, and was
WEEKLY RESOURCE/SPECIAL REPORT: THE
REVOLUTIONARIES OF THE EDUCATION WORLD
HOW IS HE GOING TO CHANGE
JAPAN'S FUTURE!? - AKAWA
MEDIA TAKES NOTICE: KOJI HIRAMATSU
THE THREAT OF THE EDUCATIONAL
SYSTEM'S COLLAPSE. SOMETHING
MUST CHANGE! - YAMAMOTO
MEDIA TAKES NOTICE: KOJI HIRAMATSU
My father used the evidence from
Koji's past to get some money.
But as they were talking, Koji
found out that my dad wrote
the Atonement Newspaper.
ln a rage, Koji murdered my father.
Leaving us behind...
We found out everything when
we were cleaning up my father's
keepsakes, and found his note.
We couldn't forgive Koji. He had to be
brought to justice, but that wasn't enough.
We decided to punish
him by tormenting you...
...by publishing the same
Atonement Newspaper.
Thank you for telling me everything.
l hope l never see you again.
Good bye.
Hold on.
There's one more important
thing l need to tell you.
What?
The student your father raped when he
was a teacher, her last name was Ohbari.
Ohbari?
That's right.
lt's the same last name as
the ringleader of the group of
guys that's been raping you.
l accidentally found this out
myself, when l was investigating.
He's your brother.
That's a lie.
You didn't have sex with
me...because we're siblings.
Why did you do something like that?
How could you do something
so terrible to your own sister?
You have no idea what kind of pitiful
life my mother and l had to live,
compared to you and your father.
That guy murdered
someone and got arrested.
He dug his own hole.
lt's too bad that he
committed suicide, though.
And who was going to
take revenge on you?
My mother got sick and died!
lf l don't do it, then who will?
Then do it yourself! lt's revenge, right?
Don't have other people do it! You
should have raped me yourself!!
Shut up! l said don't talk back to me!
You have no right to talk back!
Fuck me then! Rape me!
You know that's what
you really want to do!
No matter how much you hate
our father, no matter how many
times you call me a whore...
The same blood runs through your veins!
You must feel pleasure from
doing things that are sinful too!
Shut up!
l should have done this in the first place...
Next will be those four...
After them ...