Say, Inagaki...
I'm happy that a cute student of mine is cooking for me,
but you shouldn't be coming into a man's room so lightly.
It'd be bad if rumors started.
I don't care about the rumors.
I love you, Sensei!
Come again?
My name is Yoichi Shiraishi.
I've become a teacher as I wanted to but,
Because of my busy workdays, I've never had the chance to get a girlfriend.
I hit over 30 before I even realized it.
Even so, a guy like me was able to get a girlfriend!
This is Sae Inagaki, an honors student
who can play sports as well as study.
She's shy and has an extreme aversion to strangers.
She was always by herself in class, so I reached out to her.
And she ended up taking a fancy to me.
Inagki Sae Edition
C-Cut it out, I'm trying to take a piss! Hey now!
Hanako! Knock it off!
This is Hanako-san, who is always
hanging out in the school toilet.
She's a self-proclaimed "Toilet God," and loves urine.
She is currently in the habit of coming
and going to my house as she pleases.
Toilet Girl Hanako
My urine power levels are tip-top!
Hanako! I said it was okay for you to come over and all that,
but I never said it was okay for you to come
in as you please and drink my urine.
But, but! No one comes and uses the school toilet on Sundays.
And my urine power levels get too low.
Listen up. You're prohibited from directly drinking my urine.
Ah, you're so stingy, Sensei!
Hanako-chan...
Ah! Sa-Sawa-chan!
Inagaki?!
You promised me. I told you not to come
to Sensei's house this Sunday.
Sae Inagki
I let you drink my urine in return.
Oh... that was today? I forgot.
I'm so sorry.
Bye-bye, Sensei!
I-Inagaki, it's not what you think...
Inagaki...?
You're too kind for your own good.
I know it can't be helped that you and I are
the only ones who can see Hana-chan.
But... Hana-chan isn't your lover.
... I am!
S-Sorry...
Sensei!
Sensei! I'll make you breakfast.
Yeah, thanks.
Here you are, Sensei! Breakfast is ready!
I-Inagaki, that outfit is...
I-It was on one of the dirty DVDs I confiscated from you, so...
You're into this sort of thing, right, Sensei?
Well, yeah, but...
In celebration of your birthday...
... I-I'll do whatever you like today, Sensei.
Inagaki!
Ah, Sensei! Not yet!
You'll do anything I want today, right?
B-But...
You sure are bold today, unlike usual.
W-Well, you have been busy lately, Sensei.
You haven't been having sex at all.
And I did throw out all of your dirty DVDs and all that.
I'd feel bad if you got all pent up.
I am all pent up, and I sure want to
release all of it into you, Inagaki.
Can I?
You work in education. I can't believe you'd
ask such a thing of one of your students.
You sure are a pervert, Sensei.
Okay. I'll make an exception just for today.
Thanks, Inagaki!
Do you have anywhere you'd like me to kiss?
Kiss me wherever you like, Sensei.
Well, alrighty then!
Ah! No! Sensei!
Not a hickey!
You'll leave a mark if you suck so hard!
I marked you to prove that you're mine, Inagaki.
What! Don't do that!
It looks like you're more sensitive than usual.
You're all pent up too, Sae.
I-I am not!
I'm not a pervert like you, Sensei!
Besides, you shouldn't ask a girl if she's pent up or not!
What do girls do when they get pent up?
I told you not to ask me that!
Don't do that there!
I won't quit until you tell me.
I-I can't say it! Stop!
I imagine that my hand is your hand,
and touch myself down there while fondling my breasts.
I imagine your big, robust member,
while smelling the clothes I borrowed from you.
But.. I'm too scared to stick anything in
there aside from your penis, Sensei.
But cumming through masturbation alone doesn't
satisfy me since I've had sex before.
One hour later
I can't believe you masturbate while sniffing
clothes that I asked you to mend.
You're more perverted than I thought, Inagaki.
But ever since I had sex with you, Sensei.
I just can't get your penis out of my head!
Stop! Hurry up and have sex with me!
Was the impression from your first time that strong?
Speaking of which, you came on to me first, Inagaki.
I can't move...
I asked Hana-chan to bind you, Sensei.
Inagaki!
Your entire member... is inside me, Sensei!
You're the one to blame, Sensei!
We're lovers.
Don't you want to have sex with me, Sensei?
Well, that... But, as a teacher, I...
I want to have sex with you, Sensei!
I'm your lover after all! It'll be alright!
I'll do all the work.
I want to make you feel good, Sensei!
Wait, stop! It's still tight!
Another 45 minutes later
You were a virgin, yet you came so many times!
I did not!
You're even more perverted than I am, Inagaki.
That's not true!
You're clearly the more perverted one, Sensei!
I don't think girls who aren't perverts
would make such a declaration.
I didn't declare anything!
You kept saying such lewd things, Sensei.
You're such a mean jerk!
Oh, so you got all hot and bothered from being picked on.
Ah, Sensei! Why?
I'd stick it in you if only you were a perverted girl, Inagaki.
What'll it be?
You're a jerk, Sensei! Pervert! Sexual deviant!
Please teach my body about sex.
Please set my perverted pussy free with your penis, Sensei.
That a girl!
I can't believe you came just from me sticking it in.
You sure are perverted, Inagaki.
Well, your penis feels way too good, Sensei.
Class is just getting started.
Your penis has gotten bigger yet again, Sensei.
I'm making your member feel good, Sensei.
That makes me happy. Please feel even better through me.
Sensei!
Sex with Sensei sure feels good!
I want to feel Sensei's penis even more!
Se-Sensei! Sensei!
Sensei... I love you!
Your member is way too enthusiastic, Sensei!
You're doing me from behind like when dogs breed!
Wow, you're even into dog breeding.
You sure are perverted, Inagaki.
That's not what I meant!
Don't stick it in so deep!
I love you, Inagaki!
I love you too, Sensei!
So please make love to me some more!
Sensei!
I love you... Sensei!
Alright, drink up.
I can't believe we're having sex in the classroom!
I'm done for! I'm cumming! I can't take any more!
When I think of being fucked in a place of study...
It makes me horny! I'm cumming!
Sensei...
Today is one of my safe days, so please cum inside of me.
Please make me feel good by cumming into my womb, Sensei.
Here it comes!
Sensei's penis is starting to swell up.
Sensei's cum... hurry up! Give it to me!
My pussy! I'm cumming!
Having your cum inside of me sure is the best!
Nothing beats riding you bareback, Inagaki.
Sensei's sperm sure feels good.
I just can't get enough of being painted with his color.
I wouldn't mind having your baby, Sensei.
So I want even more of your sperm inside of me.
As our secret teacher-student relationship continued...
Inagaki ended up getting pregnant.
Fortunately, she didn't start showing until graduation.
Inagaki's father kicked my ass, but
gave us his approval to marry.
Sensei... I'm sure you know already, but...
I'll cut off your dick if you cheat on me.
Sae, I'm going to cum...
I can't believe you'd make your wife do something like this.
You're such a pervert, Sensei.
What a waste!
This won't do.
Make sure your sperm gets inside of me, please.
There, nice and dean!
Well now, did you go and get excited
from my cleaning blowjob?
You're such a pervert like usual.
Go ahead!
I'll satiate all of your lust, Sensei!
That's my job as your wife!
I get the feeling that I'm the one taking care of your lust, Sae.
Did you say something?
Nope! Nothing at all!
It's so tight!
This feels way too good!
I'm going to cum.
If I'm filled up with your thick semen, Sensei,
then I'm going to get pregnant all over again!
Even the baby in my belly is going to get knocked up!
That's taking it a bit far...
Hurry up and cum!
Release your sperm inside of me, Sensei!
I'm so happy that I became Sensei's wife!
I'm cumming!