imai
Sensei?
We came here to have baby making sex.
What? Why are you guys here?
Utilizing the powers of the Asamiya family
makes obtaining a key a simple feat.
You're just breaking and entering!
That's just like you, Isuzu-senpai.
Come on!
We've all decided.
We're all going to bear your child, sensei.
Their Sadism
Episode 2
Well then, let us begin.
Today should be the easiest day for me to get pregnant.
My body's large, so I should be able to bear you a healthy child.
Are you serious?
I think I want a boy like you, sensei.
It'd be nice to have a mini version of you, sensei.
I'll give him all my love.
Of course, I'd give my love to you too, sensei. Don't worry.
I've only put it in, but everything it touches just feels so good.
My body understands.
It knows that I'm going to be bearing your child, sensei.
Her pussy is sucking me in.
Her womb is wrapping around me as if it's
trying to guide my semen inside of it!
My student's pussy is moving as if it wants to make a child!
Oh no! My hips are moving on their own.
There's no turning back now.
I wouldn't want to.
I want your baby, sensei!
Alright then.
Then I'll give you what you want. I'll
cum in the deepest part of you!
Yes, please! Make me... Make me...
Make me pregnant!
Sensei's semen is flowing into the deepest part of me!
It's coming out! Sensei!
It's coming out!
Sensei!
Happiness is overflowing in my stomach.
I love you.
Sensei!
Sensei! Next up is me, Suzuka!
Makinohara!
Energetic babies come from energetic sex!
I'm going to let you impregnate me when I'm at my ripest!
So you need to make sure that you give me your best stock too!
And what's more is I'll give you what
you love... freshly worn tights!
So? So?! How is it? Do you like my scent?
You're such a pervert!
Shit. I hate to admit it, but I love this!
Look! Your dick's even harder than before!
When I get pregnant, milk is gonna come out of my boobs, right?
You're perverted, so does that mean
you're gonna try and drink it?
Your dick just twitched right now!
You're aroused, then, huh?
You don't need to worry. I'll let you drink
it even if you're perverted, Papa.
If you want my boobs like that so badly, you're gonna
have to cum inside me and get me pregnant!
Focus! I'm about to cum too!
It's coming! I can feel it! Your milk is coming!
Sensei's milk!
Ejaculate! Sensei, ejaculate! Give me your baby!
Sensei's milk! Sensei's milk!!
I love it!
I love this!
Now I'm pregnant too...
Please look after us, Papa.
Seriously, how rude.
Why is it that when it's our turn, you can't get it up?
You're so hopeless.
But I guess you have been pouring your cum
into us nonstop these past few days.
Can't you just let me rest for even one second?!
That's not happening.
It'll be alright. We'll get you up and running in no time.
We know your body pretty well now.
You always talk tough.
But when we play with your weak spots
you just break down completely.
If we play with you with our feet like this...
See? It's back to normal now.
I think it'll be good for about three more times.
So? Did my foot feel good?
Of course not. It was my foot that made him feel good.
My mind's going blank.
You see, it looks like you're misunderstanding
things. I'm the one who made him feel good.
If you keep playing with me like that, of
course, I'm going to get hard again!
You're the one misunderstanding things, Ako.
Stop showing me your defenseless chests!
You're thinking he reacted to your foot when it
was actually my foot that he was reacting to.
W-What are you doing all of a sudden?
That's not fair of you.
I'm not the one who told him to...
Sensei?
Sensei!
Me too.
Se-Sensei!
Please...
In me...
Please put your dick in me first!
I want it so so badly! My mind is going crazy!
Sensei's dick is filling up my womb!
Oh no!
Every time he moves I feel like I'm gonna cum!
No! I can't stop!
Sensei!
I'm sorry! I'm...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
I love you!
Sensei!
It's my turn now.
There's something I've been practicing for you, sensei.
I'm excited.
Well then, here I go.
How is it? Does my womb feel good?
Come on! Come on!
What is this?!
It's like my entire dick is being played around with.
It feels good, doesn't it?
After all, you're a pervert who gets off
by cumming inside his students.
Come on, you can cum whenever you'd like.
– Asamiya!
– Come on! Come on!
– Come on!
– I'm gonna...
I'm...
Sensei...
Sensei!
I love you!
Will I... Will I be able to make these girls happy?
I'm no one special.
No...
I need to make them happy.
They're my precious students.
They're my precious ladies.
That's why...
Papa?
Were you sleeping?
It must be because of the good weather today.
Well then, shall we go?
My mom and dad have been bugging me forever
because they want to see their grand-kids.
A lot of things happened.
And it was seriously all over the place.
But they're all fond memories.
Now and forever.
Sensei, were you a good boy?
You don't need to think about anything. Just cum.
How unreasonable.
They're all precious...
Wait! Sensei, don't! Don't!
I'm sorry! I can't!
I can't!
The time I spent with these precious girls.
And the time I will spend with them.
Papa?
Are you ready yet?
I'm coming now!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч