Just a bit more!
Hey, Chi!
Wait for me!
I'm here, mister!
Gimme some sweets!
Hey, you're too loud, Chi.
Reika, don't be too hard on Chi.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you love to spoil this girl.
Good morning.
You three are together again today.
That's right, mister!
I wonder if I should buy this.
How about this?
I already ate this yesterday.
And I don't actually love this one either.
Hey mister, what should I do?
Not bad to take that once in a while, I think.
Mister.
This.
Alrighty, thanks.
Hey, Mister!
What's wrong, Tenka-chan?
About the video uploaded a while back,
I can't get it to have more views.
What do you think I should do?
Was the video that bad?
Do something about it.
What?
Even if you ask that.
I'm pleading already, so please think about it!
Koma-chan!
I can't choose which sweets I want!
Welcome back, Chi-chan.
Back.
Mister's so terrible.
He's just talking to Tenka-chan.
Want some?
Can I?
Yay!
Is it tasty?
Yup.
But then no one will be able to watch it!
Please think about this more seriously.
Tenka-chan and Mister sure get along well together.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'll be taking out some ice tea, all of you come over here.
Don't change the subject!
'Kay!
Let's go, Koma-chan.
Wait for me, Chi-chan.
Let me see that card.
Can you give me this?
What? But I only have one of those.
Then I'll trade it with this.
Oh? But how should I decide?
Okay then.
Alright!
Chi, I'm surprised that you have a lot of rare cards.
I'm quite good at picking things.
What? That's kinda unfair.
Huh? Where did Koma-chan go?
Huh? Didn't she take a pee?
She's taking too long.
Pooping then?
Hey! Girls don't say those kinds of things!
Mister, can I borrow your toilet?
Sure, go ahead.
I'm kissing Chi-chan indirectly.
Chi-chan.
Chi-chan...
Chi-chan,
Chi-chan is going inside me.
Push it further.
Chi-chan, Chi-chan!
I'm about to pee!
Chi-chan.
Be sure to think of a solution tomorrow, okay?
View numbers, huh.
I'm leaving it to you.
Bye-bye.
Goodbye.
Chi, what's wrong?
Your mother's going to be late again?
I'm okay, I'll just stay here a bit longer.
I see.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow, then.
See ya tomorrow, Chi.
Mister, I'm hungry
Wanna eat some yogurt?
'Kay!
Hurry up, mister!
Just wait a sec.
Alright, it's done.
Okay.
Tasty.
Hey!
Your yogurt's not tasty at all!
Sorry.
Wanna eat more sweets?
I want to...
But why don't we "study" a bit, then?
I'll give you sweets if you do well.
Really?
I'll do my best!
You can't tell anyone what we're about to do, okay?
Okay.
Mister?
That tickles.
Mister, this feels kinda weird.
It gets tingly,
as you lick my breasts like that.
Are we done?
Not yet.
We're just getting started.
Hey, wait!
Mister, why are you taking off my panties?
No!
That's where I pee.
It's dirty.
Mister, I feel weird.
Oh no, I'm about to pee!
It's coming out!
Mister,
do I really have to take all my clothes off?
Just a bit more.
'Kay!
It'll soon be over.
Your peepee won't fit in.
Those inside parts are made to insert a peepee in, you know.
But, it's even bigger than my insides.
It's alright.
It'll get wider once I put it in.
Are you all right?
Mister.
It hurts.
No, don't move.
My insides are being stretched.
I can't keep up. I can't do it anymore.
It feels like my insides are firmly being tugged out.
It's getting hotter deep inside.
Your yogurt is seeping into me, Mister.
This is the "study"?
That's right.
Is it really?
Mister, aren't you just lying?
Why aren't you using your dick this time?
You love sweets, right?
That's true, but.
Here, I'll give you a popsicle too.
Wait!
My butt feels cold.
So cold.
Don't move them together.
Mister, aren't we done yet?
This feels good.
I'm going to!
Mister,
are we done?
Not yet.
Face over here.
It's too fast.
Please do it more gently.
Your peepee just twitched.
Are you going to squirt out your yogurt again?
Hug.
Hug me. Please, Mister.
I'm about to!
Squirt it. Squirt your white stuff already.
No, please don't!
Stop.
If you do that right now,
I'm going to!
It really is.
Your yogurt.
It's starting to become tastier.
You know,
I wish you were my father,
because you stay with me everyday.
What do you think, Mister?
Mister!
What should I do,
to become an idol?