Even though he’s my brother, I haven’t seen him in almost 10 years.
I’m not sure how I should handle it.
He looks at me with perverted eyes,
and despite living alone, he always comes over for dinner.
But you've looked somewhat happier ever since Onii-chan became your tutor, Usane-oneechan.
Well, he is a very good tutor, and he’s kind as well.
I guess he’s not all that bad.
I’m jealous, Onee-chan.
Penkichi
I guess I can’t tell her about what happened...
Presented by
Shikkaku Fansubs
Shoukoujo
Jeez Onii-chan, your kisses are too lewd!
I guess normal siblings wouldn’t kiss like that.
So, this is a lovers' kiss.
Aya
ne
and
O
nii-
ch
a
n
Onii-chan, I-I, um... This is my first time,
so please be gentle.
Oh, you’re a little wet. Were you feeling good?
That’s because it’s you... It’s because I’m doing it with you, I’m...!
Your fingers are inside me!
If you play with me like that, I’ll want more!
You’re squeezing me down here, Ayane.
You idiot! I don't care!
It's so embarrassing... You're making me shudder!
This is bad!
Onii-chan...!
You’re a lot more aggressive than usual today.
You’re the one who’s different today.
Showing these lewd things to me...
That’s because I wanted you to look at me, Onii-chan!
It was quite a show!
No, don’t make me remember it!
It was so embarrassing; I wanted to die!
Onii-chan...!
That’s right, I finally made him realize.
I made him realize that I was serious about him.
Even when Onii-chan came to tutor me...
So, I need to substitute this x here...
Oh, I see...
Hey, Ayane.
I can see your panties.
What is it, Onii-chan?
Do my panties bother you that much?
Idiot, it’s not like that.
Jeez, if you want to look, just tell me!
C’mon, how’s this?
It’s a girl's panties!
You know...
You should be ashamed of yourself...
Even if you say that,
you actually want to look, don’t you?
See, how’s this?
Are you turned on yet?
S-Stop that...
C’mon, look at me! You can see my cameltoe!
You can masturbate to this if you'd like.
You wanted to look at me here, right?
I’ll show you everything.
After that, I did many more things to make him come onto me.
Onii-chan is masturbating to me... How perverted!
Even though we’re siblings, I’m also a man.
If you show me these types of things, then...
You’re getting all slimy. It’s making a lewd sound, Onii-chan.
Don’t say it like that...
If you look at me like that, I...
I might not be able to hold back!
Hey Onii-chan, look at me more with that perverted gaze!
I’ll masturbate as well!
Your cock is so big!
C’mon, you can put it in if you want.
S-Since I’m this wet!
I think that’s a bit...
You’re lying! I know you want to have sex with me!
Idiot. We’re siblings, you know.
But it's ok to masturbate to one another like this?
We’re not, but I can’t help it...!
Ayane, I’m gonna...!
C-Cum...!
Let it out! Pour your hot semen onto my butt!
I’m gonna cum too...!
Onii-chan...!
It’s hot and sticky...
Since you came on me like this,
we indirectly had sex, right?
Since we haven't been doing anything but this stuff all day, we’re gonna...
Onii-chan, it's fine if you can't hold back.
It’s alright. Since you’ve been so nice to me, you can do anything you want tonight!
Onii-chan, I want your cock!
I-I don’t care if you’re my little sister anymore!
Ayane?
Go ahead, Onii-chan.
You can take my virginity!
We’re going to be connected, aren’t we?
Sorry. I’m putting it all the way in, okay?
It’s coming in! Your cock is stretching my pussy!
O-Onii-chan...!
I’m connected with Onii-chan...
Yes, we’re connected.
I was able to finally connect with Onii-chan...
I’m so happy!
Ayane, does it hurt?
I’m fine.
It hurts a bit, but it makes me shudder!
Ayane... Ayane!
You’re so cute that I can’t stop!
Onii-chan...
My pussy...
My pussy's being shaped by your thing!
It'll only belong to you!
It’s fine, since we'll always be together.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, I love you! I really do!
Because it’s you, it feels so good!
It really does!
I’m gonna cum!
Ayane… Ayane...!
I’m cumming too!
L-Let cum together!
I want to cum with you, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan! T-That’s...! Not there!
I-I’m gonna cum!
O-Onii-chan’s semen is pouring out...
I came inside you...
It’s fine, since I wanted you to cum inside, at least for our first time.
Onii-chan...
Out of the blue like this...
Penkichi:
Hey, Onee-chan, are lewd things bad?
I don’t think they're bad.
Really?
Yeah, if you do it with a person you really like,
it makes you feel really happy.
It’s true, whoever it may be.
Onii-chan!
#########Shoukoujo!########
Usane-oneechan has looked like she’s been having fun ever since Onii-chan returned.
By the way, how is it going with Onii-chan?
Eh?
Onii-chan sometimes comes to babysit...
And when Mom isn’t home...
he'll help me around the house.
Amazing! It’s like you’re newly-weds!
I-Is it really?
What should I do?
No, I can’t... I can’t tell her about that!
It’s too embarrassing!
O-Only a little, okay?
This is called your “pussy.”
Pussy?
Don’t do that, Onii-chan!
You can’t sniff my dirty spot!
Onii-chan!!
Onii-chan was Yuzu’s first friend.
He should only have been that until a few weeks ago...
But, I did something extremely perverted with him…
Yuzu
and
O
nii-
ch
a
n
That day, the bath was broken at the apartment,
so we went to a public bath, but...
Onii-chan wanted...
Are we really going to bathe together?
Then, can you go in to the woman’s bath by yourself?
So I ended up going into the men’s bath with Onii-chan, but...
O-Onii-chan, there are other men...
O-Onii-chan, please wait-
No one is paying any attention even though a cute girl like you is naked in here.
I-I don’t want them to look!
Yu-Yuzu-chan...
You sure are going at it!
Should I wash you instead?
It’s fine! Leave me alone!
Even though Onii-chan has seen my lewd bits, it’s still embarrassing for him to see me naked!
Yuzu!
O-Onii-chan!
Here! You kept washing the front and not your back.
J-Jeez! Yuzu said that she can do it on her own!
See?
Jeez, Onii-chan doesn’t understand Yuzu’s feelings at all!
Jeez, you’re too cute, Yuzu.
Hey, no need to hold back!
H-Hey Onii-chan, stop playing pranks on me!
Y-You’re touching my breasts!
Yes, they’re your breasts. We need to wash them as well!
That’s...! Stop that!
Is something wrong?
Who is it? Someone you know?
He’s a boy in the same class as me.
What should I do? This is so embarrassing!
Then...
H-Hey, Onii-chan-!
D-Don’t do that!
Shouldn’t we show him that you're feeling good?
It’s too embarrassing!
Look, we’re bubbling down here nicely!
No, oh no!
Yuzu is feeling strange just by him washing me!
Even though it’s in the bath... Even though there is a boy from class here...
So just like that, Yuzu was turned into a perverted girl by what Onii-chan did to me...
Doesn’t it feel good?
No, stop it Onii-chan!
He’ll find out!
If we’re subtle, they won’t notice.
But there’s a boy from my class here!
Don’t worry; people ignore one another in here, so they won’t find out even if I do this!
O-Onii-chan, we’re not at home or anything!
Does it feel good?
I-It feels good!
M-My pussy is starting to feel good!
I can put it in, right?
I don't know what’ll happen anymore!
Amazing!
See? No one has noticed.
But, we shouldn’t be doing these things here...
It’s fine!
O-Onii-chan!
That’s right, Yuzu-chan!
You feel good from it!
N-No! Mr. Cock is...!
C’mon, if we don’t stick closer together, people might notice!
O-Onii-chan! You really are a meany!
Onii-chan, let’s stop this...
Don’t move, it’ll be fine.
No-!
Onii-chan!
Hey, if you’re too loud, the boy from your class might hear.
He may have noticed already.
And he may be getting an erection while he's looking at you!
If that’s true, why don’t we show him some more?
No, no!!
No, t-they’re going to see!
They’re going to see us!
They’ll see my breasts and my pussy too! All of my lewd bits!
No!
O-Onii-chan, stop it, stop it!
Then...
Let’s count to ten and get out.
One... two... three...
F-Four...
Five...
S-Seven...
Nearly there!
E-Eight!
Penchiki:
Onee-chan...
are lewd things... bad?
Penchiki:
Onee-chan...
are lewd things... bad?
Ten!!
Is that about you?
No, my friend was saying that during lunch break...
I don’t think it’s bad.
Really?
Okay!
Shoukoujo!