Sensei?
We came hereto have sex and make babies.
What? How did you guys get in here?
Using the Asamiya family connections,
it was a simple feat to obtain a key.
You're trespassing!
You are the first, Isuzu-senpai.
Come on!
We've all decided.
We're all going to have your baby, sensei.
Tea Ceremony : Sadism of Girls volume 2
Well then, let us begin.
Today should be the perfect
timing for me to get pregnant.
My body's ample so I should be
able to bear you a healthy child.
Are you serious?
I think I want a boy like you, sensei.
It'd be nice to have a mini version of you, sensei.
I'll give him all my love.
Of course, I'll keep loving you too, sensei.
I just put it in but everything
it touches feels so good.
My body understands.
It knows that I'm going to
be bearing your child, sensei.
Her pussy is sucking me in.
Her womb is wrapping around me as
if it's trying to suck all my semen into it!
My student's pussy is excited
as if it wants to make a child!
Oh no! My hips are moving on their own.
There's no stopping now.
I'm gonna say it over and over again...
I want your baby, sensei!
Alright then...
Then I'll give you what you want.
I'll shoot my cum into the deepest part of you!
Yes, please! Make me... Make me...
Pregnant!
Sensei's semen is gushing
into the deepest part of me!
It's overflowing! Sensei!
Sensei!
Happiness is filling up my stomach.
I love you.
Sensei!
Sensei! Next up is me, Suzuka!
Miss Makinohara!!
Healthy babies come from energetic sex!
I'm going to let you
impregnate me when I'm at my ripest!
So you need to make sure that
you give me your best stock too!
And what's more, I'll give you
what you crave... freshly worn tights!
So? How is it? Do you like my scent?
You're such a pervert!
Shit. I hate to admit it, but I do love this!
Look! Your dick is even harder than before!
When I get pregnant, milk is gonna
come out of my boobs, right?
Since you're so perverted,
you'll probably wanna suck them'?
Your dick twitched just now!
You're aroused again. Huh?
You don't need to worry. I'll let you suck
them even if you are a perverted Papa.
If you want to suck my boobs so badly, you're
gonna have to cum inside me and get me pregnant!
Focus! I'm about to cum too!
It's coming! I can feel it! Your milk is coming!
Sensei's milk!
Ejaculate sensei, ejaculate! Give me your baby!
Sensei's milk! Sensei's milk!
I love this!
Now I'm pregnant too...
Please look after us, Papa.
Seriously, how rude.
Why is it that when it's our turn, you can't get it up?
I kind of understand.
He's been banging away
nonstop these past few days.
Can't you just let me rest for even one second?!
No way!
It'll be alright. We'll get you
up and running in no time.
We know your body pretty well by now.
You always talk tough.
But you always eventually break
down when we use our feet like this.
When we stroke you with our feet like this...
See? It's back to normal now.
I think it'll be good for about three more times.
So? Did my foot make you feel good?
Of course not. It was my foot
that made him feel good.
– My mind's going blank...
– You see, it looks like you're misunderstanding
things. I'm the one who made him feel good.
– If you keep playing with me like that, of
course, I'm going to get hard again...
– You see, it looks like you're misunderstanding
things. I'm the one who made him feel good.
– If you keep playing with me like that, of
course, I'm going to get hard again...
– You're the one misunderstanding things, Miyako.
– How could you show off your pretty boobs?
– You're thinking he reacted to your foot when
it was actually my foot he was reacting to.
W-What are you doing all of a sudden?
That's not fair of you.
I'm not the one who told him to...
Sensei?
Sensei!
Me too.
Se-Sensei!
Please...
In me...
Please put your dick in me first!
I want it so badly! I'm going out of my mind!
Sensefs dick is filling up my womb!
Oh no!
Every time he moves I feel like I'm gonna cum!
No! I can't stop!
Sensei!
I'm sorry! I'm...
I'm gonna-
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I love you!
Sensei!
It's my turn now.
There's something I've
been practicing for you, sensei.
I'm excited.
Well then, here I go.
How is it? Does my womb feel good?
Come on! Come on!
What is this?!
It's like my entire dick is being manipulated.
It feels good, doesn't it'?
After all, you're the pervert who gets
off by cumming inside his students.
Come on, you can
cum whenever you'd like.
– Come on! Come on!
– Asamiya!
– Come on!
– I'm gonna...
I'm...
Sensei...
I love you!
Will I... will I be able to make these girls happy?
I'm no one special.
No...
I need to make them happy.
They're my precious students.
They're my precious ladies.
That's why...
Papa?
Were you sleeping?
It must be because of the nice weather today.
Well then, shall we go?
My mom and dad have been bugging me
forever because they want to see their grand-kids.
A lot of things happened.
And it was seriously all over the place.
But they're all fond memories.
Now and forever.
Sensei, were you a good boy?
You don't need to think about anything. Just cum.
How unreasonable.
They're all precious...
Wait! Sensei, don't! Don't!
I'm sorry! I can't!
I can't!
I am going to live with these precious girls...
Papa!
Are you ready yet?
I'm coming now!