Are you really going to take pictures
with me wearing this, Mister?
Yup.
Don't be shy, just take some poses.
I just wanted some tips in acting as a Hydra.
Why do I have to wear this naughty swimsuit?
This is so embarrassing.
It's a gravure photoshoot, so it's definitely
going to be embarrassing.
Gravure...? Then it's still naughty!
It's not!
It's a man's admiration.
Admiration?
So you really didn't want to be an idol after all, Tenka-chan?
Of course I did!
I'll become one for sure!
Then just stick out your butt and look at the camera.
Like this?
Part your legs more.
More? But if I do that!
Just maintain that pose!
Even if you say that.
Stop! Please don't take pictures of my butthole!
It's okay. It's not exposed, anyway.
No way.
Your legs sure are erotic, Tenka-chan.
My legs?
Legs are supposed to be naughty?
Of course!
See? It's already making me lively down here.
Stop that. Don't pull out that weird thing!
It became like this as I was ogling you.
That means you have the talent to be an idol!
You were... aroused by me?
Yup.
Idols are supposed to make men excited.
Then that means, I can become an idol?
Yeah, you have what it takes.
Really?
Yeah, for sure.
Okay then.
I'll work hard.
Mister, what should I do next?
Why don't you try holding my peepee, then?
What?
Okay then.
Your peepee feels hard and hot.
It's all because I kept seeing your butthole.
See, you really were looking at it.
You're the worst!
Liar, liar, liar, liar!
You, you, you, you!
Making me wear this flimsy swimsuit.
You really are a pervert!
Tenka-chan, if you keep doing that...
What is this? It's all sticky!
It kinda stinks.
Will I really be an idol if I do this?
You need a bit more, I guess.
Are you willing to work even harder?
You bet!
I'll definitely be an idol!
Hey, mister, don't just ogle my butt.
Hey! I said you can't open it like that!
Did you get excited after seeing my peepee?
That's not it.
Mister, I don't like this. What are you going?
You inserted your finger?
What's this?
Stop that, mister!
It hurts!
I said stop.
Tenka-chan.
Wait, you mustn't put that in!
It's going inside.
My insides feel weird.
No.
Stop this already!
It's really inside my butt.
Please, it feels so weird. Pull it out!
It's going deep inside of me.
No, stop. No more, I beg of you, please!
My insides feel like they're twitching.
It's squirting something inside me, mister!
My insides feel hot.
Oopsie.
It hurts. It hurts!
I said it hurts.
Mister, I'm scared.
Please move more slowly.
You keep touching just the tip!
What's this? Something's coming out.
I'm scared. Please stop, mister.
Please, please stop!
I'll become an idol by doing this, right?
Mister,
what is this?
It's an onahole, a tool that's used to study sex.
You want to have sex with Chi-chan, right?
You wouldn't be playing with yourself
in the bathroom if you didn't, right?
Chi-chan, Chi-chan.
Chi-chan!
I like you!
Want me to help, Komoko-chan?
Would you really?
Yup.
Which is why we need to study.
And by study, I mean using an onahole.
Start by licking it. Imaging it's Chi-chan's.
Chi-chan.
Chi... chan.
Alright, now turn the onahole in the opposite direction.
Why
are you pulling out your peepee?
You're going to put that peepee into this onahole.
You need to learn what makes Chi-chan feel good through sex.
Is this enough?
Put it all the way inside, and move it gently.
Gently.
Does it hurt, mister?
Your peepee is all stiff, and it's twitching.
So it feels good, huh?
Something came out!
Imagine it's Chi-chan.
Tastes weird.
My mind's getting all fuzzy.
Komoko-chan!
Mister, what are you doing?
No, it feels gross!
Stop licking me!
My first kiss is with Chi-chan!
Stop, let me go!
Mister!
Jeez!
Don't lick me in weird places.
Not my breasts!
My nipples feel all tingly.
Mister, please stop!
I told you to stop.
You want to make Chi-chan feel good, right?
Chi-chan.
I want to make her feel good.
Alright then.
Let's study more.
Stop!
This isn't what you think.
I was thinking about Chi-chan and then.
Not there!
Stop!
Stop licking it!
It tingles!
No, I don't want to.
Don't put it in.
I don't want a peepee.
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Stop!
I told you to stop.
Idiot... Mister's such an idiot!
Stop moving.
No, please stop this already.
My vajayjay's starting to feel weird.
I don't want to feel good with this peepee.
I don't want to cum with your thing.
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Stupid brute!
I don't want it, and I like Chi-chan.
Yet I'm starting to feel good with this peepee.
Chi-chan.
Mister!
Listen to me, mister!
We need to go now!
Mom's waiting, too!
Gotcha, coming right now.
You're going out wearing that?
It'll be easier for Tenka-chan if I go with the usual, right?
Come over here too, Komoko-chan!
Komo-chan!
We'll be late!
I promised that I'd help both of you with your relationship.
Got a prize.
Oh, one free stick.
Jeez, hurry up, you two!
Tenka-chan will get mad if we're late!
ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ-ΘΑ...
Number 11, Adachi Tenka.
Pleased to be with you all!
AIM HIGH! 3RD LOCAL IDOL CONTEST
Do your best, Tenka-chan!
Chie!
Chi-chan, it's time for the radio calisthenics.
Coming!
Just wait a bit.
Mornin', Komo-chan, Tenka-chan.
Mom! Mister!
We're going out!
Good morning.
It's hot today, as well.
Chi-chan, you're supposed to call me "Dad" now.
It's okay.
Even if you're my Dad now, mister is still mister.
Okay, we're off!
Hey!
Wait up, Chie!
I'm first!
The first one gets free snacks!
What are you saying?
Wait.