Mister, are you really taking photos of me in this outfit?
Yeah. Now, don't be shy and strike a pose.
Nnngh. I just asked for help since I want to be an idol...
Why do I have to wear this lewd swimsuit? It's embarrassing...
It's for Clavier, so obviously you would be embarrassed.
Clavier... It's a porn magazine after all isn't it?
It's not porn! It's male's desire.
Desire?
Tenka-chan, were you lying about becoming an idol?
I wasn't lying! I will become an idol.
Then stick out your rear and look in the camera.
Like this?
Spread your legs a little more.
More? But if I spread them more...
Don't move!
Even if you say that..
Stop!
My rear hole, don't shoot it!
It's okay, it's not visible.
You're lying!
Your plumpish thighs are sexy as well.
What? My thighs...
Is having some fat there sexy?
Of course! Look, it makes Mister that excited.
Stop it, don't pull the weird thing out!
It became like this because of you.
You have talent to become an idol
You get excited because of me?
Yeah. Being an idol means making men excited.
Then... it means that I can become one?
Yeah, you have what it takes.
For real?
For real!
Got it! I will do my best!
Mister, what should I do next?
Then, try grabbing my penis.
Whaaat? U - Understood.
Your penis... so hot and hard.
That's because I saw your rear hole.
So you could see it after all!
You are the worst!
Liar, liar, liar, liar! You, you, you, you, you!!! Making me wear a string-like swimsuit, you really are a pervert!
Tenka-chan, if you do it like this...
Kyaa!
What is this? It's sticky... and kind of stinks.
Can I become an idol like this?
Just a little more I guess. Can you keep going?
Yeah! I will definitely become an idol.
Hey Mister, don't just look at my butt..
Aaah no! Don't make it contract like that!
Have you gotten excited by looking at my dick?
You're wrong!
Mister, no! What are you doing?
Your finger is inside... whaaa?? What is this?
Mister, stop it! It hurts!
Even though I am telling you to stop...
Tenka-chan!
What? No! You can't put your dick in!
It's entering me.
It feels weird in my belly.
N-No!
Stop it already, my butt hurts!
Something feels strange, pull it out!
It, it goes all the way!
No, you can't go further! My insides are tightening!
Mister just let something out! My insides are hot!
I-It huuurts!
I am telling you it hurts... Mister, you are scary!
Please go slower.
D-don't suck my nipples!
Something is coming. What is this? I'm scared! Stop it, Mister! Stop it, stop it! Mister!
Now I can finally become an idol right?
Mister..
This is...?
It's called onahole, it's used to practice sex.
You want to have sex with Chi-chan don't you?
Wha..?
If you didn't love Chi-chan you wouldn't masturbate in the toilet.
Chi-chan! Chi-chan! Chi-chan! I love you!
Komako-chan, how about I help you out?
For real?
Yeah, but you need to practice... using this onahole that is.
First, think of Chi-chan and lick it.
Chi-chan... Chi-chan!
Enough. Now turn it around.
Huh? Why..?
Why is your dick out?
You put a penis in the onahole.
We are practicing sex so you can make Chi-chan feel good right?
Yeah..
Is it okay like this?
Yea.. Now slowly make it go all the way.
Slowly, slowly...
Mister, doesn't it hurt?
N-nah.
Your dick got hard and is throbbing.
It must feel good...
Uwah, something came out.
No!
Chi-chan...
Kinda strange flavour.
My head feels so light.
Komako-chan!!
Mister, what are you doing?!
I don't want it! It's gross!
Don't lick it!
First kiss is reserved for Chi-chan.
Stop it! Let me go!! Mister!
Come on!
Stop licking strange places.
Titties are prohibited!
No!
Please Mister, stop playing with my nipples!
I am telling you to stop, but you...
You are gonna make Chi-chan feel good right?
Yes.
Chi-chan.. I want to make her feel good!
Got it. Let's practice more.
Ah, no!
It's not what you think, it's because I thought of Chi-ch... yaaaaaa!
Not here!
Sto-!
Stop licking! No!
..bullying me
No, stop! Don't put it in!
I don't want it! Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't! Noooo!
I told you I don't want it...
Idiot! Mister, you idiot!
Stop moving!
I don't want it! Please stop it! My pussy feels strange.
Even though I don't want to feel good because of this dick
I don't want to come by your thing!
Big idiot! Idiot! Idiot! Big Idiot!
Even though I don't want it, though I love Chi-chan, dick is making me feel good!
Chi-chan.
Oi-chan! Are you there Oi-chan? [That's how the manager calls himself]
We should get going. Mom is waiting, too!
Yes, yes, comin'.
Wha? Are you going in this outfit?
With this appearance Tenka-chan should feel at easy don'tcha think?
Komako-chan too, come here!
Koma-chan, we will be late!
To help you get along with Chi-chan, I will keep my promise, okay?
I won.
Woah, you get one for free.
Oh come on quickly, both of you. Tenka-chan will be angry if we arrive late.
Number 12. Adachi Tenka, please take care of me!
Chie!
Chi-chan, let's go excercise!
Okaay! Wait a second.
Good morning Koma-chan, Tenka-chan. Mom, Oi-chan! I'm going!
Morning. Today is hot as well.
Chi-chan, you can call me Dad from now on though..
It's fine. Even if you're my dad, Oi-chan is still Oi-chan.
Well then, I'm going!
Jeez!
Hey, Chi!
Chi is first! The first gets treated with sweets!
What are you talking about?!
Waaaait!