I think it'll clear up soon.
Komako-chan, are you warm enough?
Yeah.
Mister, um...
Thank you.
Eh? What do you mean?
It's thanks to you that I got
to have sex with Chi-chan.
Sounds like it went well.
Chi-chan liked it too.
I'm glad.
You did study hard after all.
Study?
Well if you want to call it studying...
Mister...
Can I do anything for you in return?
In return?
I bet you're thinking something lewd again.
You see right through me, Komako-chan.
Pull your cock out.
Are you sure?
Well you are a pervert.
You love it when I make your cock feel good, right?
Just for today, OK?
Thank you very much.
You're so big already...
No moving unless I say so, OK?
You're... rock hard.
Did you know?
You're what people call a lolicon.
Please... let me cum soon.
Okay.
Mister, you came too much!
Komako-chan, you've gotten even better.
It's because someone forced me to.
I'm sorry.
Mister, lie down.
You won't be satisfied until we have sex, right?
Komako-chan...
You're not allowed to thrust, OK?
Your cock... is huge!
Not even a little thrust, OK?
It feels good.
It's tingly inside me!
Mister, how does it feel?
Does it feel good?
Your cock's getting so hard.
It's filling me up!
It's throbbing!
Are you gonna come?
You can't come unless I make
you feel better, right?
It's rubbing so hard inside me!
It's grinding against my insides!
Your cock is widening my insides!
It feels so good!
I told you not to!
Mister, I'll move my own hips! Stop!
Jeez!
I-If you're gonna come, come already!
It's making lewd noises! Stop!
A jolt went up my spine!
Don't be so rough!
I'm gonna come!
Let out your semen already! End this!
M-Mister... your cock is swelling up inside me!
It's coming out! It's squirting deep into my pussy!
Your semen's all sticky...
Thank you, Mister.
Oi-chan...
Why do I have to be naked?
If a teacher finds me, I'll be in trouble!
No one's here since it's summer vacation.
We shouldn't...
be doing this!
It's fine, it's fine.
It's embarrassing!
Why?
It's weird to be naked at school!
Jeez, let's go home already!
What should we do...
Oi-chan!
OK... If you masturbate here, then we can go home.
Masturbate here?
I taught you, remember? You can do it.
I can do it, but...
If you don't hurry, someone might come.
If I masturbate here, we go home.
That's a promise, OK?
I shouldn't be doing this...
Oi-chan, is this OK?
You have to come, otherwise it doesn't count.
But I shouldn't make the desk dirty!
The teacher's gonna get mad at me!
If I do it more, it's gonna feel too good and...
Oi-chan, I'm coming!
It feels really good!
Oi-chan... let's go home now.
You're the only one who enjoyed that,
and now you want to go home?
You're a bad girl, Chi-chan.
You said we'd go home if I masturbated...
No!
Make me feel good too, OK?
That's... the wrong hole!
T-That hurts!
I-It feels bad!
Oi-chan, that won't fit in my butt!
Your slippery thing is going in me!
My butt feels weird!
Don't move inside me!
I-It hurts!
It hurts, but it feels good!
It feels weird!
It hurts... but it feels good!
Oi-chan... finish already!
You're going to break my insides!
Oi chan, I'm scared!
Any more than this and...
Jeez! I can't think about anything else!
It's so hot inside me.
My butt hurts.
I ran away from home.
My mom and I got into an argument about
my dream of becoming an idol.
So I ran away to this secret place.
But since it's dangerous for a girl
to be alone this late at night...
Your mother's worrying about you.
Let's go back.
There's no way I'm going back!
What?
I brought Mister as my bodyguard.
He's kind of unreliable, but he's an
adult who supports my dream.
You're so stubborn.
But running away at least shows you've
got the guts to be an idol.
I know, right?
I'm gonna be an idol, so...
I don't need to do my summer homework, right?
Well you should probably do your homework.
Wha?
Jeez...
I thought at least you wouldn't betray me.
Betray you? That's harsh.
Mister doesn't treat me like a child.
When I confessed to him that
I wanted to be an idol...
He didn't laugh at me. He helped me.
But... he's kind of a pervert.
What's that smile?
Were you thinking about something lewd?
That's what you ask?!
Correction: He's a total pervert!
But you know, Tenka-chan...
Inviting a man over this late at night...
If something happens, you can't
say you didn't see it coming.
We've been, um... having sex, right?
Isn't that...
It's your training to help you become an idol.
The other idol girls said they don't do that!
Well that depends on the manager or...
You like me, right?
Of course I like you!
Me too...
If I had to pick like or dislike, I guess I like you too.
Really?
I don't have sex with people I don't like.
I guess we're lovers.
If that's what you think, then I guess we're lovers.
It seems Mister likes me after all!
Since we're lovers now...
I don't mind having sex with you.
Really?
Yeah.
Tenka-chan, I love you.
Mister's tongue is going inside my mouth.
He's lewdly wrapping it around mine.
This is how adults kiss, right?
It's really turning me on.
Hey!
Jeez...
I wonder how many times he's seen me naked.
Even Dad hasn't seen me like this lately.
It sends chills up my spine!
When he touches my nipples,
it makes me tighten down there!
Mister, no!
Don't lick me!
To be honest, I don't really mind.
I want him to do it more!
Mister...
You're putting it in, right?
Mister's going to put his huge
cock inside me again.
Mister...
Aren't you putting it in?
I've forgotten where to put it.
Yeah right!
Tenka-chan, please show me.
Here! You put it in here!
Mister always teases me...
But these days I don't mind.
Does that make me a masochist?
It goes in easily now.
That's because... you force yourself on me!
Do you hate me?
I hate you right now!
Then I gotta try to make you like me!
Hey!
You're being rough all of a sudden!
His cock is deep inside me... I think it's
all the way up against my womb.
It's like his cock and my pussy
are kissing like adults!
I must look so slutty right now...
Stop! It's embarrassing!
You just got tight so suddenly!
I don't know about that, but this
feels even better than usual!
Jeez, I can't think about anyone but him!
M-Mister! Please give me what I like!
Please give me all of your semen!
As Mister's hot semen filled my belly, I thought...
"I wish this summer vacation
goes on like this forever."
Mister...
I love you!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч