Umm... well... you see...
I love you, Sensei!
I was all alone in the photography club...
... but I was able to make friends thanks to you, Sensei.
And I got better at taking pictures.
So I...
Sensei!
How did this happen to me?
It's your job to pleasure me, Hinata.
Y-Yeah...
I'm going to cum.
Drink it all up without wasting a drop!
Didn't I just tell you not to waste any of it?
I-I'm sorry, Sensei!
Hinata... what are you supposed to say
when something like this happens?
S-Since I couldn't do as I was told...
...p-punish me, please.
Punish, huh?
S-Stop it, Sensei!
What now? Bullets aren't enough for you?
You prefer something stronger, huh?
You sure are a masochistic pervert, Hinata.
Sensei! Not that! No!!
How did I get myself into this mess?
I loved Sensei when he was kind.
He's perverted, but he didn't fuck me
even when I gave him permission.
I was happy at first that he was cherishing me, but...
...it didn't feel like we were proper lovers,
which made me feel uneasy.
Hinata!
I studied hard just like you told me to, Sensei!
Haven't my grades improved?
So just as you promised...
Make me your proper girlfriend, Sensei!
Please, Sensei!
Please take my virginity.
It's in me!
Your cock is in my pussy!
It hurts, but more importantly than that...
It feels good, Sensei! You're amazing!
So this is what sex feels like.
I can't believe a virgin came as soon as I stuck it in.
You're the best, Hinata!
Harder, Sensei!
Masturbation is nothing compared to this!
If it felt this good, then we should have had sex sooner!
This officially makes me your girlfriend, Sensei!
So I can take your cock on anytime, Sensei!
Anytime?
Anytime! You can stick your cock in me whenever you like, Sensei!
Around the clock sex with Sensei!
Just thinking about it makes me excited!
Sensei... came inside of me.
Sensei...
I'm so happy!
Despite all that... Sensei stopped having
sex with me because he's too busy.
He gave me a taste for sex.
You're so cruel, Sensei!
I just got through doing this a moment ago, but...
I just can't help myself!
I'm not satisfied with just this toy, Sensei!
Stick your cock in me!
Sensei!
I can't believe he'd make me, his girlfriend, feel this way.
It pissed me off, so...
...I wanted to bug him, so I headed
over to Sensei 's house on Sunday.
I just invited myself over!
Sensei...
Let's have sex.
Then Sensei got really pissed off.
He said naughty girls who didn't do as they
were told needed to be punished...
...with grownup toys.
Two hours later
Another two hours later
Yet another two hours later
Sensei, stop already!
You don't have to have sex with me when you're busy!
I'm sorry for being so selfish!
Stop! If you fuck me so hard, then I'm going to cum!
Sensei!
I'm cumming~!
Sensei wouldn't forgive me no matter
how many times I apologized.
He just kept cumming inside of me over
and over until the sun went down.
Sensei wasn't just a pervert, he was insatiable.
I'm done for!
He kept making me cum over and over again as well.
After about the 10th time...
...I lost count.
Sensei had his cock in my pussy all day the following day as well.
I sure was in a pinch.
Afterwards, Sensei claimed
that he had been rough with me on purpose
to keep me from getting too addicted to sex.
He claimed to have opened my eyes instead...
to adult sex.
Sensei, don't do me from behind with something that big!
My ass will be destroyed if you stick that in there!
My asshole is going to get all stretched out!
Not my ass!
Making me feel good by sticking any old thing
in my ass is just turning me into a pervert!
Cut it out already!
Don't make me into anymore of a pervert than I already am!
To think that you peed yourself...
Do you really want to be punished that badly?
You sure are a huge masochist, Hinata!
That's not true! I'm not a huge masochist...
Wefll then... it's time for your beloved semen, Hinata...
I'm going to pour it into your womb.
No! Stop with the strange positions, Sensei!
I'm going to get pregnant!
No~!
You came inside of me!
Your seed is inside of me, Sensei!
Your cock is too thick, Sensei!
If you fuck me so hard with such a fat cock, then
my asshole is going to get all stretched out!
I can't take it anymore! I'm going to
cum! I'm going to cum from my ass!
Alright now... I'm going to let you have
more sperm inside your womb.
I'm begging you! Please stop cumming inside of me!
But if I don't cum inside of you...
...then it wouldn't be much of a punishment,
now would it, Hinata?
I definitely won't forgive you if you cum inside
of me any more than you already have!
Stop! Today isn't safe!
Don't cum inside of me any more!
Give it up already.
Stop!
No~!
How cruel! You're such a jerk, Sensei!
I didn't want you to cum inside me so much, yet...
...you did anyways.
Getting cummed in over and over again feels so good!
My womb has completely become
accustomed to the taste of sperm!
I just might not be able to go on living without Sensei's cock!
One year later
Thanks to him continuously cumming in me just like I wanted...
I ended up getting pregnant with Sensei's baby.
I ran away from home before I could no longer
hide my pregnancy from my parents...
...and went to live with Sensei.
Ah, please, Sensei! Cut it out already!
Let me go home, already! I can't take it anymore!
Just give up and stay with me forever, Hinata!
No! I don't belong to you, Sensei!
Alright then, I'll just cum inside of you
again to make you change your mind.
No! Anything but that!
That's right!
You cum enough to lose consciousness
just by having semen poured into you.
I'm begging you! Anything but that!
I'm going to get pregnant!
It's a little late for that, Hinata!
You're already pregnant with my child, you see.
Not true! I just put on a little weight!
I am so not pregnant!
Give it up already! You're already producing breast milk.
Are you not happy having my child?
I don't want to have your baby!
This! This is what I want!
Having semen poured directly into my womb feels so good!
Being a cum receptacle even when I'm pregnant is the best!
Are you okay? Did I overdo it, Asami?
Nope! It felt really good, Sensei!
It felt the best out of all the sex play we've done so far!
That's good... but wouldn't you like to have more normal sex?
It makes me feel really guilty given your current condition...
Nope! You're the one that turned me
into such a raging pervert, Sensei!
You have to take responsibility for your actions.
Sensei! I would like to do it while pretending
to be maid and master next time!
A scenario where the girl has cruel things done
to her like in the porno mags you had.
I wonder what I need to do in order to turn
you back into a normal girl, Asami.
You're going to be a daddy soon, so get ahold of yourself, Master!
Sensei said he would take care of me...
...but I want things to stay this way for a little while longer.
The immorality of taboo sex between
teacher and student is the greatest!