We're almost there!
Hey, Chi!
Wait up!
Oi-chan! We're here!
Give us candy!
You're too loud.
Tenka-chan, be nice to her.
Fine, but you're spoiling her way too much.
Good morning. I see you're all together today.
Yeah, Oi-chan!
Which should I pick?
Maybe this?
I ate this one yesterday.
And I don't like this one.
Oi-chan, what should I pick?
Maybe it's good once in a while?
Mister....
I'll take this.
Thank you!
Hey, Mister!
What's wrong, Tenka-chan?
It's about the video I uploaded the other day...
It's not getting enough views at all.
Hey, what should we do?
Is it not good enough?
Do something about it!
Ehh? Even if you say that...
Please, come up with something.
Koma-chan!
I don't know what I should pick!
Chi-chan, welcome back.
I'm back!
Oi-chan is such a meanie, he's always talking to Tenka-chan.
Want some?
Eh? Can I?
Yay!
Yummy?
Yeah!
No way! No-one's going to watch it like that!
Think about it seriously!
Those two are quite close.
Yeah...
I guess so...
I'll bring some barley tea, so come on over!
Don't try to change the subject!
OK!
Let's go, Koma-chan!
Chi-chan, wait up!
Can you show me that card?
Can I have this?
Ehh? But I only have one of those...
Then I'll trade it with this one here.
Eh? What should I do?
Alright.
Yay!
Chi, you do have quite a lot of rare ones...
Chi has good luck!
What? That's so unfair!
Huh? Where's Koma-chan?
Eh? Probably the toilet?
She's taking a while.
Maybe she's pooping?
Hey, girls shouldn't say such things!
Mister, can I use the bathroom?
Go ahead.
Indirect kiss with Chi-chan...
Chi-chan...
Chi-chan...!
Chi-chan is entering my body...
Deeper...
Chi-chan... Chi-chan..!
I'm going to pee!
Chi-chan...
Come up with a good solution by tomorrow, mister!
More views, huh...
I'm counting on you!
Bye bye!
Goodbye.
Chi, what's wrong?
Is your mom going to be late again?
I'm staying a little bit longer here, so don't worry.
I see.
Yeah! So see you tomorrow.
Chi, see you tomorrow then.
Oi-chan, I'm hungry.
Do you want some yogurt?
Yeah!
Oi-chan, hurry!
Wait a second...
It's ready.
OK...
Delicious...
Geez, your yogurt is not yummy at all!
I'm sorry. Do you want some more candy?
I do, but...
Then let's study for a bit.
I'll give you candy as a reward.
Really?
I'll do my best!
Don't tell anyone about what we're going to do now.
OK...
Oi-chan?
That tickles!
Oi-chan, this is weird-!
If you lick my nipples, it makes me twitch!
Are we done?
Not yet. We have only started.
What? No!
Oi-chan, why are you taking off my undies?
Not there! That's where I pee!
It's dirty there!
Oi-chan, I feel weird...
No! I'm about to pee!
It's coming out!
Oi-chan, do I really have to be naked?
We're almost...
We're almost done.
Your wee-wee won't fit in there.
Your inside is made to put a wee-wee in there.
But your wee-wee is way bigger than I am inside!
Don't worry, it will stretch when I put it inside you.
Are you okay?
Oi-chan, it hurts...
No! Don't thrust!
Y-You're stretching my stomach!
No, I can't anymore! Stop it!
My inside feels like it's being plugged up!
It's getting hot deep inside!
Oi-chan's yoghurt is spreading out inside me!
Is this really the study...?
Sure is.
Really? Aren't you lying to me?
Why aren't putting in your wee-wee today?
You like candy, right?
I do, but...
Here, have an ice pop.
No-!
My butt feels cold!
So cold!
Don't move them at the same time!
Oi-chan, are we still not done yet?
This feels so good!
I'm gonna-!
Oi-chan...
Are we done?
Not yet. Turn over.
You're too fast! Do it slower!
Y-Your wee-wee is twitching!
Are you going to spurt yogurt again?
Hold me... Oi-chan, hold me!
I-I'm gonna cum...
Hurry... Hurry up and shoot your white stuff!
No!
No! Not that!
No, if you do that...
You're right, your yogurt has become tasty...
I wish you were my father...
Because you're with me every day...
What do you think, Oi-chan?
Mister, what should I do to become an idol?