www.SubDESU-H.net
Nii-sama...
Getting rid of all the concubine's children will not be a hindrance.
Fortunately, the Tenjou household is in no need of children. Removing them will be my gift.
Nii-sama...
Kengo Nii-sama...
Please hold on.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
What are you doing, Matsuriko?
Oh, Nii-sama!
Flower seeds?
Yes.
There's plenty afar,
but here we have none.
That's why I took some.
Then, someday,
in the backyard, I'll make a garden with lots and lots of flowers.
Oh...
That would be nice.
Right?
However, for some reason,
my dream still feels so far away...
Then, after the flower garden's complete,
Nii-sama, Aya Nee-san
and everyone will go outside, and gaze at the flowers.
That's my dream.
I see.
I hope you achieve your dream.
Here, Matsuriko.
Do you not want to play with your beloved Kengo?
Be able to finally know what a woman's pleasure feels like?
Then, Kengo.
Don't you want to have all of what these girls have to give?
If you just ask, I'll be able to grant all of your desires.
W
2nd Curtain 「Shameless Lap of Luxury」
No, Tenjou-san. The girls are watching us.
Are you not the one showing it?
You're the one here who's getting more aroused.
Your cunt is gripping me tight!
It feels good.
I'll cum.
Futaba. Mitsuba. Yotsuba.
Stop watching that now.
Come on, all of you, go to the other room.
Let's have our meal.
Okay. Let's eat.
Thank you for the food.
Kengo.
Because I tried escaping that you got those injuries.
I feel really bad.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault, Aya-Nee,
I'm the one who should apologize.
I always thought that you would be okay,
but it seems I misjudged the situation.
Let's try harder next time.
Hey, hey, Nii-sama look here!
Futaba's doing a good job.
See, mother was doing this to a man's cock.
She said a man will be happy if you do this.
I'm also capable of drinking Nii-sama's white pee.
S-Stop that, Futaba.
Nii-sama, do you want me to do it?
Futaba, stop talking like that...
What do you mean?
You yourself said you wanted to do this.
I-I never said...
Didn't you say that you wanted Nii-sama's cock to go in here?
Y-You idiot!
Oh?
So you've finally become interested?
If you feel like doing it,
I'll always be ready to teach you, Aya.
No...
Father...
Matsuriko?
Nii-sama, please don't go against father.
If something happens to you, I...
I'll be okay, Matsuriko.
Father still needs me to protect the family's name.
Someday, when I become the master of the Tenjou household,
I'll set you all free.
Then, I'll make you my wife.
So don’t worry, Matsuriko.
Okay.
Yeah. But if that's not the case,
then I have something else that I'll do!
Nii-sama!
Wait up there!
Stop, father!
No! No!
No! Not there...
Not there!
I'm your daughter!
I'm already bored of those concubines.
I think doing it with their children will be of some fun.
No...
Oh... it's already wet.
Then, I'll have this now.
Shoujo x Shoujo x Shoujo
Do you really think you can escape from this mansion?
You've got a nice ass like your mother's.
Kengo was more than likely pleased with this.
Father, we can't do this.
Anything but this...
It looks like Kengo had some fun with you.
There's some semen left.
I guess I'll just help myself to your asshole.
You've also got a nice grip here.
Father's thing is hot and hard...
Stop that now.
Why are you back here?
K-Kengo...
Did you come to watch me copulate?
Kengo, did you find the girls last night delicious?
You screwed Matsuriko too, right?
Nii-sama, I've been waiting.
I-It hurts.
It hurts.
Matsuriko...
Nii-sama...
Everyone's watching us doing it...
Kengo Nii-sama's cock is going inside me.
I'm happy.
Matsuriko...
Your lewd spot is clearly visible.
It’s embarrassing...
Don’t look.
Matsuriko, if you squeeze me like that, it’s going to come out.
Matsuriko...
What’s wrong Matsuriko?
More. More.
I want more.
Nii-sama...
More. Please give me more.
I am going to cum again!
Oh, so you also screwed Matsuriko.
What!?
Her pussy is narrow and tight, isn't it?
She had been saving her first time for you.
You should be thankful.
You should...!
just disappear!
Nii-sama...
www.SubDESU-H.net
Who... are you?
He died...
Father is dead...
Father is dead!
Matsuriko, Aya-nee,
we're free now!
From now on
we don't need to worry about meeting people.
It’s okay for us to go outside!
Come on, Aya-nee...
No.
If I go outside,
I'll get caught and you'll get beaten again!
We'll get attacked by father again.
I don't want to go outside.
What are you talking about?
Father's no longer alive!
Look!
They can’t go outside anymore.
They've been in this mansion for too long.
Father?!
Don’t worry, I won’t lay a hand on them anymore.
I don't want to get killed again.
No way...
You died.
Damn...
Is that guy not dead yet?
Next!
Are all these girls under his command?
What in the world am I doing!?
Hey, Matsuriko.
Why is everyone acting like this?
Was I called back because of that?
That was father's idea.
He said "I will Grant your wishes".
Father said that?
Did father really say that?
Hey, Nii-sama.
Nii-sama is still the same person, right?
Why ask that question?
Father wants to speak with you.
Hey, Kengo.
It's not a sin to indulge in your desires.
What did you say?
Last night was the best, wasn't it?
What do you think about the girls who fell into the shameless lap of luxury?
What in the world are you planning to do, father!?
To use my status and power for my selfish purposes.
Obviously, there's no need to feel guilty.
If you are a person with high intelligence, you should value this kind of act.
What are you talking about?
I'm different from you.
No, you're no different!
You raped a lot of pure women yesterday, didn't you?
That's the real you.
But you're still surprised, right?
How could they do such things...?
That's because I tamed them to do so!
They've been locked up in this mansion for a long time.
That has caused them to become desperate for a man.
Haven't they flourished to something beautiful?
This means everything went well, Kengo!
Stop that.
Do not bend the truth with those words!
All went well?
Then, that means, I...
That's right. It's everything that I ever wanted.
You know, Kengo,
I've been planning your future for a while now.
To be able to make your desires a reality.
To be able to protect you.
I will sacrifice myself.
Father...
How terrible of you.
You haven't noticed?
I was born in order to protect you from your father.
I killed your father.
Then essentially became him.
And then ruled over this household.
What the hell are you talking about?
There's no need to worry.
Your father was really killed back there.
I'm the one who's controlling him now.
Don't let a single girl escape.
Everything here is yours.
That's what you really want.
Because you and I are the same.
Father really died...
And the one who acted like him was me?
The one who kept, Aya-nee and the others locked up, was me?
Everyone, we're leaving this mansion this instant!
What are you talking about?
Father will never approve of such a thing.
Father is no longer here!
Kengo, what are you saying?
Let's just get the hell out of here!
No. Wait...
Aya-nee!
No!
Aya-nee...
I'm afraid of going outside.
Father will get angry.
What are you doing, Kengo?!
I did not reveal my identity for you to do this!
Are you just going to let everything that I did go to waste!?
Nii-sama?
Nii-sama!
I merely wanted your desires to come true.
They're also satisfied with that.
So, what's wrong with that?
No.
That's not what I wanted!
In that case, I might as well take your place.
I've said this many times:
You cannot ignore me.
Because you and I are one.
No. That's not it.
There will be no such thing.
There's only one thing I can do to get rid of you.
Everyone will be set free this way.
Stop that!
Matsuriko, please take care of Aya-nee and the others...
Don't!
Matsuriko!
Flowers?
I see. I'm already dead.
I'm supposed to be dead, but my body hurts.
Nii-sama?
Kengo...
Are you okay?
Yea, I'm still alive.
Is everyone all right?
It seems that way.
After that, he never appeared before us ever again.
However, I'm certain he's still somewhere inside me.
Hey, Nii-sama.
My dream has already come true.
The End
www.SubDESU-H.net