Oi-chan's candy shop
Oi-chan, look at me!
Ta-dah!
I'm wearing a yukata!
Do I look cute?
Very cute.
I got Mom to buy it for me.
Festival, festival!
Sounds like fun.
Yeah!
I'm going with Tenka-chan and Koma-chan.
Oi-chan, are you going to the festival?
Um...
I'll be helping at a food stall for a bit.
Oh?
Gimme spending money!
Hm... Should I?
Oh...
Your dick...
It's gotten hard.
Oi-chan, you pervert.
It's because you're cute, Chi-chan.
Jeez, you perv!
Do you hate my dick?
I don't hate it, but...
Not now!
You're not wearing panties.
Yeah...
Don't touch me!
Why not?
Because...
You're wet.
When I'm with you, my crotch gets slippery
and I feel a tightness in my breasts.
Is that weird?
It's not weird.
When people are with those who they love,
It's natural that they get aroused.
Really?
Yukata, Fireworks, and Summer festivals
Oi-chan?
Ow!
Why are you tying my wrists together?
I can't move!
What are you doing?
That tickles!
Don't lick me!
Don't put your finger inside!
N-No!
Don't lick my breasts!
Oi-chan, untie me!
Someone could hear us out here!
If we're quiet, it's fine.
Wha?
I can't!
I'm gonna moan!
You're going in so deep.
Hey! You're being rough!
Your dick feels great!
This feels too good...
I'm going crazy!
N-No!
It feels too good there!
Please stop!
It's like I'm floating. I'm scared!
Your dick... It's getting bigger inside me!
I can't... I can't take it!
Oi-chan! Oi-chan! Oi-chan!
Oi-chan, you're going to give me
spending money, aren't you?
Oji-san, this is bad!
No one will disturb us here.
I've promised Komako and Chie that
we'd go to the festival together...
I hear that Komako-chan's going
to confess to Chi-chan.
Really?
Not so deep!
You mustn't disturb them.
I won't! I really won't!
Stop it! Stop it!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Jeez!
You made me wet myself!
You're the worst!
What if someone saw us!?
Everyone's off to see the fireworks,
so nobody's coming here.
Even if no one comes, this is wrong!
That's what you say, but you
really want it, don't you?
What are you saying?
Wait! Stop!
Why like this!?
See? It went in so easily.
You're the worst! Take it out!
I don't want to have sex!
Stop making me move!
Let me go!
Your dick is too big!
This is wrong.
That's too rough!
This position is embarrassing!
Why are you getting even rougher?
It's making me crazy!
It hurts! It's so deep!
It's going in so deep!
I-I said stop it!
I said I don't want to have sex.
Let me go already.
Take your dick out!
Stop getting bigger inside me!
You came inside me again.
What if I get pregnant?
Koma-chan...
Can we really see the fireworks from here?
Yes, that guy said this was the spot.
Really? I wonder when the fireworks start.
Chi-chan?
Yes?
Do you like me?
Of course.
Why do you ask?
I like you too, Chi-chan.
We feel the same about each other.
Can I... kiss you?
Why?
I can't?
I didn't say no, but...
Koma-chan, this feels weird.
It's not weird.
We like each other.
So...
We can have sex...
Right?
Koma-chan?
Are we gonna have sex?
I studied a lot, so it's fine.
Koma-chan... that tickles!
Your breasts are cute.
Not the nipples!
Touch mine too.
If you suck my nipples like that...
Chi-chan, you're like a baby! You're so cute!
Chi-chan, let's... let's make each other feel good!
Chi-chan, I love you. I love you!
Don't lick me there!
Koma-chan, that's so lewd!
Chi-chan, lick mine too.
OK.
Chi-chan, your pussy's making sticky sounds.
It's so cute.
Koma-chan, that's too much!
Chi-chan...
Let's do it some more.
Chi-chan, we're connected!
You're right!
It's like we're having sex!
Koma-chan!
Koma-chan, this feels so good!
We didn't see the fireworks.
Are you mad?
No!
I got to know lots of things about you. It was fun!
Chi-chan...
I love you.
I love you too.
translation: ObscureReference
timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч