Umm, sensei...
I think that you're very cool.
You always give your best for our sake.
It's amazing how so mature you are...
When I look at you,
I end up thinking that I want
to do some stuff for you...
...like making meals for you,
and even way more besides that.
That's why, umm...
I want you to make me...
...your girlfriend!
Will it be okay for me now to be
here in your home, sensei?
Sensei...
That tickles!
Sensei, the way you move your hand...
...it's kind of lewd.
This is embarrassing!
You keep on touching my boobs...
And it tickles me...
Please stop rubbing my belly button.
Don't do that, sensei!
If you'll keep poking me in there,
my voice will come out!
I know that I shouldn't, but my voice
comes out on its own...
No...
Please stop making weird noises down there!
What are you looking at?
Sensei, you're too lewd!
Please wait, umm...
It still hasn't started for me yet...
...so it will be fine even if
we don't use a condom.
Sensei, please be gentle with me.
Ouch!
Your thing went inside me!
It's huge... Wow!
It feels hot!
Sensei... Sensei! Sensei!
Sensei, you're filling me up inside!
I'm happy!
Please make yourself feel good!
Sensei, are you feeling good?
Am I doing a good job at our sex?
Your dick is getting big inside me.
I'm also feeling tingly and hot!
It started to feel good that
my hips began moving!
Sensei... Sensei!
My voice is getting louder and louder.
Wow, it keeps on going
deep inside over and over!
Sensei, you're amazing!
Oh no, I'm acting strange!
No!
Don't go that deep inside me! You shouldn't!
You can shoot it out anytime.
I want lots and lots of your semen.
Sensei, I love you...
I love you so much!
I'm acting strange right now,
and this is all your fault, sensei!
I'm not usually like this!
I don't usually make this lewd kind of voice!
This is your fault, sensei!
Come...
Sensei, I want you to pour
all of your semen inside me!
You're coming so much!
The throbbing...
...won't stop.
I'm full of your semen.
I'm so happy.
I'll do it for you whenever you can't
hold it in from now on, okay?
Sensei...
I love you so much.
ryouri mo saihou mo tokui dakedo
料理も裁縫も得意だけど
I'm good at cooking and sewing
tomodachidzukuri wa chotto nigate
友達作りはちょっと苦手
but I'm not good at making friends
kyuuto sei tte yobanai de
キュートせいって呼ばないで
don't say that it's because I'm cute
koibana datte shitai n desu
恋バナだってしたいんです
even I want to have some love talk
madogiwa de hohoemu anata ga suki
窓際で微笑むアナタが好き
I love it when you're at the window and smiling
imasugu gyutto dakitsukitai kedo
今すぐぎゅっと抱き付きたいけど
it makes me want to go and hug you tight right away
tokubetsu atsukai wa dame desu yo ne
特別扱いはダメですよね
but I shouldn't pamper you with special treatment
darashinaku deteru onaka
だらしなく出てるお腹
your sloppily bulging belly
choppiri bosabosa na maegami
ちょっぴりボサボサな前髪
your slightly shaggy bangs
otou-san no nioi ga suru sebiro ga
お父さんの匂いがするセビロが
and your suit with a fatherly smell
watashi o koakuma ni suru no yo
私を小悪魔にするのよ
are turning me into a little imp
darashinaku deteru onaka
だらしなく出てるお腹
your sloppily bulging belly
choppiri bosabosa na maegami
ちょっぴりボサボサな前髪
your slightly shaggy bangs
otou-san no nioi ga suru sebiro ga
お父さんの匂いがするセビロが
and your suit with a fatherly smell
watashi o koakuma ni shite shimau no
私を小悪魔にしてしまうの
are gonna turn me into a little imp
Welcome home!
Huh?
Could it be...
...that it started?
What should I do?
Inagaki, do you have a moment?
What's the matter?
Will it be fine right now? I can't hold it in...
W-We can't. Not at school.
Didn't you promise that you'll do it
for me whenever I can't hold it in?
Yes...
Sensei, you're too lewd.
You're being unable to hold back too often.
Sorry...
I don't believe you.
You'd start going wild right after touching me.
Even though you're an adult...
Sae, I want you to put it in your mouth already.
Gosh...
After I make you come...
...we're done.
Alright.
Let's feel good together.
Huh!?
Sex is off-limits!
Didn't you tell me that you'll do it
for me whenever I can't hold it in?
This won't take long.
I-I'll use my mouth...
We really can't have sex!
No!
What are you doing? Please stop!
Huh? Is this...
Don't look...
Did you start having a period by any chance?
That's right. I can end up having a baby now.
That's why sex is off-limits...
Sorry, I couldn't hold back!
Why can't you hold yourself back
even though you're an adult?
At least use a condom, please!
I might end up having a baby,
so please pull your dick out!
Even though we shouldn't...
Don't you want to have my baby, Sae?
I think that...
...it's too early for something like that.
No!
Sensei, you act like a huge baby
and yet you want to have one!
I won't have one...
Adults won't have sex...
...without wearing a condom!
You're just so cute that I can't stop myself!
Telling me that right now
doesn't make me happy at all!
Sae, your pussy is saying that it wants a baby!
There's no way that it does.
Please pull it out right now!
We'll be over soon...
I'm begging you...
We really can't go any further!
I'll end up having a baby,
s-so do it outside...
You definitely shouldn't do it inside.
Please shoot it outside!
No!
No! No!
No! No! No!
No! No! No! No—!
I'm begging you, please stop!
I'm coming!
Nooooo!
I'm gonna have a baby—!
This can't be real...
Even though I already
started having my period,
you came a lot in my pussy.
If I ended up having a baby,
what will I do?
I have a baby...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji