I think it'll clear up soon, but... are you warm enough, Komako-chan?
Yeah.
Mister, um...
Thank you...
Huh? What's this all of a sudden?
It's thanks to you that I got to have sex with Chi-chan.
It went well, huh?
Chi-chan was happy about it too.
I see. You did study hard after all.
Study?
Well, I suppose that's true.
Mister.
Is there something you want in return?
In return?
I bet you're thinking of something lewd again.
I guess I can't hide the truth from you.
Pull out your cock for me.
Is it fine?
You're a pervert, so...
You like it best when I make your cock feel good, right?
Just for today, okay?
Thank you very much.
You've gotten so big already...
You're not allowed to thrust, okay?
Your cock's rock hard...
Did you know?
Doing things like this, you're basically a lolicon.
Let me cum soon, please?
Okay.
Mister, you came too much!
Komako-chan, you've gotten much better.
It's because somebody forced me into it.
I'm sorry.
Mister, lie down.
You won't be satisfied unless we have sex, right?
Komako-chan...
You're not allowed to thrust, okay?
Mister... Your cock is huge...!
No thrusting, not even a bit, okay!
It feels good, it's tingly inside me!
Mister, how does it feel?
Does it feel good?
Your cock's gotten hard, it's filling my belly up so much!
It's throbbing!
Are you about to cum?
If I don't make you feel better, you can't cum right?
Your cock is rubbing against me so much, it's grinding against my insides!
Your cock is pushing up my belly...!
It feels so good!
I told you not to thrust!
Mister, I'll move my hips, so stop it!
Jeez!
I-If you're gonna cum, do it!
It's making lewd noises, you must thrust!
This is too much! It's giving my goose bumps!
Don't be so rough!
I'm gonna cum-!
Hurry, let out your semen! End this!
M-Mister, your cock is swelling up inside me-!
It's coming out! It's spurting out deep inside my pussy...!
Your semen's all gooey, Mister...
Thank you, Mister.
Oi-chan...
Why do I have to be naked?
If a teacher find me, I'll be in trouble!
No one's here since it's summer vacation.
We shouldn't...
We shouldn't be doing such things!
It's fine, it's fine.
It's embarrassing!
Why?
Because it's weird being naked at school!
Jeez, let's go home already!
Hmm, what should I do?
Oi-chan!
It can't be helped; if you masturbate here, then we'll go home.
Huh?! I have to masturbate here?
I taught you how to do it, right?
I can do it, but...
If you don't hurry, someone might come.
If I masturbate here, we'll home... That's a promise, okay?
I shouldn't be doing such things, but...
Oi-chan, is this okay?
You must cum, otherwise it doesn't count.
I shouldn't dirty the desk...
My teacher's gonna tell me off!
If I do it more, it's gonna feel too good...
Oi-chan, it's coming! I feel the pleasure coming!
Oi-chan, let's go home now...
You want to go home, even though you're only the one that felt good? You're a bad girl.
You said we'll go home if I masturbated...
No!
Make me feel good too, okay?
That's the wrong hole!
T-That hurts!
I-It feels uncomfortable!
Oi-chan! That won't fit in my butt!
Your slippery thing is entering me!
My butt's feeling weird!
You mustn't thrust!
I-It hurts!
It hurts, but it feels so good!
I'm feeling all weird!
It hurts... but it's so good!
Oi-chan, finish already!
You're going to break my belly!
Oi-chan, I'm scared!
If I feel any more aroused than this...!
Jeez! I can't think about anything else!
Inside my belly's so hot...
My butt hurts...
I ran away from home.
I had an argument with my mom about the whole idol thing.
That's why I ran away to this secret base.
But, since it's dangerous for a girl to be alone this time of night...
Your mother's probably worried... Let's go home already.
There's no way I'm going back!
What?
I called over Mister as my body guard.
Although he's not that reliable, he's an adult that supports my dream.
You're so stubborn.
Although if you didn't have the guts to do this, you can't become an idol.
I know, right?
I'm gonna be an idol, so...
There's no need to do my summer homework, right?
Nah, I'm pretty sure you have to.
Huh?
Aw man... I thought that Mister wouldn't betray me.
Betray you? That's a bit extreme.
Mister doesn't treat me like a child.
When I announced I was going to become an idol,
he didn't laugh, he even helped me.
Although, he's a bit of a pervert.
What's wrong? Were you thinking about something lewd?
Why would I be?!
Correction: He's a total pervert!
But you know, Tenka-chan.
Inviting a man over this late at night... You can't complain if something were to happen!
We've, you know... had sex, right?
Doesn't that mean...
It's training for you to be an idol after all.
The other idol girls said they don't do such things!
Well, it might depend on the manager...
You like me, right?
Of course I do.
I... I guess I like you too, if I had to choose.
Really?
I wouldn't have sex with someone I didn't like.
I guess we're lovers.
If that's what you think, then I guess we are lovers.
Looks like Mister likes me after all.
Since we're lovers and all, I don't mind having sex with you again...
Really?
Yeah.
Tenka-chan, I love you.
Mister's tongue is going inside my mouth...
He's lewdly entwining it with mine.
This is an adults kiss, isn't it?
It's really turning me on...
Hey, what are you-!
Jeez...
I wonder how many times he's seen me naked?
Even my dad hasn't seen me like this lately...
It's sending shivers up my spine...
When he touches my nipples, it makes me throb down there...
Mister! You can't!
You mustn't lick me there!
In all honesty, I don't mind it.
In fact, I want him to do it more!
Mister...
You're putting it in, right?
Mister's going to insert his huge cock into me again...
Mister...
You're not putting it in?
I've forgotten where to put it in.
Yeah right, as if!
Tenka-chan, please show me.
Here! You put it in here!
Mister always teases me... but lately, I don't dislike it.
Does that mean I'm a masochist?
It goes in easily now.
It's because you force yourself onto me!
Do you dislike me?
I don't like you right now!
Then, I gotta try and make you like me!
Hey! You're being rough all of a sudden!
His cock is deep inside me... I think it's thrusting up against my womb...
It's like my pussy and his cock is having an adults kiss!
I bet I look so slutty right now...
Stop it! It's to embarrassing!
You're tightening suddenly-!
I don't know, but...! This feels better than normal!
Jeez, all I can think about is him!
Mister! Please give me what I want!
Give me all of your semen, Mister!
As Mister's hot semen filled my belly, I wished...
I wished for this summer vacation to never end.
Mister, I love you!
It's finally over...? - Shikkaku Fansubs