Long time no see, Ryuuji-san!
I'm Obata Mia.
Mia-chan?! Wait, your outfit...
my arranged marriage is with you?!
Mia-chan's mom?!
I want her to be married young like me,
but she wouldn't go through with any I arranged.
Then she said "If it was with Yuuji-kun,
who I used to play with, then I wouldn't mind."
Mom, can you please just go somewhere else?
Let the young people talk.
From Little Girls to Slutty Woman...
We can talk now, but it's been ten years.
Where do I even start?
You know, it's amazing your mom still
looks as good as she did back then.
She hasn't changed one bit since I last saw her.
Why are you even bringing my mom up?
You just stared at her chest the entire
time she was here, didn't you?
Huh? No, I...
You know, I've done my best
to be even sexier than her.
Huh? Wai... Mia-chan?
I made sure that the left side of my kimono was slightly
open, and that I wasn't wearing anything underneath.
Wai... Mia-chan...
Oh my, Ryuuji-san, you're so forward.
We'll be married, so it makes sense
to check how compatible we are, right?
Holy shit, they're so soft!
What the?!
What the heck is a futon
doing in the room next to this?!
What are our parents thinking?!
They probably wanted to show us
how much they approve of our marriage.
Well? Haven't I grown a little?
Mia-chan...
Shit... I'll be playing right into their hands if this carries on...
thump
Compatibility checking or whatever,
my heart isn't ready for this!
I want to have an arranged
marriage with you, Ryuuji-san.
Also, even if your upper half is trying to be logical,
your bottom half seems to be more honest and impulsive.
I'm so happy! You're getting turned on by me!
Shit.
I'm going to help out the thing you've
been keeping locked up in your pants.
Mia-chan...
The smell of urine and sweat
coming from your dick is so lewd.
It's so big I can't even fit it all in my mouth!
This is going inside my pussy next?
Touch my boobs.
Mia-chan, I...
Ryuuji-san, does it feel good
when I lick the tip of your dick?
Ah, my frenulum!
What about this really wet part?
Damn, it feels so good! I can't think straight!
Yuuji-san, my pussy is throbbing and it's getting drenched.
Please, could you lick it for me?
You're licking me in such a dirty place.
What the hell are we doing?
Our parents are in the house!
How could I not lick the hell out
of this beautiful pussy, though?!
You're playing with my nipples
at the same time? It feels so good!
Please make my pussy soaking wet.
The place that you're licking
right now feels really good!
I'll rub your dick with the boobs you
like so much! I'll twirl my nipples around it!
Oh no, I'm going to cum!
The way you're moving your tongue feels so amazing!
I'm going to cum!
Oh ma...
Can I put it in now?
Of course. I'll put it in for you.
So we're finally doing it.
Your cum-covered dick is going
to go into my dripping wet pussy.
It's going inside me!
My pussy feels so great!
Your dick is going so deep in me!
Mia-chan, don't grip me so tightly!
Your dick is spreading my pussy wide open!
I'm so, so happy!
My pussy is just squeezing you on its own!
Just cum whenever you have to.
I'll do this for you as many times as you want.
I'm cumming! Take it out!
Now we've kissed, too.
Mi-Mi-Mi-Mi-Mia-chan?!
I just came inside you, that's not good!
It's not bad at all. Everyone's given us their blessing,
so it's okay for you to keep cumming in me.
Mia-chan... whatever happens, happens!
For now, I'm going to take my time
and get a good taste of you!
You're ramming your thing into me from behind!
Rub my boobs as much as you want!
Make them bigger than my mom's!
Damn, they're so smooth, Mia-chan!
When you play with my nipples
like that it feels really good, too!
Ryuuji-san, that feels good! That feels really good!
Let's cum together, Ryuuji-san!
Cum inside me!
Wow, you're still cumming inside me.
We can stay like this for a little longer, right?
Kiss me.
Well? How did the talk go? Everything good?
Looks like it went quite well.
I already talked to your company,
and gave them your letter of resignation.
What?
Your things are being moved over from your place.
They should be here by tomorrow.
Huh?!
Since you're marrying Mia-chan,
you'll be taking over our farm.
I'm inexperienced,
but please take good care of me, Ryuuji-san.
Arranged marriage love!
I was worried if you two would be
fine or not, since you're both so young.
Don't worry, we'll be fine.
Maybe I should give you a little treat? I wasn't able
to take my clothes off or have sex in this episode at all.
M-Mother?!
Bonk
What the hell are you doing, mom?
Why'd you hit me?
From Little Girls to
Slutty Woman...
Shatter
S-Sorry, Takuma-kun.
Sorry about that.
I'll make it up to you, so come over for dinner.
Well, you see...
Don't be so shy.
My husband's going to be home late anyway.
O-Okay.
Housewarming party!
Come in!
I'll have everything ready soon,
so just give me a second, okay?
Y-Yuuki-san, what are you wearing?!
What about it?
Oh no! Sorry, I just got out of the bath!
I-It's no problem. I didn't see much anyway.
I'm usually dressed like this whenever I'm in my room.
I'll go change now.
O-Okay.
I don't really have a robe or anything
to wear around the house.
No bra and panties?!
Just the two of us? And I'm this dose?!
Oh shit, this is the first time I've seen
a girl's butt in person! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Takuma-kun?
It's so fucking soft!
This is a married woman's ass?!
Takuma-kun, did you just turn into a beast?
Yuuki-san!
Bam
This is your fault, Yuuki-san!
It's your fault for wearing such seductive clothes!
Wait, calm yourself down!
I can't hold myself back anymore!
Boobs! Boobs!
Okay, I get it. I get it.
I'll give you a blowjob. Will you calm down after that?
Boys can't calm down until this part does, right?
We have a deal?
She's nibbling on my balls too?
Wow, it's so stiff!
It's so hard, and it's twitching a lot, too.
Did my body really turn him on that much?
Yuuki-san...
I drank all of it.
Well? Did that calm you down?
As if I'd be calm after that!
You just turned me on even more!
Okay, okay!
My, you're such a handful.
I'll play with you until you're satisfied, Mr. Animal.
Y-Yuuki-san...
Don't tell anyone about this.
Not your parents, or your friends, okay?
Okay.
Look, can you see your dick going in and out of me?
Yeah, it's so wet... I feel like I'm going to melt!
Am I really that wet? How strange.
Takuma-kun, you're fucking me so hard!
You're going to make me feel good too? You're so nice.
My hips are moving on their own!
Like that! Just like that! Shove it in just like that!
It feels so amazing!
Hey, you need to tell me when you're cumming!
How could you cum inside me?
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
It's not fair if you're the only one who feels good.
It's hitting me so deep!
I'll let you do me as many times as you want!
Just fuck me harder!
Wow, your pussy is gripping me so tightly!
It's so deep!
I feel so good! My pussy is so hot and wet,
I feel like I'm going to melt!
Yuuki-san, I think I'm going to cum again!
That's fine. I'm going to cum too! Cum wherever you want!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Oh god, it's sucking me dry!
So, do you feel satisfied now?
Y-Yes.
Thank you for the meal. It was delicious.
Also... um...
Um... sorry...
It's me, it was just a matter of time anyway.
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just got a message from my husband
saying he'll be back late tomorrow, too.
Would you like to come over for dinner again?
Starting today the neighboring young housewife
Entrance Exam Failed 2nd time
3 times
before
the day
of the
test
Should I be your tutor from now on?
If you study like your teacher tells you to,
she might teach your body some nice, naughty things.
Oh man! Hell yeah!
Entrance Exam Failed 3nd time
From Little Girls to
Slutty Woman...
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie