The tall woman wears a hat
and a white dress.
The woman peeks from above the wall,
Whoa!
saying "po po po".
Onii-chan, I'm too scared to sleep alone!
You have to sleep with me in my room, okay?
Zzz...
Zzz... Zzz...
Peek!
Onii-chan, I wonder when you will...
...mess around with me.
You even pretend to be asleep!
Rub...
Rub... Rub...
Rub... Rub... Rub...
Rub... Rub... Rub... Rub...
Rub... Rub... Rub... Rub... Rub...
Peek!
Isn't it about time to make your move?
You're making me wait too much.
Huh? You really are asleep!
I don't believe this! You're sleeping
on the same bed with your little sister!
When you're sleeping with your little sister,
check how her boobs are growing
or something!
Worry if your little sister
is keeping her hymen intact!
And then take a peek in her pussy!
Shouldn't you do that!?
Now that it turned to this, I have no choice...
...but to mess with you!
I'll start with your dick!
I need to make it hard!
Pokey-poke!
It still throbs even when you're asleep.
It feels hot...
Whoa... It grew big!
So it can get this huge...
I think this is my first time
to have a close-up look.
I wonder if this will fit in my pussy...
It twitched!
I wonder if he'll get angry at me
if he catches me licking his dick.
But there's no way for me to win
against his dick's temptations.
It really tastes weird...
Is this what they call delicious?
His dick squirms around in my mouth
when I slurp the tip.
I wonder if I woke him up.
You can come if you want to.
You can squirt it in my mouth.
Yes, it came out!
You came so much from getting
sucked by your little sister...
You're too energetic, onii-chan!
Hmm!?
Uhh...
Umm, this is...
I-It's your fault, onii-chan!
You're sleeping with your cute
little sister but won't mess with her!
You hate me now!
That's not true...
Do you love me?
Then, we'll be having creampie sex!
No, no! Siblings shouldn't have sex!
Uhh... Then won't it be fine if it's in my ass?
Here we go!
It's won't be my pussy,
so I won't have a baby and it's safe!
Isn't that right?
Oops...
O-Ouch...
It hurts, but I love you...
...so I can bear with it!
The whole thing went in...
You see, I want to make you feel good...
If you'll come inside me,
I'll be so happy!
Won't that mean that you love me
so you ejaculated inside me?
Onii-chan, feel even more pleasure!
It feels like it got hotter deep in my ass!
It feels weird!
Keep using my ass-pussy!
Your dick is making my ass
feel so much pleasure!
I'm so happy right now!
Your dick throbbed!
You're feeling good as well, right?
I'm glad!
Onii-chan, I love you! I do!
There's plenty of your sperm pouring in!
It feels like my ass will melt...
You came a lot inside my ass...
Hey, onii-chan...
Will you take my pussy's virginity as well?
Listen, sibling shouldn't have sex!
No way! I never agreed to that!
I want to have sex and bear your child though...
Futsuu? Joushiki? Mukamuka shichau!
普通？常識？ムカムカしちゃう！
Normal? Common sense? They piss me off!
demo daijoubu, shinpai shinai de, Nana wa saikyou da mon
でも大丈夫、心配しないで、那奈は最強だもん
But it's okay! Don't worry, I am the strongest!
yume mo kibou mo ai de sae mo
夢も希望も愛でさえも
As long as I have dreams, hopes, and love,
sokosoko no doryoku de norikiru no
そこそこの努力で乗り切るの
I'm gonna make it through with enough effort.
amaitsuki de yaritai koto yatte
甘いつきでやりたいことやって
I'm very optimistic and I do what I want.
akichattara tsugi o mitsukete
飽きちゃったら次を見つけて
When I get fed up, I look for the next thing.
mama no hougou to mo papa no tameiki mo wakatterutte
ママの咆号ともパパのため息もわかってるって
Mama yells at me, and papa sighs... I know!
miteru tsumori wa nai n dakara
見てるつもりはないんだから
I'm not going to see those!
Nana wa saikyou, futsuu nante tsuyoshinai
那奈は最強　普通なんて強しない
I'm the strongest. Being normal isn't strong.
warai dakya waraeba ii deshou
笑いだきゃ笑えばいいでしょう
Laugh at me if you want.
ayamattatte yurushite agenai
謝ったってゆしてあげない
Even if you apologize, I won't forgive you.
saigo ni katsu no wa Nana da mon
最後にに勝つのは那奈だもん
I'm going to win in the end.
Nana wa saikyou! Joushiki nante buttobashiteyaru!
那奈は最強！常識なんてぶっ飛ばしてやる！
I'm the strongest! I'll send that so-called common sense flying!
zenbu keikaku doori nandakara
全部計画通りなんだから！
Everything is according to my plan!
Namida datte mahou no hitotsu!
涙だって魔法の一つ
Even my tears are magic!
onii-chan wa Nana no mono
お兄ちゃんは那奈のもの
Onii-chan belongs to me.
Onii-chan, have sex with me!
I told you many times that sex is not allowed!
Don't you love me?
I love you as a man!
Didn't you already ejaculate
both in my mouth and ass?
You love me!
You definitely do!
That's why I want it in my pussy...
Put your dick inside, okay?
But...
Just a bit should be fine!
It won't be considered sex
if you won't tear my hymen!
Just the tip, you hear me?
Alright.
I can feel your dick...
Your dick is only rubbing against
the entrance of my pussy.
This should be safe.
It's only the tip but it's thick...
I want it deeper!
This is so lewd!
Your dick is rubbing against
and making my pussy tingle!
The tip of your dick is driving me crazy!
Doesn't it feel good when I do this?
Stop moving! Your hymen will get torn!
I'm only stroking it using
the entrance of my pussy!
Onii-chan, I want more!
Onii-chan, it hurts...
Sorry... I'm gonna pull it out now.
No... These are tears of joy.
That's because we managed to have sex now.
You're so adorable!
Onii-chan?
Yes, you can move a lot.
Your dick also gives me lots of pleasure.
Your dick is filling up my belly
and grinding against it inside!
Sex really does feel good, right?
I'm so happy right now!
P-Please...
Keep pounding my pussy a lot!
I can see my pussy and your dick connected!
Listen... It's my first time,
but I'm feeling good like a heroine in porn comics!
It's your fault that I became
a very lewd girl, you hear me!
It's because you're a degenerate
that ejaculates in your little sister
that I also ended up becoming this lewd!
It feels good when your dick
is poking deep inside me!
Make my whole pussy yours, onii-chan!
Fill my womb with your dick!
Onii-chan, isn't sex fun?
No... my belly feels hot!
It's squishy! Onii-chan!
Let's come together! I'm coming as well!
Your sperm is spurting into me!
My pussy completely belongs to you now!
Onii-chan, you made my pussy
for your exclusive use slimy...
I started doing it myself so they started to grow.
Being rubbed like that tickles!
Onii-chan, your finger is thick and it feels good!
Now I won't be satisfied
with masturbation anymore.
Let's have sex one more time!
Your dick went in!
My pussy is exclusively yours!
Your dick is exclusively mine as well!
That's why I'll squeeze you a lot using my pussy!
I'm already captivated by your dick, you know!
I'm craving more of your sperm
that my body is moving on its own!
Hey, kiss me!
Your dick started throbbing inside me.
You can come if you want.
Give me lots of your sperm!
I love you, onii-chan!
Listen, onii-chan...
I had a dream!
I became your wife and I gave birth
to plenty of children.
Siblings can't get married, you know.
I know that much!
That's why I'll become a president
and change the law!
We only have a prime minister in Japan though.
Huh!? Is that so?
You'll have to study when we get home...
I don't wanna study!
Bleh!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji