Say, Inagaki...
I'm happy that a cute student of mine wants to cook for me...
But you can't just come into a guy's room like this.
It'd be bad if any rumors started, right?
I wouldn't mind if it became a rumor.
Sensei, I love you!
Eh?!
My name is Shiraishi Yoichi.
I've become a teacher as I wanted to but,
because of my busy work days,
I've never had the chance to get a girlfriend.
Before I realized it, I was already over 30.
And now, I finally have a girlfriend!
Inagaki Sae,
an honor student who excels in studies and sports.
She gets embarrassed easily and is extremely shy,
so she's always been by herself in class but,
It seems somewhere along the way, she fell in love with me.
GIRL'S EDUCATION
"Inagaki Sae"
D... Don't, it'll come out!
Hey!
Hanako, stop!
This is the girl bound to the toilets of the school, Hanako-san.
She calls herself the "God of toilets" and loves pee.
She even creeps into my house sometimes.
"Toireno Hanako"
My pee power is full now!
Hanako!
I told you that it was fine to come over and play but,
I don't remember telling, you it's okay to
come in whenever you want to drink my piss.
But, but, since no one uses the school toilets on Sunday,
Hana gets low on pee power!
Listen, okay?
Directly drinking pee is forbidden.
Eh? Sensei you're so stingy!
Hanako-chan...
S-Saya-chan?
Inagaki?!
We had a promise, right?
"Inagaki Sae"
That you wouldn't come to Sensei's house this Sunday.
I let you drink my pee in return, didn't I?
It was today?
I completely forgot.
I'm sorry!
Sensei, bye bye!
I-Inagaki... This is...
Inagaki?
Sensei, you are way too kind.
I know it can't be helped because Sensei and
I are the only ones who can see Hana-chan...
But... Sensei's lover is me, not Hana-chan.
I-I'm sorry.
Sensei?
Sensei, I'll make breakfast now, okay?
Yes, thank you.
Here Sensei, breakfast's ready.
I-Inagaki?
That outfit is...
I-It's because I saw it in that porno I confiscated from Sensei before.
Sensei, you like this sort of stuff, right?
That's, you know... yeah I like it...
Since it's your birthday today.
To-Today, I'll do anything Sensei wants me to do.
Inagaki!
Sensei, not yet!
You said you'd let me do anything I want today right?
B-But...
You're being more aggressive than usual today...
W-well... Sensei has been so busy recently,
that we haven't had any sex...
I also disposed of all your porn DVDs...
Then I felt bad for you.
It's been building up, so I want to let it all out on Inagaki.
Is that ok?
Asking your student for something like
that, even though you are a teacher...
Sensei, you really are a pervert, aren't you?
It's alright, today I'll make an exception.
Thank you, Inagaki!
Is there a place you'd like me to kiss?
The place that Sensei likes...
Then...
Noo, Sensei, not there!
If you poke it that much, you'll leave a mark!
I put my mark on you to show you're all mine.
Ehh?! Don't do that!
You seem to be feeling it a lot more than usual though...
So it's been building up for you too, huh?
Y-You're wrong, I'm not perverted like you, Sensei!
And you shouldn't ask a woman if it's been building up!
What does a woman do when it builds up?
Even though I'm telling you to not ask me that...
That place... Don't!
I won't stop until you tell me.
I-I won't tell you...
No!
I touch myself imagining that it's Sensei's hand that's fingering me.
And fondling my boobs.
I smell the clothes that Sensei left me,
fantasizing about Sensei's big, hard cock.
But I was scared of putting anything other than Sensei's cock inside.
"One hour later"
But ever since I had sex, doing it with my hand just wasn't enough.
Using and sniffing someone else's properly like that...
Inagaki is an unexpectedly perverted girl isn't she?
But, ever since I had sex with Sensei, I couldn't get you out of my mind.
Don't! Hurry up and just have sex with me!
Did your first time really leave that big of an impression on you?
That reminds me, that time, it was Inagaki who started it, right?
My body is...
I asked Hana-chan and bound your feet and hands.
Inagaki!
Sensei's thing went inside me!
It's Sensei's fault, you know.
Even though we're in a relationship...
Sensei, don't you want to do dirty things with me?
Well... That's...
But as a teacher...
I want to do it with Sensei!
It's alright since we're lovers!
I will do all the work.
I want to make Sensei feel good!
"45 minutes later"
No! I'll cum again!
Even though I told you over and over again that you were a virgin.
You're wrong, I...
You're way dirtier than I am, aren't you?
That's not true.
Sensei is definitely dirtier than me.
A girl who isn't dirty, shouldn't be getting this wet.
It's not my fault, it's because Sensei kept saying dirty things,
and teased me!
Hmm? O you get off on being teased, huh?
Sensei? Why?
If Inagaki were a dirty girl then I would put it in, but...
Tell me what you'll do.
Sensei, you idiot! Dirty! Pervert!
Please teach my body about sex.
Please mess up my dirty pussy.
Well said!
To cum just by me putting it in...
Inagaki, you're a real pervert, aren't you?
B-But, Sensei's dick feels so good!
This lesson is just getting started!
Sensei's penis is... getting bigger.
Sensei's thing is making me feel real good!
Sensei please make me feel you more!
Sensei!
Having sex with Sensei feels so good!
I want to feel Sensei's dick inside me!
Se-Sensei... Sensei!
Sensei... I love you...
Sensei, you are way too energetic!
If you keep doing me from behind like a dog...
To even know how dogs do it...
As I thought, you really are a pervert, aren't you?
That's not what I mean...
Don't go in so deep!
I love you, Inagaki!
Me too, Sensei!
That's why... make a lot more love with me!
Sensei!
I love you so much... Sensei!
Good, now drink it.
Having sex in the classroom...
No, I'm cumming!
I can't anymore, at a place meant for studying...
I get excited when I think about the dirty things being done to me!
I'm going to cum!
Sensei... Today's a safe day as well, so.
Please cum inside me!
Please let me feel Sensei's semen inside my womb.
It's coming! Sensei's penis is twitching!
It's coming!
Sensei's semen... Hurry! Hurry!
My pussy! Cumming!!
Getting creampied is just the best...
Having raw sex with Inagaki always feels so damn good.
Sensei's semen feels amazing.
I can't help but be soaked in his colors!
I'm fine with bearing Sensei's baby so...
I want him to cum inside me a lot more!
And just like that, as I continued this secret relationship with my student,
Inagaki got pregnant.
The good thing is that her stomach
didn't stick out until after her graduation.
And while I got hit by Inagaki's father, he approved of our marriage.
Sensei, I think you know already but,
If you try to cheat on me, I'll blackmail you, ok?
S-Sae, I'm already...
Making your wife do something like this...
Sensei really is a pervert.
What a waste!
You shouldn't do that, you need to make
sure you give all of your semen to me.
S-Sorry.
There, I made it all clean!
Did you get excited by a little cleaning fellatio?
You're a pervert as usual.
Here you go.
I will take care of all of Sensei's sexual desires.
It's the wife's duty, after all.
I feel like I'm the one who's taking care of your sexual desires though...
Did you say something?
No, nothing at all!
It's going in so deep!
It feels way too good!
I'm about to cum!
If Sensei keeps pouring his thick cum inside me,
I'm going to get pregnant again!
You'll even get our baby pregnant!
That's horrible...
Hurry up and just let it out!
Let Sensei's semen flow inside Sae!
I'm so happy I'm Sensei's wife!
I'm cumming!!
Translator: Maq-kun
Timeer: MrMew
Editor: hikarukon & punk4real