Episode
The Heart-pounding
Photo Shoot and
The ABC's of Love
Mister! Are we really going to take photos of me like this?
That's right. Strike a pose, don't be embarrassed!
I was only asking how I'd become an idol!
Why do I have to be in this lewd swimsuit?
It's really embarrassing!
It's a gravure photo shoot; being embarrassed is normal.
Gravure? It's a lewd photo shoot, isn't it?!
Not at all!
It's every man's romantic dream.
Romance dream?
Tenka-chan, were you lying when you said you wanted to be an idol?
It's not a lie, I'm going to be an idol!
Then stick your butt out and look at the camera!
Like this?
Open your legs wider.
Wider? But if I do any more...
Stay still!
Even if you say that...
Stop it!
You can't take pictures of my butthole!
Don't worry, I can't see it.
That's a lie...
Your thighs are so sexy, Tenka-chan!
Feh? My thighs...?
Are thighs sexy?
Of course, it's gotten me this  excited!
Stop! Don't show such lewd things!
I'm like this because of you, Tenka-chan.
You have a talent as an idol!
Are you turned on because of me?
That's right.
It's an idol's job to turn on men!
Does that mean I can become an idol?
Yep! You have talent!
Really?
Really!
Okay, I'll do my best!
Mister, what should I do next?
Next, try holding onto my cock.
G-Got it...
Your cock's all hot and hard...
It's because I saw your butthole, Tenka-chan.
So you really could see...
You're the worst!
You lier! You lier! You lier!
Take this, and this!
Making me wear such a skimpy swimsuit; you're such a pervert!
Tenka-chan, if you do that much...!
What is this...? I'm all sticky...
It smells a bit...
Can I really become an idol from doing this?
Nearly there, do you think you can continue?
Yeah! I'm definitely going to become an idol!
Hey Mister, don't just keep staring at my butt...
No-! Don't give me a wedgie!
Did you get turned on from seeing my cock?
I didn't...!
Mister...!
Stop! What are you doing?
Is your finger in me?
What is this...? Eh?
Stop it, Mister! It hurts!
I told you to stop...!
Tenka-chan...
No way! You can't put it in there!
No!
It's coming in...!
My belly feels weird!
Stop it...!
Stop it already! My butt hurts!
It feels weird, pull it out!
It's... It's coming in deep!
No more... Stop! Stop it, really!
It's causing my deep spots to quiver!
Mister's let something out in me!
My belly's filling with hot stuff!
Whoopsie daisy....
I-It hurts! It hurts-!
No... I told you, it hurts...!
You're being scary, Mister!
No-!
No! No...
Please thrust slower...!
Don't just keep stimulating my nipples!
It's getting big, what's happening?
I'm scared, stop it Mister!
I told you to stop! Mister!
I can become an idol now, right...?
Mister...
What's this?
It's an ona-hole, it's used to learn about sex.
You want to have sex with Chi-chan, right?
Eh?
If you didn't like her, you wouldn't masturbate in the toilet, right?
Chi-chan... Chi-chan...!
Chi-chan!
I love you!
Komako-chan.
Should I help you out?
Really?
Yep.
So you've got to study.
By using the ona-hole.
How about you try lick it, imagining it's Chi-chan?
Chi-chan...
Chi-chan...!
Okay, hold the ona-hole up the other way.
W-Why do you have your cock out?
You put the cock in the ona-hole.
You've got to study sex and learn how to make Chi-chan feel good.
Okay.
Like this?
Yeah, push it right in there...
Try moving it slowly.
Slowly...
Mister, doesn't it hurt?
Nope.
Your cock's all hard, it's throbbing too...
It must feel good.
Uwah! Something came out!
No-!
If I imagine its Chi-chan...
It's a strange taste...
I'm feeling all floaty...
Komako-chan!
N-No!
Mister, what are you doing?
Stop! It feels gross!
Don't lick me!
My first kiss is for Chi-chan!
Stop it! Let me go!
Mister!
Geez!
Don't lick me in weird places!
No-!
Not my breasts!
It's stinging a bit...
Mister! Please, stop this!
I said you couldn't...
Aren't you going to make Chi-chan feel good?
Yeah... Chi-chan...
I want to make Chi-chan feel good.
Got it, let's study some more.
Ah, no!
Don't be mistaken! It's because I was thinking of Chi-chan, I-
No!
Not there!
Stop!
No more licking!
It stings!
No! N-Not that!
Don't put it in!
Not the cock! No, no no!
You can't-!
I said you can't!
You idiot...
You idiot, Mister!
Don't thrust into me...
Stop it!
No more! My pussy's starting to feel strange!
Your cock... I don't want to feel good from your cock, but...!
I don't want to cum from your cock, Mister...
You idiot, you idiot, idiot!
I don't want it... Even though I like Chi-chan, I'm...!
I'm starting to feel good from your cock!
Chi-chan...
Oi-chan!
Hey, Oi-chan!
We've got to go!
Mom's waiting too!
Okay okay, I'll be right over.
Eh? You're going wearing that?
Tenka-chan will be more at ease if we're as usual, no?
C'mon over, Komako-chan.
Koma-chan!
We're going to be late!
I'll keep my promise to help you get along with Chi-chan, okay?
I've won.
Whoa, another one!
Geez! Hurry up, you two!
Tenka-chan will be mad if we're late!
Number 12: Adachi Tenka.
Thank you very much!
Just like falling in love
aa renai mo sodashi
the time spent with friends is precious
tomodachi to no jikan datte taisetsu
There's no time like the present, that's why
nidoto konai kyou dakara omoikkiri
you've got to cherish every moment
tanoshimanakya mottainai
There's a dream to aspire for
akogareteru yume datte aru no
Because of you, pushing me forward
kimiga senaka wo oshite
push me forward
kureru
with your smile
sono egao de
that's why
dakara
I can become strong!
tsuyoku nareunda
I can do my best!
ganbarerunda
Chie!
Chi-chan, let's go do some radio exercise.
Okay, wait a sec!
Good morning Koma-chan, Tenka-chan!
Mom! Oi-chan!
I'm off!
Good morning!
Today's hot as usual!
Chi-chan, you can call me dad  now, you know...
It's fine!
Even if you're my dad, you'll still be Oi-chan!
Okay, we're off!
Hey! Geez...
Hey, Chi!
Chi-chan's going to be the first!
Everyone shouts the winner lots of candy, okay?
Wha-? What are you talking about?
Wait!
No karaoke? As expected of Shitkakku - Shikkaku fansubs