Hey there, Mr. Single Guy's Fantasy.
You like these kinds of panties don't you, Kuroda-san?
H-H-Hey, you shouldn't tease adults like that.
Hey!
I saw your "Single Guy's Fantasies" Blog.
Single Guy's Fantasies Blog
Theme: Blog
If I show you a little cleavage like this,
you'll fap to it later, won't you?
Th-That's enough!
I-If you keep acting like this, I'm going home!
Even though you're rock solid?
Don't you wanna try out all of the things
you fantasized about with me?
N-No, I can't.
Kyouka-san would...
You think you can just say my mom's name and run away...
Kazu-kun?
From Little Girls to Slutty Women...
Wha...
Why do you know that name, Asumi-chan?
To Shiroi-san
Every time you say my name, my heart gets
all fuzzy and starts beating furiously.
My love letter?!
Looks like your instincts are starting to kick in.
W-Well, um...
Look, your thing is knocking on my door.
I feel like I have to pee now.
So how about it?
Wanna try doing the things you blogged about?
Wow, you're really drinking it!
Try not to make a mess, okay, Kazu-kun?
I must say, we're really suited for one another, aren't we?
We're both such big perverts after all.
You kept updating your blog, hoping that
this would someday happen to you, right?
Poor little Kazu-kun.
I'm the same though.
I want to do these dirty things in the
flesh, not just read about them.
Just reading about naughty
things gets me really homy.
Actually getting to do them makes me so happy!
You were trying so hard to hold it in,
but in the end, you blew it.
Asumi-chan, we should really stop here...
Stop here?
You say that, but deep down,
you just want to do even more, don't you?
Oh my god, it's so much bigger than I expected!
I don't even know if it'll fit!
Asumi-chan...
It's so tight...
It feels so good!
I put it all inside me.
Every time your cock thrusts into me,
it molds its shape into my pussy!
Mama
Wait, this sound...
Sorry, Asumi. There's something I needed to ask you.
Y-Yeah, what's up?
So, about the break that's coming up...
Do you want to go out for
dinner with Kuroda-san again?
Huh? Uh, yeah, that sounds good.
Oh, great.
I'll call him right now then.
I wonder if he's at work...
Call
from
Kyouka
Oh, hello? Kuroda-kun?
Hello? Are you there?
H-Hello, Kyouka-san!
Hello, Kuroda-kun?
Are you okay?
S-Sorry, I'm a bit... busy right now.
What's the matter? Are you okay?
I feel...
You feel?
I am putting all of my feelings
lnto my work right now.
Oh, sorry to bother you when you're at work.
I'll call you back later, okay?
Kyouka-san...
Crap, I'm gonna cum!
I guess I called at a bad time.
I'll call back later.
I'm going back to work now, okay?
All right... Bye, Mom!
Asumi-chan!
Now, you've done it!
You're always teasing me, but...
Does having your tiny pussy reamed by
my huge adult cock really feel that good?
Oh my god, it feels so amazing!
I'm so happy, Kazu-kun!
You've made a lot of progress for a guy
who just fantasizes about sex all the time!
I love feeling your cum swish around and mix
with my love nectar! It feels so amazing!
Don't call me Kazu-kun!
No, I'll keep calling you that because
I want you to love me like you love Mom!
Kazu-kun... Kazu-kun! Kazu-kun!
Kazu-kun?
This position is so embarrassing.
You think you can play around with
an adult when you're just a child?
Well fine! I'm gonna play the hell out of your body!
Yes, do it! Play with me to your heart's desire!
Your tight pussy's squeezing my cock so hard!
It's going all the way into my womb!
You fucking slut!
I'm gonna flood your pussy with my baby batter!
Oh god, there's so much!
Crap, I'm so sorry, Asumi-chan!
You're such a fun guy, Kazu-kun.
After that, the three of us met up periodically.
Oh, excuse me...
I'm not wearing any panties today <3
I'm not wearing any panties today!
But my relationship with Asumi-chan...
I feel like I'll be seeing a lot more of her.
Call from a Slutty Woman
I can't do it!
I can't believe I can't type whatever
I want into my blog anymore!
I can't take this anymore!
I definitely won't have sex
with Asumi-chan anymore!
Tomorrow? Yeah, I'm free.
I have work off.
Huh? You wanna use my computer?
You need to use Winger? Yeah, yeah, no problem!
From little girls to slutty women.
Um, could you do me a little favor?
Could you show me your penis?
Hello?
You really came.
Thanks.
Is that all manga?
Are you an otaku, Amamiya?
Y-Yeah.
I know it's sudden, but don't judge me, okay?
What's this?
What the hell is this?!
That's one I drew.
Are you serious?
You drew this?
Glisten
I want to be a manga artist, so I've been doing
this kind of work to earn some money.
So, why do you wanna see my dick?
I've never seen one before, so I can't really draw one.
Sh-Should I not have asked?
Well, as long as it's fine with you...
Th-Th-Thanks...
So this is what they look like...
I'm looking at the real thing.
But guys have a way to make it bigger, don't they?
Hey, while we're at it, do you wanna
see what it looks like when it's hard?
If you wanna see it get big, I'll need your help.
Wait, do I really need to touch it?
Gently hold it and stroke it up and down.
It's starting to swell up.
Wow, it really did get bigger!
So if I keep going like this,
you'll cum on my face, right?
Your hands are so soft and smooth...
It feels so good!
It has a really interesting scent to it.
My bad, I got my jizz all over your clothes.
Hey, what are you...
You better throw it in the washer fast, or it'll stain!
Wh-Why are you taking off all my clothes?
It's not fair that I'm the only one who
has to do something embarrassing.
Why don't you try licking it.
What?
I think it'll be some good experience for your manga.
I-If it's for my manga, then...
Like this?
Lick up all the jizz.
It tastes so strange.
Lick my balls as well.
Shit, this feels good!
My nipples!
Ero manga have these kinds of scenes, don't they?
No... I can't... No!
What?
It feels totally different than when I do it myself!
It feels so good... I can feel my body losing strength!
Huh? You don't need any more blow job pictures?
No, I can't muster up any strength!
All right. Then I'll get some good
reference shots for you down here.
I don't need any of myself!
Don't take any pictures!
Just take a look.
Your pussy's so fucking wet right now.
Don't you wanna try it out for the sake of your manga?
I won't do anything you don't want.
Oh, you were a virgin?
It's for the manga, so it's fine.
I want to be able to draw
the pain and everything perfectly.
Wow, my stomach is being stirred up so violently!
Sorry, I can't help myself
when your pussy's so damn tight!
It's fine.
Slimy stuff is starting to flow out of me!
The pain's fading away,
and it's starting to feel really good!
It feels so good when you rub
my boobs while fucking me!
I feel like I'm going to melt!
No! No!
I'm going to lose my mind!
It feels so good! So good!
It's so warm... So this is sex?
Amamiya?
Hey, Sawamura-kun, let's do it again.
I need to get a lot of reference pictures of sex!
Hey, wait!
It feels even better than before!
Look at how big your dick is!
Look at how naughty it is!
You're enjoying this too much!
If I capture this on camera,
I'll be able to draw the greatest ero manga ever!
Stick out your tongue.
Shit, her pussy is so amazing.
This feels so fucking good.
I can't stop plowing her.
My pussy feels so good!
I feel like my mind's gonna fly away!
Amamiya, I'm gonna cum again!
That's fine, just cum inside!
Let me capture the moment you cum in me!
I can feel your hot stuff flowing into me!
I need to take a picture of my orgasm face!
I also need to take one of the cum dripping out of me!
Look
how much
you come.
What the hell? This is exactly
what we did, scene-for-scene!
Forget about that,
I need more material for my manga.
Can you help me?
Excited by Reference Materials.
You need another person's help
for what you're going to draw next?
Does that mean you're going
to do this with another guy?
No, not exactly...
So does that mean she brought
another girl in for a threesome?
In that case...
H-Hey, wait!
– Sorry, I got asked to draw some yaoi too.
– Get the fuck off me, you piece of shit!
– Get off!
– Stop! No!
From little girls to slutty ones.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: cockslider
quality conrtol: fyurie