Oi-chan's
Candy Store
Oi-chan, look at me!
Tada! Do I look cute in this yukata dress?
It's very cute.
Mom bought it for me!
I can't wait for the festival!
It's going to be fun.
Yeah! I'm going with Tenka-chan and Koma-chan.
Are you going to the festival as well?
Um,
I'll be helping a stall, so a little bit I guess.
Oh really?
Gimme pocket money!
Oh what should I do...?
Oh, your cock...
It's gotten hard.
Oi-chan, you pervert.
It's because you're too cute, Chi-chan.
Jeez, you perv!
Do you hate cock?
I don't hate it, but...
Ah, we can't do it now!
You're not wearing panties?
Yeah...
Don't touch there!
Why?
Because...
You've gotten all wet.
When I'm with you my crotch gets wet and sticky,
and my chest becomes sensitive as well.
Is that weird?
Not at all.
People are made to get aroused when they're with those they love.
Really?
Shikkaku Fansubs
Episode
Yukata Dresses and Fireworks
at a Summer Festival
Oi-chan...?
Ouch!
Why did you tie my wrists together?
I can't move!
What are we going to do on this deck?
That tickles! Don't lick me so much!
No! Don't put your finger in there!
N-No! Don't lick my breasts!
Oi-chan, please untie me!
Someone's gonna hear us out here!
If we're quiet, it's fine.
Eh? It's not possible...
I can't hold my voice!
It's hitting me so deep... You're being a bit rough...!
Your cock feels amazing!
This feels too good, I'm...
It's going to make me feel all weird!
No... No...!
It feels too good there!
Please stop!
I'm feeling all floaty, I'm scared!
Your cock has gotten bigger inside me!
I-I can't hold it back!
Oi-chan! Oi-chan, Oi-chan!
Oi-chan, I'm gonna get pocket money now, right?
Oji-san, this is bad!
No one is here.
I've promised Komako and the others to visit the festival together...
Komako-chan's going to confess to Chi-chan, apparently.
Eh-? Really?
Not so deep!
You mustn't disturb them.
I won't, I promise I won't!
Stop this, stop it!
I'm gonna cum!
Jeez! You made me wet myself!
You're the worst! What would you do if someone saw us?!
Everyone's off to see the fireworks, so no one's around here.
We shouldn't, even if no ones here!
Even though you protest, you actually want it, right?
Wha?! What are you saying?
Hey wait, stop!
Why are we like this?!
See? It went in easily.
You're the worst! Pull it out!
I don't want to have sex-
Don't thrust it inside me!
Let me go! Your cock's too big!
We shouldn't be doing this...
You're being rough!
This position is embarrassing!
Why are you thrusting harder, jeez!
It's going to make me feel weird!
I-It hurts! It's so deep!
I-It's hitting me so deep!
S-Stop it!
I said I didn't want forceful sex...!
Let me go already...
Pull it out! Don't get bigger inside me!
You came inside me again...
What should I do if I get pregnant...?
Koma-chan, can we really see the fireworks from here?
Yeah, Oji-san said it was right about here.
Oh really? I hope we can see it soon.
Chi-chan...
Yeah?
Do you like me?
Of course.
Why's that?
I like you too, Chi-chan.
Guess it's mutual?
Can I kiss you?
What's up?
Can't I?
I didn't say you couldn't...
Koma-chan, this is a bit weird.
It's not weird since we like each other.
So, we can have sex...
Right...?
Koma-chan...?
Are we gonna have sex?
I studied a lot, so it's fine.
Koma-chan, that tickles...
Your breasts are cute.
Not the nipples!
Do it to me now, okay?
If you suck my nipples that much, I'm...!
Chi-chan, you're cute like a baby!
Chi-chan, let's feel good together!
Chi-chan, I love you! You're the best!
Don't lick me there!
Koma-chan, you're being so lewd!
Chi-chan, lick me too.
Okay...
Your pussy's making sticky wet sounds Chi-chan!
So cute.
Koma-chan, that's too much!
Chi-chan...
Let's do it again.
I'm connected with Chi-chan!
You're right, it's like we're having sex!
Koma-chan!
Koma-chan, this feels so good!
Guess we missed the fireworks.
Are you angry?
Nope! I had lots of fun getting to know you better, Koma-chan.
Chi-chan...
I like you.
I like you too.
POMF POMF! - Shikkaku Fansubs