www.SubDESU-H.net
Somewhere below the Tenjou Mansion,
in a quiet, secluded forest,
lies a secret hot springs cave.
These girls...
were all waiting there.
The eldest is
hot, voluptuous, Aya-neesan.
These other girls are Mitsuba, Yotsuba and finally, Futaba.
Three angelically innocent sisters.
And finally my childhood friend, Matsuriko.
The girls and I,
continued to spend that time...
... in a nightlong, ecstatic, orgy.
This long night...
is still far from over.
W
Act 1 "Matsuriko"
It's been almost seven years...
since I was here last.
Nii-sama,
Mother has passed away.
I have broken all ties with that House.
Please, Nii-sama!
Come back!
Right now,
Father is totally...
Nii-sama, you are the only one left for us...
Please save us!
W-welcome home Nii-sama!
Welcome home.
I wanted to see you!
I'm glad you all look well.
Kengo, it's because you came home.
Aya-Neesan!
We now only have Kengo left to rely upon.
I really missed you.
It's good to be home.
D-drink what I brewed next!
Mine too!
Here you go.
You lucky...
Mine next!
No, mine next!
These girls were actually daughters of the concubines my father had kept over the years.
Of course since we were raised together I thought of them as my siblings.
Oh?
Wow..
So, there was a fireworks display tonight?
Here,
Aya-nee, over here.
N-no!
I'm sorry, o-outside, I just can't....
I'm sorry, too.
Being children born out of wedlock...
the girls were never allowed to leave the mansion walls.
They'd learned to fear
any unfamiliar view.
This all happened,
because of one man.
It was all my father's fault.
For God's sake,
please release the girls!
I have not laid a finger on my daughters.
Though if you wish it...
they are yours to do with as you please.
You're disgusting!
All of this is the fruit of your insatiable lust!
Have the years so sharpened your tongue, Kengo?
Because I frightened him seven years ago,
this idiot ran away from this house.
Shoujo x Shoujo x Shoujo
Nii-sama.
Matsuriko.
It's been a long time.
Nii-sama,
would you be kind enough to take a walk with me?
I didn't know...
there was a hot spring under the mansion.
I'm sorry, Matsuriko.
Even though I've come home, I don't think I can save all of you.
Matsuriko.
N-Nii-sama!
Just you coming home,
makes me happy!
Since Nii-sama disappeared, I..
was really worried.
I'm sorry.
Nii-sama.
We want you to hear our one request.
Request?
You'll know soon.
First,
please rest your body in the hot bath.
I will take care of your clothes.
N-Nii-sama?
T-this is...
I-I'm sorry.
It's alright.
But,
as we go further in, please keep your voice to a minimum,
for this is a sacred place.
Sacred?
Go ahead, inside.
It's not just a plain hot spring?
O-ohh!
Female bath!?
S-Sorry!
Ehh?
A... Aya-nee.
This is...
A-Aya...
I, who had never till now been intimate with a woman,
had my senses and reasoning blown away with that one kiss alone.
This is a SubDESU-H release, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
It's jolting me, Kengo's....
It's really hard and hot, rubbing against me.
It's still so hard.
It's e-embarrassing but...
It's writhing all around inside me.
Spread open so wide...
I'm embarrassed!
N-No, if he keeps touching me that way, I'm going to go crazy!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
Kengo's...
P... Put it in.
I-It's in! It's all in!
Kengo's... So amazing...
Aya-nee's cunny...
Hot like, enough to melt me.
So tight.
I almost came just putting it in.
It felt so good.
The girls have no entertainment.
Confined for as long as they can remember...
helplessly hungry for men.
That's why, to answer their lust,
I thoroughly tasted their insides.
Unable to think anymore,
I pounded into Aya-nee,
into her raw and sensitive parts.
The sensation of the rough and slippery rubbing...
put me in an irresistible trance.
Inflaming Aya-nee from inside...
Giving her climax after climax...
From the moment I rammed my cock into Aya nee's hole,
I felt I would never stop coming inside her.
Aya-nee!
That day,
my sexual desire...
did not know how to dwindle.
The long night...
had just begun.
Shoujo x Shoujo x Shoujo
Nii-sama leaves the House of Tenjou.
Help! Please help me!
Oh, my.
This late at night...
Who's child are you?
T-Tenjou's...
Tenjou?
You must be...
The daughter of one of Tenjou-san's concubines?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm called Aya.
So, you're Aya.
It's safe now.
This old man will take care of everything.
Yes!
Stupid daughter!
You!!
Why did you help my daughter escape?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Sorry!
You stupid idiot!
Konda no Oyaji: "Konda's Father", traditional oriental form of address.
Thanks for telling me about this, Konda no Oyaji.
Oh, it's fine, it's fine..
I don't give a two bit shit about a concubine's daughter but...
That day,
my sexual desire...
did not know how to dwindle.
The girls...
were a bit shy as well.
But, as they gazed...
on my hardened cock,
their interests were piqued.
This is Nii-sama's...
It's gotten so large.
After Nii-sama and Aya-nee it's all sticky.
Amazing. Such a sexy smell.
The girls could do even this much,
only because they had seen what Aya-nee had done.
It's so hard.
As I continue to lick Nii-sama,
I am starting to feel a bit weird as well.
So much thick soup is pouring out from the tip.
Futaba.
Nii-sama, is that warm white stuff going to come out?
It's okay, I want it all inside my mouth.
Lots of white stuff!
Lots!
So much spurting!
The hot stuff is going down my throat.
Smells just like Nii-sama.
Still unsatisfied,
one by one I embraced the girls.
Nii-sama please, put it inside me too!
Nii-sama, it h-hurts but, it feels so good!
Nii-sama's white stuff is slippery inside me and it's amazing!
Amazing! What is this sensation?
The inside of my head is going wild! Yes... I am cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Mitsuba.
Nii-sama, that's, embarrassing.
It's embarrassing! No!
Nii-sama is licking me.
My shameful parts are slurping!
Don't look.
That's Nii-sama's...
I feel it.
Amazing, I feel like he's turning me inside out.
I'm going to break, but it feels so good.
More, more!
Nii-sama,
can you see all my embarrassing parts?
I'm losing control!
No, it feels so good I'm going crazy!
Nii-sama is filling me up!
It's reaching my womb.
Something is coming... What? What?
I-I'm going to...! I'm cumming!
Cumming!
Matsuriko.
Nii-sama...
This long night,
was still far from over.
www.SubDESU-H.net