Sensei, you can't move!
It still feels really tingly!
Oh, what are you doing, sensei?
Asamiya?
You can't be getting hard because
of your student, can you? How shameful!
You guys set me up?!
Sensei, it feels so good! Please, get even harder!
Sensei, it doesn't feel tingly anymore. Now it just feels hot.
Sensei! Sensei!
It's fine, I want more!
I want something even better, so get harder!
I'm surprised the drug had
this much of an effect on Miyako.
This is even better than I expected!
Sensei! Sensei!
– Sensei, your dick is starting to twitch.
Could it be that you're about to ejaculate?
– Sensei!
– Is the drug really that strong?
Wow, look at all that cum!
There's still more coming out!
Oh? It looks like you're still full of energy.
Unless you use this antidote,
the aphrodisiac won't wear off.
A-An antidote?! Hurry up and give it to me!
Wait, what are you doing, Asamiya?!
Calm down, sensei. I never said that I'd give it to you.
Look at what happened to our legs.
Why don't you suck the antidote off of us?
You look just like a baby.
I'm at school, but the feeling of her tights
is spreading across my tongue as I lick.
I can't help it, I'm getting so turned on!
It's because of the antidote!
It's because I haven't had enough of the antidote yet.
I need to suck harder!
Hard enough to get every last drop out of their tights!
I have to get in between her toes,
under her nails... my tongue needs to be there!
I have to take care of the lovely fabric
wrapped around their young, soft skin.
I'm violating their scent on this heavenly
garment with the lapping of my tongue!
How does it taste? Do the feet
of your beloved students taste good?
Sensei, you're just like a baby!
I'm supposed to be getting better,
but it's only turning me on even more!
Oh my, it seems like you're a failure
as a teacher, and also as a man.
You're basically nothing more than a dog in heat.
Even now, you're trying your best to mark
your students with your pre-cum.
Is there anything more pitiful than this?
Look. I'm going to play with your dick with my calves.
Cover your student in the disgraceful cum you've stored up!
I can tell that the warm cum from your
naughty dick is soaking into my tights.
What a pitiful expression you're wearing.
It seems you haven't had enough.
Sensei, you're bright red.
Urn, this is kind of... embarrassing...
Go on, then. You have two pussies
ripe for the fucking. Take your pick.
In front of me are my students' dripping wet virgin pussies.
Can't you see just how wet they've gotten?
They're practically begging for your dick, sensei.
Your beloved students got wet just for you, sensei.
They're waiting for you now.
You can't just ignore them like that, can you?
There, there. Good boy.
Both of them are virgins.
You need to make sure you're as wet as can be.
Y-Yeah, that's true, but...
If you're going to make me that wet,
I'll cum from your hand!
Oh? It looks like you're in pain.
This is for the sake of the students you love so much.
Can't you restrain yourself for their sake?
Please, I'm begging you, let me put it in them!
Shouldn't you be asking them, and not me?
Fujieda, please, let me put it in you!
I want you to let me cum with your virgin pussy!
Okay! Please, use it as you wish.
Sensei's dick went inside me!
Sorry, Fujieda.
Huh?
Your pussy just feels too good, I...
I can't stop!
I... Your dick feels so good!
Sensei, aren't you too focused on pleasuring Miyako?
Can't you see how lonely Isuzu looks?
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry. You're my precious student as well.
I'll love you all equally.
I'll use my dick to turn you into a woman as well.
It's going in! Sensei's dick is...
Sensei's dick is throbbing inside me!
Oh my god, it's so hot!
Sensei, please make sure you take
really good care of the both of them.
Of course I will.
I'll make sure to fuck the two of you evenly!
Sensei, which pussy do you like more?
Fujieda's pussy is wrapping around me so tightly,
like it doesn't want to let go.
Every time I move I feel like I'm going to bust my hip!
Yamamoto's pussy is small and narrow,
so all I have to do is put my dick in,
and it'll squeeze like nothing else!
Sensei!
Sensei! Please cum inside me!
Hey, no fair! He's going to cum inside me!
You're going to make me choose?
You have quite the admirable relationship
with your students. Isn't that wonderful?
I'm here to witness your instinctual,
primal urges on your students.
I'm going to pour my seed deep into both of your wombs!
O-Okay!
Sensei!
– Please plant your seed in me!
There's so much!
He's still cumming!
That made for a great video, did it not?
Yes it did!
I was able to capture it perfectly on camera!
Y-You!
How careless, sensei.
You should know that our club has four members in it.
This was just too erotic! It was too stimulating!
Sensei, please take responsibility for that, okay?
Boobs are only boobs if you can put
stuff between them. Don't you think?
See? Your dick looks so happy!
Fine, whatever. Suzuka's fine with kissing this dick anyway.
You're a good girl. I'm going to shoot
out my cum into your dirty mouth.
Drink it up, Suzuka!
You came so much for me!
Saori?
Prez?
Sensei, could you come here for a sec?
Wait, what are you doing?
Saori, don't you like him too?
Wh-What are you...
I don't like him... at all...
Don't worry, Suzuka will record
every detail of your first time!
Huh? Wait, no, don...
Huh? What's this? Are your nipples inverted?
Here you go sensei. Have a feel.
Thank you!
D-Don't!
Your nipples are really shy, Asamiya.
There we go. All it needed was a little encouragement.
Y-You're being stupid!
No, don't! Stop!
Stop! Don't suck...
Isuzu, don't put your tongue insi... Stop!
Inverted nipples smell so good!
Your face is already full of ecstasy!
Here it goes.
Take it off!
Okay, please put it inside her now.
Wait! Wait!
You three, is this your idea of a prank?
You can still redeem yourselves!
We're prepared for any punishment.
That said, how about we start, Prez?
It's time to become sensei's woman, okay?
No! Stop! I'm telling you to stop! Listen to me!
Stop! Please, please stop!
Asamiya...
Sensei?
Sensei, do you know about my family circumstances?
I don't know anything.
All I know is that right now, I want you.
Is that not enough?
Sensei, it's hard to see her losing her virginity!
Well then, everyone gather around!
No!
Is it easier to see now?
H-Hey, what are you doing, you idiot? You can't...
Asamiya, now that we're doing it doggy style,
your pussy's getting really tight.
No, I'm going to cum again!
It feels so good! Your dick feels so good, sensei!
Sensei?
Sensei!
What should we play next?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч