Hey… Onee-sama,
Want to invite Usa-nee
and Pen-kichi out to ice cream?
Sorry…
I want to go, but I have to study.
I didn’t score well on our last midterms…
Study, eh? I guess there's no helping it.
Haruto Onee-sama sure is lucky to have a private tutor.
Compared to that…
Jeez, that stupid tutor!
Shit.
I’ll make that jerk quit if it’s the last thing I do!
Idiot.
That jerk… getting to cocky…
And thinking of the strangest “Punishment Games.”
Shoukoujo, The Animation
W
Virgin 2: Perverted Experience with my Tutor
Rin and the jerk
I apologize about that.
I’m sorry I haven’t been able to help much.
I’m sorry, too. Sorry to bother you when you’re so busy.
Oh, fine. I’ll just do it.
It’s a punishment game, so I’ll endure it for you.
Wh-What is this thing?
How does it vibrate like that?
No…
It’s whirling so much…
It’s much more intense… than I thought…
Excuse me, sorry for the wait.
Is something wrong, Rin?
Eh? N-Nothing!
Ohhh, you’re a strange little girl.
Now, Sensei, please partake before it cools down.
Okay, thank you.
Itadakimasu.
What the hell?
Easily acting like that…
I can endure this just fine.
I won’t become your bitch!
It’s suddenly so… strong…
Whirling so much… I’m gonna lose my mind!
Which is it, Rin-chan?
Yes.
You wanna pee, right?
This is our game.
I’m competing against my tutor.
The rules are simple: Whoever wins gets the other person to do
whatever he or she wants.
If I score 100% on my next test, he’ll quit being my teacher.
But if he wins…
You want me to put this on?
That’s not right, Rin.
You have to do exactly as I said.
Now, punishment game time.
Rin…wants a cock…
Please give it to Rin…
See, you can do it?
Okay, Rin-chan, let’s put on your diaper.
No!
Ohhhh, Rin-chan, your pussy is all wet.
Are you aroused?
No, I’m not.
Come on.
Your diapers… before you put it on… gotta make you all clean.
No… no…
Stop it!
Oh, there it is, Rin-chan.
Look at what you’ve got going on there.
You’re still so small, yet you released all this wetness.
Bad girl.
N-No…
Pervert!
What’re you…
This is where pee comes from.
I don’t wanna do this!
Don’t worry. After it feels good, you can piss yourself if you want.
No! Why do I have to be embarrassed like this?
This is unfair!
This is why I put a diaper on you.
Well then, Sensei, sorry to put this on you, but I really appreciate it.
Okay, I’m fine with it, ma’am.
Rin?
You need to study hard.
I know that.
M…Mom… hurry, please leave.
Hurry… put me at ease…
Oh dear, Rin-chan.
You pissed yourself already?
No… I can’t stop it…
Jesus, you’re pissing right through your diaper.
That’s quite a bit.
What a nice smell.
Idiot!
Don’t smell it.
Stop it. Stop it now!
Wow, lots of pee came out.
Pissing yourself is so embarrassing.
Rin-chan.
Well~, before I change your diaper,
Let’s make you all clean.
Don’t suck on it!
It’s embarrassing.
Please… let me go!
Not again?
No!
I can’t stop it.
A lady is peeing herself in her doorway?
We need to punish her.
Pervert!
Putting it in the normal way is no fun.
Idiot!
Idiot, hey…!
See? Don’t scream so loud.
Or the neighbors will all know what a slut you are.
Idiot. They really can see us.
This is gross… I don’t like it… so why?
Idiot… don’t say strange things.
I’m not a slut!
Oh really?
In that case…
I’m sorry I called you one.
Why are you stopping?
Well, you don’t like it, right?
Then we’ll end things here.
Go back up to your room, and continue studying.
Stopping it right now? I’ll…
Did you say something?
Never mind, just continue!
Come on.
Hurry
Hurry, finish yourself off.
Beg.
If you want me to continue, then beg for it.
Bu… But I can’t…
Then, maybe I’ll stop.
Rin is… a slutty young lady.
Say it louder.
I want your cock. I want my pussy messed up.
With your fat… cock… shove it in my young pussy…
Mess it up…
Swirl it all around…
Please fuck me to death!
That was very well said.
N-Not there!
If you hit so hard… no!
See? Your boobs need to get bigger… so I’ll massage them for you.
Th… That’s not true…
Don’t squeeze… so hard…
In this position, everyone can see your pussy, Rin.
No!
Stop it, I’m telling you!
I don’t want…
Don’t look at me!
No!
It’s all over…
Just a bit more.
Just a bit more, okay?
I don’t like this…
I’m losing my mind!
Jerk!
Fuck him, fuck him, fuck him!
There!
Jeez!
Now you’ve made me remember!
Jerk!
I might like him
Tiny dick
But… Rin is pretty amazing.
Despite everything, she’s studying well and raising her grades.
How can you say that?
Haruto Onee-sama, you’ve had a tutor for a while.
And your grades are better than mine.
And you’re also cool!
Cool… huh?
I think I feel like ditching. I didn’t do too well on my last test.
Yes… I'll continue to have a tutor…
But he’s teaching me something not related to school…
Haruto and Sensei
Haruka.
Will you suck my dick?
No?
Sure. If you want me to, I’ll give it a try.
Very good girl.
The tip has stuff flowing out of it.
Suck it in your mouth.
Ye-Yes.
Swallow more in.
Doing this makes me taste his flavor even more.
Haruka, what are you doing?
Try saying it.
I am… doing… fellatio…
That was close.
But I can’t give you a perfect score for that.
Student number 001
Nanasaki Haruka
(Midterm Test)
Subject       Score     1     2     3     4     5
Masturbation  40                                    x
Fellatio
Standing
Vibrator
Umm…
Sensei, put your thick cock in my mouth…
Let my mouth be your pussy.
Very well done.
Yes, yes, that’s right.
Sensei… he’s enjoying it.
His dick is getting harder.
He’s getting aroused… in my mouth.
Amazing!
It’s so hot and throbbing.
I’m almost there.
Sensei…
Cum, cum, Sensei.
Haruka… Haruka…
Sensei’s dick-juice… all over my face.
It’s a part of Sensei.
Look, Haruka.
If Sensei wants to, I’ll do anything for him.
Now, smell it plenty before licking it clean.
Okay.
I…
Oh, Sensei.
I feel embarrassed… but I’ll do anything slutty for him.
Highlighted word: Fellatio
Good.
Yes. Sensei’s tests are divided up into specifics like that.
And I’m doing my best on them.
Pee is coming out.
Because I’m drunk, because I’m drunnnnnk!
Ahhh, it’s a pretty boy.
You wanna pee with me?
Niiiice.
He hasn’t noticed, has he?
If he notices I’m a girl, he’ll do something gross to me.
Pee standing up?
But that’s something a man does.
Yes.
If you can do it unnoticed, you’ll get 100%.
But I…
If you’re noticed, 0%.
Plus… you might be assaulted a little
Please… don’t watch. Keep looking that way.
Hey, kid… your dick is so small.
Woah? No reason to hide it.
Go ahead and pee. Come on.
Sure…
It’s coming out.
Wh-What the hell?
Just pee straight!
So-Sorry!
Oh no. Everything’s getting all wet.
I mean, I can’t pee standing up… I’m a girl!
Oh no… I…
Hey!
Cut it out already!
Girl…?
I should’ve known.
That’s’ why your dick is small.
No… I’m a bo-boy…
I…
Hey.
Still not done yet?
Se-Sensei!
Sorry about that, but you get a zero on Standing.
Signs: Caution, wet floor
Consider yourself lucky you weren’t assaulted by that drunk.
Sensei.
I can’t…
You want it, right?
Here’s your final test of the day.
Show me your pussy.
I’ll give you a dick and turn you into a man.
Sensei.
Come on.
You need to relax more or it won’t go all the way in.
Okay.
See? Now you’re a man, Haruka.
I have a dick…
It’s so big… and slippery.
Now that we’re both men, let’s bump dicks.
Sensei…
What the hell?
I’m stroking Sensei’s dick and he’s stroking my dick… my pussy?
Is this male mutual masturbation?
Dick… bumping… stroking…
My head is… whirling around!
Come on. There’s something you want to say, right?
What do you want me to do to you?
I want you to… give me the butt test…
Very well done.
This feels a little strange, but it also feels good.
It feels good to me too.
Sensei… we’re connected, aren’t we?
Come on, stroke harder.
Okay.
It’s so… dirty… putting your dick… in my butt… it’s throbbing…
Yes, it’s throbbing!
Haruka… I’m cumming.
Good. Then cum. Cum.
I’m cumming… from this… too… oh no…
Good.
I’ll take back your zero.
Texts: Open, Compose, Menu
Then, would you like to cheer up by inviting Usa-nee and Pen-kichi out
to ice cream?
They just put up a great shop by the station.
Sorry, but I have to study.
I didn’t do well on my last midterm.
Hey. Still not ready?
I’m sorry!
I’m coming!
Now, Haruka.
Let’s start to study.
Okay.
Sensei can only love me this way… but I love him.