I thought the rain would stop quickly, but...
Komako-chan, aren't you feeling cold?
Yeah.
Mister,
well...
Thank you.
Eh? What's wrong all of a sudden?
It's all thanks to you, that Chi-chan and I were able to have sex.
So it all went well, huh?
Chi-chan was happy, too.
I see.
You sure did your homework well.
Homework?
I guess you could put it that way.
Mister,
do you want me to do something for you as thanks?
As thanks?
You're thinking of something dirty again, aren't you?
It seems I can't hide it from you.
Pull out your dick.
Is it okay?
Because you're a pervert,
pleasuring your dick will make you real happy, right?
Just for today, though.
Thank you very much.
It's already this big.
Don't just move on your own, okay?
Your thing is so hard and stiff.
Did you know,
that this is what it means to be a lolicon?
Let me cum soon.
'Kay.
Mister, you came too much.
You've gotten good, Komako-chan.
It's all thanks to the pervert standing before me.
Sorry.
Lie down over there, mister.
You won't be satisfied until you have sex, right?
Komako-chan...
Don't move.
Your dick is so big.
Don't you dare move.
This pleasurable thing is sloshing up and down inside me.
How is it, mister?
Does it feel good?
Your dick feels so stiff,
and I can feel it filling me up inside.
It's twitching.
Are you about to cum?
Looks like I still need to pleasure it a bit more.
It's rubbing really hard.
Really, really, hard.
Your dick is prying open my insides.
So good...
I said don't move!
I'll do all the hard work.
Please stop.
Oh, come on!
If you're going to cum, then go ahead!
It's making sloshing noises, that's why I don't want you to do it.
My spine feels all tingly.
Please don't push too hard.
Just cum already.
Let it all out!
Finish it!
Your dick is bulging so much inside.
It's coming out.
It's pumping deep into my pussy.
Your cum feels so sticky.
Thanks.
Mister...
Mister,
why am I naked?
My teachers will get angry if they see us here.
It's summer vacation, so nobody's here.
We can't do this here.
Don't worry.
This is embarrassing.
Why?
Because it feels weird being naked at school.
Let's go home already.
Maybe we will. Maybe we won't.
Mister!
My hands are tied, then.
We'll go home, but only if you masturbate.
You want me to masturbate... here?
You can do it since I already taught you, right?
Yeah, but...
Somebody might come if you don't hurry.
We'll go home after I do it, okay?
Promise me.
I shouldn't be doing this, and yet...
Mister, is this okay?
You have to cum.
I can't soil the desk like this.
My teachers will get mad.
It'll feel too good if I continue doing this.
Mister, it's coming!
An amazing sensation is coming!
Mister, let's go home already.
I'm going home with a very selfish girl,
Chi-chan's such a bad girl.
You said we'd go home after I masturbate...
I want you to pleasure me as well, okay?
That place is forbidden!
It... it hurts!
This feels kinda gross.
Mister, I don't think it'll fit in my butt.
It's sloppily making its way inside!
My butt is starting to feel weird.
Please don't move.
It hurts!
It hurts... and yet it feels good.
I'm the one who's becoming weird.
Ouch!
So good.
Mister...
Please finish it already.
My tummy might get torn apart!
Mister, I'm scared.
If it starts feeling any better then...
My entire world will be turned upside down!
My insides feel warm.
My butt hurts.
I ran away from home.
I got in a fight with mom over what I want as an idol.
That's how I ended up reaching our secret lair.
But, it's kinda dangerous for a girl to be alone at this hour.
Your mom is worried about you.
Come on, let's go home.
Hmph. I'll never go back there.
I called mister to act as my bodyguard.
He's not that reliable,
but he's one of the few adults that supports
my dream to become an idol.
You're quite the stubborn one.
Though, if you weren't so feisty, I guess becoming
an idol would be a pipe dream.
I know, right?
I'm planning to become an idol,
so I don't need to do summer homework anymore, right?
Wait, you need to do your summer homework!
What?
And here I thought you'd be the only
person who would never betray me.
Betray?
Don't you think you're jumping the gun a bit?
He never treated me like a kid.
Even when I said I wanted to become an idol,
he never mocked me, and supported me every step of the way.
He's a pervert, though.
What's wrong?
Are you thinking about something dirty right now?
Why would I be having lewd thoughts?
Okay, I take it all back.
He's the worst kind of pervert there is.
Calling out a guy this late at night,
means you can't complain over what happens next, you know.
Well, we've...
We've been having sex anyway, so...
So...
You've been training to become an idol, right?
The other idols have said they've never done such things!
Well, I, umm... think that it depends on the manager...
You like me, right?
Of course I do!
Same here.
I guess if I had to decide, I'd say I like you too.
Really?
I won't have sex with someone I dislike, you know.
Then we're officially a couple.
If that makes you feel better, than I guess it's okay.
So he really does like me.
Now that we're official,
I can... have sex with you now.
Is it all right?
Yeah.
I love you, Tenka-chan.
His tongue is entering my mouth.
It's lewdly entwining itself around my tongue.
This is what they call an adult kiss, right?
I'm starting to feel horny.
Hey, wait...!
I wonder how many times he's seen me naked.
Even my dad hasn't seen me naked in quite a while.
My back feels tingly.
My thing down there pulsates whenever he touches my nipples.
Mister, stop!
Please don't lick them.
I actually don't want him to stop.
I want him to keep doing it.
Mister... you're putting it in, right?
He's going to fuck me with his dick again.
Mister...
Aren't you putting it in?
I kinda forgot where it goes.
There's no way you've forgotten!
Tell me where, Tenka-chan.
In here!
You put it in here!
He always likes to tease me.
But, I've come to like it lately.
Could it be that I've become a masochist?
It slides in easily now.
It's all because we've done it a few times.
Do you hate me?
You bet I do.
Then, I'll have to work hard so that you'll like me.
Hey, you're being too rough right now!
I think his dick has reached my womb.
It's like his dick and my pussy are doing an adult kiss.
I probably have a sloppy expression on my face right now.
Stop!
This is embarrassing.
It suddenly squeezed me tight...!
I'm not sure,
but it feels so much better than usual.
He's the only thing on my mind right now!
Mister, dump your load inside me.
I want lots of your cum right now.
As his cum filled me up inside, I had an epiphany.
I want my summer vacation to last forever.
Mister,
I love you very much!