Sensei, you can't move!
It still feels really tingly!
Oh, what are you doing, sensei?
Asamiya?
You're not getting hard looking
at your student, are you? How shameful!
You guys set me up!
Sensei, it feels so good! Please, get harder!
Sensei, it doesn't feel tingly anymore.
Now it just feels hot.
Sensei! Sensei!
It's fine, I want more!
I want it even better, so get harder!
I'm surprised the drug
has this much of an effect on Miyako.
This is better than I expected!
Sensei! Sensei!
Sensei, your dick is starting to twitch.
Is it because you're ready to ejaculate?
Is the drug really that strong?
Wow, look at all the cum!
There's even more coming out!
Oh'? It looks like you're still full of energy.
Unless you take the antidote,
the aphrodisiac won't wear off.
A-Antidote?! Hurry up and give it to me!
Wait, what are you doing, Asamiya?
Calm down, sensei.
I never said I wouldn't give it to you.
Look at what splashed all over our legs.
Why don't you lick the antidote off of us?
Tea Ceremony : Sadism of Girls volume 1
You look just like a baby.
The texture of her tights creates
such a sensation across my tongue.
I know I'm at school but I can't help it,
It's because of the antidote!
I haven't had enough of the antidote yet.
I need to suck harder!
I need to suck every last drop out of their tights!
I have to get in between their toes,
under their nails-my tongue needs to be there!
I have to experience the lovely
fabric caressing their young soft skin.
I'm absorbing their scent from
this heavenly garment with my tongue!
How does it taste?
Do the feet of your beloved students taste good?
Sensei, you're like a little baby!
I should be calming down but
I'm only getting more turned on!
Oh my, it seems like you're not only
a failure as a teacher but as a man too.
You're basically nothing more than a dog in heat.
Even now, you're trying your best to
mark your students with your pre-cum.
Is there anything more pitiful than this?
Look, I'm going to tease your dick with my legs.
Drench your student in that
disgraceful cum you've stored up!
I can feel the warm cum from
your naughty dick soaking into my tights.
What a pitiful expression you're wearing.
You still haven't had enough.
Sensei, you're bright red.
Uh, this is kind of embarrassing...
Go on now. You have fresh pussies
ripe for fucking. Take your pick.
Staring right in front of me – my
student's dripping wet virgin pussies.
See how wet they've gotten?
They're practically begging for your dick, sensei.
Your beloved students are wet just for you, sensei.
They're waiting for you now.
You can't just ignore them like that, can you?
There, there. Good boy.
Both of them are virgins.
You need to make sure you're as wet as can be.
Y-Yeah, of course, but...
If you make me any wetter,
I'm gonna come from your hand!
Oh'? It looks like you're in pain.
This is for the sake of the
students you love so much.
Can you restrain yourself for their sake?
Please, I'm begging you, let me put it in them!
Shouldn't you be asking them and not me?
Miyako, please, let me put it in you!
I want you to let me cum inside your virgin pussy!
Okay! Please do as you wish.
Sensei's dick slid inside me!
Sorry, Miyako.
Huh?
Your pussy feels so good!
I-I can't stop!
Your dick feels so good!
Sensei, aren't you too
focused on pleasuring Miyako?
Can't you see how lonely Isuzu looks?
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry.
You're my precious student as well.
I'll love you all equally.
I'll use my dick to turn you into a woman as well.
It's going in! Sensei's dick is...
Sensei's dick is throbbing inside me!
Oh my god, it's so hot!
Sensei, please make sure you
take really good care of both of them.
Of course I will.
I'll make sure to fuck the two of you equally!
Sensei, which pussy do you like more?
Miyako's pussy is wrapping around
me so tightly, like it doesn't want to let go.
Every time I move I feel like
I'm going to dislocate my hip!
Isuzu's pussy is small and narrow.
So all I have to do is put my dick in,
and it'll squeeze!
Sensei!
Sensei! Please cum inside me!
Hey, no fair! He has to cum inside me too!
You're going to make me choose?
You have quite the admirable relationship
with your students. isn't it wonderful?
I'm here to witness you unleash
your animal urges on your students.
I'm going to shoot my seed
deep inside both of your wombs!
O-Okay!
Sensei!
Please plant your seed in me too!
There's so much!
He's still cumming!
That made for a great video, didn't it?
Yes it did!
I was able to capture it so perfectly!
Y-You!
How careless, sensei.
You should know that our
club has four members in it.
It was just so erotic, so stimulating!
Sensei, please take responsibility for that, okay?
Boobs are only boobs unless you squeeze
something between them. Don't you agree?
See? Your dick looks happy!
Fine, whatever.
Suzuka's fine with kissing this dick anyway.
You're a bad girl. I'm going to shoot
my cum inside your dirty little mouth.
Drink it up, Suzuka!
You came so much just for me!
Asamiya?
Prez...
Sensei, could you come here for a sec?
Wait, what are you doing?
Asamiya, don't you like him too?
Wh-What are you...
I don't like him... at all.
Don't worry Suzuka we'll
record every detail of your first time!
Huh? Wait, no, don...
Huh? What's this? Are your nipples inverted?
Here you go, sensei. Have a taste.
Thank you!
D-Don't!
Your nipples are really shy, Asamiya.
There we go.
All it needed was a little encouragement.
Y-You're being stupid!
No, don't! Stop!
Stop! Don't suck...
Isuzu, don't put your tongue insi... Stop!
Inverted nipples are so cute!
Your face is already full of ecstasy!
Here it goes...
Take it off!
Okay, please put it inside her now.
Wait! Wait!
You three, is this your idea of a prank?
You can still redeem yourselves!
We're prepared for any punishment.
That said, how about we start, Prez?
It's time to become sensei's woman, okay?
No! Stop! I'm telling you to stop! Listen to me!
Stop! Please, please stop!
Asamiya...
Sensei?
Sensei, do you know about my family?
I don't know anything.
All I know is that right now, I want you.
Is that not enough?
Sensei, it's hard to see her losing her virginity!
Well then, everyone gather around!
No!
Is it easier to see now?
H-Hey, what are you doing you idiot? You can't...
Asamiya, now that we're doing it doggy style,
your pussy's getting really tight.
No, I'm going to cum again!
It feels so good! Your dick feels so good, sensei!
Sensei?
What should we play next?