Uncle, look!
Tada!
I'm wearing a yukata.
Is it cute?
Yup, it is.
Mom bought it for me.
Festivals, festivals!
I can't wait to see if for myself.
You bet!
I'm going with Tenka-chan and Koma-chan.
Are you going to the festival?
Well...
I'm going to help set up the stalls.
Oh, I see.
Can you give me some money?
Should I or should I not...?
Oh,
your peepee... it's gotten stiff.
Mister's such a pervert.
It's because you're cute.
Jeez, that's dirty.
Do you hate peepeees?
I don't hate them, but...
Wait, not now!
You're not wearing any undies.
Please don't touch it.
Why?
That's...
It's gotten wet.
My thing down there gets wet,
and my breasts feel tingly whenever you're around me.
Is it weird?
No, it's not.
Humans become perverted when they're with someone they like.
Really?
Mister...
Ouch!
Why are you tying my hands together?
I can't move them.
What are you going to do?
That tickles.
Don't lick me like that.
Not the fingers, please!
Please don't lick my breasts.
Untie me, mister.
Someone's going to hear us if we do it here.
It's all right, just try to restrain yourself.
I can't do that!
I can't help but moan!
It goes all the way inside, it kinda feels full.
Your peepee feels good.
It feels so good.
I'm starting to feel weird.
N-No...
It feels good when you tease that spot.
Stop,
my mind feels fuzzy.
I'm scared.
Your peepee is bulging hard inside.
I can't hold it in any longer...!
Mister, mister... mister!
Mister, you're giving me money, right?
Mister, this isn't good.
Nobody's coming.
I already told Komako I would go to the festival with her.
Komako-chan's about to confess to Chii-chan.
Really?
Not inside, please!
You can't interrupt them right now.
I won't.
I won't bother them.
Please stop this already.
I'm going to cum!
Oh, come on!
You made me pee!
This is the worst.
What were you going to do if I was seen?
Everyone's busy watching fireworks. Nobody's coming here.
That's not the point!
But you actually wanted to, right?
What are you saying?
Hey wait, stop!
How did things turn out this way?
You see? It just slid all the way in.
You're the worst!
Pull it out!
I don't want to have sex right now!
Don't just move on your own.
Let me go.
Your peepee is too big!
We can't do this!
This is too intense.
This position is embarrassing.
Why are you thrusting even harder?
I'm going to start feeling weird.
Ouch!
It's...
It's hitting me deep.
I said stop!
I told you I don't want to have sex here!
Let me go.
Pull it out.
Don't make it big inside me.
You came inside me again.
What am I going to do if I get pregnant?
Koma-chan.
Can we really see the fireworks from here?
Yeah. Mister told me that this is the spot.
I see.
Is it coming already?
Chii-chan.
What is it?
Do you like me?
I do.
Why do you ask?
I like you, too.
So it's mutual.
Can we... kiss?
What's wrong?
Can't I?
It's not that, but...
Koma-chan, this feels weird.
No, it's not.
Because we like each other.
That's why,
it's okay...
Even if we have sex, right?
Koma-chan?
Are we going to have sex?
I've practiced a lot, so it's all right.
Koma-chan, it tickles.
Your breasts are cute.
Not my nipples...!
Touch mine, too.
If you suck my nipples like that...
You look like such a baby, and it's cute.
Chii-chan, let's... let's make each other feel good.
I love you, Chii-chan.
I love you very much.
Stop, don't lick me there.
Koma-chan, you're so dirty.
Lick mine too, Chii-chan.
Okay.
Your pussy...
It's making sloshing sounds.
So cute.
Koma-chan,
you're too intense.
Chii-chan...
Let's do it more.
We've become one.
Yeah.
It's like we're actually having sex.
Koma-chan.
Koma-chan,
it feels good.
We weren't able to see the fireworks.
Are you mad?
No.
I had a blast learning more about you.
Chii-chan.
I love you.
I love you, too.