Ah!
Eh?
In a place down below the Tenjou Mansion,
extending from a quiet passage, there exists a secret hot spring.
The girls were all waiting for me there.
The eldest among them was the extremely voluptious Aya
These three girls brimming with innocence are Mitsuba, Yotsuba and lastly, Futaba.
Three particularly naive sisters...
And the last of them is my childhood friend, Matsuriko.
These girls and I continued on to a nightlong orgy.
We fucked till we could not go on anymore.
The long night...
is far from over!
First act: Matsuriko
It's almost been seven years
since I've been back to my hometown.
Brother, our Mother has passed away.
I no longer have any relations with that house.
Please, I'm begging you, Brother!
Come back!
Right now, our Father has lost it all...
There's no one left for us but you Brother.
Save us, please!
W-welcome back, Brother!
Welcome!
Welcome home!
I'm glad to see that everyone seems to be doing well.
That's because you came back, Kengo.
Aya!
There's nobody else we can rely on anymore other than you, Kengo.
Welcome home, Kengo...
Glad to be back!
N-next, drink what I brewed!
Mine too!
Here you go!
That sure is nice...
Try mine next!
No, mine!
The girls were actually of the concubines my father had accumulated over the years.
Since we were raised together, I naturally thought of them as my siblings.
There were supposed to be fireworks tonight?
Look, Aya, over here!
N-no!
I'm sorry, but the outside, is impossible for me...
No, I'm sorry too.
Since they were children born without wedlock,
they'd never been allowed to leave the mansion.
And thus, they'd learned to fear unfamilair sights.
All of this is the fault of that one man.
My Father, that is.
For god's sake, please liberate the girls already!
I've never laid a finger on any of my daughters.
However, if you so wish,
you are free to do whatever you please with them.
How filthy!
This is all the fault of your insatiable lust, is it not?
The years have sure sharpened your tongue, Kengo!
Seven years ago, fearing me, you ran away from the house, you fool!
Brother.
Matsuriko?
It's been a long time.
Brother, could you come with me for a little walk?
I've never known that
we had a hot spring under the mansion.
I apologize, Matsuriko.
Even though I finally came home, it doesn't look like I'll be able to rescue you guys.
Matsuriko?
Matsuriko?!
B-brother...
Just you coming back is enough to make me happy.
Ever since you went away, I was feeling really insecure!
I'm sorry.
Brother.
We would like you to hear one of our requests.
Request?
You'll understand soon.
To begin, please use the hot springs to rest your body.
I'll take care of your clothes.
B-brother...?
T-this is, umm...
I'm sorry!
It's fine, but...
please keep your voice to a minimum once we head in deeper,
since this place is sacred.
Sacred?
Please come inside.
It isn't just a plain hot spring?
W-women's bath?!
I-I'm sorry!
Aya?
T-this is...?
Aya-
That kiss alone was enough to break my senses and blow away all reasoning
for me who had never been touched by a woman before.
Kengo's thing is hitting me...
Something really hot and hard is rubbing against me...
And it's still so hard.
It's embarrassing, b-but...
He's stirring up my insides...
Being spread open like this, I feel so embarrassed!
N-no! If he keeps on teasing me like this, I'm gonna go crazy!
No, I'm gonna cum!
Cumming, I'm cumming!
Kengo's thing...
P-put it in!
It's in! It's inside!
Kengo, amazing! So deep!
Your hot pussy is melting me, Aya!
It's so tight that I almost came just by putting it in!
That felt so good!
They had no means for any entertainment.
Being in confinement for so long, they were desperately hungry for men.
And so, to answer their desire,
I slowly relished them all!
Losing my ability to think straight anymore,
I simply pounded Aya.
Her naked, sensitive insides
and the sensation of the rough, wet rubbing put me into a delirium.
Aya's hot insides, and taking her to new heights time after time...
Ever since the first time I pounded my cock into her hole,
I felt like I could keep cumming inside forever!
Aya!
That day,
my lust knew no bounds.
The long night
had just fallen.
Brother left the house.
Help me! Please help me!
Oh dear!
At such a late hour...
From which house are you?
T-tenjou!
Tenjou?
Are you perhaps, the daughter of one of Tenjou's concubines?
Yes.
What's your name?
I'm Aya!
I see, Aya, eh?
It's safe already, leave the rest to me.
Retarded daughter!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Why did you help my daughter escape?!
You...!
Touching something from my house, you moron!
Thanks for telling me about this.
It's fine, it's fine.
I don't really care about a concubine's daughter, however...
That day,
my lust knew no bounds.
The girls seemed a bit bashful as well.
But as they gazed upon my hardened cock,
their interests were maxed.
So this is Brother's...
It can get this big...
It's sticky from Brother and Aya's stuff...
Amazing, what a perverted smell
The only reason they could do this much
was because they'd seen Aya do it.
It's so hard!
Licking Brother's thing, I'm starting to feel weird as well.
A lot of thick soup is flowing from the tip...
Futaba.
Brother, are you gonna put out that scalding hot stuff again?
It's alright, I want it inside my mouth!
A lot of your white stuff!
A lot!
So much of it is coming out!
Your hot stuff is flowing down my throat!
It smells just like you, Brother!
My lust still insatiable,
I embraced the girls one by one.
Brother please, put it inside me as well!
Brother, it h-hurts a bit, but it feels amazing!
Brother's white stuff has made my insides so slippery, amazing!
Amazing! What's this?
My head's turning all blank!
I... I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Mitsuba.
Brother, t-that's embarrassing.
It's so embarrassing, no!
Brother's licking me.
All my shameful parts are being licked!
Don't look at me!
That's Brother's...
I can feel it.
Amazing, it feels like he's turning me inside out.
I'm gonna break, but it feels so great!
More, give me more!
Brother... is seeing all my embarrassing parts.
I can't hold on.
No! It feels so good I'm gonna go crazy!
Brother's thing is coming deep inside me...
It's even reaching my womb!
Something's a-already coming! What?
Cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Cumming!
Matsuriko.
Brother...
The long night
is still far from over!