Um, so... well...
Hinada Asami
I'm in love with you, Sensei.
I used to be alone in this photography club.
But thanks to you, I was able to make friends
and get good at taking pictures too.
I...
Sensei!
Girl's education
Hinada Ami Arc
How did I get to be like this?
Making me feel good is your job, right Hinada?
Y-Yes...
I'm going to cum. Make sure you drink
it all without spilling any of it!
I told you not to spill any of it, didn't I?
I'm sorry, Sensei!
Hinada, what do we say in these kinds of situations?
I couldn't follow your instructions, so please punish me!
A punishment, huh?
N-No! Sensei!
What? Vibrators aren't good enough for you?
You want something stronger? You're such a pervert, Hinada.
Sensei, no! Not that!
No!!!
How'd it end up like this?
I loved the kind side of him.
Even though he liked doing dirty things, if
I didn't say yes, he wouldn't do anything.
At first, I was glad that he promised to treasure me, but...
But I got uneasy because I began to
feel that we weren't really lovers.
Hinada...
I tried studying harder, just like you asked, Sensei.
My test scores have gotten better, right?
So, as you promised...
Make me your real girlfriend! Please, Sensei...
Take my virginity!
It's in me! Your dick is inside me!
It hurts but... It feels so good!
It's just amazing!
So this is sex?
You came the instant your hymen broke?
You really are the best, Hinada.
Sensei, more!
This can't even compare to masturbating!
If I knew sex felt this good, I would've
asked you to do it sooner!
With this, I've finally become your real girlfriend.
So now I can accept your dick whenever you want!
Whenever?
You can stick your dick inside me whenever you want!
Just thinking about having sex with
you 24/7 makes me ecstatic!
Ah, Sensei came inside me...
Sensei...
I'm so happy!
Photography Club
Even though I said that.
Sensei has been so busy that we haven't
done anything in a while.
Even after giving me a taste of sex... he's so mean!
I just came, but
I can't hold back!
This kind of toy isn't enough!
Sensei!
Fuck me with your dick!
How can he make his girlfriend feet like this?
I got mad and decided to bother him
by going to his house on a Sunday.
I'm here.
Sensei...
Let's have sex!
Sensei was furious.
He said that bad girls that don't listen, get punished.
And with adult toys, he...
2 hours later
2 more hours later
Sensei, please stop!
It's okay if we don't have sex when you're busy!
I'm sorry for coming here without asking you.
No! If you do me like that, I'll cum!
Sensei!
I'm cumming!!
Sensei wouldn't forgive me no matter what
I said, and kept cumming inside me.
Sensei isn't just a pervert, he's a huge pervert!
No!!
I kept cumming too.
But after the 10th time, I don't remember.
The day after that, I had this feeling
that his dick was still inside me.
It was really terrible.
Sensei told me later that he was rough with me because
he wanted to make sure I wasn't addicted to sex...
But instead, that woke up something inside me.
The adult sex-loving side of me...
Sensei, you can't stick something that big in there!
It's going to break my ass! It's going to split apart my asshole!
No! I can't be the kind of pervert
that gets turned on from this.
No, stop! Don't make me any more of a pervert!
You let it out again. Do you really
want to be punished that badly?
You're such a masochist, Hinada.
No! I'm not a masochist...
Okay Hinada, I'm going to give you that cum you like so much.
No! Sensei, don't say it like that!
I'm going to get pregnant!
No!!
You came inside me!
Your seed's inside of me!
Sensei, your dick is too thick!
If you keep thrusting like that, my asshole is going to open up!
Oh no, it's coming! I'm going to cum with my ass!
Okay, I'll let your womb taste my semen again.
Please don't cum inside anymore!
It wouldn't be a punishment if I didn't, now would it?
If you cum in me anymore, I definitely won't forgive you!
No! Today isn't a safe day, so any more and I'll...
Just give up.
No!!
You're horrible! Sensei, you idiot!
Even though I didn't want you to cum inside...
I'm cumming!!
It feels so good when he cums inside me!
My womb's able to feel so much of his cum!
I might not be able to live without his dick anymore.
One year later
The result of having him cum inside me like I wanted was that,
I ended up having Sensei's baby in my stomach.
I left home before my parents could
find out and hid at Sensei's house.
Please, Sensei, let me go. Let me go home!
Any more of this and...
Just become mine already, Hinada!
No! I won't become yours!
Well then, I'll just cum inside you again
to make you change your mind.
No, please! Anything but that!
Oh, night. Just me cumming inside makes
you feel so good that you almost faint.
Please, don't cum in me. I'll get pregnant!
A bit late for that. You're already carrying my child.
No! I'm just a bit bloated. I'm definely not pregnant!
Just give up, you're already lactating. You
have no choice but to give birth now.
No! I definitely don't want to!
No!!
This! This is it!
Cum straight into my womb!
It feels so good!
Being creampted while I'm pregnant feels the best!
Are you alright? Did I overdo it, Asami?
Not at all. It was really good, Sensei.
This felt the best out of all the role playing we've done!
That's good then.
But how about we have some normal sex?
I feel guilty doing you like this, all things considered...
Nope. You're the one who made me this perverted,
so I need you to take responsibility.
Sensei, I want to do master-servant role playing next!
Just like in the ero manga you've got, that hardcore stuff.
Ugh, how can I turn you back into a normal girl?
You're going to be a father soon, so
get it together, okay? My husband.
He said that he would take responsibility, but
I want to stay like this for a little longer.
Afer all, the feeling of forbidden sex between
a student and her teacher feels the best!
Translator: Hikarucon
Timer: MrMew
Editor: Punk4Real
Encode: Punk4Real