....
(text says same thing)
He might be my 'brother', but it’s been more than ten years since I last saw him.
It’s really stressful.
He always undresses me with his eyes.
He lives alone, but sometimes he’ll want to eat dinner at my house.
Pen-kichi
But since he became your tutor, it seems like you've been having fun.
Well, I have.
He’s a good tutor,
and he’s a pretty nice guy otherwise.
He’s not all bad.
Pen-kichi
I’m happy for you, Onee-chan.
I could never tell Pen-kichi about THAT...
Shoukoujo, The Animation
W
Oh... Onii-chan, you're kissing me too forcefully.
Well, I don’t usually kiss you like that.
This is the kind of kiss to celebrate the fact that we've become lovers.
Ayane and her Brother.
Onii-chan... I... Um... You’re my first, so... Please be gentle.
Huh? You’re a little wet.
You're turned on?
Because... It’s you... Because I missed you... I...
It’s inside! Your fingers...
If you wiggle them so much... It’s strong... And painful.
Ayane, you won’t let go of my fingers.
Idiot! Onii-chan, it’s your fault.
This is really embarrassing, but it’s squeezing hard!
Onii-chan...
You sure seem determined today... Completely unlike the way you’ve been before.
You’re the one who’s acting differently.
Acting all slutty in front of me, making me want you more.
But that was just... Because I wanted you to notice me...
Even so, you were being very bold.
No! Don’t remind me...
I was really embarrassed... I’m so embarrassed I could die.
Onii-chan!
Yes, I finally made him notice.
That I was serious about him.
Even the first time he came to tutor me...
Um... I have to factor out this x...
Oh, I get it.
Hey, Ayane.
I can see your panties.
What’s wrong, Onii-chan?
Are you really that bothered by my panties?
Idiot. It’s not that at all.
If you wanna see them that badly, then go ahead and look.
See? Girl’s panties for your viewing pleasure.
Listen, you...
Try having some modesty, will ya?
That’s what you SAY, but... You REALLY wanna see them badly, don’t you?
Look! What do you think?
Doesn’t this excite you?
S-Stop it already.
Hey... Look at it.
I’m lifting it all the way up.
Look... You can masturbate while watching me.
You wanted to see it, right?
I’ll show you everything.
Ever since then, every move I made was to come onto him.
Onii-chan, you’re jerking off while staring at my pussy... You pervert.
I may be your brother, but I’m still a man.
If you show me that much...
I’m so turned on and wet.
You’re making naughty noises, Onii-chan.
Don’t talk like that.
I... If you look at me like that... I can’t hold back either.
Come on, Onii-chan, look at me with those sexy eyes.
I’ll masturbate with you.
Your dick... Looks like it’s gonna burst.
Come on. You can put it in.
I’m so wet already.
But I can’t...
Hey... Don’t you wanna shove your cock in and fuck me?
Idiot.  We’re siblings.
Then... Watching me masturbate is okay?
It isn’t... But I can’t stop.
Ayane... I... Can’t...
Then finish.
Cum.
On my butt... On my pussy...
I want your hot semen on me.
I’m gonna... Cum...
Onii-chan!
So hot...
You came on my panties...
That’s almost sex, isn’t it.
We’d only ever done stuff like that...
So today, I decided...
Onii-chan... If you can’t hold back, then do it.
I’m fine.
I’ve been so selfish this whole time... So now it’s your turn to have your way with me.
Onii-chan... Your cock... I want it...
I don’t care anymore. It doesn’t matter that we’re related.
Ayane.
It’s okay.
Onii-chan.
You’re my first... I’m giving it to you.
We’ll be joined together.
I’m sorry.
I’m going in.
It’s going in.
Your cock's spreading my pussy open.
Onii-chan!
I... I’m connected to you, Onii-chan.
Yes, you are.
We’re really connected.
I’m so happy.
Ayane! Does it hurt?
I’m okay.
It doesn’t hurt... It just aches a bit.
Ayane... Ayane...
Ayane, you’re so sweet I can’t stop.
Onii-chan...
My pussy... My pussy... It’s fitting around you like a glove.
It’s turning into something that only fits you.
That’s ok.
I want to be with you for the rest of my life.
Onii-chan, I love you. I love you so much!
It feels so good because I'm with you.
It’s no good. I’m cumming already.
Ayane... Ayane!
It’s ok.
I’m about to cum too!
Let’s cum... Let’s cum together.
I wanna cum at the same time as you.
Onii-chan! Right there... Right there!
I’m cumming!
Onii-chan’s cum... So much came out.
I came inside of you.
That’s ok.
I wanted that to happen my first time.
Onii-chan...
That’s sudden.
Hey, Onee-chan... Is sex a bad thing?
I think... It’s not a bad thing.
Sex is fine.
Pen-kichi
Really...?
Yes. If you do it with someone you really love...
I guess... You get indescribably happy.
Yes.
No matter where you both come from...
Onii-chan!
Shoukoujo
Usami-onee-chan, ever since your brother came back, you look so happy.
By the way, Pen-kichi-chan, how are things going with you and Onii-san?
Um... Onii-chan... Helps me take care of the house when mom is gone.
And when mom is gone...
Onii-chan helps me take care of the house when mom is gone.
And when mom is gone, he helps me cook and do chores.
Awesome! That’s almost like you’re married.
You... Really think so?
What should I say?
I can’t.
I can’t tell Usami-onee-chan that.
It’s embarrassing.
J-Just a little bit.
This is called a 'pussy'.
Pussy?
No... Don’t do that, Onii-chan!
You can’t wiggle them around in there!
Onii-chan!
Onii-chan was... My first friend.
That’s all we were supposed to be, but...
But I sure did something really slutty with him.
Yuzu and Onii-chan
That day, the bath was broken.
So we went to a public bathhouse together.
Women’s bath
And he...
Are you really coming in with me?
Then are you ok with going in the women’s bath alone?
So I went into the men’s bath with him.
Onii-chan... There are other men here.
Onii-chan, wha...
I can’t stop when I have such a pretty naked girl with me.
No one’s watching.
B-But if they do, I won’t like it!
Yuzu-chan... Those are some big bubbles.
Want some help?
No. I’m fine!
Onii-chan saw so many embarrassing sides of me.
But... Seeing me naked is also embarrassing.
Yuzu!
Onii-chan!
Come on, wash your back as well as your front.
Geez! I told you I can wash myself!
See?
Geez, Onii-chan just doesn’t understand how I feel at all.
You’re so cute, Yuzu.
See?
Don’t hold back.
Geez! Onii-chan, stop teasing me.
N-Not there! Those are my boobs!
Yes, your boobs. I need to clean them too.
Don’t!
Is something wrong?
What? Do you know him?
He’s in my class.
What should I do? I’m so embarrassed.
Then...
Wait, Onii-chan, don’t!
We should show him how much fun you’re having.
I’m embarrassed!
See? There’s so many bubbles down here.
Don’t!
Just having my body washed makes me feel funny.
Even though we’re in the bath... And even though a boy from my class is watching...
Like this, I became a slutty girl from Onii-chan washing me in the bath.
This feels great.
Don’t, Onii-chan, people will notice.
It’s under water. No one will.
But a boy from my class... Is here...
Don’t worry.
City people always ignore each other. No one will even notice.
Onii-chan!
We’re in public...
Does it feel good?
This... Feels great!
My pussy... It’s... It’s throbbing...
Then, you’re ready?
I don’t care anymore!
So thick!
See? No one’s noticing.
Even so... not here...
Don’t worry.
Come on.
Onii-chan...
Yes, yes, Yuzu-chan, it’s okay to be sexy.
D-don’t!
Your penis is...
Come on.
Like this. We need to get closer or people will notice.
Onii-chan... You’re such a tease.
Onii-chan, let’s just stop.
Don’t move. We’ll be fine.
Onii-chan!
Come on. Don’t cry out or he’ll notice.
Or maybe... Maybe he's already noticed.
I’m sure his dick is hard while he’s watching you.
In which case, we might as well show him even more!
Don’t!
He’ll see... He’ll see us!
He’ll see my pussy... My boobs... Everything private about me!
Onii-chan, stop... Stop...
Then... Let’s count to ten and get out.
One... Two... Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Just one more...
Eight...
Nine...
Pen-kichi
Hey... Onee-chan... Is sex... A bad thing?
Ten!
Are you actually talking about yourself?
Nope. Just, a friend was talking about it at lunch.
I don’t think it’s a bad thing.
Really...?
Yup!