Tonight, I'm going all the way with Azumi!!
"Let's watch a video together," I'll say. Just as excuse, of course.
Azumi-chan will be staying in my room tonight.
I've kissed her many times before...
Deep kisses too...
It's not the first time I've fondled her breasts eigher.
Yu...
Yuzuru-kun...
Just kidding! Just kidding...
I'm sorry... We haven't eaten yet, have we?
I'm hungry... And we haven't rented a video yet.
Let's go.
VIRGIN NIGHT
Azumi-chan...
...My first girlfriend.
Having her as my girlfriend is the first miracle that has happened to me in my eighteen years.
Ah, this looks like it would be interesting!
Also, right now she's seriously like a national treasure in her naiveté.
Even when we went to a Karaoke Box, she said it was her first time.
But... She sure does have big breasts.
It doesn't really go with her face...
Have you decided?
It wouldn't be good if I didn't have this.
Your change is 9,036 yen.
Thank you very much!
I bet she's a virgin...
She must be!
Geez, with how this turned out, I shouldn't have gone to that bathhouse...
If I had just waited half a year longer, my first time would have definitely been with her.
I'd be able to boast about it for the rest of my life...
Alright, when we get back to my room, I'll do it quick without watching the video!
But... I wonder... Does she really want to do it with me?
I wonder if it's alright for someone like me to take away her virginity.
Would she be able to forgive me?
It might hurt...
She might cry...
She might be hurt by it...
That's right... If she carries a deep scar in her heart from it...
...When I think about it... I worry about tearing away her heart...
If I think Azumi-chan never turning towards me and smiling...
...About her stepping into a place where I can never get her back...
...My limbs get all cold.
I feel like I want to die.
If I was another guy, I wonder if I wouldn't even think about these things, and just do it.
Idiot! Azumi-chan is special!
Yuzuru-kun?
Wh... What?
We don't have to say "good night" here tonight... Do we?
Alright! I want to do it as soon as we get back to my room after all!
Ay yo trip, dupe this tape and we dun gon' bust a cap in yo ass.
If I allow the time slip away like this, there won't be any change to do it!
Well, shall we watch the next one?
Geez, it's already past midnight!
Can't help it... I guess we'll have to do it next time.
It seems like this video is different from the others...
Yuzuru-kun?
Do you...
...Love me?
Ye...
Yeah...
I love you.
Oh...
A... Azumi-chan...
I'm going to use the bathroom.
This is bad...
Azumi-chan... Came prepared.
If we don't do anything tonight, we'll just become friends!
Okay...
Okay!
Alright!
When she comes back, I'll suddenly kiss her, and push her down.
Yuzuru-kun...
I used... Your shower a bit.
I made sure... To wash up.
Is it about time to go to bed?
Yeah.
I'll turn out the light.
Um...
Yeah...
She's really shaking...
Be gentle with your hands, okay?
Was what I said strange?
Yuzuru-kun...
I'm taking it off.
Okay.
Azumi-chan's breasts are big... Tender... The best.
How is it... Doesn't it feel good?
Not there!
Please wait!
I'm... This... It can't be good for me to do this.
It's okay.
Even if it hurts me, it's okay!
If it's you, it's alright.
Put yourself inside me.
Th... That's right...
Azumi-chan.
It's okay because I'm the only one in the world who can do this with you.
Geez, it's past noon!
Yeah, we completely overslept.
Good morning.
Looks like our plans for today are done for.
What should we do now?
First I want to take a bath, then go eat somewhere.
Tempura sounds good, don't you think?
Tempura is a classic Japanese dish of deep fried battered vegetables or seafood.
And then...
...Let's come back here and have sex.
In the twilight, look...
yuuguredoki ni hora
A small star is shining.
chiisa na hoshi hikaru
Hey, being here without saying goodbye, today is a good day, isn't it?
nee sayonara iwazu ni ite mo kyou wa ii hi yo ne
Right now, coming from your direction.
anata no kata ni ima
I can feel a cool breeze.
suzushii kaze fureru
I want to blow over to your side, nonchalantly.
fuite ikitai, tada sarigenaku, anata no sobae
Both the first smile...
hajimete no egao to
...and the first tear-stained face.
hajimete no nakigao
One by one we walk through the course...
hitotsu hitotsu kasa e aruite yuku
Hey look, isn't this strange...
fushigi na koto ne hora
No matter how far away...
donna ni tookute mo
surely, just by being connected, we can decide on love.
kitto tsunaide tte sore dake de, suki to kimete mo