SubDESU-H.net
There... no... not there...
Yes!
Not there, dea!
No... not there...
What do you mean no? You're so wet.
No, it feels good!
Yes, it feels so good there!
My boobs, my boobs feel good too!
Yes! My nipples... I'm really feeling it there.
Keiichirou-san!
Suck harder!
I'm putting it in, Ayuki.
Yes!
That hot penis...
Put it in me, Keiichirou-san!
It feels good there!
Harder! Do it harder!
Yes!
It's been a while since I've had a penis in me... oh, yes!
Harder, do it harder!
It feels so good, Keiichirou-san!
Deeper, go deeper!
It's hitting so deep!
You're a bit rough today.
That's because you're always busy working.
Because you got sick from overwork, I've been so lonely.
I wanted you to have me every day.
Yes, there!
I'm sorry, I'll make it up to you, so please forgive me.
Okay.
It's okay, I'll forgive you...
So please, love me more, Keiichirou-san!
More...
Yes, it feels so good...
Your hot, hard penis feels so good.
No... Keiichirou-san, I'm cumming!
Keiichirou-san!
What are you doing? Mom...?
Eh?! Um...
W-Welcome back.
Yeah. Hi.
I was just staring into space.
Isn't it almost time for the doctor to get here?
Eh?! Is it that time already?
Ah, looks like he's here.
How about you greet him once in a while?
I don't want to.
That doctor makes me sick. I hate him.
Don't say things like that.
He's been our family doctor for a long time.
W
Doctor's
Conspiracy
Part One
Alright, we'll finish here for today.
How are you feeling? Well, I hope?
Yes. I'm taking the medicine you gave me, but...
It hasn't really...
It's only been two weeks since you started the treatment.
But if I, the president, am not at the office...
Please put more trust in your employees.
Your illness is caused by working too much.
Please forget about your work for a while,
take a long break.
But still...
You see, it's bad to keep getting stressed about things.
You're doing a great job as a son in law.
You rebuilt the company that you inherited and more than doubled the family wealth.
Isn't everything alright at the moment?
What if something terrible happens because of you overdoing it?
What will happen to your wife and kids?
You're right.
I don't want to make my wife and kids suffer.
I'll rest for a while.
Alright then, we'll be going now.
Thank you, doctor.
Please take care of yourself until the next visit.
Eh? A massage?
Yes.
But...
Don't over think it.
From what I can see...
You look like you haven't been relaxed for a while.
You look like you're mentally and physically exhausted.
Let me help you get better.
I'm exhausted?
Yes.
You look pale and Keiichirou-san will not get well if you are tired all the time.
People can be affected by those around them.
If the wife doesn't get better then neither will her husband.
Listen to me.
The human body will lose its balance because of the smallest things.
For example, a sexless couple.
This happens if the wife has too much stress to deal with.
This has been recently proven in the scientific community.
A woman of your age often experiences a hormonal imbalance due to stress related complications.
In your case, because your husband is ill at the moment,
mentally and physically, your hormones are becoming imbalanced.
In other words, you are putting yourself under a lot of pressure without realizing it.
Especially at your age, having reached your sexual peak,
this isn't the best situation to be in.
Yes...
Unfortunately I'm not a specialist in that area.
I can't do much, but..
First of all, we'll warm up the outside and slowly start to release the tension.
Drink this herbal tea.
Okay.
You drank it, right?
We'll start now, so please lie down on your bed.
From here on, please think of this massage as a treatment to release your stress.
Let's get started.
Does it hurt?
No.
It feels very good.
Tokuko-kun, please take care of the shoulder.
Yes, doctor.
Ah, this feels so good.
What is this feeling...?
My body feels so hot...
I'm losing all my strength...
It feels like I'm about to melt.
D-Doctor!
What are you...?
It is really hard to find the right spot here.
What do you mean by "the right spot"? That's my ass!
Madam, I'm about to put pressure on this spot, so please relax your body.
Eh?! What do you mean?
No. Not there...
I can't gather up any strength in my body.
No... That's my...
Madam.
Your shoulder still seems to be stiff.
Please relax and concentrate on where my fingertips are.
Why is my pussy hot?
Don't... No, this feels too good! What is this?
No!
Why am I feeling like this even though I'm getting teased by him?
I can't move my body...
No...
I don't want this...
Don't! Don't enjoy it!
Ah... It's starting to feel really good.
I'm going to cum...
Am I really cumming? Eh? I'm cumming!
Alright, today was just a sample.
Let's leave it here for today, Madam.
Was I able to satisfy you?
Until our next session, please take this.
It's made from the same ingredients as the herbal tea.
Use it when you're on your own and need to release some stress.
Just apply it gently on your crotch.
Alright then, we'll leave for today.
What is it, Keiichirou-san?
You've been staring at my face for a long time.
Nothing... you look better than usual today.
Did something happen?
N-Nothing happened.
Let me wipe your back.
Since I became ill...
I've put a huge burden on you.
You didn't look so well these days, so I was really worried.
Keiichirou-san...
I'm sorry for making you worry so much.
Don't worry.
But when I see you healthy,
I feel a little better too.
Dear...
Don't overdo it and get ill, okay?
I'm worried about that more than anything else.
Keiichirou-san...
I love you, Ayahi.
I really want you now, but...
Sorry.
D-Don't say things like that, Keiichirou-san.
You have to recover from your illness first.
I'll be waiting for you, so don't worry.
I didn't expect to get so wet just from a kiss.
I want to do it.
I want Keiichirou-san to have sex with me.
Please use this when you're alone and need some comfort.
It is a medicine to console that emptiness in your heart.
It's so hot...
No... my fingers... my fingers won't stop!
Even though I just came...
It feels good!
What is this sensation?
Amazing... This is amazing!
Yes... it feels so good!
Oh no! I'm about to go crazy!
I'm about to lose it!
No, I can't anymore...
Keiichirou-san, this is great, it's so good!
No... I can't...
No...
I'm about to cum again...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Keiichirou-san...
I'm so lonely.
Then please, look after yourself.
Thank you, doctor.
Alright then, Madam.
Let's get started.
Okay.
Um, doctor?
What is it?
The medicine you gave me earlier this week...
I used it all... so...
I need some more....
There was enough there to last a week.
But you managed to use it all in four days...
There's nothing to be shy about.
Because you have not had sex with your husband for a year now.
But using it all alone is bad for your health.
Ok then.
Starting today, I will give you your daily dose myself.
No, it's fine. That would only cause you more trouble.
I am a doctor.
Looking after the patient's family is also part of my job.
Alright, we'll massage your whole body today,
but I would like to concentrate on the inside.
Inside?
Tokuko-kun.
Yes.
Please excuse me, Madam.
Doctor? What is this?
I'm going to take your underwear off and start the massage.
Eh?! W-Wait, that's...
It's all for your husband's sake.
For Keiichirou-san?
Yes.
No... stop...
What exactly were you expecting, Madam?
Look.
It's soaking wet.
I'm going to apply the medicine and start the massage.
It's so hot... no...
Doctor! That's...
Not there...
Madam, how does it feel here?
No, not there... it feels too good... no...
Listen to me, Madam.
There is a pressure point under the vagina.
It's useless to just move your fingers in and out.
A pressure point? There! It feels amazing!
Tokuko-kun.
Yes.
I'm going to rub your breasts and nipples, Madam.
No.. don't pinch my nipples and boobs!
Wh-What are these people doing?
D-Doing that with that man...
It's... immoral.
Mother...
Doctor... coming... something is coming...
Please stop!
She squirted a lot didn't she, doctor?
This is just the beginning.
We have to make her remember the pleasure.
Here you go, doctor.
No... What?
No... not there.
Yes.
I'm cumming!
No!
You managed to control yourself even though you went that far, master.
If you don't control yourself then it's all finished.
I've been planning this for a very long time.
If we don't do it slowly then we won't be able to steal their wealth.
But it's as expected of a wife who doesn't know anything about society.
She's doing exactly what we want her to do and my mind control seems to be working.
Maybe it will be time soon.
Master.
Hm?
My pussy is also ready.
Please give me your cock, coated in the medicine.
I rubbed on plenty.
Put it in yourself and move your hips by yourself.
Yes!
Master's thick cock is going in!
Don't just feel good by yourself. Hurry up and move to make me feel good too.
O-Of course, master.
Yes! It feels so good, master!
Yes!
It's grinding more and more inside!
It feels so good.
Yes!
Master, it feels so good!
I'm cumming!
What?
That doctor is coming again?
Wasn't he just here yesterday?
He's coming to give Keiichirou-san his medicine and my massage.
Massage?
Yes.
He said that my face looked pale so...
He said he should help to relax me at the same time,
because if I don't get well then that will affect Keiichirou-san too.
Madam.
We are going to begin proper treatment starting today.
"Proper" treatment?
Yes.
What we have done so far was just the warm-up.
The real thing begins now.
Lie down on your bed naked.
Eh?! Naked?
This is for the sake of your husband's health. Hurry!
Fine.
That's right, Madam.
Tokuko-kun, please begin the preparations.
Yes, doctor.
Don't lick there! It's dirty! No!
Tokuko-san, please stop!
Madam, this is called cunnilingus and it's an excellent way of relieving stress.
And this too.
No... not that!
You should know about this.
This is that which you most desire.
Yes.
But I don't want to make that mistake... I can't be unfaithful.
This is a medical treatment!
If it is treatment, then Keiichirou-sama won't mind either.
He will have no right to prosecute me.
Listen to me, right now, you have to get well soon and help Keiichirou-san to get better.
Now! Lick it for Keiichirou-sama's sake!
A cock. Haven't had something this delicious in a while.
My pussy... it feels good there too.
No...
Doctor, it's soaking wet down there and it's ready to go.
What?! Am I going to be raped?
I can't summon any strength... but that cock!
I want it! Please, put your cock in!
In my... in my pussy!
Yes... your cock feels so good!
More! More! Do it harder!
Yes! There! Harder!
Keiichirou-san, I'm about to go crazy!
Do it harder!
No, it's hitting there... I'm about to cum!
No!
Come in.
Well?
What's the matter? Coming here at this time, Miss Kirara...
What are you doing to mother?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb.
I know what you're doing to mother! I've seen it!
Right there... oh, doctor, right there!
It's not just your mother.
Eh?
Miss Kirara...
It looks like you need the treatment too.
In the next episode:
My daughter has seen the lewd act of her mother and her physician.
In order to save her mother, she went to the physician's alone...
No!
However, her virginity was stolen by the physician's slave.
It hurts. Stop it!
Meanwhile, Ayahi is brainwashed by the physician and is forced into sexual acts with him.
My daughter, Kirahi, is broken and sexually "trained" by the physician.
What will happen to our family?
Answer me, Keiichirou-san!
To be continued
SubDESU-H.net