SubDESU-H.net
The Toudou household.
My husband, Keiichirou, has fallen ill.
For a year before that, our sexlife was pretty much nonexistent due to the pressures of work, leaving me, Ayahi, a lonely wife.
Ah, yes! There!
Yes! It feels so good. Keiichirou-san... more!
Day after day, I masturbated to comfort myself.
I'm tired?
Yes. Your face looks pale, and...
If you're so tired then how is your husband going to get better?
People can be affected by those around them.
If the wife doesn't get better from the stress from looking after her husband,
then neither will he.
But I was deceived by the physician.
Using massage as an excuse...
Doctor, not there...
No...
This was the beginning of it all.
No, not there... it feels too good...
No!
The massages kept on escalating.
Madam, this is called cunnilingus, an excellent way of relieving stress.
Tokuko-kun, stop it...
Yes!
And this too.
No... that's...
Madam, you must know. That this is what you really want.
Yes...
But I can't do this!
I don't want to be unfaithful to my husband!
This is a medical treatment.
Madam, you've to relieve your stress own first; only then can you help your husband get better.
Until I finally crossed that line...
Yes! The cock feels good!
More! Do it harder!
Keiichirou-san, I'm going crazy!
Yes!
Part Two
W
Well, well.
If it'sn't Miss Kirara.
Why have you come here now?
You...
What are you doing to mother?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't mess with me!
I...
What you are doing to mother...
No.. Yes! Amazi... no!
I'm cumming!!
I've seen everything!
I'm just treating Ayahi-sama the way she told me to.
Don't joke with me!
How can something like that be a treatment?!
Miss Kirara.
Every time you peek on us you masturbate.
Even if you go back to your room, you still carry on.
I can't believe a young woman in puberty is peeking and masturbating everyday.
It's so unhealthy.
Well, I can't blame you for not getting a lover since you're a lesbian.
What are you saying?
You don't have to hide it.
Isn't it that upperclassman from you club?
Singoumei Umeko-san.
Graceful and elegant, a very cute person, isn't she?
You like the same sex rather than the opposite.
That's just twisted.
What is this nonsense?!
Tokuko-kun!
Yes, doctor!
It's all ready for you.
Isn't that right, Miss Kirara?
Why are you dressed like that?
Don't worry.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
It looks like you also need the treatment, so...
What are you doing?!
No! Stop it!
You've finally calmed down, now we can get on with the treatment.
L-Let me go!
What treatment?
I'm going to scream!
Miss Kirara...
Aren't you misunderstanding something?
What are you talking about?
Your mother is doing it of her own free will for the benefit ofyour father.
For father? Of her own free will?
That's correct.
T-That's a lie!
How can you say this is a treatment?!
That's why we're going to let you experience it for yourself.
Isn't that right, Tokuko-kun?
Yes, doctor.
W-What are you...?
Miss...
No...
It's getting moist.
N-No it's not!
Then let's take off your panties, ok?
W-Wait a second!
It's so sticky.
What a beautiful pussy.
It's pink and twitching.
No, don't look!
Please stop it...
No...
No!
Not there!
This is bad. It feels too good!
What's this feeling?
Electricity is running through my pussy, and I can't summon any strength at all...
Doctor...
She came quite easily. We're ready to go.
The camera is ready too.
Now, go on and take her virginity away.
Oh, and don't forget the medicine.
Yes!
No... it's so hot! What is this?
Miss Kirara.
It only hurts at first.
What?
Soon, you will feel like you're in heaven.
No... stop it!
For a lesbian like you I thought your first partner should be Tokuko-kun.
You can't!
Please accept my humble offer.
No... stop!
I just took your virginity, miss.
So cute.
I'll make you feel really good, so loosen up.
Look into my eyes, okay?
How is it? Does it feel good now?
Your turned on face looks so good.
I'll go faster now, ok?
Yes!
No, don't!
No... my insides...
It's hitting so deep!
I'm cumming! I can't hold on!
I can't anymore!
How was it? The treatment, that is.
These subs were done by Subdesu-h.net. These ungrateful assholes just stole our subs.
Your reaction was as good as your mother's. Just as I expected of her daughter.
Please... let... me... go.
The treatment has just started.
Let us continue, Tokuko-kun.
Okay, doctor.
No... don't lick my asshole!
Morning.
What's the matter, Kirara? You look pale.
It's nothing. I just didn't sleep well.
Take a day off school if you aren't feeling well.
I'm okay.
I just didn't sleep well and I don't want to miss school.
I see.
Is that doctor coming today as well?
Y-Yes, in the evening...
Is there something you want?
No...
It's nothing.
It's really nothing.
No...
What if someone comes to the door and sees me like this?
Madam, the body doesn't lie.
Your pussy is getting so wet with your naughty juices.
Look at it. There's a sticky thread.
And your clitoris has gotten so hard...
No!
No, no, no, you are gonna squish it!
It's coming!
I'm going to pee myself!
Isn't it nice to do this kind of thing once in a while?
This makes your nerves very sensitive, making you feel even better and relieving more stress.
This is also a part of your treatment.
I'm home!
Looks like she's early today.
So this is where you were, mother.
I thought you were with father.
No, there were some dishes that needed to be taken care of.
You're early today.
W-What about your club?
I'm not feeling well so I skipped it.
I see.
What's the matter, mother?
N-Nothing... my stomach is a bit...
I'm going to the toilet and to see how the doctor is doing with Keiichirou-san.
Please stop it.
Not here, Kirara is in the living room!
Getting off from the vibrator in your panties in front of your own daughter... What a slut you've become.
P-Please don't say those kinds of things.
Look how wet your panties are.
You were feeling it more than usual weren't you?
Yes... I got really excited.
Not there!
I'm gonna cum!
Oh no, you can't just come by yourself.
Stick your ass out.
I'm gonna put it in.
If we do it here, Kirara might find us!
You don't have to worry about Kirara anymore.
"Don't have to worry"?
Yes.
Don't worry at all.
All you have to do is think about you and your husband's treatment.
Alright. Is this okay, doctor?
Please put it in and make me cum... hurry.
So good!
More... more, doctor...
Madam, call me master from now on, not doctor.
Yes, master.
Yes! Master, I'm about to cum!
What are you doing inside my room?
I'm here for your treatment, obviously.
I was told by the doctor to do it.
Please take care of me, Miss.
All right, lets get started then.
Please take your clothes off.
W-Wait a second!
Eh?!
I'm not good enough?
N-No, it's not that, but...
Would you rather have it rough with doctor like yesterday?
No!
D-Don't.
Do it... Do it more gently...
That's...
I'm glad...
Did a kiss really feel this good?
The medicine you just swallowed, I changed it a bit from the one the doctor made.
You will feel a lot better than you did from the doctor's.
Oh? Even though you were raped last night, you're so obedient today.
I don't care what happens anymore.
Yes! More! Do it harder! Yes, this feels good... amazing!
Um...
P-Please be gentle.
Don't worry.
Just relax and let me handle everything.
Ok?
Okay... Tokuko-san...
From now on, call me master.
Yes... master
Good! Well done.
What do you want me to do to you as a reward?
K-Kiss...
Kiss me a lot.
And also make me feel good...
Master!
Yes... there!
Madam, your mouth is slacking off.
I'm sorry.
But even if I lick or suck it it doesn't get up at all.
For a man, even if he can't get it up, it's a wife's job to let him cum once in a while.
If you don't hurry up, the medicine I used on your husband will run out.
Oh? What's the matter?
I want a rock hard one instead of this floppy dick.
Master, please, I beg you to put it in.
Please, ejaculate your healthy sperm into my soaking womb!
Hurry!
Amazing!
It feels so good, Tokuko-san!
No... That place feels so good!
Yes!
What do you think? How is my technique, Kotone?
Amazing, this is my first time like this.
There!
I can't hold on! I'm cumming again and again and again!
Doctor, am I really ok?
What do you mean?
I've been living like this for more than six months.
But instead of getting better, I feel like I'm losing all my strength.
Don't think negatively.
If you worry about too many things it will affect your body.
Even if you say that...
What about my family who are so worried about me?
For Ayahi and Kirara...
Don't worry about that.
Because neither Ayahi nor Kirara need your help at all.
Yes!
My hips are moving on their own!
It feels so good.
Look, look, Keiichirou-san!
If feels so good! I love cock!.
Ayahi!
What are you doing, Ayahi?
Can't you see? I'm having sex!
A thick cock is stuck in my pussy!
Father! Look! Look!
I can fit vibrators in both my pussy and asshole!
Father, watch me cum!
Harder... do it harder!
Yes! I'm about to cum! I'm really cumming!
Cum a lot inside my pussy!
He died?
In the end, Tadamichi was arrested for making illegal drugs and murder.
If we think about it, that man was also being controlled.
And then, I took over from Keiichirou-san and became the company president.
Our stocks are soaring. They're higher than when he used to be here.
Because of this...
Yes, there!
Mister, no, not there!
No!
Kirara and I - we're both using our bodies to affect the board's decisions.
We two are living normal daily lives now.
Excuse me.
President.
I just seduced the big C.E.O. you were worried about - he's toast now.
And I got the government officials under control with the drugs.
Well done.
So... Um...
M-Master...
P-Please give us our reward!
We beg you!
Ka-boom!
Doctor's
Conspiracy
W
SubDESU-H.net