I want you two to make a suit for him.
Of course.
He's so tall!
Manager, may I leave now?
Sorry, he's very shy.
Sugawara-san.
I'll do my very best on this.
Let's run to the car!
You're soaked, you're gonna catch a cold.
Put on my shirt.
This is so large!
It looks like pajamas on me.
My shirt looks so good on you.
Hadano-san?
Despite the rainstorm,
I can feel his heart beating.
Aizawa.
No!
Hey, calm down.
Hadano-san.
It feels too good.
Stop...
I can't hold it anymore.
Hadano-san?
Don't worry, just relax.
My fingers dilated you just enough.
You're pretty tight.
You have to squeeze it.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's cum together.
I feel a little weird today.
I can't keep myself from wishing this moment lasted longer.