Minori-chan.
Kei-kun.
I suppose it doesn't make sense to say goodbye.
What! I thought I'd be getting it that time!
In-Incredible!
So cute! Thank you! I'll take care of it well.
Isn't he the famous model?
Of course not! Why would he be in a place like this!?
Let's go there.
Sure.
Sorry for making you go out with me.
Don't worry I had fun, but.
I'm really sorry about the design.
Don't worry.
I...
Always wanted something different than those
who surrounded me when I became a model.
Why do I have to focus on selling? Why can't I do what I want to do?
I don't know how to say this, but I think the
most important thing is to make others happy.
Kei-kun.
To make someone happy...
You'll have to supplement for the day you lost.
Hadano-san, I'm very sorry. I was too egotistic about the
design and I forgot that we had to make everyone else happy.
I understand that you want to do the best at what you do.
Kei-kun taught me something valuable.
I see...
That's why he was with her...
I can't anymore...
Hadano-san?
This is your punishment for not working today.
Hadano-san, stop!
It's too sudden. Why is he doing this?
Why is he doing it?
N-no!
He treated me so nicely before...
I don't want this!
No!
I'm sorry.
What's going on with me.
Why do I feel like this?