As I ended up getting cold, I invited him to
my house since I didn't live far away, but...
I never imagined that
we'd make love in her car!
Damn, I have to stop thinking about it!
We can take a bath together after all, no?
Hadano-san!
Shuudengo,
Capsule Hotel de,
Joushi ni Binetsu Tsutawaru Yoru.
It's too cold.
04. 「In the bath, two close and ardent bodies.」
No, wait...
Did you wash properly?
S-Stop, please...
Don't start...
Even if you tell me to stop...
you seem to appreciate that, am I wrong?
Hadano-san, why are you still
doing these obscene things?!
"Why?"
Because I can't help myself,
when I'm next to you.
S-Stop...
This is impossible for me.
No, not that...
Don't... Don't do that...
Here, drink that.
This situation...
It's like he was my boyfriend...
I'm tired...
Wait...
Damn...
Follow me, Aizawa-san.
You have ordered a large number
of pearls of the same type?!
I confused 50 pieces with 50,000!
What am I going to do?!
Come in!
Aizawa-san did something?
A command error.
I present you my apologies.
I take full responsibility
for her mistake.
Hadano-san?!
Subtitles made by Japon Hentai
https://japonhentai.com
Animes Hentai raw / vostfr / english subbed
softsub: торрент иваниваныч