Oh, what? You're still here?
Don't overwork yourself.
Otherwise Aizawa will call me a
terrible boss again, to my annoyance.
Oh, you were watching.
Thank you for supporting
the series the entire time.
You should see your face right now.
It's like you're saying you
don't want this to end already.
You have your cute side too.
That face... it's so irresistible...
Looks like I have to teach you a lesson
for taking that attitude with me...
Here, this is Vol. 2 of the
comics for the original work.
The anime had its climax with Kei's show ending,
but the original work is still going.
Aizawa and I skip meetings, go to the aquarium...
and the backstage of the show is also featured.
Come on now, you have to behave yourself...
What, you want to hear some lines from Vol. 2?
Guess I have no choice.
Come over to my place...
We don't have to make the last train...
There's no way I can go home like this...
Well?
If you're wondering how those lines fit into
the story, check out the original work as well.
Also, this marks the end of this anime, but it's cool
if you want to rewatch as many times as you want.
I'm also looking forward to
seeing you again once more...
Alright then, I'll see you around.
Translation: Haru
Timing: Haru
QA: Fogil
softsub: торрент иваниваныч