At last, you finished the dress.
Yeah. We were at the doors of the event, but we did it.
Man you worked hard.
You could say that again.
Oh, now you're all that eh? Do you want a reward?
Reward?
Hey...
Hadano-san?
This is for everything you've done.
There's people outside.
Don't moan.
Don't ask for the impossible!
You know you want it here too.
No!
You like this, don't you?
We're doing it in this place...
We shouldn't be!
This is my favorite set.
This one brings up the most memories for me.
I failed the task so Hadano-san had to cover for me.
I couldn't live with the guilt.
Man you're strong...
You're wrong.
You taught me that.
I'm glad I was able do work with you.
Me too.
I only had faith because you were involved.
Kei-kun?
Maybe I don't know her as well as Hadano-san does...
I always envied that.
I've always wanted her to look at me like him.
I want to be by your side!
Because I like you.
I'm leaving.