Do you know how you look like right now?
Raw: Muchohentai
Subs: Kawaii Neko Team
Shuudengo, Capsule Hotel de Joushi ni Binetsu Tsutawaru Yoru
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Aizawa, there's still a long way to go!
Hadano-san, today, I'll get right to the point!
They're at it again.
They get along very well.
Since when!?
Because of you, we had to leave.
I'm sorry.
What do we do now?
We can't go back home.
What do you think of this place?
"We don't have a choice" is what he said...
There's someone sleeping in my room
and he wont wake up.
I ended up in his room.
How embarrassing.
Sorry to bother,
can you lead me your charger, please?
Yeah.
There's a plug on the back wall.
Ummm, your breasts...
Hey!
Do you know how you look like right now?
I love the look on your face.
W-Wait!
Come on, you can't moan.
No!
I told you, don't moan.
Hadano-san?
It's really wet.
I don't want to.
Your words don't match your actions.
No!
Hadano-san!
Usually, you're really a pain in the ass,
but today, you're really cute!
No!
What should I do?
If this continues,
I...
No, stop it!
Don't do that!
Just relax.
You're tight!
No, not there!
I'm going to feel weird...
Again...!