Kei-kun looks incredible!
He's glowing!
Y-yeah!
God, you drank too much... We won't
find any vacancy at this time...
I'm sorry...
Hadano-san...
What's up?
Kei-kun confessed to me...
Aizawa, listen to the first.
Sure.
I told you that I had something to tell you
once the event was over. Remember?
Yeah.
I love you.
Aizawa?
I love you too.
But what about Kei-kun?
I turned him down. I told him I liked someone else.
Someone is sleeping in my room again!
A-and that's why I came to your room.
Do you know the kind of face you have right now?
You're the only one I show this kind of face to...
I would only do those kinds of things with you too.
Don't make any noise.
But...
Hadano-san!
Minori...
You shouldn't make any noise...