This hour, already?
Hadano-san?
He could have woken me...
Damn!
I'll be late for the meeting!
Shuudengo,
Capsule Hotel de,
Joushi ni Binetsu Tsutawaru Yoru.
Just... Just in time...
02. 「A slight heat in the fitting room.」
Ouch...
You arrive at the last minute.
When you're ready,
join me in the costume room.
Ha... Hadano-san!
Hurry up.
We've just received it.
Although I put forward some strict requirements,
surprisingly, you've performed well.
I was right to have
confided it to you.
I don't know what to say to him,
after telling me that with such sincerity...
That said, she lacks impact.
Would you like to try it?
Huh? Me?!
Hadano-san...
I have a favor to ask you, please...
See, the zipper is stuck...
Is this an invitation?
Of course not!
She suits you perfectly.
No...
Stop...
Be careful, you'll dirty the dress.
Open your legs.
No, not here...
You're already very wet.
No, this isn't true...
Hadano-san...
Aizawa...
Leave the cab.
Please...
My apologies. My joke was very heavy.
Hadano-san...
I don't understand...
Subtitles made by Japon Hentai
https://japonhentai.com
Animes Hentai raw / vostfr / english subbed
softsub: торрент иваниваныч