Is it that late already?!
Hadano-san?!
Would've it have killed him to wake me up?
Damn,
I have to return the room key!
Brought to you by Kawai Neko Team and MuchoHentai
Capsule Hotel de Joushi ni Binetsu Tsutawaru Yoru Shuudengo
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
Ugh, I made it just in time.
Ouch!
You came just at the right time.
When you're done here, come to the fitting room with me.
H-Hadano-san!
Hurry up.
It just arrived.
I was critiqued it heavily it but these bastards are quite stubborn.
I'm glad that I left it in your hands.
I don't know how to answer him after he was that sincere with me.
However,
I think the most important thing is the impact.
Would you mind trying it on?
Me?
Hadano-san,
I need some help.
H-Hm!
I can't close the zipper.
Are you trying to seduce me?
O-Of course not!
It suits you well.
No!
St...
stop!
Hey,
you're gonna ruin the dress.
Spread your legs.
No!
Not there!
You're already so wet.
No.
Not that!
Hadano-san...
Aizawa...
Get out, please!
Pl...
Please.
Sorry.
My joke went a little too far.
Hadano-san...?
I...
don't understand!