Oh, that reminds me, Kei-kun is really happy.
Eh?!
He mentioned it was fun to go shopping with you.
I enjoyed it as well.
Can I have a moment, manager?
Ah, sure.
Oh no, the fireworks festival is today!
Oh, it's really a shame about that.
This photo shoot will run late.
I missed it last year because of work
and it's the same for this year.
Thank you very much for your hard work!
Great job, everyone!
See you next time!
Let's take a detour.
Eh, I don't exactly have so much free time.
Says the person who was fussing about fireworks.
A cute cottage!
What's here?
It's my secret hideout.
Come on inside.
It's amazing!
I wanted to have a work space for private use.
That's really nice. I'd like to try working in this setting.
Well, let's leave that for next time.
Come over here.
Huh?
I designed it when I had time in hopes to
learn more about Japanese style clothing.
Thanks for waiting.
I've also designed one for men.
How is it?
I-It really suits you.
It's such a waste. You would have looked
cool if you kept your mouth shut.
The same goes for you, too.
Uhm...
Hadano-san...
Your nether part here is giving a
good reaction when I stimulate it.
You're teasing me.
It's in the right spot!
Insert it inside of you in this position.
It feels really embarrassing having to
put it inside on my own.
Start moving.
You mean, on my own?
Don't worry.
I'll be holding your hands.
I can't...
Being like this...
Wait...
It's too much...
It is as if we are lovers.
That thought makes me really happy.