Kei-kun was very happy.
He said that he had a lot of fun shopping with you.
I should be saying that instead...
Do you have a moment?
Sure!
Today is the Firework's Festival!
Really? That's a shame. This photo shoot took way too long.
Last year I couldn't go either because of
work & it looks like the same this year...
Good work everyone!
See you later!
We're going to take a detour.
What? But I got stuff to do...
A little while ago you were super excited for the fireworks.
What a nice cabin!
Where are we?
My escape.
Come on in.
Incredible!
I wanted a place to work in private and I got just that.
I'm jealous! I'd love to design here!
Well you could next time.
Come!
I designed this when I had some down time. It
would help me as reference for the next model.
Sorry for the wait. I made a male model too. What do you think?
Y-you look very nice.
Hadano-san you look amazing when
you're quiet. Too bad you talk too much...
I could say the same about you.
Umm...
Hadano-san...
What a great reaction.
Don't be mean.
It's touching me!
Stay like that.
It's like I'm doing it to myself. It's so embarrassing.
Move.
No way! I have to do it myself!?
Don't worry. I'll hold your hand.
Not... this...
Hold on!
No! No!
It feels like... we're a couple...
I feel... so happy!