I wanted to ask him to take me near my
house so I wouldn't catch a cold, but...
I never thought I'd end up doing something like that in the car!
Damn...
I wont think about it anymore!
Do you want us to bathe together?
Hadano-san!
It's cold!
H-hey!
Did you wash well?
S-stop please.
No...
You ask me to stop...
But you seem to be enjoying this.
No!
Hadano-san, why...
do you always do this kind of thing?!
"Why" you say?
Because as soon as I'm with you,
I can't help it.
No, stop!
Impossible.
I can't take it anymore.
N-no, I'll...
Here, take some water.
This situation...
It's like he'd be my boyfriend.
I'm tired.
Hey...
Damn...
Miss Aizawa.
Do you have a moment?
Here is the result of your order.
A thousand mother-of-pearl pearls, fifty
thousand coulored pearls, that's a mistake!
What should I do?!
Come in!
Aizawai was wrong?
See for yourself!
My apologies!
I'll take responsibility for this mistake.
Hadano-san?!