Do you know what facial expression
you are showing right now?
Shuudengo,
Capsule Hotel de,
Joushi ni Binetsu Tsutawaru Yoru.
1. 「I feel the warmth of my boss at the Hotel Capsule.」
You haven't finished, Aizawa!
I'll be very clear, Hadano-san!
It starts again...
That's true, they look like old friends,
don't you think?
Where?!
We missed the last train, by your fault.
I'm sorry...
What are we going to do?
We aren't going
to sleep outside, either.
What do you think of this place?
I didn't really have
the choice, but...
Anyone sleep in my room?!
He doesn't intend to wake up...
I ended up going to his room...
What clumsy I'm...
Excuse me, where can I plug my charger?
Ah, you'll find an outlet,
on the back wall.
Say, your cleavage...
Say...
Do you know what facial expression
you are showing right now?
I like the expression of your face.
W-Wait...
Don't moan.
Don't moan, I told you.
Hadano-san?
Unbelievable...
No...
Acts speak louder than words
Ha... Hadano-san...
Usually, you're cautious about me.
I find you very cute, today.
No...
What am I going to do?
If he continues, I'll...
No, stop... Don't do that...
Relax.
She's all tight...
No, not there!
I'm starting to lose my head!
https//japonhentai.com
softsub: торрент иваниваныч