I caused Hadano-san to get in trouble because of me.
You're here.
Hadano-san!
I caused you trouble. I'm so sorry!
You don't have to worry. You do so much better
witnout having to worry about anything.
Not satisfied?
Of course not!
It's fine, it's obvious that I am.
There is so much work to do, and I'm in everyone's way.
Who would've thought you'd have a cute side.
Hey!
Stop mocking me!
Why do you pretend to be so strong?
You can't do that Hadano-san!
This way no one can see us.
That's not what I meant!
There is no one here.
This is bad. I shouldn't be doing this in the company.
Stop!
I'm cumming!!!
I'm opposing Hadano-san less and less every time.
I love it! The design adjusts to perfection.
I love your sense of style
I always get yelled at by Hadano-san about it.
Well...