It's so hot that I can't think of any designs.
I wish that air conditioner did something.
I'm dying overhere.
We can't do anything with this heat.
Alright! I'll fix it. Everyone go home.
Hadano-san, could I help you with anything?
I told everyone they could go.
Why are you talking to me like that!
Oh be quiet, you're just making me get hotter.
Hey Aizawa, do you think I'm a good boss?
I would've never thought you'd worry about those things.
I actually think about it very seriously.
Nevertheless you showed me that side
of you so it makes me a little happy.
I can't win with her.
Hadano-san?
His tongue is so hot.
I think I'll go mad with this heat.
Hadano-san...
No! He's doing everything at the same time!
No! I'm sweaty and it's embarrassing!
I'm sorry, I can't resist any longer!
His body is so hot. I think I'm going to melt!
Why are you reacting like that? It makes you look too cute!
Minori...
Let's cum together!
Do you only see me as a co-worker?
Tell me what you think.
What I feel? What would happen to our relationship
if I truly told him what I'm thinking right now?
Hey, Aizawa.
When this project is done,
there's something I have to tell you.