l... l... l...
l'm cumming!
As you can see from the three examples on the previous page...
Even though it's the same verb...
...depending on the preposition following it, the translation changes.
Keeping that in mind, please work on question three.
Hey.
Togawa.
lf you're going to be late, act like you're sorry when you walk in!
Did l do something wrong?
Guys with no manners like you need to start over at kindergarten.
Professor. l want some booby milk!
Oh, l'm sorry.
My body moved on its own because you were being inappropriate.
lt's dangerous, so be good, okay?
That's enough for today.
Ayaka!
l... l don't have the confidence to continue being a Professor.
What's wrong?
There's a student in my class that always touches me...
l can't take it anymore...
Professor Sayo, goodbye!
Hey! Hold it right there!
Please don't go, Ayaka!
They tease you because you're popular.
You think so?
l'll protect you Sayo. So, please stop crying.
Thank you, Ayaka...
Stand up straighter...
Stick your chest out...
Okay...
L... Like this?
Put a little more strength in your hips.
Huh?
lt looks like you're tense somewhere else.
This needs to relax.
P... Professor?
Well? Will this relax it?
Yes... but...
But what?
N...Nothing... Well...
Professor... l...
l can't...
lt's okay, you can cum!
Well? Are you relaxed now?
Y...Yes... l'm much more relaxed now.
But, why did you...
You were too tense there.
You needed to relax in order to focus on practice.
l did it especially for you, because you're so cute.
Well, good luck!
Professor Yuuki.
l'm sorry my twin brother caused problems today.
Just because you're his brother doesn't mean you have to apologize.
l'll make sure to warn him.
By the way, would it be possible to receive your instruction, please?
Sure, no holding back just because you're captain.
Thank you.
Well then...
Feel free to hit me!
Okay!
M... Mercy...
You need to practice more.
l heard you've caused another problem...
You know already, Father?
Call me Chairman!
l get complaints every time you...
...overstep your boundaries as a teacher.
Even though you're my daughter,
that doesn't mean l can continue to protect you.
l brought you coffee.
Oh, Professor Kitano. Thank you.
You must be exhausted from instructing the karate club.
Thanks Kitano.
Ayaka! l don't want this to happen again, so l'm going to suspend you...
...from instructing the karate club for a while.
T-That's not fair, Father!
Chairman, that's taking it a bit too far.
Plus, ever since Professor Yuuki took over as coach,
the club roster has doubled.
lt's great!
They've taken up both studying and sports.
She sets a great example.
T... That's not...
But she's too stubborn.
l'm afraid the arranged marriage meeting...
...won't work out because of it, either.
Father, you're making me sound like a wild child!
You just now realized this?
Why... am l doing this here...
My body suddenly felt numb, and my pussy...
No...
l can't stop myself...
Why is my body...
l look so embarrassing...
lf someone were to see me...
But l'm so hot, l can't stop...
l've never felt like this before...
Why are there clothes here?
Oh? lf it isn't Professor Ayaka.
l thought l heard strange sounds...
l wouldn't have guessed that Professor Ayaka was masturbating on campus.
Leave... Get out of here!
Yeah, right. You perverted professor...
Look at you. You're trying to seduce me...
G... Get away from me!
lf your pussy is lonely, l'll fix that for you.
Your pussy is wet and twitching.
S... Stop.
l'll go down on you, Professor.
N...No...
Here, suck on this Professor.
No, l can't resist him...
Thanks for kicking in my nose. lt still hurts.
l'll make your pussy a slobbering mess.
l came... But l can still keep on going!
Stop!
Are you sure you don't want it?
Not him... l... lt's my first time...
lf you beg, l'll stop.
T... That's...
Here it comes!
No! Stop! Please stop! l'm begging.
Let me see...
But l can't stop myself!
lt's tight!
Take this!
No! Please stop!
This is amazing!
Get up!
Y... Yes...
This is great!
Wow! l came a lot...
Damn, you came too? l can still cum again.
Oh well... Suck my pussy juice-covered cock...
...and make me cum again.
lt smells! l was raped by this disgusting thing?
That can't be! No! l can't stand it!
Yes! l hit his vital point...
Huh? His vital point!?
What was that sound?
P-Professor Kitano...
Professor Yuuki, what is this...
Togawa! Togawa is...
Kiai General Hospital Togawa! Togawa is...
Kiai General Hospital
l can't believe l did that to a student...
lt's okay. l'll give him emergency first aid.
Please call an ambulance!
Professor Kitano... l...
But why did they come to the shower room?
And why was l so horny?
lt's Yuuki.
Oh, come in!
l've been looking forward to you visiting me.
Y...You're doing better than l thought...
Huh? ln what way am l doing better?!
lt's your fault l'm like this.
Jeez... You've got to be kidding me!
l... l'm sorry.
Come here.
You almost killed me...
Come closer and apologize.
Y... Yes.
l'm sorry.
But this is bad for you...
A professor raped a student and tried to murder him...
Don't be foolish!
l can tell the police what really happened!
l'll take responsibility for seriously injuring you.
You're the chairman's daughter, right?
lf people find out the chairman's daughter almost killed a student...
The academy itself might have to fold.
l don't plan on talking to the police.
But you're going to make it up to me for the rest of your life.
What am l supposed to...
Turn your ass this way.
What?
Hurry up!
N...No! Stop!
You've rendered me useless.
What are you going to do about it?
No... That's...
First, make me hard.
Make you hard? What am l supposed to do?
Suck it.
Hurry up.
l'll lick your pussy too.
That feels good...
The way you use your tongue will get me hard.
You're getting horny too.
l knew you were a pervert.
That's mean...
Hey, don't stop!
lt's hard...
Then use your dirty nipples and rub it.
Like this?
lt feels good right?
Your pussy juices are flowing.
No... Don't say that...
lt's been a while, so l can keep cumming.
Make me cum with your pussy next.
You're not going to say no, are you Professor?
Togawa
Like this?
That's great, Professor!
Your hot cock is inside me!
lt feels sweeter than last time...
l'm feeling pleasure from fucking a student...
Am l really a pervert?
You're such a slut.
You're shaking your ass on your own.
You're such a dirty woman.
Turn around.
You know you like it!
Please... No more...
What? You know you're loving it.
For some reason it feels good...
My body wants to be pleasured.
l don't know who l am anymore!
l'm gonna cum! l'm gonna cum! No...
l'm gonna cum!
Then l'm gonna cum again too!
lt's hot inside!
l'm gonna cum!
Suck the rest of the cum out.
Togawa. l want you to explain these pictures!
Explain? That's what l'd like you to do!
What did you do to my brother?
All l can tell from these pictures is that you seduced, raped...
...then tried to kick my brother to death.
Th... That's wrong...
W... What do you think you're all doing?
We all looked up to you.
S... stop...
Stop? l'm sure that's what my brother wanted.
What did my dear brother taste like?
We want you to check how we taste as well.
No!