Good morning, Kouhei.
Good morning, Yoake.
Isn't today a warm day that's ideal
for an afternoon nap as well?
Yeah!
This greenhouse now looks more beautiful.
It's a sanctuary now compared
to how it was back then.
Yeah, that's right.
Well then, good night.
Are you going back to sleep again?
Now that I think about it, this place
was in a bad shape back then.
Female Companion
– Tightly Hug Me –
Soikano: Gyutto Dakishimete The Animation.
– 3 Months Ago –
This rooftop greenhouse being called a "birdcage"
had been left unattended in the past,
and became a place where people rarely come.
On that particular day, I found one of its windows open.
I thought it was a nice place for being
secluded and had a nap inside.
I always see the same dream.
I keep falling down beneath a deep blue sky.
This dream of me falling down is like
a manifestation of my own helplessness.
Having no particular goal, I couldn't
bring myself to go anywhere.
On this particular day, my dull
everyday life took a detour.
I can hear a breath of someone sleeping.
And I feel a somewhat warm and soft sensation...
Wh-Who is this girl? I'm sure
that she wasn't here before!
She has a silky smooth and beautiful hair.
What's with these squishy cheeks
urging me to touch them subconsciously?!
...and also, these warm...
G-Good morning...
Good morning.
Uhh... Umm, who were you again?
Umm, nice to meet you.
My name is Kozuya Kouhei.
Uhh... Oh, right...
You see, I am...
...pillow.
Huh, a pillow?
Not a pillow...
Kumakura...
I'm Kumakura Yoake.
Kumakura, I'm sure that
I've heard that name before...
Oh, you're the SS-Rare girl in our class!
She hasn't been seen since the year started.
Why is my special super rare and mysterious
classmate in such a place like this?
SS-Rare?
Ah, nah... It's nothing.
By the way, why are you here?
That's because...
I'm the club president of the gardening club!
The gardening club had been disbanded
if I remember it correctly.
It's only suspended, not disbanded!
I'm the one who's keeping
the key of the greenhouse...
Huh?
Oh... Oh... Where is it, where is it!
Maybe it's up here.
There's no way that it would be there, right?
I found it!
No way!
Oh... I'm glad that I managed to find the key.
That's dangerous!
Oh, thank goodness that you
were just below to catch me.
Thank you!
Th-That's good to hear...
I-It tickles when you try to speak!
Oh my, do we have a guest?
Tsubame!
P-President?!
Oh my, I already am retired
so I'm not the student council president anymore.
That's right!
Tsubame is my personal pillow!
She's talking casually with the president?
Or rather, why is she in a maid uniform?
This is bad, I have to go back to the classroom...
Kouhei, are you going back already?
Come on, let's go.
You see, I'm...
Listen, the greenhouse is open
whenever I'm around...
So you can sleep here whenever you want.
Is that so, I understand. Thank you!
Our afternoon nap alliance is now established!
You should sleep at home and not here, okay?
Okay—!
Chiyuki.
Kou-kun, where are you going?
Well... Just somewhere...
...and that's what happened.
I see, so Kuma-chan is going here at school.
And what's more, an afternoon nap alliance...
I haven't been getting enough sleep lately too.
Hey, listen, Kou-kun. Can I come
with you and have a look in there?
Hey there, Kumakura.
So it looks like this now...
Kouhei!
J-J-J-J-J-Jeez!
Well, the more the merrier.
So you've been studying alone
here all this time, Kuma-chan.
I'm not alone.
Tsubame helps me with my lessons.
Sounds great...
I want to be tutored by Katagiri-senpai too...
Oh yeah, how does having a study
session with everyone sounds?
That sounds great! My grades
have been going down lately.
I'd be glad to help if you want.
What day would be good?
Oh! How about you, Kumakura? You don't have
to force yourself if you don't want to go.
I'm going to join and study too!
I don't want to be left out!
It will be on the first day of Golden Week, then.
The place will be at Kou-kun's!
So it's gonna be at my house?!
We'll welcome ourselves!
We will!
Pardon our intrusion.
Nice to meet you, I'm his younger sister, Riku.
I-I'm their cousin, Hanatsuka Aika.
N-Nice to meet you.
For sparing your time today on helping
my undeserving brother, I'm truly—
Huh?!
Oh my, Riku-san. Hello there!
K-K-K-K-K-Katagiri-senpai, why are you here?!
Why are you in a maid uniform?
Oh, so the upperclassman she admires
and always talks about was Katagiri-senpai.
Kumakura-senpai, are you
reading "The Tragic New Recruit"?
Yeah, isn't the latest release amazing?
Who knew that the captain...
Please don't spoil the story for me!
I was a little worried about Kumakura being shy,
but it seems that everything worked out.
Just like this, and the desolate "birdcage"
with just Kumakura and Katagiri-senpai
have gradually grown lively.
I can't eat anymore...
G-Gosh, Kouhei!
What do you think are you doing in such a place!
Sorry, I wasn't able to hold myself back.
But, Kouhei...
You got that much aroused because of me, right?
Yeah, I got like this from looking at you.
R-Right... Then, I have to take responsibility for it.
You're still not used to doing this?
Isn't that a given?
There's no way that I'll get used to
doing something so embarrassing.
Alright then, I'll get on it!
Are you alright?
Does this feel good?
Yeah, you're the best!
I see.
You really are cute down here, Kouhei.
Wait, Kouhei! What's with this pose?
We should make each other
feel good while we're at it.
You feel uneasy being the only
one with his dick exposed, huh?
It's unfair of you to drag me
with you into this, Kouhei!
I wonder what you're talking about
when you're so wet down here.
D-Don't lick me down there, Kouhei!
Aren't you licking me as well, Yoake?
You are right, but...
So this is a Yoake flavored juice.
It tastes exquisitely delectable.
Gosh! You're a pervert, Kouhei!
Now that it turned out like this...
I'm gonna counterattack you as well!
It's coming out...
It's alright!
I'm fine if it's yours!
Kouhei... You're shooting it inside my mouth!
I'm sorry, Yoake. I'm still...
Yeah, it's alright.
Come to me, Kouhei!
Yoake...
Your thing went inside me!
Kouhei... You're being intense right off the bat!
I'm sorry, I'm being too rough on you.
Th-That's not the case! Umm...
I've been holding myself back since earlier.
This feels incredibly good!
I see, so you like it rough?
Th-That's...
I-I love it!
If you're the one doing it,
I'll love it no matter what it is!
Kouhei, what are you doing?
No...
I like your tits so much, Yoake!
I-I'm glad to hear that you like them...
But I just came earlier...
If you fondle my tits right now...
I'll end up feeling
too much pleasure from this!
It reverberates in my belly as
you keep shoving it inside me!
No, this is really bad!
I'll end up moaning loudly!
It's alright, let me hear more
of that cute voice of yours!
Idiot, idiot!
I don't care anymore,
even if someone comes here
and ends up catching us!
We'll deal with it when it happens.
Kouhei, you got bigger inside me!
You're stretching me wide inside! Wow!
Wait, wait! Kouhei, I'm gonna...
Could it be that you're about to come?
How did you know?
That's because you're making
an incredibly erotic face, Yoake!
Hey, come together with me too!
I want us to do it together at the same time!
Alright, Yoake!
Shoot it out!
Give me your semen just like this!
I'm coming!
Okay! Kouhei, Kouhei!
Kouhei! Kouhei!
Huh, the pool?
I just happened to get my hands
on tickets for a few people.
What a pain!
But won't an afternoon nap
at the poolside feel good?
That is worthy of consideration.
Well, let's have the members of the afternoon
nap alliance gather and participate.
It's going to be fun, isn't it?
This place is more amazing than I expected.
Kou-kun, sorry for the wait!
Oh! Chiyuki, that was fast.
How is it, Kou-kun?
I'm sorry, it took longer to help Yoake-chan change.
I feel sleepy after all...
Kou-kun, where are you looking at?
Ah, could it be...
Nah, I'm not looking, I'm not!
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting, everyone.
I don't have any other swimsuit
with me besides this one...
School swimsuits are fantastic swimwear as well!
Thank you.
Alright, let's play to our heart's content today!
Yay!
Here, right here!
Yes, right there.
Kozuya-san, I'm truly grateful
to you for Yoake-chan.
Huh?
And even today as well. It's all
thanks to you and everyone.
I wasn't able to take Yoake-chan out
from that "birdcage" just by myself.
Even at that time when the greenhouse
was about to be locked down.
We just helped out a little.
Yoake herself spent a great effort on it.
I got an information about some truants
using the rooftop as a place to hang out,
so I went here to see for myself.
It seems to be true.
Especially you, Kumakura Yoake!
You never attended a single class ever
since you started your second year.
And also, Katagiri-senpai!
Why is someone like you wearing
such a lowly attire in the campus?!
Well, that's...
But this place is at least under the gardening club.
You're yet to take care of this garden.
Aren't you all just hanging
around here to chatter?
The flowers are gone and the weeds grew so much.
This garden looks so miserable!
Th-Then we, the gardening club,
are going to rehabilitate this greenhouse.
And there will be no problems if we open
this place up for all the students, right?
Huh?
Let's do this, Kumakura.
I'll help out as well!
I'm gonna help too!
M-Me too!
Yeah, I'm doing it!
Interesting. If that's so, I'll give you a month.
Make sure to submit a weekly
written report of your activities to me.
The submission deadline is to be strictly observed.
This deal will be off if you'll get even a little late.
And also, studying is every student's duty.
If anyone fails to fulfill that duty,
I'll get this place shut down at once.
It means that we can't be
loitering or be late now, huh?
That's dangerous!
Please take this.
Alright.
This month has been a long one, huh?
Yeah, but it's all going to end after
submitting this club activity report.
Huh?
What's the matter?
It's not here... Our activity report isn't here!
No way, could you have dropped it somewhere?
Damn it! I won't be able to make
it in time if even if I rewrite it!
Forgive me, Kumakura!
Here.
Huh?
Kumakura!
Kuma-chan, why are you here?
You left this at the garden earlier.
Kumakura, you're...
Kumakura?
Huh? Is she really Kumakura-san?
Kumakura-san, your seat is right here.
Everyone's waiting for you!
Kumakura!
I want to thank you, Kumakura.
Yeah...
You managed to go by yourself.
I... I...
When I thought that I'd be unable
to spend time with you anymore...
I absolutely don't want that to happen!
Kumakura...
I did something which I'm not used to,
so I'm all worn out now.
It's been a while since I last
had you as a pillow like this.
Listen, Kumakura...
Hey, Kouhei...
Kumakura, I'm...
Kouhei, I'm...
...in love with you!
Wh-What's wrong with the two of you?
It's embarrassing when you both
keep staring at me like that!
Hey—!
Kuma-chan, let's play together!
Kumakura-senpai, let's do the swimsuit
dialogues from "Yumeka the Magician"!
There, there!
Kumakura-senpai, no—!
Ain't it fine? Ain't it fine?
Alright, then. I think that you're tired
already so let's call it a day, Yoake.
Kouhei, you are my pillow,
so you can't go home.
Wait, Kouhei!
You're supposed to be my pillow,
so you shouldn't be moving!
Wait... No way! Kouhei...
You can't touch me like that!
Kouhei, do you like my tits?
Yeah, I love them a lot.
I'm happy that my tits are up to your liking.
Kouhei!
Yoake, you're wet.
What do you want to do to me?
Isn't that obvious?
Th-Then, I'll do the same.
Yoake, you're all mushy and gooey down here!
Your dick too...
It's getting harder and harder in my hand!
Are you feeling good right here, Kouhei?
But, not yet!
I-I wonder if this feels good for you?
It's something called titfuck and blowjob.
Yoake...
Kouhei, you taste good down here!
How is it?
I looked up and studied about this for you!
Jeez... You're such a cute girl, Yoake!
I love it when you pat my head...
Keep doing it!
Okay.
Kouhei, I love you a lot!
Your dick is throbbing in my mouth.
I can't hold it in, Yoake!
Shoot it out! Shoot it out!
Kouhei, you came a lot!
I'm going to give you lots of service for today,
so leave everything to me.
It went in!
Kouhei, your hands!
Okay.
When we do this, we look so much like lovers!
Yeah... We're lovers, aren't we?
That's right... We are, right?
Kouhei, you're reaching deep inside me!
I feel happy to be connected with you like this!
My body is so delighted!
Don't! You shouldn't move yet, Kouhei!
I'm supposed to be the one servicing you!
This is incredible!
I can feel your shape inside me as I move by myself!
Yoake, you're so cute that
I can't stop myself anymore!
Right there! Your thing really does feel good!
It's sloshing inside me and it's
making an incredibly lewd sound!
We're making this sound together, Yoake!
Doesn't it feel so good when
we're moving together?
Kouhei, are you feeling good as well?
Are you feeling me down there?
Yeah... I can feel you with my whole body!
You're seeing the part where we are connected!
It's embarrassing!
You look sexy when you're embarrassed!
Gosh! No matter what I do, I end up sexy for you...
Yoake, your insides are already a perfect fit for me!
What's with that, Kouhei?!
That sounds so lewd!
It's squeezing tightly and
you're coiling so much on me!
Th-That's not true! I'm not really...
I don't know what you're talking about, I'm...
I'm not that lewd!
Then, shall we stop now?
No, you can't!
Kouhei, you're a meanie!
I get it, I get it already!
Keep having sex with me.
The truth is, I'm a lewd girl!
Yoake!
Do it more!
Mess me up even more with your dick!
Your dick is rubbing against my deepest part!
I love that! I love it when you're
grinding against me deep in my pussy!
Come! Let's come together like this
and shoot it inside me! Shoot it!
Come as you feel good from me!
I'm gonna come too! Coming... Coming... Coming!
Yoake!
I keep falling down beneath a deep blue sky.
I see that same dream every day.
However, that's all in the past now.
Good morning, Yoake.
Good morning, Kouhei!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization