It's really pouring, isn't it?
Eh? Ah... Yeah...
Nuresuke JK Amayadori Rape
Sopping Wet Highschool Girl Rainy Rapeover
I-If you won't mind, want to use this?
I don't mind it, thank you.
How about you, mister. Are you alright?
You'll catch a cold if you stay drenched like that.
Ah... Yeah...
At least an hour...
The bus here is usually late.
The driver sometimes dozes off at the station.
I didn't know that it will be pouring today.
Is your house far away from here?
It's about an hour away from here.
There's really nothing to see on where I live.
No one else usually rides on the bus here.
It really is the boonies out there.
So that's how it is...
Are you perhaps not from here?
Ah... Yeah...
I'm came from Tokyo for a negotiation
in the client's business office.
You're from Tokyo? Isn't your job tough?
Oh... Nah...
Are you perhaps married?
Yeah... I have a wife and a daughter.
She's about your age.
So, you already have a child.
She used to be cute.
But she won't even talk with me nowadays.
Is that so?
My wife too, she doesn't talk to me much.
I'm totally being treated like I'm some sort of burden.
Who do they think is the reason
that they have food on the table.
What's the matter?
Hey, no one comes here, right?
Yes, it's always that way.
No... Mister! S-Stop...
Please stop!
H-Hey...
W-Wait!
I won't, I won't stop.
No, no!
No... I don't want this!
Stop! No way!
Eh... If you're doing that...
Ouch!
No, no way, no!
Please don't... bite me!
Don't you have something to say?
I'm sorry!
Hey...
Hey... What are you doing?
No, no way!
What's this? It feels disgusting!
Such a thing is in between my breasts!
So soft! They're so soft!
It feels great... It feels great!
No! No way!
Why... Why is this happening?
Something's dripping out!
Something's dripping out of its tip!
No, no way! I don't want this!
Please stop... doing such a thing!
Good! Good!
Please... forgive me already...
I can't take this!
It's thrusting deep in my throat and I can't breathe!
If he keeps thrusting harshly like this...
No way, I feel like I'll throw up!
I'll end up swallowing that ooze before...
I swallowed it... I swallowed it!
I can't take this, it's unbearable!
Just stay still!
Umm...
I'm putting it in!
Doesn't it hurt? Isn't it unbearable?
But you see, I'm the same as well!
I'm also tormented like you! That's why it's okay!
Hey... You started moaning!
Huh? How is it? Come on!
Come on!
Why is such a thing happening to me?
Isn't this what they call 'rape'?
Am I getting raped?
By a stranger that I just met earlier?
Why is this happening to me?
Did I do something bad to deserve this?
Why am I getting raped?
I can't get enough of this!
I'm gonna come!
No, stop thrashing around!
Look, there's nothing you can do about this!
Sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry if you get pregnant from this!
It's coming! It's coming out! I'm coming!
No... No more!
No... Stop!
No...
Why... Won't this be over yet?
What will happen to me?
Is he going to do this to me even more?
I'm going to break if this goes on!
Somebody help me! I have to call for help!
I have to say that I'm getting raped!
I have to say that I'm getting raped
and about to get impregnated!
I have to shout! Shout for somebody to help me!
Hurry! Come here, anyone! Hurry up!
The bus isn't coming! It's not coming!
That's right... No one will come here!
Even though I already knew that
neither the bus nor anyone will come...
No! It's going in deep!
It feels good! That's it, squeeze me!
I'm gonna come again! I'll shoot it out!
I'm sorry, I'm gonna come inside you again!
No way, stop—!
But it's gonna come out already!
I'm going to pour a lot
of my baby seeds inside you!
No! No way! I don't want to!
I'll... I'll get pregnant!
Stop—!
It's pouring... inside me...
His fresh and warm stuff...
Will I end up having a baby?
If that happens, I won't be able to go to school!
If I end up having a baby...
What am I going to do from now on?
P-Please... tell me!
Tell you what?
Why did you do this...
Why did this have to happen to me?
What should I do...
There's no particular reason.
Look, it got lively again!
You're amazing!
No matter how many times I come, I still get hard again.
Don't we still have time before the bus arrives?
We can still a do it at least one more time, right?
I'm going back to Tokyo before the day is over.
And then you have to make sure
to continue going to school.
Go to school and take care of your studies...
Graduate and become an upright
member of the society.
You're cute and you have this amazing body
so you'll surely live a happy life, right?
Come on, one more time to finish this up!
I'm going to pour my sperm inside you, okay?
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization