Why did someone I just met earlier...
do something like that to me?
And I thought that he looked like a kind person...
Sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry if you get pregnant from this!
It's coming! It's coming out! I'm coming!
Pregnant... Where babies come from...
No way, I'll get pregnant from this...
N-No! Why am I doing this?
This isn't right...
It isn't really like that...
No, even though this is wrong...
My body is gradually feeling hotter!
Even though a cruel thing has been done to me...
Even though shooting sperm inside me is bad...
I want more of it...
More!
It feels good, it feels good! I can't stop!
Why does it feel this good?
Not enough... This is not enough!
I want something bigger than this
to rape me!
Nuresuke JK Amayadori Rape Sono Ato
Sopping Wet JK Rainy R*peover - After
That's not it, I'm...
There's no way that I can be forgiven!
Even so...
Why am I craving even for something like that?!
What am I doing, coming back in this place?
I've been dreaming about it all the time.
About what I did on that girl,
and what I should do about it.
Apologize... Or maybe, yet...
It's pouring again.
I find it puzzling as well. Even after having
something like that done to me...
I couldn't make myself hate you, mister.
I want to confirm my feelings...
I wanted to see you again!
I want you to caress me once again.
It would be bad if you catch a cold.
You should go in first.
Umm...
If it's okay, shall we go in together?
When I was little, I always take
a bath with my father just like this.
Is that so?
That was when I was still little.
My daughter too...
We take baths together when she was little.
It would be unthinkable nowadays.
U-Umm... Mister, that's...
Your hard thing is poking me...
I've been itching to do it so much so...
I couldn't help it...
W-We can't! Not in here!
Then, how about I wash your body?
Th-That's my...
Hey, it's only you doing it...
Me too!
You're adorable.
You're beautiful!
No! Please don't stare at it too much!
Even when it has a lovely shape like this?
D-Don't!
Umm...
Even though I never bothered asking you once last time...
Yes...
Can I put it in?
Yes.
Doesn't it hurt?
Y-Yes... I'm alright.
You're squeezing down there again.
I-Is that so?
That was your first time back then, right?
Yes! You were my first!
Then... Glad to have your second time, huh?
The whole thing is inside!
Yes!
Then, I'll start moving. Just tell me when it hurts.
Please move a lot!
Is it fine?
It's because...
I wanted to do this again with you!
I yearned and yearned for this!
And I never thought that I'll see you again!
Is that so?
Incredible! This is incredible!
It feels like I'm being electrocuted!
N-No way! S-So deep!
What's wrong? Could it be that...
You can't!
Are your tits your weak spots?
Don't rub them—!
Hey...
Answer me properly.
No!
Not right there!
No! No!
Good! Good! That feels good!
Ouch! Stop! That hurts but...
It feels good!
Mister, your thick thing is hitting me deep inside!
Amazing!
My body feels... like it isn't mine!
It's coming! That stuff from mister is coming out!
Wow It's sloppy down there.
Then you should clean it.
This went inside me earlier, huh?
This is your flavor...
You got big again, mister.
Then use your tits.
If you do, It'll get even bigger.
Like this?
Yeah...
Does this feel good, mister?
It feels good!
You're doing good! Good!
It's like I'm getting
praised by my father!
It's coming out! It's coming out!
I was trying to clean you up,
but I made you come again.
I was on my way home from school
due to an early dismissal of classes.
I was taking shelter from the rain at the bus stop,
when I met a middle-aged man by chance.
He kind of resembles my father.
While I was a little bit nervous, I tried to talk to him.
We were having a fun conversation,
but he suddenly took my clothes off.
He forcefully pushed me down.
Let's go.
Not knowing why, I got raped.
He violated me again and again.
He kept on filling me inside where the babies come from.
Even so, now I'm...
Now I'm doing something like this.
I love your embrace, mister!
Mister... I love you! I love you!
More, more, do it rougher!
Lots of it, lots of it!
Shoot it, shoot it out please!
Inside me, inside!
I want to have his baby!
I'll shoot it out!
Yes!
I never thought
that I am this much of a lewd girl.
I'm sorry, it's all because I did those things to you...
It's alright already.
It's because I'm just like you now.
I can't help myself wanting orgasm.
I already am broken way beyond repair.
For today again after class,
I'm going to meet with mister again.
Using the spare time in between his work,
he goes to meet me.
Hello.
I now probably have
his baby inside my belly.
Even so, I want to do more and more
of these stuffs together with him.
From now on, I want to be with him like this!
That's because I am already broken.
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization