Why was I...
Why was I raped by a stranger?
I thought he wasn't a bad person at first!
Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry if you get pregnant!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Pregnant... How babies are made...
No... I'm really gonna get pregnant!
No! Why?! Why does this...
This isn't right!
I'm not this kind of person, but...
No, I shouldn't be doing this,
but it's like there's a fire growing deep inside me!
I was just raped, but I...
I need to get the semen out of me, but I...
I want more...
More!
It feels... It feels so good!
Why... Why can't I stop?!
Why does it feel so good?!
This... This isn't enough!
I need something bigger!
I need something bigger to fuck me!
Wet and transparent high school girl
Raped while taking shelter from the rain 02
No, I...
I'll never be forgiven for this.
But...
But why can't I stop lusting for her?
What the hell am I doing?
Why'd I come all the way out here?
I keep seeing her in my dreams.
What am I supposed to do when I meet her?
Apologize? Or again, am I supposed to...
It's really coming down again, isn't it?
I find it strange myself.
Even after all that happened...
I couldn't bring myself to hate you.
So I wanted to confirm what my feelings are.
I kept thinking I wanted to see you again.
I wanted to touch you again.
It'd be bad if you caught a cold.
Go ahead and take a bath.
Um, if you'd like...
Would you like to take one together?
I used to take baths like this with
my dad all the time when I was a kid.
Oh, really?
Only when I was a kid, okay?
Yeah, my daughter did the same when she was little.
I can't even imagine that happening now, though.
U-Um, so your hard thing is knocking against me...
Well, when we're this close to each other, I can't help it.
W-We can't!
Not here!
Then how about we wash your body?
R-Right there...
U-Um, I'd like to...
I'd like to help you too!
You're so cute.
You're beautiful.
N-No! Please don't stare so much!
Even though it's shaped so beautifully?
N-No!
U-Um...
Last time, I didn't let you have any say in what we did.
Yes...
May I put it in?
Yes.
Does it hurt?
N-No. I'm okay.
You're getting tighter.
A-Am I?
That was your first time back then, right?
Y-Yes!
You were my first time!
And now I'm your second too, I guess.
It all went in!
Yes!
All right I'm going to move. Tell me if it hurts, okay?
Yes! Please... do me hard!
Are you sure?
I wanted to do this with you again so badly! So badly!
I wasn't sure if we'd ever see each other again.
Really?
It's so good!
I feel like electricity's running through me!
N-No, th-that's...
What? Don't tell me...
No!
Your boobs are sensitive?
No...
Come on, tell me the truth.
Right there feels too good!
No! No!
Good! So good!
N-No, I said no!
Y-Your hard thing is hitting me so deep inside!
Wow, it's like this isn't my body!
It's coming! His stuff is coming!
Wow, I'm drenched down there...
Can you clean me up?
So this was inside me, huh?
It tastes like you.
You've gotten hard again.
Then how about you use your boobs?
I bet I'll get even bigger!
Like this?
Does it... feel good?
Yeah, it does.
You're very good at this.
I'm so happy, it's like my Dad's praising me.
I'm cumming!
I was trying to clean it up, but I made you cum instead.
On the way back from school...
In a sudden downpour...
At the bus stop I was taking shelter from the rain in...
I met him by pure coincidence.
He resembled my dad a little bit.
And I called out to him even though my heart was racing.
Even though we were having a nice conversation,
he suddenly stripped me and pinned me down.
I was raped without understanding
what was going on at all.
I was raped by him over and over again.
He poured so much of his semen inside of me.
But even after that, I... I...
I'm now...
I love touching you like this!
I love you! I love you!
More! Do me harder!
Cum! Please cum!
Cum inside me! Inside me!
I want his child!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Yes!
I never knew that I was this perverted.
I'm sorry. It's all because of what I put you through...
It's fine.
After all, I can't live without you anymore now.
I broke a long time ago.
After school today too...
I'm going to meet with him.
– Whenever he has work here, he comes to meet me.
– Hello.
I think I've already gotten pregnant with his child.
But I want to do this kind of stuff with him so much more!
I want to be like this with him forever!
After all, I'm broken...
translator: hikarucon
timing: kurosagi
typesetting: hybrio21
editing: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч