It's really coming down, isn't it?
Huh? Ah, yeah.
Wet and transparent high school girl
Raped while taking shelter from the rain
W-Would you like to use this?
No, but thank you.
Are you sure you don't want to use it?
You're going to catch a cold if you don't dry off.
Ah, right.
The next bus isn't for over an hour?
Yeah, the buses don't really come too often.
Sometimes the bus drivers even fall asleep at the station.
Really?
I didn't know it was going to rain today.
Do you live far from here?
A little over an hour away.
I really live in the middle of nowhere.
There aren't usually any people who ride the bus out here.
We're really deep in the countryside.
Ah, I see.
Are you not a local?
Yeah, I'm not.
I'm here on a business trip from my company in Tokyo.
Wow, you're from Tokyo?!
You must be really busy with work!
Oh, kinda.
Are you married?
Oh, yes.
I have a wife and daughter.
She's actually about your age.
Oh wow, you have a child?
She used to be really cute.
Now she doesn't even listen to me.
Oh, really?
My wife doesn't really listen to me either.
They just treat me as if I'm a complete nuisance.
Who the hell do they think puts food on the table?
Are you okay?
Hey, nobody's coming here, right?
Huh? Ah, yes.
Usually, no...
M-Mister?!
P-Please stop!
U-Um...
S-Stop!
I won't! I won't stop!
No! No!
No! Don't!
Stop!
That's...
If that's how you're going to be, then...
No! No!
Don't bite it!
Looks like you have something you want to say.
I-I'm sorry.
U-Um...
U-Um... What are you...
N-No, what is this?!
It feels gross!
This thing is in between my breasts!
They're so soft!
They're so damn soft!
– The feel so good! So good!
– No! Stop!
Why?!
Why is this happening?!
There's... There's something coming out of the tip!
No! No!
No!
Please stop!
This isn't...
I-I-I'm cumming.
P-Please let me go.
I can't breathe!
He's shoving it deep down my throat, I can't breathe!
If he keeps thrusting it that hard...
No, I feel like I'm gonna barf!
He's pushing it so hard, the liquid from before is...
I drank it! It went down my throat!
I can't breathe! I can't breathe!
Stay still!
U-Um...
Here it comes!
It hurts, doesn't it? It's rough, isn't it?
But, it hurts for me too!
I'm in pain too!
So, this is okay, right?!
Okay, looks like you're starting to get wet.
How's that?! Come on! Come on!
What's going on? This is rape, right?
I'm being raped, right?
I'm being raped by a person I just met, right?
Why?! Why do I have to go through this?!
Did I do something wrong?!
Why am I being raped?!
I love the nape of your neck!
I'm gonna cum!
Stop! Don't struggle!
There's nothing you can do about this.
Sorry! Sorry!
Sorry if I get you pregnant!
Ah, I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Please... No!
Please... Please stop!
No!
Why isn't this over yet?!
What's going to happen to me?!
This person is going to break me!
At this rate, I'm gonna...
Somebody, please save me!
I need to call for help!
I need to tell them that I'm being raped!
I'm being raped and about to be impregnated!
I need to scream! I need to scream
and get somebody to help me!
Hurry! Somebody come!
Hurry! Where's the bus?! Where is it?!
That's right. Nobody's coming.
I already told him that nobody comes here...
That, right there...
Does it feel good? It's getting tighter!
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming! Sorry!
I'm cumming inside you again!
Don't!
Well, I'm cumming. You're gonna get a load of my seeds!
No! No! No!
Y-You're going to get me pregnant!
Stop!
It's coming out... It's coming out inside me...
His raw, warm stuff is...
Am I really going to get pregnant?
I'm not going to be able to go to school anymore.
If I get pregnant, what's going to
happen to me from here on out?
Please... tell me...
Tell you what?
Why did you...
What did I do to deserve this?
Nothing. There's pretty much no reason at all.
Look, I'm hard again.
You're amazing!
No matter how many times I cum, I just get hard again!
We still have time before the bus comes, right?
We can probably go one more time, right?
I'm going back to Tokyo today,
but you need to stay in school, okay?
Study well, graduate and get a good job.
You're cute and you have such a nice body,
I'm sure you'll have a great life.
Don't you think?
Come on, I'll give you one more pump of my semen!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editing: oblivionshadow
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч