Yuuto...
Marika-san!
I love you!
Me too!
Yuuto... You're the man that I love!
Sensei!
Sensei... Sensei!
How did this happen?
Still, I Love My Wife 2
The Case of The Female Teacher Housewife Marika
Gotcha!
Hello, Yuuto-kun!
Uesugi-san...
You can just call me Rumi.
B-But, that's...
Huh, you look down for some reason.
Could it be that you had a fight
with your beloved wife?
We didn't have a fight, she got a job transfer.
Oh... That's something to worry about.
Worry?
Isn't that a given? There's no way that men
will be able to leave alone
such a young beauty like her.
Everything's fine. Marika is a P.E. Teacher.
She always says something like
"I won't lose against those rascals."
And also...
And also what?
We're both deeply in love with each other.
Yeah, yeah. Thanks for the scoop!
Stop... Stop this!
Amakawa!
This is all your fault, sensei!
You invited me here to your house
as a reward for my hard work!
This can't be happening...
Was it because I look just like your husband?
I am your student, but I fell in love with you!
I'm fine even if you only treat
me as his substitute, sensei!
Don't do this, no way!
You're being rough! If you keep on doing that...
I'm... I'm gonna...
I'm really sorry!
I will forget about what happened today.
It's partly my fault to invite you to my house.
Umm...
Umm... Do I really look a lot like your husband?
Just a little.
Sensei...
Hmm?
Will you hear my one last wish?
After that, I'll give up on you.
Alright, then.
Sensei!
Good morning, Amami-san.
Oh... Good morning, Mr. Caretaker.
May I have a moment?
Well, things have been dangerous around here lately.
Even the entrance of this building
has a security camera now.
Way to go, Amami-san.
To think that you've brought a student
home while working far away.
Won't it be a huge problem if
you husband finds about this?
What do you want me to do?
Okay then, strip.
Don't you think that blackmailing is going too low?
That upfront haughtiness of yours...
I'll thoroughly smear your resolute attitude
with lots of my love!
That's good, keep it up.
Don't you like the taste of a man?
Enough to lure even a young boy
and get a taste on him!
You're doing great! Keep that up, ma'am.
You're gasping so hard.
Aren't you aroused right now?
Okay, time for your reward.
I'll make you feel good too.
How is it? Doesn't it feel good?
You're throbbing right here.
But you really have such a nice body.
No wonder why that boy went after you.
Enough of that, just tell me what you want!
Good, that stubborn attitude of yours is the best!
Making such a woman submit to and serve me...
I feel like coming just from imagining about it!
Hey, come here!
No, stop!
It really went in!
What, aren't you feeling good?
That's not it... I can't breathe!
Stop, you're crushing me!
Stop, you're heavy!
Stop already!
You're stirring me down there... my pussy!
Your pussy is twitching inside!
Ohh, you're tightening up!
You're a fine specimen, indeed!
No... It's throbbing inside me!
Your dick is twitching!
No! D-Don't!
I'm about to come!
I'm close as well!
No, no way! You can't... Not inside!
We're far from done...
The fun is just about to start.
Missed Call
Amakawa Yuuki
Oh, that's it... You're good at this, ma'am!
It's because you've been sucking
that brat's cock, isn't it?
It seems that you're quite motivated now.
You started to feel like sucking now?
You're not doing a bad job, but...
Can't you do it with more passion?
Huh?
You're slacking, aren't you? Do it properly!
Not that kind of sloppy job which
won't satisfy your partner!
Hey, do you understand the position
you're in right now, ma'am?
This feels good!
Good! Don't loosen up your mouth!
I'm coming! S-Swallow it!
You have to do at least that much.
Not so bright, huh? Jeez...
It seems like I have to teach you more about this.
We'll have a long-lasting relationship, right?
Amakawa... Why?
Sensei, you never went to school today, so...
I was worried, and...
Worried with a boner?
That's good. Join us.
Wh-What are you saying?
You're partly to blame why this happened.
To prevent your kissing photo from getting out,
your teacher is putting her body to work.
If you'll have a threesome with us,
then I might be fine on letting her go afterwards.
Wh-What the hell is this?
You're enjoying your first anal sex.
What a slut!
Y-You're tearing up my belly!
Oh... It's alright, it's alright.
It'll feel good eventually.
Sensei!
Hey, switch places with me.
Work hard and make your teacher feel good too!
S-Sensei!
Amakawa, you can't! Stop!
M-My ass feels crazy!
What the hell is this? My ass...
I-I'm coming, I'm gonna come!
I-I'm coming...
It's going inside me... Your hot stuff...
It's flowing all over inside my belly!
How does a semen enema feel?
It feels like I'm getting filled in with bath water!
My belly feels like it's burning!
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Oh, it's a call from your husband.
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Amami Yuuto
Decline
Accept
Yuuto?
It would be a waste so pick it up.
Marika-san?
Yuuto?
Sorry for calling out of nowhere.
I just felt a little lonely.
How are you there?
I'm fine.
Marika-san?
What's wrong? Are you with someone?
No... I'm just feeling a bit sick...
Is that so? Sorry.
Get well soon, then. Okay?
Yeah, I want to say the same!
Marika-san?
I'll be hanging up.
I'll come back there at the end of the year.
Don't push yourself too hard, okay?
I love you.
Me too.
Marika-san... Could it be...
Uesugi Rumi
Wanna meet outside?
Cheating?
I don't really know.
I wonder what should I do.
Cheer up, today's gonna be my treat!
Master, give us the usual.
Amami-kun?
What's the meaning of this?
You really are such a cutie...
Uesugi-san...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization