March 09
Image Club
Aruchin girl
Sex Services aren't considered cheating.
Understand?
There's no problem as long as Nanami-chan doesn't know.
If you strengthen your manliness by doing other women,
then you won't have to get so worked up about
that good looking neighbor of yours.
These came from our neighbor Shinagawa-san.
He said it's a souvenir from France.
I got this spicy oil from our neighbor Shinagawa-san.
I went to this event with a friend and Shinagawa-san today,
we then ate at an eat-all-you-can cake shop.
Honda-san?
I wonder how Shuuichi-san is doing with his work today.
Despite that I still love my wife
Episode 03 - The price of Jealousy
I shall start now then.
Sir, is this your first time here?
You can tell?
You seem to be nervous.
Or maybe, you don't like to be with me?
That's not it.
I'm glad.
Then let's enjoy this together okay?
It's all stiff.
Your cock is already dripping Sir.
It's really hard.
It really looks wonderful.
Feeling horny now?
For you to already feel very aroused with just this,
so it really is your first time here.
Hey, does it feel good?
Yeah, it does.
I'm happy to hear that.
It's still getting harder.
This cock is amazing.
It feels great.
Is it also getting aroused from your lewd thoughts?
Well that's...
No need to be shy about it.
Even I get horny when thinking of those things.
Just keep on thinking about lewd things like that okay?
Lots of it came out.
It just came, but it's still stiff.
I'm really wet now.
This really isn't allowed but,
you look quite cool, so let's keep this a secret okay?
Your cock feels really good Sir.
My pussy feels tender right?
I can feel that it fits just right.
Your cock feels great.
Look, my pussy is really getting wet.
Does it really feel good?
It does.
It feels good.
I'm happy.
It also feels great for me.
It's hitting deep inside me.
It's okay for both of us to feel good right?
It's actually my job to do it but,
it's okay to feel horny while doing it right?
I haven't asked your name yet Sir.
Well, it's Shuuichi.
Shuu-chan, let's kiss some more.
Amazing.
This is the first time I've felt so ecstatic.
Hey, Shuu-chan.
Please call me by my name.
It feels better for me if someone calls my name.
Shouko!
Call me, call me more!
Shouko.
Yes, my pussy feels like it's melting.
Wow, your cock is really rubbing inside me.
Please make my pussy feel it more!
So, are you about to release your "cock milk" ?
You can cum inside me if you want,
so please do it until the end.
Just a little more.
I'm cumming.
I'm going cum.
Please rub my pussy, rub inside me more!
Lots of it came out again.
Did it feel good?
Yeah...
That's good then.
Thank you for today.
Here's my calling card.
Please come again okay?
I'll be waiting.
Despite that I still love my wife
Welcome home dear.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Dear...
Dear, you see,
I want to have your baby.
Here, come.
I love you Nanami.
Dear...
Dear.
Dear!
I'm, about to...
Here I go.
Come to me, dear.
What's wrong?
Dear...
I'm sorry.
You're tired from work,
so I should be the one apologizing.
Sorry, I'm going to sleep first.
This is...
No way...
I'm sorry, Dear.
Shouko
Image Club
Aruchin Girl
To Shuu-chan, that really felt great today.
Let's do lots of it again, okay?
I'll be waiting.
He said he'd be home late because of work.
But he did it with another woman.
And then he didn't do me...
He didn't finish it with me.
I'm sorry.
He's not satisfied with me?
March 16
I had too much alcohol and got drunk.
I'm sorry.
Do you feel a bit sober now?
Yes.
Thank you for listening to what I have to say.
You've been acting a bit weird these
past few days so I got worried.
But I never thought your husband would do such a thing.
I love my husband, but...
I want to mend your broken heart.
Shinagawa-san, we can't do this...!
Don't touch me there...
Shinagawa-san, we mustn't...
We mustn't do this.
This is embarrassing.
Please don't.
Nanami-san, I want to feel you more.
But that would be...
It's okay isn't it?
Shinagawa-san.
We really can't do this.
This is...
Shinagawa-san, stop...
Don't...
We mustn't do this, but...
Dear...
This is embarrassing...
Nanami-san, does it feel good?
Yes, it's amazing.
It's so big.
Your thing feels great.
I'm sorry, we shouldn't do this and yet...
Your thing feels amazing inside me.
But we can't do this...
If we start doing this...
Umm, about what happened today.
Of course, this will be a secret between us.
Thank you very much.
Despite that I still love my wife
April 1
Yes.
I feel so ecstatic!
Hey, hey.
But this sure is amazing.
Oh wow.
No...!
My pussy feels hot.
I want more of your cock.
Wow...
Nanami doesn't even react that much to me...
You've been working hard.
My mother's injuries weren't that serious.
But I'm sorry, I'll be staying here for the night, just in case.
Nanami...
Don't worry about me.
Hope she gets well soon.
With that, until dawn tomorrow...
No, until Shuuichi-san gets back from work.
I can be together with you.
I want your semen Shinagawa-san.
Your semen tastes great.
I want more of you Shanagawa-san.
Please enter me.
Beyond these walls, is our room.
I'm such a terrible woman.
After the day that I crossed the line with Shinagawa-san,
we did it almost every day.
Dear...
Shinagawa-san sure is amazing.
I can hear her voice here.
April 2
After a while, the time I spent with Shinagawa-san
started to become longer,
than the time I spent with Shuuichi-san.
Your husband might be home already, you know?
At this time, maybe he really is home already.
What's wrong, Nanami-san?
Don't tease me, like this.
Even if he could hear you, I don't think
he'd know that it's really you.
That's...
But...
It looks like you don't want to raise your voice too much.
Shinagawa-san.
I don't want to cause any discomfort for you.
Move.
Move, please.
Are you sure it's okay?
I don't care anymore.
I don't care.
Please,
thrust it in all the way!
Dear...
Shinagawa-san.
Your cock feels hot.
It feels really good.
I'm moaning louder.
I can't stop it.
It feels great.
Oh wow.
Oh no...
It's deep.
It's hitting all the way inside.
You're amazing.
Your cock is very deep inside.
I want it.
I want more of your cock.
Please feel my cock more,
because this thing is only for you.
I'm happy.
It really feels good.
Amazing.
I can feel it. I can feel it!
Shinagawa-san, do it more intensely!
This stiff cock...
Makes my pussy really horny.
My pussy feels great.
Your cock is rubbing inside.
There, that part feels good.
Shinagawa-san.
Oh no. Oh no!
It feels too good.
Please, please do it more!
Shinagawa-san!
I'm cumming.
It's coming out.
Shuuichi-san, I'm now...
Despite that I still love my wife
April 3
During the times when I need a break from work,
I go to the balcony, and light a few smokes.
There, I can hear it.
You humming as you do the laundry.
That alone was already enough to make me happy.
If your husband didn't do that,
I would have had no choice but to forever seal my feelings for you.
Shinagawa-san.
Nanami-san, I love you,
from the bottom of my heart.
Your insides feel very good.
My hips just won't stop.
Me too.
Your big thing also feels very good.
You're just too great Shinagawa-san.
My pussy feels really good.
Shinagawa-san.
Please push it farther into me.
Do it more intensely.
Please do it more intensely.
Push it harder!
Yes, that feels great.
You do seem to feel it really well.
I'm embarrassed.
But I can really feel it.
Your cock is amazing.
Yes!
Where is it that feels great?
In my pussy.
Your cock feels hot.
I can't get enough of it.
It's drilling deep inside me.
I like you.
I love you!
So please,
please do it more!
Are you alright with me Nanami-san?
Yes, I am.
I won't do it if it's not you.
Oh no...
I can't hold it in anymore.
Please, let me cum.
Let me cum with your cock.
It's feels a lot different from my husband.
It feels very good.
Since then, I haven't been having sex with him.
If I had known right away that he went to a sex service lounge,
I would have simply felt depressed.
But the thing I lost inside as he refused to do it with me,
is now being filled up by Shinagawa-san.
Shinagawa-san.
I think I have seriously fallen in love with you.
Oh no...
I'm going to cum if you continue.
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
Oh no!
My head is starting to go blank.
Everything's turning to white.
Can we do it one more time?
Yes.
Please, love me more.
April 4
I'm sorry
Nanami
September 7
Shuuichi and Nanami's
Wedding Anniversary
Nanami...
Dear, you see,
I want to have your baby.