Wh-Where am I?
Master, give us the usual.
Amami-kun?
That's right, I was...
Where's Uesugi-san?!
What the hell is this...
No, don't act recklessly.
You'll hurt yourself if the chair falls down.
Huh?
Uesugi-san! You're alright, aren't you?
I suddenly felt sleepy when I drank that wine...
You really are such a cutie!
You're in this situation yet you still worry about me.
Wh-What do you mean?
You sure are easy prey, huh?
You're too trusting to a fault
and never doubt people.
You're suspicious of your own wife though!
It really made me happy when you
consulted me about your wife!
I've had my eyes on you all this time!
At the examination period...
You cooped yourself up at the library on
weekends, studying until its closing time.
I've been seeing you a lot in the
rental store at the station too!
You've always been going there with your wife ever since you got married.
Oh... At your wedding too...
Wasn't that a beautiful chapel?
Have you ever noticed me stalking
you through all those years?
To make it so that you're overwhelmed by lust...
I'll have you utilize that.
That manhood of yours, I mean.
D-Don't do this!
Right now, your thing is
at the entrance of my pussy!
Uesugi-san...
Let's enjoy ourselves, Yuuto-kun!
Your dick is pulsating inside me!
You should make yourself enjoy this.
I'm also enjoying myself with your dick!
I won't back down from this!
You should just enjoy this as well.
I'm not letting you go.
You're already mine, you hear me?
Fill me up!
Fill my womb with your semen up to the brim!
Do it... Do it... Do it!
It's so hot! It feels so hot!
Your semen is flowing inside me!
Your semen is filling my womb up to the brim!
Hey, there's something I want to show you.
Huh?
Then, Mari-san...
You've been fucking like bunnies when
you're still with your husband, right?
You're both young, after all.
Umm, well...
We've been doing it quite often.
Well...
Is once or twice a week too often?
Nah, that's normal.
But it might not be enough for young couples.
Moreover, were you satisfied from just that?
What's the meaning of this?
I-I wonder...
Umm, well... I'm not really sure...
Didn't you say that you're a P.E. teacher?
With that beauty and body of yours...
You've had people looking at you indecently, right?
Well, that...
...happened a lot.
But I just ignore them.
But doesn't that make you horny?
Well... You are right!
And you said that you need some cash too, right?
Yes... That's right.
The man who's taking care of me
right now is in huge debt.
You see, I'm shouldering that debt.
Enjoy yourselves with my payment!
That's the very reason I trained her hard.
I kept raping her over and over again each day.
And here she is now,
totally captivated by sex.
Sh-Should I stroke this for you?
You're good on this just as I expected!
I'll use this thing
to enjoy you a lot for today!
It's twitching and throbbing in my mouth!
This is turning me on!
You're starting to get in the mood, ma'am.
Th-That's incredible!
I'm about to come!
Looks like you now have a taste for it.
Marika-san...
Amami-kun, your wife is doing
stuff like that behind your back.
That can't be true...
She said that it's for paying someone else's debt.
I wonder if that's the man
she's having an affair with.
Shall we watch the rest?
How does it make you feel,
being nude right here at your workplace?
I'm feeling nervous.
What are we gonna do if someone sees us?
Please enjoy this scenery that's different
from where we usually do it, alright?
But this spells trouble for me.
Outsiders are actually not allowed in here!
You're right.
But, well... See, that's it.
Let's just do it without any worries.
Don't thrust so hard on me!
You're quite a natural!
I feel like this will get popular!
I want to make this into a series...
No way, you said that this will be a one-time thing!
Really?
Your pussy is feeling this good, you see!
Wow! I'm feeling good down there!
This is great, you have a fine thing down here!
Seriously, this feels good!
I'll come from this in no time!
D-Don't come yet!
No way... What am I saying?
I'm feeling so good that it's messing up my mind!
I'm getting sopping wet deep inside!
It's reverberating inside my womb!
Don't be so rough on me!
No! My voice... My voice is...
No way, we'll be heard!
Someone will end up coming here!
But I can't keep my voice down...
No, that part of me is... My pussy is...
It's going numb!
No, I can't! I'll end up making a mess in the classroom!
I'm coming—!
The tip is throbbing...
I'm getting filled with your hot stuff!
Do you like creampies?
Hey, don't you love them?
Look, your pussy is twitching.
No way... Don't ask me...
Marika-san...
Marika-san!
Amami-kun, you poor thing!
I'm going to ease your pain, okay?
I'm coming—!
I came again...
Oh, she's totally a best-seller!
No, no... I'm grateful here as well.
I'll have her work for you again
to cover my the remaining debt.
Marika-san!
Huh?
Y-You...
Are you awake now?
Yuuto, I'm...
It's alright.
I'm the one who owes you an apology.
You were suffering, and yet I...
I...
Isn't this like that time but in reverse?
I comforted you when you were
depressed from your parents' divorce.
I held your hand...
But right now, it is you who saved me instead.
Thank you.
I love you.
Yuuto, your thing is pressing against
the spot where it feels good!
No, I'm shaking my hips!
It feels good!
Your dick...
It feels like it's filling me up
and stretching me loose inside!
Its tip is rubbing
against my womb, the part where it feels the best!
No, I'm about to come!
Shoot it all inside me just like this!
It feels good! I'm coming!
I'm gonna come!
I'm coming—!
I wonder if we'll have a baby now...
Yeah, I'm sure that we will.
I'm looking forward to it.
Sensei!
Yuuto... You're amazing! You're so intense!
Marika-san... Marika-san!
Marika-san, Marika-san...
Marika-san!
I love you!
Still, I Love My Wife 2
The Case of The Female Teacher Housewife Marika
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization