Have a good day at work.
Thank you, Nanami.
About the plan for our wedding anniversary tonight...
7 o'clock at the hotel, right?
Yeah.
I can't wait!
I'm going to dress up.
All right, I'm leaving now.
See you later, darling.
This is going to be great!
Her lewd pussy is trembling.
This is Honda Nanami-san, a faithful wife.
A public restroom is not the place
for a beautiful wife like her.
I love her face when she strains.
I can see her sexy pussy very clearly.
What lewd sounds she makes.
Oh, yes! That's the face I was waiting for.
Excuse me, it's Honda.
Hi, Kamata-san.
Sorry I'm late.
It's been a busy day.
Don't worry.
Your body will be stressed if you hold it in for too long.
Huh?
I've been waiting for you.
I-I'm sorry.
S-So you wanted to talk about the
neighborhood association?
I smell a toilet.
Huh?
I-I don't...
Anyway, please come in.
We'll talk about it over a cup of tea.
Please, I insist.
Wh-What are you doing?
I have something I want to show you.
Huh?
Translation: May & Snak | Timing: Splash | Editing: Collectr | TS & Encode: ShocWave | QS: Brurush
Presented by Erobeat | http://www. erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc. rizon.net
And yet I Still Love My Wife
Episode 1 A Wife with a secret
What are you going to do?
Take a look at this.
As manager of this building...
No way...
...It is my duty to watch out for your safety.
No way! What are you...
No... No, please stop this!
They're pretty well recorded.
No! Stop this!
Hey, we're getting to the good part.
Please, stop!
No!
How cute.
I've been watching you for a long time.
No! Don't!
Every part of your body has been recorded.
Let me go, please!
This is your fault.
I was okay with just watching you.
But I can't restrain myself anymore.
I want to have sex with you.
That is why I called you here.
No, that's... Stop!
That is only for my husband!
Please...
S-Stop!
It... It hurts...
It's too big!
It hurts.
Yes! I'm finally one with Nanami-san!
I don't want anyone inside of me besides Shuichi-san...
Help me, Shuichi-san!
This is great, just as I thought.
Nanami-san's pussy is squeezing my dick hard!
Please take it out!
Take it out! I'm going to break!
Please! I'm not going to tell anyone!
I won't say a word about what I saw!
This is being recorded too, you know?
You'd better behave.
No, that's... No!
It gets even tighter if you bend backward like that.
You haven't had kids yet, right?
I can help you with that!
Don't cum inside me!
Not inside! You absolutely mustn't!
I'll do whatever you want,
but don't finish inside of me!
I'm... I'm cumming!
No!
Today is our wedding anniversary, so I'll go home early,
do my make-up, meet Shuichi-san,
and then celebrate together.
I'm glad that we can celebrate our special day today.
I'm being too loud.
It's embarrassing.
Don't worry.
I don't think the people next door can hear us.
I mean, I don't want you to think I'm a naughty wife.
I wouldn't, you silly.
You're my cute wife.
Yeah?
You're wilder than usual, Nanami.
No, don't say that. It's embarrassing.
I feel you deep inside of me.
We've been married for three years.
Maybe you are ready for a baby?
No... Stop saying embarrassing things.
You haven't had kids yet, right?
I can help you with that!
This is great, just as I thought.
Nanami-san's pussy is squeezing my dick hard!
Nanami-san! It's so good!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Darling, I love you. I love you. I really do.
I'm going to finish inside of you!
Yes, darling!
Please!
I want lots of you inside me.
Please...
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I feel the heat spreading inside of me.
I love you, Nanami.
I love you too.
Let's make today our anniversary.
We'll do this every day from now on.
Don't worry. I won't tell your husband.
Nanami?
You're here right on time.
Did you miss my dick?
No... I didn't!
You went out for a drive in this car
with your husband today, right!?
Even though you're recalling the fun you had
earlier today, you're having sex with me.
You're too cruel!
Hurry up and finish, please!
Darling... Save me!
I can't take this anymore. It's too much.
I can't go on any longer.
You sound really cute.
Did you start loving my dick?
Why would I...
I'm sorry, Shuichi-san. I'm sorry.
Darling. Darling!
So you're thinking about your husband
even though my dick is inside of you!?
Stop!
I'll... I'll break!
By the way, how do you feel about coming here to
get raped after you just slept with your husband!?
No! Darling...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, darling!
That's good! I'm getting even more excited!
I'll cum inside you again!
Please, no! Outside... Cum outside!
I've cum inside you many times by now!
No! I'll get pregnant!!
Please don't!
No one will know as long as you
do this with your husband, too!
No!
Nanami, I have to get up early tomorrow, so...
I'm sorry.
I'm going to do all the work tonight, so please...
I want to be connected with you as much as I can.
What's wrong, Nanami?
You've been acting strange lately.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm going to move, so...
I want... I want to feel you more!
Darling, I feel so good with you inside of me.
I want you deep within me.
Please cum inside of me!
I can't.
I couldn't do this with someone watching me.
What are you saying? I gave you an enema for this.
I'm ready.
You can shit as much as you want at any time.
No, no... I can't hold it in anymore.
Let me help you.
You've got a pretty face, but you can
let out quite a lot of disgusting stuff.
Why are you doing this to me?
We got some great recordings today.
Now that you've taken a dump and are feeling
better, we can have sex right here!
No way!
This is insane! Having sex right after...
That's right! Sex and more sex with your ass still dirty!
No, don't! Stop!
We're having sex after shooting
a scatological video. Super!
Please, let me wipe my bottom!
It's even better doing this with the smell of your shit!
No!
I'm sorry, Shuichi-san. I'm sorry!
Oh, more shit is coming out of your ass.
Taking a shit with my dick inside you, huh?
What a dirty girl.
You're wrong! I'm not...
You're a pervert who likes scatology, Nanami-san!
No...
No!
Help me, darling!
Cum while you smell your own shit!
There. There. There!
I'm cumming, cumming!
Accept all of my cum!
No!
Don't cum inside me!
Thank goodness. I'm not having a baby.
I'm sorry, Shuichi-san.
Oh boy, did you black out again, Nanami-san?
This is really happening...
How long have I been doing this?
I don't remember much of what has happened...
I cum easily now because I do this all the time.
Nanami-san, did you just cum again?
You love my dick, don't you?
I wonder what Shuichi-san is doing now.
Nanami-san, you have a call.
Who's that?
Yes?
Hello?
Hey, Nanami. It's me.
Hi, darling.
I just got back to the hotel I'm
staying at for this business trip.
You must be tired after working for so long.
Yeah, I think I can come home tomorrow evening.
My darling is coming home.
Hey, Nanami! Are you okay?
I'm all right. Don't worry.
Nanami? Nanami?
I'm just a little sick.
But I'm all right.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
So please keep up your hard work.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be waiting for you at home.
All right, I'll come back as soon as possible tomorrow.
Just don't overwork yourself.
I'll be waiting for you, darling.
I love you.
I love you too, Nanami.
I'm sorry, darling. I'm sorry!
How faithful, Nanami-san.
Darling... Darling I'm sor-
You got even tighter inside after
you talked to your husband!
Wh-What did you just make me swallow?
It's something that will make you feel even better!
We'll have fun until your husband comes
back tomorrow, right, Nanami-san?
No...
I'm so hot!
It feels good.
What exactly feels so good?
No. I can't control myself. It just feels so good.
What feels so good?
Your cock. It feels good.
You're a nympho wife who loves sex, Nanami-san!
No, I just can't control myself.
I can't stop myself.
I'm cumming again!
No, I'm about to faint.
No, I'm going blank!
Hey, Shuichi-san, I want to remain your wife...
But I'm not the person I used to be.
Hey, Shuichi-san, will you still love me?