I'm home.
Welcome home, darling.
Nanami?
What's with the outfit?
It's called "naked apron."
You see, today is your birthday.
Do you like it?
Thank you, Nanami.
That's the best present ever.
Translation: May & Snak | Timing: Splash | Editing: Collectr | TS & Encode: ShocWave | QS: Brurush
Presented by Erobeat | http://www. erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc. rizon.net
And yet I Still Love My Wife
Episode 2 A Wife a Sin
Darling...
Sorry...
I can't stand it.
I'll do it now!
Darling, I feel you inside me!
Nanami, you're squeezing me.
I'm really embarrassed to have sex
with you in a place like this.
I've put it all inside, you know?
Yes. Your cock is completely inside me.
You're wilder than usual today.
Oh, no! So rough.
Darling. Darling!
Thank you. I love my present from you.
I'm happy to hear that.
I can feel how happy your dick is inside me.
I can feel you going crazy, and it's making me crazy, too...
I'm going crazy!
Please feel me... Please feel more of me...
Take every single part of me! Darling, darling it feels good!
Darling, you're more amazing than usual.
I'm willing to be half naked like
this more often, if you like it.
To be honest, it's really embarrassing to be in a
naked apron and show my ass and everything,
but I wanted to arouse you with my body.
It turns me on when you penetrate me with great passion.
I must be really naughty.
Darling, I love you, I love you!
Your cock is going wild inside of me.
It's sexier than usual.
My body is all yours.
My pussy, boobs, ass...
Make them all yours!
Oh, no!
You look so cute.
I almost want to take a picture of you right now.
No, I don't want anyone to see me in an outfit like this.
If someone saw, I'd die of embarrassment.
I'm embarrassed even right now.
You're so embarrassed that it's
getting you excited, Nanami?
No, don't say that!
That sounds as if I enjoy being half naked.
Darling! Darling!
I am embarrassed, really.
But I can't stop. I can't...
Oh, no! It feels so good!
I feel you deep inside of me.
Darling, I love you. I love you!
I love you too, Nanami.
I love you the most in the world.
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy, darling.
Does it feel good inside me, darling?
I'm really happy that I can make you feel good.
Please feel good from me!
No. This is... I can't control...
No! I'm too embarrassed.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm such a lewd wife.
But I can't stop myself. It feels so good.
I can't stop! Darling. Darling!
Your cock is getting bigger inside me.
Please, darling, finish inside of me.
I want to accept all of your cum!
Please pour the seed for your baby inside me!
I want it deep in my womb!
So much of your sperm is flowing into my womb...
Thank you, Nanami.
I'd do anything that makes you happy.
What would you like for your birthday?
Don't worry about it.
I've already received what I wanted.
I'd like to have your baby.
Darling, thank you for making our baby.
Nanami!
You want to do it again?
Darling. Darling!
It feels so good!
Oh, this is great!
The newest footage of Nanami-san's nocturnal
activity with her husband. Amazing!
Having a second round without a break, huh?
Her husband is working hard to make a baby.
Darling!
He's moving his hips madly.
I wonder how long it's been since I became Kamata's slave.
The relationship between me and Kamata still continues.
I can't keep Kamata from raping me.
I might get pregnant anytime, so I must
continue to have sex with Shuichi-san.
This is my daily life.
Darling! Darling!
I'm tainted, but I definitely don't want
Shuichi-san to know about that.
Kamata reached out his dirty hands to people I love, too.
My closest friend, Misaki...
and my sister, Chihiro.
Do you like that kind of stuff?
Huh? No.
I know you wanted to see this.
No!
Peeing yourself, huh?
No. This isn't... It isn't...
Chihiro got caught by Kamata when she showed
interest in the books he left in front of his room.
Misaki was invited to a party by her male friends,
and the place they brought her to was my house.
I need help here too.
What? No!
That's how Chihiro and Misaki ended up
being Kamata's sex slaves, like me.
When Shuichi-san was on his business trips,
Kamata brought strangers into my house...
and ran videotapes of our racy sessions.
Oh my, you are so excited.
Don't get so wild between my boobs.
What's that wonderful smell?
H-Hey, are you recording me? Geez...
Your dick is getting so big.
Amazing.
Give me your cum, all of it.
Hurry up and give it to me.
It's hot...
....smelly, and tasty.
Onee-chan, I feel good.
Chihiro, me too.
Your pussy is dripping wet.
It's embarrassing... So embarrassing!
Chihiro, are you turned on?
No, don't say that, Onee-chan!
But, but, but my pussy wants more!
Please hurry and put it in me now.
Now, remember how to ask properly, Chihiro.
Onee-chan, please thrust the toy into my pussy as usual!
Onee-chan, I want it too.
I'm going to put it in.
Yes, go ahead.
It's embarrassing.
You're so lewd, Chihiro.
It's going inside!
It's amazing!
Please move.
Mess me up with your cock like always.
Yes.
Onee-chan, it feels so good!
What a view.
The sisters are nymphos.
My hips are moving on their own!
Because it's so good!
We're being watched.
I'm embarrassed!
Oh, no. I can't take any more.
I'm going to cum! Cumming!
Onee-chan, Onee... Onee-chan...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Me too.
I'm cumming, too.
And the nympho sisters' friend is quite the slut, too!
Harder!
Cum inside my dripping wet pussy.
I just met this dick today and yet it fits my pussy perfectly!
It's too strong. I feel it bumping
around deep inside of me...
You're squeezing my boobs too hard!
They feel like they're coming off!
I like this dick. It's rough.
The tip clings to the walls of my pussy!
Hey, do you want to be my sex friend?
It'd be a shame to have to part with your
huge tits and pussy after today.
Stop saying that while you rub the walls of my pussy!
No, this is only for today.
I have no intention of dating you.
Just be my sex friend, and let me do you whenever I want!
Don't stir up my pussy!
No, your dick will not make me your sex friend!
Amazing!
Oh, it fits so well
It feels so good.
Do it harder so I can cum!
You want to cum?
Then your pussy is reserved for me from now on.
All right!
I'll tell you my number, and you can call
me anytime you want to have sex!
So please let me cum!
You can do whatever you want, just let me cum!
Give me your cum!
A man I just met today is going to cum inside me!
Give it to me! Fill me with your cum!
Nanami-san, I'd feel bad for your husband
if your pussy became too loose,
so we're going to use your ass.
I'm so happy.
A married woman's ass is awesome!
I love anal sex, too.
I have a cock in my ass too!
It's so tight, Chihiro-chan.
The cock is... The cock is...
It's almost like my dick is gonna get bitten off!
I feel like I'm pooping.
It's embarrassing!
This feels so great!
No, no, I can't go on anymore!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming from anal sex!
It's so tight!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I love Shuichi-san.
That's indisputable.
But I'm beyond the point of no return.
Because now I feel better getting raped
by Kamata or by strangers...
than from having sex with Shuichi-san.
Darling, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll cum plenty inside your pussy as usual!
I have a delivery for you.
Huh?
Nanami?
Hino-kun?
So this is your house?
Nanami, what's going on?
Help me, please, Hino-kun.
I'll put some towels and your clothes over here.
Thank you so much, Hino-kun.
Nanami, what happened to you?
I'm no good anymore, Hino-kun.
I'm the worst aren't I?
I don't know what to say.
I bet you think I'm a horrible person now.
I'm dirty now... and I don't deserve
to be loved by Shuichi-san...
You're not dirty!
I know you're not, Nanami!
Hino-kun.
I love you.
I've been in love with you, Nanami...
since I met you in college.
Hino-kun...
But I couldn't tell you how I felt,
and I've always regretted that.
I always wanted to do this, Nanami.
Hino-kun!
N-Nanami...
Okay, you can do me now.
Please.
T-To be honest I've never done this before.
I don't know if I can do it right.
You'll be fine.
So please put it in me.
I'm putting it in.
Huh? That's strange...
Sorry.
Here. Apply mild pressure from above and insert.
A-Are you all right?
Yes, please move.
I can't believe I'm having sex with
Nanami for my first time.
You really haven't had sex with anyone?
No. You were the only one I wanted to do this with.
I'm so happy!
You're doing well, Hino-kun.
Now feel me more, and let me feel you too!
Nanami!
Harder. Do it harder, please!
I can't stop my hips!
It's all right, Hino-kun.
You can do it harder.
But...
Yeah, you can move however you want.
And let me forget about everything!
Nanami... Nanami. Nanami!
That's the spot.
That's the spot I want you to hit!
You're amazing, Hino-kun.
Yes!
You're so rough!
Hino-kun, I'm...
I can't... I'm about to cum.
Hino-kun! Hino-kun!
Please cum inside of me, please!
Thank you, Hino-kun.
But now I have another sin that I can't tell Shuichi-san.
It's already this hard.
Oh, you're impatient, aren't you?
Yeah, I am.
I shouldn't be doing this on my wedding anniversary!
Leave that guy to me, Nanami.
Hino-kun said that to me after I had sex with him that night.
A few days later, Kamata disappeared completely.
Hino-kun took care of all the videos
that Kamata had recorded as well.
He didn't tell me what he did to Kamata,
but we're free from Kamata now.
I was so happy...
to have my peaceful life back.
But I keep doing the same thing.
I'm a slut now.
Hino-kun stops by during his
deliveries a couple of times a week.
And I can't stop myself when he comes by.
I do feel bad for Shuichi-san,
but I can't reject Hino-kun.
Looks like I can head home early today.
She'll be surprised to see me this early.
Your pussy is amazing, Nanami!
How can you tell if mine is the only one you know?
I just know it!
I know you love your husband, but you're mine now, right?
Yeah. Right now, I'm your woman.
Please cum deep inside of me, and make me feel good!
That's good! I'm feeling it!
Yes! It's so hot!
I feel the heat inside me!
I'm having sex with Hino-kun. I'm doing it!
Don't worry. You can do it harder!
Just for now... Just for now you can...
It's hitting deep inside...
Amazing! It's hitting my womb!
Oh, no! It feels so good that I'm wetting my floor!
Yes! It's so good!
Moving so rough!
Is it good?
Is sex with me better than with your husband?
Don't be mean!
But yeah, this is good!
I feel... I feel better with you, Hino-kun!
I can't even count how many times I've
had sex with Hino-kun like this...
or how many times I've betrayed Shuichi-san.
I love Shuichi-san.
He's the only person in my heart.
Hino-kun saved me, so I want to give him my body in return.
I'm cumming.
Yes! Yes!
But I can't keep doing this forever.
I have to stop this before Shuichi-san learns about it.
To give him all my love is the only thing I can
do to make up for all the sins I've committed.
I'm home!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
Today is our fourth anniversary.
I have something to tell Shuichi-san when he comes home.
I wonder if he'll be happy to hear this.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
Shuichi-san, I'm having a baby.
Maternal and Child Health Handbook
I've gone through a lot of things,
but this is our baby Shuichi-san.
And yet... I Still Love My Wife
And yet... I still love my wife.
And yet... I still     my wife.
And yet... I Still        My Wife