The mothers of Shimozuru Nanami and Kamishiro Sakura
are close friends, so their families are getting along together.
Their daughters get along well just like sisters.
Based on their personalities,
Nanami would be the older sister and Sakura the younger one.
When it comes to their bodies,
Sakura's eye-catching huge breasts make up for her shortcomings.
However, Nanami's well-filled body is enough to titillate men.
Sakura often gets teased because of her enormous breasts.
She finds it difficult to deal with boys.
Nanami's headstrong personality helps her in protecting Sakura.
She grouches at the boys and even resorts to hitting them with her fists.
This resulted in Nanami getting an unladylike nickname attached to her...
These two girls are kindly looked after by Sakura's father, Shouhei.
He works at an IT firm and attained a high position there at a young age.
Besides Sakura, he takes care of Nanami as well.
Nanami's father may be gone, but Shouhei dotes on her
like how he does on his real daughter when they go out together.
Nanami herself also loves him like a real father.
It is in the early summer...
At a humid day of the season when sudden thunderstorms commonly occur...
Dark clouds started to spread out as if it was overcasting
Nanami and Sakura's peaceful days.
Assertive and Beautiful Girl: Shimozuru Nanami
Nanami is a competitive girl who hates losing so much.
She has always kept the easily bullied Sakura safe ever since they were little.
The two get along well like they were sisters.
She acts as an older sister who protects Sakura.
Nanami confronts boys with no fear,
even resorting to using force to deal with them at times.
Thanks to that, she was given a nickname of "battering wife"
which she gets teased with.
The Huge-breasted Childhood Friend: Kamishiro Sakura
Sakura is a beautiful girl who possesses breasts so huge that they stand out a lot.
She is a bright and cheerful girl when it comes to her fellow friends.
Despite that, she isn't good at dealing with boys
who often make fun of her for having huge breasts.
She tries to avoid them as much as possible instead.
Her close friend Nanami pampers her like a little sister all the time.
However, she thinks that she has to get her act together somehow.
A Helpful and Ideal Father: Kamishiro Shouhei
Shouhei is Sakura's father.
He is an ideal father who voluntarily works hard on taking care of his daughter.
He even treats Nanami the same way he does with Sakura,
looking after and thinking of her like she is his own daughter.
Shouhei's relationship with his wife is going well.
He socializes with his wife's good friend Kanako.
But on the other hand...
It's been a while since they went out for a vacation on a holiday.
Shouhei brought Nanami to a resort
together with Sakura so they can enjoy themselves.
Their fun times went by so fast and it's all memories now.
Sakura invited Nanami to take a look
at the photos of those memories they shared together.
She forgot that she had something to do first,
so she told Nanami to go to her house alone first.
"Nana-chan, you can go first and wait there for me."
"Jeez, you're such a handful, Sakura."
Nanami wryly smiles as she reaches the entry hall
of Sakura's house, bringing the key with her.
Nanami walked into the Kamishiro household
where there should be nobody around.
The sky is overcast, and the vicinity is dim from the downpour.
She accidentally saw a particular scene...
If she just went back with Sakura instead...
If she just waited until tomorrow for this...
The thoughts that faintly swept through her...
They are all getting wiped out by the fleshy member
than approached in front of her...
Original Animation
And then, what uncle did to me...
A Sworn Betrayal
Do something about your clumsiness.
Well then, uncle. Thank you.
You did a great job. That's for looking after Sakura.
Huh? Even you are talking
like that about me, papa.
Thank you for taking care of her, Kamishiro-san.
Thanks to you as well, Sakura-chan.
Don't be. I also had a great time.
Join us with Misaki next time,
Kanako-san. Well then!
We're a family with a single mother.
I get along well with my mom like we're sisters.
Sakura's mom has been long-time friends with mine.
From being acquaintances when
we started being in the same class,
we got along well as close friends.
Uncle and auntie also treat me like their own daughter.
I also am allowed to get rides on uncle's car.
He is a kind uncle. He knows a lot
of things and he's fun to be with.
I'd love him to be with my mom if he was single.
I'll do it right next time.
I hope so, though it'll be the third time.
Gosh, you always say stuff like that...
Nana-chan is bold and good at taking care of others.
She's more of an older sister than a friend.
She always pampers me and comes to my rescue,
like how she covered up for me
today when I made a mistake.
I've been thinking that I need
to get myself together, but...
Things aren't working out this way...
Nana-chan...
Oops...
They're jiggling today as well!
That's a sight for sore eyes!
Hey, do you want to get hit?
Oh no, it's the battering wife!
Who's the battering wife? Idiots!
Jeez, they really are brats...
Are you alright, Sakura?
Yeah... This isn't anything new.
Uhh... So, this is what they
mean by "traumatized".
Jeez, just take these goodies out and flaunt them!
Nana-chan!?
We'll be wobbling them for today!
Hi-yah!
Uhh, gosh... Mika-chan too...
Our class ends here, but carefully check
every detail of the information.
Nana-chan, let's check the photos
from last time at my house.
We'll get plenty of instagrammables!
You're right. I want something to upload.
Alright, go straight home.
Oh... Wait, Sakura! Didn't you say
that you'll take a look at that thing?
Oh, yeah. I forgot about it!
I'll wait for you.
Hmm... It's gonna take me some time, though...
Oh, you can go first and wait there for me.
Here's the key.
Kamishiro, will that take longer?
Okay! Bye, Nana-chan. I'll leave it to you.
Alright, then. Get that done quickly.
I understand.
Mika-chan...
It's because I'm slow on these things.
Okay, let's get this done already!
Sakura can be pushy at times.
Yeah, this should be it.
Just as I expected from you, Kamishiro-kun...
I'll be going in!
I always come here, but it's my
first time here when nobody's home.
The thunders are loud.
Huh!?
Huh? Ah!
Sensei, that feels good!
It feels good when you scrape my pussy inside!
Were you jealous that you want to do it here?
Jeez, Sensei... You're such a tease!
You're aiming for Sakura, though!
You're the only one for me right now.
Jeez, what do you mean "right now"?
Sensei! Yes!
I'm gonna come!
That took me longer than expected.
Oh, Nana-chan!
I'm home!
Welcome back, Sakura.
That took some time, huh?
The train came late and it rained heavier
on top of that. It was awful!
Let's hurry up and go to your room.
Huh? Did something happen?
Welcome home. I went back
for the same reason.
The typhoon is getting bad
so I finished work early.
So that's what happened.
Aren't you soaked? You're gonna catch a cold.
Okay, I'll take a shower first.
P-Please stop.
Didn't you promise? Or would
you rather have Sakura...
I'll do it, so don't get her involved...
Shall we go inside?
Yes, you have a plump and meaty ass.
You have childbearing hips, Nanami-kun.
Huh?
Please get through with it already!
Oh, I knew it. It's just you, Nanami-kun.
I thought it was someone else.
Wh-What were you doing, uncle!?
P-Please tuck that in!
You talk harshly for someone who barged in.
That's because Sakura gave me
the key and told me to go back first.
That's why... You see...
If Sakura knows about this...
You're mistaken.
You see, I'm only checking Sakura's growth.
No way, doing such a thing...
No! Please stop doing that!
I do this and massage Sakura's tits as she sleeps.
Didn't she grow up?
That's gross...
Are you giving me that kind of look, Nanami-kun?
Take your hand off, uncle! I'm begging you.
Don't do anything that will upset Sakura!
I understand. But in exchange...
Will you do it for me using your hand?
It'll only be until Sakura goes back.
Just a little... We'll be done in no time.
Only until she comes back...
Okay.
It feels hot and it's twitching...
This is disgusting!
That's it, Nanami-kun. Keep that up.
Sakura
I'll be home soon! (Read@18:23)
S-Sakura is...
Uncle, if we keep going on...
Hey, Nanami-kun. Show me your panties.
No! Wait, uncle!
Don't! No!
We'll be done soon. Just a little more.
No way... You said that it's only
until Sakura comes back...
I'm begging you, uncle!
Any more than this and...
Are you still not done?
Sakura is about to go out, so hurry!
He's been groping me the whole time...
I just wanted to feel your hands.
You're a pervert!
Raise your hips.
That's it. Don't move.
H-Hey, what are you doing?
She'll find us out if you're too loud.
I'll calm down sooner if we do this.
Ah, that was refreshing!
No way, uncle!
Stop it already! Sakura is coming here!
Just stay put.
Huh? What are you doing?
Looks like she's making snacks.
Is that so?
This won't take long.
I was keeping it as a surprise!
I'm looking forward to it.
It's been rubbing against me for the whole time...
P-Please hurry up and make it calm down!
You're right, then...
Uncle, no! It went inside!
That's because you want it done right away.
Huh?
This can't be! It went in! This is...
It's inside! No way...
We're at such a place, and uncle is...
Bear with it, alright? This will be over soon.
Uncle's thing is inside me while we're at this place.
Even though Sakura is around...
Don't do that, uncle!
Sakura will notice if you're too loud.
Is uncle planning to shoot his stuff just like this?
No! No! No!
This can't be...
He's coming inside me!
The rain isn't stopping...
Nanami-kun, you got dirty.
Come on, you should take a bath as well.
What happened?
Oh, she just spilled something.
Just wait for her in your room, Sakura.
Okay! Make it quick, Nana-chan!
Nanami-kun, stay here for tonight.
The transit system is down due to heavy rain.
Really? She won't be able to go home, then.
B-But...
I already called Kanako-san.
Alright...
Goodnight, Nana-chan!
Sakura...
Are you already asleep?
You're so cute!
That's true. Isn't she cute?
Make any noise and you'll wake her up.
So, you're not wearing panties.
Were you waiting for this?
No! After you soiled them like that,
there's no way that I can wear them!
That's the proof of your first time.
Keep it as a token.
You pervert! Stop talking nonsense!
You offered yourself as
a replacement for Sakura.
No way... Stop making up
a convenient excuse.
Is that so? Then, let's end it right here,
and I'll check Sakura's growth...
Please stop that...
You can do it with me instead.
Sakura is such a lucky girl.
Papa?
Don't catch a cold, alright?
Yeah... Thanks, papa...
Wasn't that surprising?
Your pussy also tightened and it felt good.
You can make that kind of face as well, huh?
No!
He's doing this even when Sakura's next to us!
Does it still hurt?
Maybe you're a bit used to it now?
Don't mess with me! This only feels bad to me!
Even though Sakura is here... Scum! Pervert!
Your pussy tightens while you complain.
I'll shoot it out in no time.
No, don't! You'll stain my pajamas!
Sakura will notice! No!
It can't be helped, then...
That's right.
Uhh... Papa?
It's alright. Go back to sleep.
I can't breathe!
I'll have to swallow this...
This stuff is disgusting...
But I'll get dirty if anything spills out!
That was great, Nanami-kun.
You're the worst!
I can't tell even to Sakura that
uncle did such a thing to me!
It's her early shift today... Mom!
Mom!
Yes. So, Misaki will join as well.
Sounds like it'll be fun.
Oh! Welcome home, Nanami.
Welcome home, Nanami-kun.
Uncle...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Next Time on Soshite Watashi wa Ojisan ni...
Please, enough of this!
Uncle's thing is inside me again!
It's easier to put it in now.
Not with this man... I'll never ever...
That face will be a fond memory.
Oh, Nanami-kun.
Huh!?
Huh? Uncle...
N-Nobody would be coming here...
P-Please make it quick.
It's because I happened to see you, Nanami-kun.
I couldn't hold myself back.
No way...
Please make this the last time!
Brute! Pervert!
I'm thinking that I should hold back.
It's just that I lose my self-control when I see you.
You never even considered that!
You're wrong!
That's definitely not true at all!