The mothers of Shimozuru Nanami and Kamishiro Sakura are close friends,
so their daughters naturally got along well just like sisters.
Based on their personalities Nanami is the older sister
and Sakura is the younger one.
When it comes to their bodies, Sakura's eye-catching
huge breasts make up for her shortcomings.
However, Nanami's body is amply filled at the right places
which was enough to titillate men.
These two girls are kindly looked after by Sakura's father, Shouhei.
He works at an IT firm and attained a high position there at a young age.
Besides Sakura, he takes care of Nanami as well.
Nanami only has a mother in her family,
but Shouhei has been doting on her
like how he does on his real daughter.
Nanami also loved and fully trusted him like a real father.
Early summer...
On one humid day of the season...
Dark clouds started to spread out and a thunderstorm started its downpour
as if they were shrouding Nanami and Sakura's peaceful days.
Assertive and Beautiful Girl: Shimozuru Nanami
Nanami is a competitive girl who hates losing so much.
She has always kept the easily bullied Sakura safe ever since they were little.
The two get along well like they were sisters.
She acts as an older sister who protects Sakura.
Nanami confronts boys with no fear,
even resorting to using force to deal with them at times.
Thanks to that, she was given a nickname of "battering wife"
which she gets teased with.
The Huge-breasted Childhood Friend: Kamishiro Sakura
Sakura is a beautiful girl who possesses breasts so huge that they stand out a lot.
She is a bright and cheerful girl when it comes to her fellow friends.
Despite that, she isn't good at dealing with boys
who often make fun of her for having huge breasts.
She tries to avoid them as much as possible instead.
Her close friend Nanami pampers her like a little sister all the time.
However, she thinks that she has to get her act together somehow.
A Helpful and Ideal Father: Kamishiro Shouhei
Shouhei is Sakura's father.
He is an ideal father who voluntarily works hard on taking care of his daughter.
He even treats Nanami the same way he does with Sakura,
looking after and thinking of her like she is his own daughter.
Shouhei's relationship with his wife is going well.
He socializes with his wife's good friend Kanako.
But on the other hand...
It was only because Sakura suggested Nanami
to take the key and go to Sakura's house in advance
that she accidentally saw that.
The man that Nanami supposedly trusted
requested her something, which rarely happens.
Without minding her hateful gaze,
he reached out his arm and sank his hand
to her plump breast.
His burning hot, revolting, and upright thing
forcibly infringed her pure light pink flower bud.
Unbelievable as it seems, he's penetrating Nanami
who's worried about Sakura sleeping right next to them.
She desperately tries to resist as he humps
on her soft, bare, round, and bouncy butt,
but she became aroused in the end.
And he ultimately screwed
his upright and outrageous thing
into Nanami's mouth.
Original Animation
And then, what uncle did to me...
A Faded Hatred
Last Time on Soshite Watashi wa Ojisan ni...
Do something about your clumsiness.
Well then, uncle. Thank you.
You did a great job. Thanks for looking after Sakura.
Huh? Even you are talking
like that about me, papa.
Thank you for taking care of her, Kamishiro-san.
Thanks to you as well, Sakura-chan.
Don't be. I also had a great time.
Join us with Misaki next time,
Kanako-san. Well then!
The thunders are loud.
Huh!?
Huh? Ah!
Oh, I knew it. It's just you, Nanami-kun.
I thought it was someone else.
Wh-What were you doing, uncle!?
P-Please tuck that in!
You talk harshly for someone who barged in.
That's because Sakura gave me
the key and told me to go back first.
That's why... You see...
It feels hot and it's twitching...
This is disgusting!
I'll calm down sooner if we do this.
Uncle's thing is inside me while we're at this place.
Even though Sakura is around...
So, you're not wearing panties.
Were you waiting for this?
No! After you soiled them like that,
there's no way that I can wear them!
Please stop that...
You can do it with me instead.
Sakura is such a lucky girl.
No!
He's doing this even when Sakura's next to us!
Does it still hurt?
Maybe you're a bit used to it now?
Don't mess with me!
This only feels bad to me!
I can't tell even to Sakura that
uncle did such a thing to me!
It's her early shift today... Mom!
Mom!
Yes. So, Misaki will join as well.
Sounds like it'll be fun.
Oh! Welcome home, Nanami.
Welcome home, Nanami-kun.
Uncle...
Is that so? She doesn't seem
that way to me.
Right, Nanami?
She's different when outside.
We tend to be extra strict
when it comes to our own child.
Oh...
Huh? Oh, my tea...
No, please stop!
I'll show you the pictures from yesterday.
So you're wearing bloomers.
That's a wild choice.
Huh!? It's because you soiled them
that I have no choice but to wear these, pervert!
I like this.
But couldn't you just have
borrowed a pair from Sakura?
Sakura's are... Umm, tight on me...
Oh, right... It was Sakura's, after all.
You sound like having fun.
Please, enough of this!
You don't want to give Kanako-san trouble, right?
You're a scum!
Sakura's body may be lacking when
compared to yours, but her tits grew big.
P-Please stop saying disgusting
things! You are her father!
Pervert! Ugh...
Scum!
You're drinking my stuff...
I can't get enough of this!
You're the one making me drink it!
Nanami, I made some tea. How about
taking a little break from studying?
Oh, you shouldn't have bothered.
I'm about to go home.
Oh my, you should take your time.
You went out of your way to drop by.
Uhh... Uncle seems to have some stuff to do.
I see, have a tea at least. It was only
a gift from someone though.
Go away already!
That's mean. Then, I'll just have a taste...
N-No! We can't do this!
I'll partake of you before going home.
Uncle's thing is inside me again!
It's easier to put in now.
Looks like you got used to the shape of my cock now.
Say what you want!
I don't care whatever you do to me!
It's a treat for me when you look like that.
Not with this man... I'll never ever...
That kind of face will turn
into a fond memory in time,
since my cock is incredible!
That won't happen!
I'll only stay this way!
Again!?
He just came earlier but he still has this much!
They got soiled again.
Get out of here already.
See you next time, Nanami-kun.
Scum!
Sakura
I found something new again! I'll let you know about it
next time so come here for a sleepover! (Read@20:12)
I got tainted by uncle... Even in my room too...
Sakura...
Sakura, what are your plans at lunch break?
Oh, sorry! I need to check that
thing from last time again.
Is that so? That sounds difficult.
Sakura, It's okay now.
Okay! You should've taken your time.
I don't want to make you wait!
What are you saying, Mika-chan! Gosh...
Alright, Nana-chan. I'll be going.
Do your best.
Sakura's not with me, so maybe
I should eat on the rooftop
Oh, Nanami-kun.
Huh!?
Huh? Uncle... Why are you...
Sakura made me bring something
she forgot. I gave it to her earlier.
I was thinking about going back, but...
I want you to show me around, Nanami-kun.
I'm talking about somewhere secluded.
What are you thinking? Sakura is here too!
You're crazy!
Doesn't she have an errand? You're lonely
that you two couldn't eat together.
I'll accompany you in her place.
N-Nobody would be coming here...
P-Please make it quick.
Being touched like is becoming normal to me now.
We'll be done in no time.
It's because I happened to see you, Nanami-kun.
I couldn't hold myself back.
O-Ouch... You're squeezing it too hard!
You make it sound like it's my fault, scum!
We should do more of this at various places.
That way, you'll remember
about me wherever you are.
No way...
Please make this the last time!
Brute! Pervert!
I'm thinking that I should hold back.
It's just that I lose my self-control when I see you.
You never even considered that!
Scum!
It went in smoothly.
Looks like your pussy was waiting for me.
Please don't say gross stuff!
There's no way...
...that it's waiting for you!
I can tell that your body is being honest.
Your insides get oozy when I do it hard.
I also know that your nipples get hard
when I'm being rough on you.
You're wrong!
That's not true at all!
No! It's overflowing from inside me, but my body is...
Your pussy is amazing, Nanami-kun!
It felt like you're milking my cock dry.
Please pull it out already.
Any more of this and...
Hey, hurry up!
It should be fine here, right?
Sakura! No way, what should I do?
She's going here!
No way!
What's behind that door?
Huh? That's it!
Didn't you say that nobody would be here?
Nobody usually comes here, that's why...
And why is Sakura here?
Isn't it for an errand?
But it should be in that usual classroom...
What errand is here in the first place...
Come on!
Time will run out if we don't hurry, sensei!
This place is far away...
It's dark and nobody comes here...
That's why around this time of the day...
But...
But there are rumors that after school hours,
couples are supposedly using this room...
Huh!?
Sensei, your hands are naughty!
No way, those are my nipples!
Hey...
I love it when you rub them with your hands!
It feels so good!
Didn't I teach you to let me feel
good too, not just yourself alone?
It's huge!
Isn't this harder than usual, sensei?
Seems that you can't take it anymore
and want to put it in already.
It's okay, put it inside me!
It went in!
Your stiff dick feels great!
Your insides are squishy, Sakura.
This part is the one that couldn't take it anymore.
No way! If you say something like that, I'm...
That's right.
I've been craving for a dick that
I couldn't hold myself back!
That's good, sensei!
Keep pounding it deep inside me!
Harder!
Sakura...
Sensei...
Stir me up with your dick!
Fondle my pussy a lot!
I'll be shooting plenty for today as well.
Sakura... Sakura!
Come!
Shoot lots of semen into my pussy!
Sensei!
Yes! I-I'm coming!
Sensei, let's come together!
I'm coming! I'm coming—!
Yes...
It's gushing into me...
This feeling is amazing...
Sensei, your dick was incredible...
I need to go back immediately...
No way, give it back!
Having classes with no bra
last time was embarrassing.
But didn't that make you horny?
Uhh... You're right, but I don't want that...
Sakura...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji