The shadow-leader of Draktown, Bozuk, had imprisoned Iris,
an Armored Knight Ace pilot with the Galactic Federation Senate.
Another pilot in her team, Meiri, was also taken.
She discovers a woman calling herself "Riruru", who looks exactly like Meiri.
Taking a liking to Iris. Riruru has the Duck People,
a slave race brought to Darktown, gang rape Iris.
As Iris's body undergoes violation from numerous different alien species,
her body changes into a lustful one that derives pleasure from deviant sex.
When Iris returns to the brothel, a new customer awaits her.
And Riruru embraces a secret and unstoppable lust for Iris.
Iris then begins to suspect that Riruru and Meiri are actually the same person.
Is Riruru really Meiri?
And what will Iris's fate be now that she has awakened to ecstasy?
Soukou Kijo Iris
From Oppressed Warrior to a Survivor
So you're awake, Iris.
Bozuk?
What are you trying to do to me?
Actually, I've got a special visitor for you.
Wh-What did you say?
Ouch!
W-What's going on?
Have you heard of the planet "Bokyun" in the outer galaxy?
The place where super-large aliens live?
That's right.
I just reconstructed your genitals so they
would be more compatible with theirs.
H-How dare you!
How dare you do this to me, Bozuk!
Would you have preferred I left you small?
If I leave you the way you were,
you might not survive as a human, Iris.
Stop messing around with me!
And put my body back to normal!
Stop putting up such a fight.
Sex with that kind of body might be extra nice, Iris.
Stop saying stupid things. Hurry!
Come back!
D-Don't tell me...
Where is she? The specialty of this brothel...
I had no idea he was this big.
Oh, down there?
Got you!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Don't hate me so much.
But you sure are small compared to girls from other planets...
Excuse me a minute.
Hey!
Th-That hurts.
Stop it.
No, I can't.
After all, if I find something dangerous inside of you, I'll be in trouble.
How about your insides?
Lemme see...
That hurts!
That... hurts.
Stop it!
Looks like there's no danger.
Sorry about that, pretty doll.
I'll fix your wound now.
What are you doing?
Stop that!
Stop it, please...
Pretty doll!
So soft and squishy...
Your delicious looking figure. It's time to eat!
What a big tongue...
It feels so good.
Now I've licked you all wet.
It's time to go.
Here I go.
It'll be fun.
But it's so big!
That hurts!
S-Stop it, Mr. Giant!
I'll break!
My uterus... My whole body... It'll break!
Wow, it's so tight.
I love them small!
Stop it, please!
But I can't stop it.
I just started.
It's so tight.
So tight.
That hurts!
Yes... Yes... Yes!
I can't stop myself.
I can't stop!
Wh-What are you doing now?
I'm... I'm breaking!
My hole... It's breaking in half!
This is the best!
It's so tight on me!
Oh, my doll!
I-I'm cumming!
Yes!
That felt great!
Well then...
I guess small girls really are the best!
I... I...
What did I...
Wh-Where am I?
Don't worry, Iris.
Riruru!
I returned your body to normal with surgery.
How much longer do I have to put up with this!?
Well... That's a good question.
I'm not even sure myself.
Stop joking around, Riruru!
Open your eyes!
Let me out of this place!
I'm begging you, Meiri!
Wh-What?
So you finally woke up.
A master's wall?
What are you going to do to me this time!?
Today, it's Special Visitors Day.
Lord Bozuk ordered me to send the guests of honor to you.
Special visitors day?
Here we have a special day where we invite special guests in for free,
and we have a special service where we incapacitate a
prostitute's body so they can do whatever they want to it.
Wh-Why is that?
Your body is separated by that special wall into two separate rooms.
One is your top half, the other your bottom.
The special visitors flip a coin to determine which half of you they get.
Give me a fucking break!
Well. Your customers are about to arrive.
Be a good whore.
H-Hey, Riruru! I don't like this!
Let me go!
Aww, looks like we got stuck with the top half.
But she's really pretty!
Good point.
I wouldn't mind cumming into her mouth.
Wh-Who are you guys?
Someone... is touching me.
S-Stop it. I don't wanna do this!
Hey, come on, it's a free service day.
Suck it dry!
Very nice!
Stop it, I'm telling you!
Pretty defiant for a whore.
This is what you get!
You're hurting me!
Stop it!
You like it?
Doesn't it feel great back by your throat?
I feel the back of your throat!
Feels great!
Go! Go! Go!
Shove it deeper, you female pig!
Here I come!
That felt really great.
How terrible...
Wh-What?
Someone is sucking on me?
N-No...
Stop it... Please...
It's hot!
Ah! Isn't she enjoying it?
No surprise! Whoever's back there has her vagina!
All right! That's got me excited!
Stop it!
You female pig!
What's your problem?
Ah! It's so tight!
What's her problem?
She's thrusting into me!
Ah, her other hole.
Whoever's on the other side is shoving her closer to me.
This feels great!
Looks like whoever's on the other side of the wall is fucking her hard too.
I wanna fuck all the way down to her stomach!
That's pretty good, you pig!
I'm cumming!
That's right! Drink it, female pig!
Ah, it's out.
Okay I can't hold back anymore.
Move it!
My turn next.
Come here. Take it!
Amazingly perfect!
You're good.
It's... so tight! What the hell?
So tight!
It hurts...
My penis is getting squeezed so hard!
Yes...
Yes! This feels great!
It's amazing!
My vagina... is going crazy!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
What a bitch.
She's completely nuts.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Iris.
Looks like you«had lots of fun.
Something like this...
If that many penises are shoved into me and I feel
that much pleasure, of course I'd lose my mind.
l can't go back to the way I was.
You'll be on duty tomorrow as well.
After all, you get to taste some new penises.
The longer I stay here, the more I'll lose my mind.
I must do something.
How is it? Did you get a signal?
No good.
Too much jamming in the radar.
I can't catch any signal.
Don't give up!
At any cost, we must rescue Lieutenant Iris.
Roger.
Lieutenant Iris... Lieutenant Meiri...
It's open!
So Riruru was telling the truth!
If Riruru was trying to deceive me... I don't care if I die.
Now, Iris. It's time to go.
No one's here?
I think I can escape!
Where's the transmitter?
Found it!
So you finally came, Iris.
Riruru.
So you tricked me after all!
I'll kill you!
Iris!
W-Wait a minute!
T-Take a look at this!
Yeah? So what.
Go ahead and shock me with it if you want.
My goodness, you are so predictable.
Wh-What? What's going on?
You wanted to escape, right?
I'll let you escape.
Let me escape? But why?
I loved watching you in pleasure.
But I hated watching other guys sharing the pleasure with you.
It looks like I've seriously fallen in love with you.
And if that's the case, then I'll give you what you want.
Riruru!
Take this with you, too.
Wh-What is this?
It's an Armored Knight survival kit...
There's an emergency tracing signal in there.
Riruru!
You must hurry.
I've suppressed the security system, but it won't last long.
Me? Oh, don t worry about that.
Nothing will change.
I'll still be Bozuk's slave, same as before.
I can't get any lower than that.
What are you doing? Hurry!
Hey, Riruru.
Do you want to escape with me?
Hey, Iris... What are you talking about?
I decided from the very start that when I escape, I'd take you with me.
Is that because you think I'm Meiri?
Not really.
That has nothing to do with it.
Because I think that this could be the beginning of a great friendship.
Iris... I'll take that seriously.
I won't let you do that.
Bozuk!
Lord Bozuk!
I knew it.
I've been tracking Riruru because she's been acting so strangely lately.
Shit!
Lord Bozuk, I...
Hey, Riruru, if you see this thing, would you still want to escape?
B-But that's... Lord Bozuk...
Riruru, what's wrong? Did something happen?
You want it, don't you?
If you want it, I'll let you have it.
I want it! I want your penis, Lord Bozuk!
Lord Bozuk... Your penis...
Yummy!
Wh-What's going on?
What is this?
Shall I tell you?
Riruru has split-personalities.
Split-personalities?
That's right. "Riruru" is an alternative personality your friend Meiri created.
So Riruru really is Meiri!
Right. Meiri was sold here before you.
And just like with you, I forced my lust onto her.
No!!
No, stop it!
And just like you, Meiri was a virgin.
And then, when I ejaculated into her,
Meiri's atmosphere changed immediately.
She suddenly became lustful and asked me for my penis on her own will.
She called herself "Riruru".
What the hell? What does this mean?
Sexual Shafting. It's a special skill the Elves have.
I have heard of that phenomenon.
When an Elf undergoes severe sexual trauma,
she creates another personality
She seals off her original personality and lusts after sex.
Riruru is a completely different personality than she was before we had sex.
Oh, no! Meiri!
Now that you have learned that Riruru is really Meiri, I cannot let you escape.
If you want to save Riruru's life, then put that collar back on.
Shit!
Get a move on!
And then, hand over that survival kit thing to me.
Very good. Good girl.
But you must still be punished...
Please... Please spare me...
Save me!
Don't hurt me!
Huh? Lord Bozuk, what's wrong?
Ouch! That hurts!
Meiri!
Iris...
I...
Meiri, your memory is...
Captain! I've picked-up Iris's signal!
Everything's fine now, Meiri.
Yes - "Meiri".