Lowering speed.
Cutting thruster engines.
Plotting invasion course - all green.
Until the point of descent;
another 200.
Good.
After we've sent Hina off,
plot a course for the rendezvous point.
Roger...
Head towards 7- 6 Cruise Mode.
Lower your altitude.
Roger.
Releasing the hatch.
Mission Control reporting, safety clearance granted.
Until the point of descent;
another 150.
Preparing to cut communication lines.
TMM-wave levels set.
Until the point of descent;
another 50.
Commence transport to the ruins site.
Cutting communications.
Go.
May our mission be a success.
Little birdies... Now's your time to fly!
The human race separated itself from the birdcage called Earth,
and have favored traveling to the distant stars.
The galaxy holds many different types of races which,
under control of the Galactic Federation Senate,
were ruled and regulated peacefully.
However, time, location, and the races were destined to change.
The purging of evil from the galaxy was wishful thinking.
The Galactic Federation Senate created a special task force,
the SSF, which holds strong orbital power.
It shortened the distance between the planets,
The SSF101 special large armored suit...
Its body was supported entirely by a group of women.
In the shape of a human and the size of a skyscraper, it patrolled the galaxy.
These young innocent women defend the honor of the galaxy.
The people had a special name for these women -
Soukou Kijo Iris
Descent From the High Sky
There's something on the radar?
Iris!
Meiri!
We aren't supposed to use our transmitters!
It's a trap.
There's an enemy straight ahead!
Were they expecting us!?
Meiri! Are you okay?
Meiri!
Are you all okay!?
Jamming?
Don't tell me our intelligence reports were leaked!
We were deceived... Unbelievable!
It's useless...
When I lost my armored suit,
I was taken by the Orc race for healing.
They purge battlefields,
and comb the wreckage for anything they can use.
Even if the "wreckage" includes human beings...
Almost time, I see.
What do you think?
Anything else you'd like to see?
Please calm yourselves. We have plenty of items for sale.
Please follow our rules.
I've destroyed places like this before...
But I never dreamed I would be sold in one of them.
Don't convince yourself you can escape, girl.
If I have to put a scar on your pretty face, your price will go down.
10 million credits.
Then the deal is closed.
Well then, next up is this month's crown jewel.
Now, I hope you recognize her.
She is of the mysterious primitive race...
She is an Earthling!
"Mysterious primitive race"? How rude!
Don't do anything tricky.
If you don't behave like a commodity, I will kill you
You think I'll let myself die in a place like this?
I will live through this at any cost!
Earthlings usually go for lower prices,
but this specimen is pure.
And, moreover, she's a virgin!
A pure one?
That's tempting.
Hey, how do you know she's really a virgin?
Oh my, oh my. However the customer is always right.
Allow her to prove to you that she is indeed a virgin.
"Prove"? How can I do that?
I'll release your hands. You'll be able to show them proof yourself.
But still, how can I show them pr-
It appears as though she still needs more education.
No!
I can't... Ah, stop it!
Oh, excuse me.
Well then, let's make it clearly visible to the gentlemen here.
How dare he inflict such torture on me!
Now that we have seen proof of her virginity,
let's test out her other selling points.
We can't just test her out as we please?
Well, I wouldn't want her virginity to be lost before I sell her.
So everything else is okay then, right?
No... Stop this at once!
You think you're in the place to give orders?
You're a slave now. Give up!
No! Stop this!
Not with that foul thing...!
If you don't cooperate, there's no telling what will happen to you. Got it?
Squeeze it.
That's right!
Can't use her the way I want.
I wanna bury myself so deep in her, it feels like a waste!
Don't rest your mouth!
Put mine in too!
I guess since she's a virgin, she's never given head before.
Oh well, it can't be helped.
Stop crying and start sucking!
I can't be satisfied with just her boobs!
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm making do just by rubbing it against you.
Use your tongue!
Her nipples are hard.
You think she's enjoying it while she's crying?
This hurts... Please... Please, just finish already!
Yeah, that's it! Suck it harder!
Harry! Let this be soon!
If you want it to end faster, help make it happen!
Your semen... Hurry and release your semen!
Fine. Then I'll shoot it out!
She's finally become a good girl, eh?
Is there no mistaking it?
10 million credits.
Shit. The boss gets really bad deals these days.
Yeah, the Elf-girl he bought the other day was also 10 million.
They're draining us of our money.
An Elf?
Could Meiri have fallen into the same trap I did?
I have come to take you to him
Beyond that door is the man who bought me.
Maybe even Meiri.
Oh, it looks good on you.
This "thing" bought me?
What a horrible stench.
The smell is not coming from this room, it's from him!
What's wrong? Is this mansion so strange to you?
Wh-What do you intend to do with me, sir?
I want you to join my harem. You'll be the jewel of my collection, I'm sure.
But I don't want to join a harem...
On this planet, you are a slave. You have no rights.
And what's more, if I take possession of your
armored suit, I'll be the talk of the town.
So you knew?
There is nothing that goes on in this city that I don't know.
Allow me to educate you into a proper little whore.
I was planning on laying low and cooperating,
I'll do this!
Damn...
I bought you.
You must not forget that fact.
So you're still conscious.
Armored Knights sure are tough.
Don't put such a smelly thing on my body!
Just behave yourself.
Unless you'd rather I shoot you up with more electricity?
Stand up.
Undress.
At last you have accepted your status as a slave, I see.
Good. Spread your own legs,
and come to me!
So at last you have become docile.
That is a quality I look for in a whore who needs to be fucked!
Please... Fuck me, sir.
If Meiri was also captured here...
Then I can't let myself die.
So...
This gross beast will steal my virginity!
Meiri...
Save me... Meiri!
Meiri?
So even the strong Armored Knight has a tough time withstanding this pain?
That hurts! Please be slower!
A whore has no right to give orders!
Force yourself to like it!
But I... That's impossible!
That's a virgin for you.
She's squeezing my thing really tight!
Hurry! Just finish quickly!
It feels like my insides are being ripped apart.
If this pain continues much longer, I'll lose my mind!
What do you think?
My thing's pretty great, isn't it!?
Deep... It's too deep! It's hurting me!
Can't you start moving your own hips for me?
I can't... There's no way I can do that!
You're so tight, I'm gonna cum right away.
No! My insides are getting swollen!
Don't! Don't cum inside of me!
Stop it!
My insides... are being dirtied.
How strange. My body is... so hot.
I can't hold back!
My hands are moving on my own.
Oh no! My head is drifting away!
I can't think anymore.
Looks like you've made it past the first stage.
With Ecstasia, it is ten times more potent than the other.
No!
It's flowing inside...
My insides are twitching!
Oh no!
Oh really?
Does it really feel that good?
In that case, I'll use my special thing from now on!
Now, talk to me like the whore you are!
Please cum. Please cum inside of me!
I want your semen! I want your semen inside my violated vagina!
You've said it! That's the ticket!
Why did I just say that?
You're a good girl. Well then, here I come!
It's no good.
My consciousness...
I'm going to... I'm going to right here...
Footsteps...
Who... Who's there?
I'll use this antidote to return your sanity.
However, it will send you from Heaven to Hell...
Mei... ri?