I'm home.
Sexual Pursuit.
Part B
It's so hot...
I'm so hungry.
Yuji, is he home already?
Umm.
Yuji...
who in this age plays dice games?
Yuji... why you!
What!?
What the...
What is going on...
One, two, three...
it's a red square.
Oh yeah.
Kiss.
So what am I supposed to do with this?
Yu-chan, hold on.
Take off your clothes.
Stop, Yu-chan...
Please don't look.
Oral Sex.
Yuji, please stop. Mom, you too!
Why with Yuji...
Get away from my Yuji!
Mom! Lt... it feels so good!
It feels so good!
Mom, are you filled with me?
Yu-chan...
if we are lovers...
I want to kiss!
Yuji... please stop...
Stop it...
Stop it!
That... dream again...
it can't...
right.
Agh... I'm so sweaty. Yuck.
Why a dream like that...
Mom, I'm embarrassed.
Yu-chan...
Oh my...
Why am I doing something like this?
That dream...
Yu-chan... hold on.
Yuji...
Mom, it's dirty down there.
No, no, no... Yu-chan, stop it!
Ah... no, not there... please don't suck on it...
Yu-chan!
Yuji's penis...
I thought... it was still small.
They're not as big as Mom's but...
Yuji wouldn't... laugh at me right...
Ah... no...
Yuji, you can't...
Not so much on the breast...
you're not a baby, so...
No...
My nipples are hard.
It's because Yuji teased them so much...
it's so hard now...
Why do I keep on repeating Yuji's name so much?
Why?
I can't...
it's better than usual...
M-my voice...
I can't...
it's so much better than the other days...
M-my voice...
I can't stop it...
But... this, this is important to me...
I'm giving it... someone special to me!
Ah, no... I'm going to pee...
it's going to come out. It's coming out. It's coming out!
Why did I have something that intense this morning...
Oh yeah, at times like this...
This kid...
Sis...
I...
The truth is... of you Sis...
What?
Sis...
You don't think you are fat?
It's the truth...
it's just that your arms and stomach with your breast size...
Yuji!
Yu-chan... what happened to your cheek? It's all red.
Did you sleep on it wrong or something?
Oh, this is...
Ah, yeah...
it seems like I fell asleep with one of my hands on my cheek.
Hey Sis... hold on for a sec!
I don't care anymore, forget Yuji...
forget...
What are you so angry about today?
Maybe you should ask your heart why?
Eh!
Watch out!
Sis... are you okay?
Yeah...
Sis, ultimately you're a girl too...
You shouldn't get scars on you...
You should watch out more.
Thanks...
I-I know that.
Even I know stuff like that...
You do?
Ouch!
Why!?
What the hell...
What was with his smart ass comment...
He's Yuji...
For these past few weeks I've been having that same dream...
Why is it...
Maybe I should cut my hair...
Oh, I know what it is!
H-hey...
I was given this on the way home.
I thought you and I could play together...
What? A dice game?
I'm too busy right now, so another time.
Oh...
Okay, then maybe another time...
That's it...
Ever since the day Yuji brought home that weird game...
Okay... he's not here...
Yuji!
You...
What the hell is this?
Oh...
that card is...
from my room?
That's not the concern right now!
What is up with this card?
Huh?
What do you mean what's with it?
I mean...
this card that has this obscene word written on it!
Eh? What do you mean, obscene?
Huh?
I mean this!
Masturbation
Uh, um... Sis?
L...didn't understand the characters because it was too hard for me...
That was why I brought it to you to ask that time...
Ah, ah, Yuji, don't you get it?
This means... ma...
Ma...
Ma... Ma?
Ma... it means masturbate!
Huh? Why am I standing?
Huh?
Why... no, l...
No!
Yuji!
Close your eyes and don't look!
Don't even try looking!
If you look I'll kill you... kill you!
S-Sis...
I told you not to look, didn't I?
No...
I don't want this...
I don't!
Stop it!
No...
No, no, no...
Why am I showing myself to Yuji like this!?
I'm so embarrassed...
Yuji...
Don't look...
please...
S-Sis...
Your pussy is getting wet...
I can't put my finger in...
Don't, don't... no!
Not...
my breasts, too.
S-Sis with no bra...
T-today was too hot...
Of, of course l...
h-had it on when I went to school!
L...
No!
Don't look, Yuji!
You can't look!
Sis...
it's so pretty.
Yuji?
No, ah, don't, no. No!
S-Sis...
I didn't see anything and nothing happened.
This is... this is not possible!
You've witnessed such an embarrassing moment for me...
I won't be able to get married anymore!
Huh? What are you doing!?
At a time like this... l thought this would be the best thing to do...
No?
Yuji...
Not allowed.
Wha?
Sis, let's not do this.
My embarrassment was...
nothing compared to this.
Hmm...
there's something missing.
Sis, not that, please don't make me do that!
Come on!
Yuji, stop running around!
Okay, Yuji...
could you masturbate?
It's impossible.
Even though you say that...
Your crotch area is getting bigger, isn't it?
Cause... this underwear...
you were just wearing it...
The warmth from that is still...
Wh-what are you saying!?
I can't believe it!
Because... when I think that you were just wearing it...
Move your hands!
I can't tell.
Wow...
What...
Why is it... pulsing like that?
S-Sis... don't...
Please don't!
Don't...
You can't.
S-Sis...
My bad...
it was my fault...
I'll apologize...
I'm sorry, Yuji.
You're so cruel...
Sis, you knew if you did something like that...
there was no way I could have held it in...
My feelings... you know how I feel...
Wha... wait...
What do you mean?
Uh, um...
Just kidding!
Wh... wha, wha...
I'll kill you!
I'm definitely gonna kill you!
Sis?
Why are you like that?
L, on the other hand...
I've been thinking so much about you...
But then look at you... you...
Yuji?
S-Sis...
That kiss with you...
it felt so good...
I lost my strength...
Let's... keep... going.
Sis... are you okay with this?
Isn't this... your first time?
Cause it's...
No... because I want to be with you, Yuji.
Me too...
I'm happy we're like this, too...
Sis, are you okay?
It's fine, keep putting it all the way in...
Sis, inside you...
something's moving...
Wai-wait... Yuji...
Don't move, please wait a little.
S-Sis...
Can I move now?
The pain... it eased a little...
You can... but slowly, okay?
Are you okay?
Maybe we should stop...
it's okay, keep going...
This pain is also from you, so...
Okay...
Yuji's penis...
Yuji!
Sis... Sis's pussy...
so good...
I'm sorry, Sis. My hips are moving faster on their own!
Sis, I like you... I've liked you for so long.
I'm sorry for everything.
Me too...
me too...
I've liked you so much, Yuji.
What is this, something big! It's big...
Ah, it's like...
it's coming!
Ah, no... it's going in so deep!
Even though it's my first time...
I...
Sis?
Sis? It's different...
it's because I'm happy...
Please kiss me.
Yuji, I'm glad we became like this...
Yeah.
Um, Yuji?
Huh?
Huh? You're...
only mine, right?
Yeah.
You...
You and Mom are...
Umm...
Huh?
What about Mom?
Nah...
Never mind.
Come on... I'm gonna leave before you.
Okay, we're leaving.
Okay, both of you, be careful.
Hmm...
Huh?
Recently, both of you...
haven't been playing jokes on each other lately.
T-that's 'cause...
Y-yeah...
Hmm...
Whatever...
I guess you guys are both adults now.