Rumors say that the more lust Uwa people
experience, the thicker their penises get...
and rougher...
Yes! Yes!
This just feels too good!
I am pleased that you enjoy this.
However the real fun begins now.
D-Don't tell me you're going to metamorphose...
Don't be scared.
Just for a little while, our bodies will be one.
Will be one...?
Will be one...
I get it!
I feel it!
I feel your sensations!
It feels like I'm fucking myself!
Wow!
This is amazing!
I feel my penis in me!
My penis in my pussy!
I feel my pussy around my penis!
If only my penis could go deeper into my pussy...
Into my pussy!
Wow! Wow!
I feel it deep in my uterus.
I feel the tip of my penis deep in my uterus!
My penis and clitoris.
I feel both sensations overwhelming me.
So this is the sensation a man feels when he ejaculates.
I feel it!
My pussy and my penis!
I can feel both at once?
How... How wonderful!
My pussy... My penis...
feel great!
He's already gone.
Filth and fatigue were left on my body, but that was all.
This is my own body.
However...
I felt like I lost half of myself.
And I was unable to hold back those painful feelings.