Sexual Pursuit.
Part A
Mom, Mom, Mom, your pussy.
It's so good! My penis is being squeezed, and...
I think I'm going to go crazy!
What am I doing?
Oh yeah, I have to start preparing dinner before Yuri comes home.
Breasts... your breasts... Mom, your breasts feel so good.
Dinner, what should I make?
Recently Yuri is concerned with calories...
that she's constipated and she wants fiber and things...
She's still in her growing stage, so if she gets hungry she has to eat...
and it's normal to gain weight...
Well, when I was her age, I was concerned about the same kind of things.
Mom!
Mom, I can't hold it anymore. I have to pee so bad.
No! Not that, if you do that...
But... I've been trying to take it out, but...
My hips keep on moving on their own...
it just feels too good and it won't come out!
What is going on...
Why am I doing this with Yu-chan...
I'm gonna pee... it's gonna come out...
My penis is going to burst...
it's gonna come out!
Yu-chan, not that... just not that...
Please don't pee!
No!
Yu-chan's... penis is swelling...
Swelling is bad...
No... no...
it's coming!
N-no!
Mom...
My hips... my hips kept on moving on their own and it wouldn't stop...
And then... it kept on feeling better and better, and...
I'm so sorry... Mom...
I'm so sorry I had to pee...
Why... did this happen... why...
Come on Yuji, hurry up.
You're always so slow.
Ouch!
Sis...
stop hitting my head every time you say something.
You're really strong, so it actually hurts.
Hitting, how disgraceful.
I just touched you a little bit, didn't I?
Hitting means...
like this!
If you're that much of a coward, you won't be able to get a girlfriend, huh?
Well Sis, if you're that violent you'll never get a boyfriend...
Actually, with an arm that size...
even if you were kidding it could turn into bloodshed.
Then you would get imprisoned, so...
you wouldn't be able to enjoy teen life...
Sis, make sure you don't hurt any of your friends...
be really careful.
Yuji...
Do you want me to shed some blood just like you said!?
Ye-yeah right...
the nicest sister in the world wouldn't hurt me...
Right?
Um... I don't know...
Even if I was just joking around...
as you say there could be bloodshed, so...
Ok, ok...
You both get along so well...
The world says people like you that fight as much as you get along...
By the way are you both doing okay on time?
If we don't leave soon we'll be late, won't we?
That's true...
Okay Mom, we're off!
Okay, bye.
You both be careful.
A blanket?
Yu-chan, are you there?
Hmm...
This is it for instructions?
I don't really understand...
Yeah, Mom?
Yu-chan...
Um...
The person... that put the blanket on me was...
Yu-chan, right?
Yup.
Thank you.
You left the window open...
and when it becomes evening, the wind is chilly.
You'll catch a cold.
C-come on.
You get emotional so fast.
Mom, maybe you're tired?
Heh, maybe. Maybe I'm getting old.
L-I don't think that's true.
Because... during visitation day you're the youngest...
and prettiest...
Eh?
W-well I need to start preparing dinner...
I'm sure Yuri is going to come home starved...
Y-yeah...
Even though Sis is worried about her weight, she eats a lot...
Th-that's true...
Oh yeah!
Oh yeah! What?
Ok. I have a favor I want to ask you, Mom.
Oh, what is it?
It's rare that you have a favor to ask me.
It's this...
What is it?
Um, how can I say this...
it's just...
Hmm?
Th-this was...
given to me as a sample on my way home.
Apparently all the people that play this become really close.
It just seemed like they sounded pretty serious about it...
so it's a little interesting...
I can't play alone, so...
Hmm...
So, I want you to play this dice game with me... if possible...
Um, never mind... please forget about it.
Not a dice game, right?
It's fine...
I haven't played a dice game in a while so it's nice, isn't it?
Really?
Even though it's not even New Years?
Yeah, just for a little.
Okay.
Umm...
Let's see.
M-Mom... h-hey...
Hm?
You're a little too close.
Oh, Yu-chan... you hurt Mom's feelings.
It's not like that!
Are you sure? I guess it's okay then.
Anyway, look at this.
What is it?
"Roll the dice and if it lands on a red square, draw a card"...
is the only things it says.
Then after that is... "Aim for the goal"...
There isn't a game like this nowadays.
U-um... Mom?
Hey, hey, Yu-chan... l wonder what kind of cards are in there.
These games, the most essential thing are the cards.
Mom, are you like, really interested?
Ehh? It's not like that.
But...
Well, Mom doesn't understand current video games...
I think while watching Yu-chan and Yuri having fun playing games...
"I'm jealous, if it was a board game I would be able to play too, "...
I was thinking about that and you asked me...
"Let's play this together, "... But it's not like I was overjoyed or anything.
Yup, nothing like that...
Mom...
Well, I guess we have to see once we play it...
Ok, I'm going to roll the dice.
One, two, three, four...
Oh well.
Certainly, this game does make you closer.
It seems so.
Okay, it's my turn.
Oh... a smaller number than Yu-chan's...
Heh...
But, I'm gonna outrun you so watch carefully.
One, Two, Three...
Oh, it's a red square.
Yeah, it is.
It seems as though God came to Mom's side instead of yours.
Come on, hurry and draw the card.
Let's see...
What kind of card is it, what kind?
Huh? What's written on it?
It's this, but...
What does that say?
What's it mean?
Embrace.
What? Um... M-Mom?
This is what "Houyou" (Embrace) means...
Um! Ahh... umm... M-Mom!
Ahh, Yu-chan, your cheek feels so good...
Oh, stop it now. I'm not a baby...
it tickles.
I did what the card told me to do...
Next is Yu-chan's turn...
Huh?
Yu-chan?
Ah, okay...
it's my turn.
Look, you stopped at a red square.
Y-yeah...
What's wrong?
This game, the words are too hard.
Okay, okay... I'll read it for you so let me see.
This reads "Seppun" (Kiss).
And what am I supposed to do?
Kiss.
Here.
Huh? What?
Come on! "Seppun" means Kiss...
So, you just have to kiss my cheek.
What!
Heh...
it's the rule of the game, you have to do it.
Oh, okay. I guess...
Okay, whenever you're ready...
Hey! Yu-Yu-chan?
Yu-chan... n-no, not the lips... ah!
Yu-chan, hold on...
Yu-chan... I'm sorry... from the middle of it...
no, it's nothing.
Yeah, it's nothing.
Y-yeah.
Uh, um...
but, Mom's kiss just felt so good... so... something's wrong with me...
Huh? What is it?
Well... it just seems like there's something wrong with my body...
Like... towards the bottom of my body...
um...
it's hot down there...
and...
it's just unbearable...
O-oh really...
I wonder why.
Hmm, I don't know why...
Well, I should go start getting ready for dinner...
Oh well...
it was starting to get interesting, so it's a little disappointing.
I'm sorry...
I thought of that, but...
do you want to play a little more?
Eh...
Mom gets the picture.
Okay, here we go!
Great, Yu-chan is left in the dust!
Arg...
One, two, three, four, five... ah.
Mom... what's wrong?
Oh, it's a red square.
Can I draw your card?
What does this card read?
This game's words are so difficult...
Take off your clothes.
M-Mom!?
No, Yu-chan...
Don't look... please...
M-Mom...
Y-Yu-chan...
Th-this isn't me doing it.
Please close your eyes...
Don't look.
M-Mom's nude...
Yu-chan... you have to take it off too.
What!? Me too? Why?
Wh-what?
Huh? My body...
Why am I taking my clothes off?
Mom, my body is moving on its own.
Hey! I'm embarrassed!
M-my underwear, too? This is awkward...
M-Mom... I'm embarrassed.
Yu-chan...
Hey, Yu-chan... let's stop playing this game.
Y-yeah... there's something wrong...
No! I don't want to, but... My hand!
Yu-chan!?
Oral Sex.
W-why!? I didn't move it!?
Yu-chan!?
Mom! What's wrong?
N-no... I can't!
Mom... it's dirty down there!
No, no, no... Yu-chan, stop it!
Please don't suck on it...
Yu-chan... stop it!
My crotch is gonna be soaked!
Yu-chan's tongue... your tongue!
It feels so good...
More, more... Yu-chan... Yu-chan...
Yu-chan...
Do it
for the first time.
What... why... why is this dice game... moving on its own!?
No more, no!
Boob job.
Y-Yu-chan...
Mom...
M-Mom... please stop... it's going to come off...
My penis, it feels like it's going to come off...
No...
I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come... Mom!
Continuous ejaculation.
Y-Yu-chan...
I can't anymore... no more than this...
M-Mom... l...
I don't really want to do this...
it's true.
I don't want to do things that Mom doesn't want to...
Yu-chan...
Yu-chan's penis... is inside...
My pussy... with Yu-chan's penis...
it's making so much noise.
L-I'm sorry, Mom! My hips are doing it on their own...
But, it feels so good... it won't stop.
It's rubbing on it tightly...
Mom, I was... going to control myself...
if you didn't want to do this, but...
I can't anymore... I'm at my limit.
Yu-chan...
You don't have to suffer for me.
But... it's because I brought that dice game here...
I believed a lie that we could become closer...
it's okay, Yu-chan.
You and I have gotten closer...
just like lovers.
Lovers?
Lovers? Yes, lovers.
Lovers become closer like this...
Really?
So... so please...
I want you to pound my soaking wet pussy more...
Yu-chan, could you please?
Soaking wet pussy...
Yu-chan, could you see yours going into mine?
It's in.
Mom...
Can I move it?
No, you can't...
I'm the only one that gets to move.
But...
M-Mom... am I a per... a pervert?
Yes, you are. Yu-chan, you are such a perverted boy...
because, you are pressing it so hard against inside me.
It's because...
But, I like the perverted Yu-chan so much...
Yu-chan's penis, it's hitting all the way in the back...
So good! It feels so good!
No don't stop, please screw me more...
Mom... it feels so good!
It feels so good!
Mom, are you filled with me?
Is it filled?
Yu-chan's penis... because it's Yu-chan's...
Please come, please come a lot...
a lot of milk... fill me with it!
Yeah, I'm Mom's!
Mom!
Yu-chan!
Yu-chan...
if we are lovers...
I want to kiss!
I'm gonna come... I'm gonna come!
Yu-chan!
Me too... Mom!
Yuji... what's up with you?
Why are you holding hands with Mom?
Oh, I get it... you're still a momma's boy, right?
Is that bad?
Because Mom and I are...
We're close!
Huh?