Your secret?
That's right.
I'll tell it to you.
My secret.
Wh-What are you...
The shadow leader of Darktown, Bozuk,
had imprisoned Iris, an ace among the Armored Knights.
Another pilot in her team, Meiri, was also taken.
She then meets Riruru.
Riruru seems to have fun being Bozuk's sex slave.
Inside of Iris's body a substance called "Ecstasia" has been implanted.
It reconstructs the body to feel pleasure countless levels higher than normal.
After that, Iris made her debut as a prostitute in Bozuk's brothel.
She undergoes days of hardship in which...
...the customers' regular visits change the temperament of her body.
With Ecstasia still left in her body Iris is violated by members of different races.
She begins to awaken to the immeasurable pleasure inside.
Soukou Kijo Iris
From Warrior to Prostitute
What are you...
We Elves have free body types.
This thing is hidden inside our bodies.
It's only supposed to become erect when we meet our intended Elven lovers.
But ever since I met you, something's changed in me.
Watching people fuck you just makes me feel so lustful towards you...
My penis always gets erect,
and my vagina stays wet.
And you're not even an Elven.
No! Stop it!
Now's no time to pretend you're not turned on.
You were masturbating to my sex scene earlier.
In that case... Well?
Wanna do it?
I told you to stop it!
Oh dear, oh dear. Are you mad at me?
Oh, well then.
In exchange, can you come with me for a minute?
What do you mean?
I want to take you to a nice place.
Wh-What is this place?
Even by Darktown's standards, it's a very seedy spot of the city.
You can never tell what will happen to you here.
So watch your step.
What the hell?
What wonderful thing is supposed to be here?
You'll find out when we get there.
Riruru?
Riruru? Where did you go?
Hi, Iris!
Welcome!
Riruru? Where are you? What is this place?
You'll find out in time.
Now, Duck People!
Your feast has arrived!
Wh-What are these things?
Haven't you heard of the Duck People who live on Planet Henkyo?
They're not very smart, but they've got strong bodies.
They were transported to this planet as slaves.
But their sex drives are abnormally strong.
They need to be gratified regularly otherwise they revolt.
D-Don't tell me you intend to use me!?
This isn't funny!
If you fight and defeat them all. I'll take you home safely.
Bring it on then!
I can take you all on!
Wh-What?
Aww, too bad.
The Duck People's secret weapon,
illegal darts, seems to have worked on you.
Round one, over!
Next, it's time for the Duck People's attack.
I wanna fuck hen!
No!
No! Stop it!
Ouch! That hurts!
Ouch... That hurts...
Well, please make them happy, Iris.
No! Stop it!
Put it in your mouth.
What is this smell? It reeks.
Stop! Not this...
Well! Duck People!
Time to change fighters.
Let me have fun too.
Thrust those dirty dicks inside me.
Yes!
More! More!
I love it!
I love your peruses!
Deeper into me!
Hurry!
M-Meiri...
Iris! Look! Look at me!
Look at all the penises inside of me!
Look at me!
Meiri...
Harder! Harder!
Mei... ri...
Iris! Iris!
Let's clean this up and go home.
When we get home, I'll make you a cup of tea.
Earthlings like that, right?
Meiri... Meiri...
Wait... Wait, I said! Riruru!
Riruru?
So you're finally awake.
I called out to you over and over, but you never woke up.
What? Where are we?
Never mind that.
Your next customer is here.
Next customer?
That's right. Be a good whore.
Like you were with the Duck People.
Stop joking around!
What? What's this noise?
An I-Igulian?
Don't do this! Our races are biologically way too different!
Stop it! What s that?
Ouch!
My body... it won't move.
Don't tell me he's poisoned me...
About that customer of yours.
They're currently banned by the Federation.
But they still remember what humans feel like,
Stop fooling around! I'll die!
Ouch! That hurts!
That hurts!
Please, stop it!
Ouch!
Well, Mr. Customer. Now the real pleasure begins.
Iris, be a good whore.
With your famous moves.
Is it over?
Wh-What's that for?
D-Don't tell me... With that!?
Yes... Iris... You really are a bad girl.
Please get turned on more.
More... More...
Iris!
Yes! Iris! Iris!
More! More!
Show me your nasty self more!
Let my penis cum!
And let my vagina cum too!
More!
Iris!
Wh-What's this? Hot!
What is this? Is this an Igulian's sex organ?
Wh-What? What's that?
N-Not there!
That hurts!
So deep inside...
So hard... His penis is so hard!
So tight!
Yes! It's so hard!
Yes!
His hard penis... I love it!
I'm cumming!
His hard penis...
Yes... Yes...
Penis!
Iris...
Ah, you look horrible.
D-Don't touch me!
Don't worry.
I'm just healing your wounds.
See? Now you're all clean.
Watching you get fucked turns me on so much.
Even though you're not an Elf like me.
Why is that?
I-I want to cum with you.
Iris... with you!
You're so kind.
Th-That's not it!
Y-You're a precious commodity.
If you lost your quality, we'd lose business.
That's all.
Hey, Riruru, could you really be...
So you found me out?
What are you doing? Stop it!
Iris... I can't hold back anymore.
I don't know why, but you turn me on the most!
Please? So...
I'm telling you to stop!
Stop it, Meiri!
That's the name of the Elf who looks exactly like me, right?
That's not true.
I'm talking about you.
Meiri.
You're wrong!
I'm Riruru!
I'm not Meiri!
No. I've watched you the whole time.
And I finally learned the truth.
You are Meiri.
Though you've changed a lot from the Meiri I know.
What the hell?
What do you know about me?
Lightning Gemini.
That is what we were called.
The fighting Gemini twins.
We were the strongest pair among the Armored Knights.
I know you better than anyone else does.
Are you an idiot?
I don't have such memories at all!
I'm not sure what happened.
Maybe you got amnesia in that surprise attack.
But there's no mistaking it. You are Mei~
No I'm not!
I'm Riruru!
I'm not Meiri!
Meiri! Don't go!
What is it?
You having fun with your job now?
Give me a fucking break.
I'm not having fun in the slightest.
I wonder how many days it will take to cure you of that foul stubbornness.
By the way, I've got another job for you.
Report to the experimentation lab immediately.
Go now.
What kind of customer is it this time?
A slug? An insect? Or maybe...
You'll see when you get there.
Where's the assigned room?
Longtime no see.
Doctor B?
What is a Federation bastard like you doing here?
Bozuk is letting me continue my research in this facility.
And I hear you're taking on customers.
"Research" you say?
You murdered thousands of innocent lives; you're just a sick, mad scientist!
Despite your armored suit, you were captured and brought here!
I have plenty to complain to you in regards to that!
Putting me in this position... What do you intend to do with me?
I intend to make you a part of my research.
Give me a fucking break!
I like your spirit!
Though I wonder how long you'll last.
You bastard!
You like it?
This stupid thing... Doesn't hurt or feel good!
Then what about this?
Stop it!
You like it?
Even a Armored Knight like yourself can't stand this intensity!
But I'm telling you... It has no effect on me whatsoever!
An ordinary woman would be putty right now.
So this is what they mean when they say Armored
Knights have stronger bodies than most.
And I've been looking forward to this for so long...
Wh-What? You mean there's more?
The real experiment starts now.
What are you trying to do? Stop it!
If you want to survive, don't make any sudden movements!
Well? How does it feel, Iris?
What is this sensation?
It's a sensation I've never felt in my head before...
My body is hot... My clitoris is throbbing...
Looks like my experiment is a success.
I have linked your nervous system with my nervous system
to experience all the sensations I experience.
I have especially linked the parts of our brains that feel lust.
Right now, you are feeling the sensation of my lust!
Wh-What?
What is this? My body is...
You like it?
You like my lust?
Makes you wanna have sex with me, doesn't it!
Why would I... No one would... I feel nothing!
Then how about this?
You want me to fuck you, don't you!
Answer me honestly!
No one would... That's not true at all!
Lying is useless!
I can feel your lust too at this moment.
Well then? Don't you feel like you wanna be fucked really hard by me?
Not with that... Not me...
What are you...!?
I-I wanna fuck...
Please... Please mess me up.
Please thrust my penis into my vagina.
I wanna fuck...
I want to thrust my dick into myself.
I want it in me.
I want to fuck me!
It appears you've finally come to terms with it.
Then I'll give you what you desire!
My penis... My vagina will receive it.
Penis! Penis! Penis!
Go forth!
My machine!
Taste it as much as you want, Iris!
It's inside! The penis is inside!
Inside of me is my penis!
It feels great!
It feels great for me too!
Make me feel even better!
Yes. Move more.
Move deeper inside.
Harder... Harder!
This is so...
Deeper! Thrust it deeper!
Deeper!
My penis is inside my uterus.
The uterus walls...
Yes! Yes, this is wonderful!
Shit!
Amazing! I feel your sensations with my sensations!
Oh, no!
I'm going to cum!
Oh, no.
My penis and my vagina are cumming!
My penis and my vagina!
That was a very nice experiment!
My body... has been made so nasty.
There's no turning back now.
Everyone... Meiri...
In the morning of the day after tomorrow... I'm unlocking the front gate.
Meiri...