Iris, wake up already!
M-Meiri?
Is that you, Mein?
Meiri...
Wh-What is this for?
Meiri, what are you doing?
Stop staring and help me!
What've you been talking about?
Meiri, what's wrong with you!?
It's me! It's Iris.
My name is Riruru.
I was preparing the Master's supper.
I am a sex slave.
I'm well suited for it. It's fun being his slave.
You're not... Meiri...
You seem to be doing well, so no worries.
Looks like the antidote worked.
What is this thing?
It's a reconstruction operating table.
Reconstruction operation?
What are you going to do with me?
Isn't it obvious?
I am going to reconstruct your body, so that you can serve others better.
D-Don't do it!
No, stop this!
Don't raise your virgin cries against me.
Didn't I tell you? You are merely a commodity now.
Help me!
You are a woman just like myself!
Yes, I am. That's why it's my duty to teach you a few things.
I need to teach you about a woman's pleasures.
No! What's that?
You don't need to worry.
Stop this!
I'm begging you!
No... Don't.
No!
Stop it! Please, Meiri!
My name is Riruru...
That one is rather thin.
But if your pussy gets a bit teased, you get soaking wet.
How nasty you are.
It's going inside... my uterus!
Hitting against the walls!
Deep inside!
Don't! Don't move it!
Please!
Looks like we're at a good point.
It's coming! So hot!
No!
The human race separated itself from the birdcage called Earth,
and have favored traveling to the distant stars.
The galaxy holds many different types of races,
which under control of the Galactic Federation Senate,
were ruled and regulated peacefully.
However, time, location, and the races were destined to change.
The Galactic Federation Senate created a special task force,
the SSF, which holds strong orbital power.
It shortened the distance between the planets,
and helped protect the peace of their peoples.
The SSF101 special large armored suit...
The people had a special name for these women: Armored Knights.
Soukou Kijo Iris
The Prostitute Warrior
Wh-What did you do to my body?
I'll show you right now.
See?
It's called Ecstasia.
Your body has been incorporated with three times its own libido,
as well as the nervous system to transmit
these stronger sensations to your brain.
See?
Just someone squeezing your boobs really gets you going, doesn't it?
As if you feel like you're going to die.
Amazing! Just by having your breasts massaged,
so much has flowed out of you.
Only because you" reconstructed" me that way!
Yes, but wouldn't you say you're better off that way?
Now you can have even more fun with sex
Your customer is waiting.
Come! Put these on.
What are they?
The customer who paid for you is very wealthy...
But he's into some pretty weird fetishes.
Change quick, okay?
I think this is the beginning of a great friendship.
Mmm, nice!
Looks great on you.
Ever since I laid eyes on you, I wanted you to wear this uniform.
U-Uniform fetishism?
And for an Armored Knight at that!
Well?
Oh, all I'm doing is touching your boobs, but you're reacting so strongly.
Good girl.
My nipples are throbbing.
Because of that stupid Ecstasia...
I feel it...
Even though I'm trying to hold back...
It still feels too amazing!
Oh my? Waterworks already?
You've got spunk.
Well then, before it dries...
You smell like piss.
For a noble Armored Knight, that's a bit embarrassing.
You're such a bad girl.
This binding...
Stop it!
You taste like piss.
Is this what the piss of an Armored Knight tastes like?
Not there!
No, don't!
Do you like it?
I don't... I don't...
Oh no. I like it.
Is this also because of the Ecstasia?
Now I feel like taking a piss too.
Of course I don't want to do it!
I can do anything I want to you here as long as I pay enough money.
I can even kill you if I want to.
Well, open up that pretty mouth of yours.
No!
Hurry up.
Ah, it's coming out.
You're spilling my piss.
Gross.
Swallow it. Hurry.
Good!
Next, shove my dick in your mouth and clean it up.
No, no, not like that.
Your throat sure is nice.
Very good.
Why? Why did this happen to me?
I... can't go back anymore.
How long... How long will this continue?
It's finally... over?
Don't be so stupid.
My body has also been reconstructed.
I can regain my lust three times as quickly as the normal man.
It's no good.
And yet it feels everything.
I'm cumming!
Is it ove~
Well then, I think I've had enough fun with the uniform.
Time to have fun with your body now.
What's that for?
What are you doing to me now?
It's a beam-cutter designed for special surgery.
This is the only instrument that will cut through an Armored Knight uniform.
No way... Do you intend to cut me as well?
Of course not, don't worry.
But if you move an inch, your precious areas might get a bit snagged.
Well then, time to enjoy your insides too.
Very nice.
Feels so... good..
Very good!
So this is what an Armored Knight's vagina feels like!
Tight... So tight!
Come on!
Please, just stop it!
I'm losing my mind!
Here I come!
He came inside of me... how dare he!
That was pretty nice.
I heard that this was the only place where I d be
able to have sex with a real Armored Knight.
Though I doubt they were telling the truth.
I'm ordered around... and embarrassed...
Will this continue forever?
Iris, you were very good.
Especially the parts where you were holding back.
That was great.
Stop joking around!
You did something to my body!
Talking time is over.
Your next customer is waiting.
Be good to him.
My next customer?
He's an Oktoreron nobleman.
An Oktoreron?
The comet-lifeform from that strange planet?
So you're my next customer, right?
How do you expect to draw pleasure from me?
Wh-What are you going to do to me?
No! Stop it!
What? This is all slippery and gross!
Valued customer, this prostitute has been injected
with three times the amount of Ecstasia.
Have all the fun you wish.
He's biting my nipples!
Oh dear?
You getting off just on having your nipples bitten?
I'm not getting off on it!
Wow...
Stop it, please!
Don't bite me down there!
Stop it!
No, no. The real fun starts now.
What are you doing?
Don't tell me you're putting that gross thing inside of me...
What? Stop it!
No! It won't fit!
Not my butt!
That hurts!
I'm losing my mind.
Stop it! I'll die!
The... tentacles are entering my uterus.
Entering my intestines.
I love it.
My vagina and butt are both throbbing.
It's no use.
l can't hold back any more.
Why? Why do I enjoy this?
So many of them are inside of me.
Inside of my throat.
Oh no.
I can't help but enjoy it.
All of my organs are being raped.
But it feels great.
Why does it feel so great?
It's coming.
This monster's semen is going inside me.
Hurry and shoot it.
Please shoot it inside of me.
Hurry!
You're screaming so loudly.
If she takes on another two or three
customers, she'll be a true veteran whore.
Hey, Lord Bozuk.
What is it?
Why you talking so sweet to me all of a sudden?
Looks like you already know the answer.
Yes. You. Do.
Very amazing!
Lord Bozuk, you're so big already.
How naughty.
And what about you then?
Your vagina is all soaking wet!
You little slut!
That's because...
Lord Bozuk, your penis is so stinky and beautiful.
Lord Bozuk, your tongue is going deep into my vagina and uterus.
Come, suck me dry too!
More. Let me drink more.
Oh, I can't stand it!
Then I guess I'll thrust myself inside of you!
Lord Bozuk... Lord Bozuk. Hurry.
Hurry and come inside.
It's coming! It's coming!
Lots are coming!
Coming... Coming...
It's so big!
It felt so good.
I-I wanted to scream even more.
Lord Bozuk. More! More!
It's spreading wide! Deep into my uterus!
Feels good!
Riruru, you're pretty. You're so pretty.
Lord Bozuk. Down there too.
Down there too...
My butt!
It's scraping into it. Feels great.
More... More, please!
Harder! Harder, please!
Both my vagina and my butt. More, please!
Yes!
Riruru, are you cumming? Are you cumming?
Me too... I'm going to cum.
Riruru, I'm about to cum!
You're cumming?
Then cum inside of me!
Fill me full of your wonderful seed, please!
Here I come!
Cum!
Unfair... How unfair!
I want... I want to cum too!
I want someone to come in my vagina.
Please!
Why did I act like that in the hallway?
Why?
Well? Used to things here yet?
The room is gloomy and makes me sick.
Oh, too bad.
Then do you want to masturbate to me and Lord Bozuk having sex again?
How did you...!?
Looks like you had lots of fun.
You slutty woman.
But...
What was that for?
Didn't I say so?
That this was the beginning of a great friendship?
So... I want to teach you
Teach you... my secret.