That day, Miyuki finally asked me out.
For weeks, we'd barely looked at each other.
And then for some reason, she suddenly
asked me to go skiing with her.
Wanna go skiing?
Thinking about it now, she really
looks like my little sister.
Everything must have been fated.
What?
Welcome back.
LOST VILLAGE
Episode One
The Cold Demonic Village
I'm sorry.
Did I wake you?
How do you feel, sir?
Oh, you mustn't.
You still have a fever.
You must rest well.
Um... did you rescue me?
You made it here on your own.
Don't you remember?
Yuki, you’re being rude.
This is my daughter, Yuki.
Then... who was that?
The long, black haired...
She said, "Welcome back."
There's no one of that
description in this snowy village.
Don't you think you were mistaken?
I already heard your circumstances from
the other person who woke up.
What a pity.
Um, where's Miyuki?
Um, I mean, how are the other tourists?
You needn't worry.
The driver confirmed that they're all okay.
Everyone is resting in other rooms.
This is a lodge, so we do have
plenty of rooms, at least.
Fushimi Lodge
It's cold.
My body is... almost frozen.
Someone...
Someone, please help me!
Welcome back.
Wh-Who are you?
Who are you?
Naoto!
Miyuki?
Is that you, Miyuki?
I don't care who you are.
Just help me.
Help me. Get me out of here!
Did you have a bad dream?
Miyuki!
Are you okay?
Looks like your fever broke.
Huh? Oh, you're right.
I feel better.
Jeez! You really worried me!
When I lost you...
I'm sorry.
I'm glad we came here. On this trip.
Even though we've experienced such trouble?
Because... we can be together.
Miyuki.
A lot happened between us, but..
Now we're together.
There's nothing else we need to say.
Yeah.
You're already so big.
Maybe the blizzard turned me on.
I want you.
I'm starting to feel good too...
just from doing this.
M-Miyuki...
I can't take it anymore.
I'm gonna cum.
I-I'm sorry!
Delicious.
What's happened to you?
I thought you didn't like me
cumming in your mouth.
I'm not sure.
But I just naturally felt like I wanted to do that.
Amazing, Naoto.
You're even bigger than before.
Th-This big.
Miyuki, you re also really wet down there.
How embarrassing.
What do you want me to do?
Don't make me say it.
Your pu**y is filled with naughty juice.
M-My pus–
Don't say something so dirty.
W-Wow.
All my fingers fit in.
That feels great!
I-I can't hold back anymore.
Hold back what?
You'd better tell me, or I won't know, Miyuki.
Oh, you big tease!
I want your c**k.
I want your c**k inside me.
In my...
In my pu **y.
I want your c**k in there, Naoto!
Oh well, then.
My body's on fire!
It's on fire, and it's melting!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming.
I'm gonna cum!
What's wrong, Naoto?
What's... happening to me?
I know I'm very young.
And I know these are special circumstances.
But that night... Miyuki and I played very roughly.
Thinking back on it... by then...
inside of me... something had
already begun to change.
The next morning...
The tourists from our bus assembled and
listened to the mistress of the lodge.
The road was completely snowed in.
The one bridge that led out of the village
had collapsed from the blizzard.
And to make matters worse, all the
phone lines had stopped working.
In this village, they had never
had cell phone networks.
This meant we were completely
cut off from the outside world.
We were in a situation where
we had no choice but to wait.
We really were in a dead end at the lodge.
Good morning.
I'm sorry.
The people around here aren't very friendly.
Sayo-san, the other daughter
of the lodge mistress,
took us on a walk around the village.
Well then, take care.
Thanks.
See you later.
Take your time, okay?
Paradise, paradise.
I wish Miyuki-had come with me.
Customer, how does the water feel?
Is that you, mistress?
It feels perfect.
I had no idea such a wonderful
hot spring was here.
I guess that's the silver lining in this huge cloud.
I'm sorry!
I'll get out right away.
You needn't inconvenience yourself.
This is a mixed bath.
Or am I disturbing you?
No, that's not it exactly.
What's the matter?
N-No, it's nothing.
Oh, is that it?
You're so big.
S-Sorry.
You don't need to apologize about it.
You're a healthy young man.
It's only natural.
Mistress?
Call me Natsuyo.
O-Okay.
Oh, customer.
I'm Naoto.
Naoto-san...
I can't hold back anymore.
I know you came here with someone, but..
Please?
S-Sure.
Th-This feels great.
Naoto-san, your hard, thick thing
is hitting so hard inside of me!
Natsuyo-san!
I-I'm sorry... I'm gonna cum!
Not yet!
I'm almost there too.
Let's cum... Let s cum together.
I'm at my limit!
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming, cumming!
What a waste.
You came so much.
And it's still throbbing.
That's why I love them young.
Natsuyo.
Suck it.
Yes, I'd love to.
That's no good.
Suck it harder.
Harder.
Harder, harder, harder!
S-Sorry I was so rough with you.
I said... Something horrible.
Don't worry about it.
Being treated like this isn't bad thing sometimes.
Naoto-san...
It's not enough.
No!
What are you saying?
You're soaking wet down there.
I don't care anymore.
Just go for it.
Since we've already come this far,
you might as well fuck me to smithereens.
What was that?
Is that the tone of voice you should
use when you beg for something?
In that case, I'd better just stop now.
No! Don't stop!
Please don't stop!
More. I want your more of your
flesh rod, Naoto. Soil me!
I want your cum to make me dirty!
Good. That will do.
This time I'll use this hole.
Not there!
Is this your first time?
I'm surprised.
That hurts!
A slut like you would never hate anal sex.
After a while, you'll feel good,
and you'll squeal for more.
I feel... kind of weird.
Could it be... that I feel good?
Wow!
Deep inside my body... it's like
I'm being electrocuted.
Passing over reality.
This was the first time I've had sex like that.
And... no matter how much I was pleasured...
not only was my lust unsatisfied...
but I walked a tightrope of gluttonous rage.
It was no surprise...
that I began to notice my transformation...
and was confused and frightened by it.
I guess... the hot water tired me out.
It's almost like... I'm inside a dream.
Sex with my mom felt great, didn't it?
Don't worry.
I won't tell your girlfriend.
You came from Tokyo, right?
Yes, I did.
What's it like, I wonder?
You've never been?
Nope.
I've never been anywhere.
Nowhere?
Well then...
Miyuki...
There it is again!
That hurts!
You fucking slut!
You pig!
That's... the married couple from our bus.
Stop it, Yoji-san!
What?
Are you getting turned on by being whipped?
No way is that true!
Then what's this all about?
It came out of your pu**y.
What's this juice!?
Looks like an uppity pig needs some punishment.
Let's put in another squirt.
It'll come out!
Let me go to the bathroom!
If you wanna go, then just go.
No! I can't!
I'm at my limit!
No! Stop it!
This feels pretty nice.
You've got a nice pu**y.
Damn, I envy you.
You can have sex with such a cute wife every day.
From time to time, its nice to see your
wife fuck another man, right?
Huh?
I'm gonna cum!
Please, don't cum inside of me?
Today's not a good day for me!
You don't have protection?
I think that's a violation of nature.
That's what all the churches are saying.
And on that note, I'm cumming inside.
No!
Stop it!
Please!
No!
Lots came out.
Now you'll definitely get pregnant.
My turn next.
Hurry up. I'm next in line.
Don't make a fuss.
We're trapped in here because of the snow,
so there's no escape for a while.
That hurts!
It hurts?
I don't think it can when you're acting so slutty.
We can go even further.
It feels good.
Huh?
There's nothing in this village to do,
so we might as well do what we
can to entertain ourselves.
Very nice.
Young girls are great at putting
up with a rough flesh rod.
Hey, bus driver, I think she wants
to use her mouth next.
Leave it to me.
I'm cold.
And this little guy is also cold and sad.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
So what?
So... So I...
I want to use my mouth to make
your c**k warm and happy again.
You understand well.
Then do it at once.
How is it?
The flavor of a c**k that's
just been in your asshole?
Delicious.
Your ass-flavored c**k tastes very delicious.
Oh, very nice.
I've got the perfect shots.
This has to be a dream!
Because if it isn't, the what is this?
It hurts, but it feels great!
But.. But I can't take it!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Everyone is changing.
So it's not only me that's changing.
I noticed that something was happening
to all the tourists who were on the bus.
Miyuki!
Could it be that she too is...
Natsuyo-san! It's an emergency!
The tourists on the bus are all-
Natsuyo-san is a hermaphrodite?
How is that possible!?
I would've noticed!
Something's wrong with everyone.
We need to get out of this place fast.
Miyuki... where did Miyuki go?
There it is again.
I'm being raped, but why...
Why does it feel so good?
I hate it, but...
Miyuki... it's got her too?
I can't talk.
I-I can't take it.
I'm cumming.
I-I'm gonna cum.
Everyone in this village was strange.
The villagers...
and we tourists as well.
But... we couldn't run away.
And l won't run away... until I rescue Miyuki.
toumei na tsuki no shizuku ga mawaru
The transparent moondrops spin
Translation:
Voldemort
Edit:
Collectr
omoide ga majiwaru youni
as if to merge with my memories.
Timing:
MrMew
sugite yuku toki no omosa ni shizumu
Sinking into the heavy weight of time,
Typeset & Encode:
ShocWave
Quality Check:
Morpheus_Stiltzkin
mainichi nara sutete ii
I want to abandon days like this.
Presented by:
Erobeat
tobitatsu mizu no hi no mure ga
A flock of sparks flew from the water
nami ni kiete yuku
and then disappeared into the waves.
http://www.erobeat.net
mimamori yurete nijimu
Watching them, they blur...
namida hitotsu (white feeling)
in my tears ( white feeling).
#erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
kikasete ano koro to onaji
Please tell me what you used to tell me.
ari fureta kotoba wo
Just those everyday words.
ima wa omoi dasenai
Because I can't remember them anymore.
I never play again
I never play again,
Will say again
Will say again,
Still love me
"Still love me."