BONUS VIDEO
Spice Pirates Sala
Sarah, do you think we can relax tonight?
Blankenheim's leftover minions are laying low.
Tonight should be quiet.
In that case...
Sylia! Always with the hard-on.
I could say the same for you.
That's true.
All right, we'll enjoy ourselves tonight.
That's right, Sylia and I had a secret.
What's the holdup? I'm still waiting to cum here.
I'm sorry. I need to rest.
Your cock is too big for me to-
So much cum... It's warm.
Oh God, if you do that with your fingers...
I'm going to...
You mustn't. I won't let you get off that easy.
I'm sorry.
I'll try harder.
You're... driving me crazy!
Reached the limit, have you?
Goodness. You came before me.
That calls for punishment.
Your dick...
Yes... I love your dick!
Ow!
What a dirty mouth you have.
Cecil, you're quite the nympho.
That's because... dirty things... make me hot...
It make me feel so good!
Please slowdown.
I seem to recall asking you to do the same earlier, to no avail.
I've forgotten. I forgot about that.
Forgive me!
Please, spray your cum all over me!
I'm cumming!
Our bodies never did return to normal
Sylia and I experience endless pain and longing.
Truly, our taming has only just begun.