Sensei, does it feel good?
How cute.
S-Shinohara.
Please call me Katsumi.
And now I'll lead you all the way.
Sensei...
K-Katsumi...
Sensei, you too...
My boobs feel good.
Do you feel good too?
Cum.
Please cum, Sensei.
Don't...
I just did it...
Part 01 The Athletic Body A.L.L.U.R.E
Here you go, Sensei.
Terashima.
That's right.
You transferred schools, just for me?
Yes.
And you even let me freeload in your grandfather's home.
That's right.
Moved
She's a good girl.
Terashima's a really good girl.
But...
Her body had some nice curves...
Sensei?
Oh, it's nothing!
It's nothing!
Thanks for the meal!
I'm going now!
Carnal desires go away!
Hey, have you done your homework?
Just how perverted am I?
Even though I was seduced, doing that to a student is still...
Already lively this early, eh, Tsuji.
Kaburagi-sensei!
My mentor, Kaburagi-sensei!
Yep, this is your mentor, Kaburagi.
Well?
Have you decided which club you are going to supervise?
Each club's invitations are coming off a bit too strong.
All of the clubs are fighting over which you're going to coach in.
You, the genius who left a mark in each major sports category in the country.
They all consider it a great honor to be under your guidance.
No, that's not really true.
Hi, Tatsuya.
Good morning.
Belmont.
No, I already told you to call me Anna, right?
Her boobs, her boobs are outrageously...!
Tatsuya!
Coach.
Shirato, save me!
When are you finally going to choose the tennis club?
You sure are popular.
What is she doing?!
Genius coach.
I want you to be in the cheerleading club.
This is my "invitation."
Your, invitation...
I heard from Katsumi, Coach.
How she tried to... seduce you.
We're not about to lose to the swimming and cheerleading clubs.
So please, join the tennis club...
Usagi, no fair.
Even I...
What a great titty fuck.
Suck my tits.
Tatsuya, does it feel good?
You can cum if you want to.
Coach, coach!
Hi!
S-Sorry for intruding!
We were seen.
After School!
You're late, Sensei.
Shinohara, you're...
Oh my, I already told you to call me Katsumi.
How was it with Anna and Usagi.
How do you know?
Oh? I was right then.
Stop this already, this...
Are you really sure about that?
If I suddenly start screaming here...
If you don't want to get fired,
then just keep quiet and follow my lead.
You're protesting, and yet it's already getting big.
It's okay, I'm really going to insert it this time.
Thanks for the meal.
It's starting to go in slowly.
It's already in.
This is my first time...
Me too...
It's my first time too...
Do you really want me to be your coach that badly?
Yes.
So, how did you know about Anna and Usagi?
It's because you're a coward.
What?
You're the Joushou Academy's King of Sports.
Yet your abilities are steadily waning.
You were supposed to be this school's pillar, and now its savior.
Are you really... okay with this?
Give and take.
I don't care, if it means getting this school back on its feet.
I'll become your "give", Sensei.
Shinohara.
I told you to call me Katsumi.
Katsumi, I'll work hard to make you feel good.
Sensei, I'm starting to feel good.
My body feels hot...
It's my first time, and yet...
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming, very soon...!
Oh yes, it's rubbing in me.
Oh no!
No, I'm cumming.
I'm really about to cum!
Wait, I just came.
Please...
Don't, any more and I'll cum again.
No, it feels good.
Sensei, please, let's...
Let's cum together...
I'm cumming.
Sensei!
Sensei...!
Oh wow, it won't stop.
No way, it became big again.
It feels great...
I'm... cumming again.
I'm going to cum.
I just won't stop cumming!
I'm home.
Welcome home, Sensei.
Welcome home!
W-Wait, why are you two...?
We came to get tutored by Terashima-san!
Umm, it's not just a two-person study session.
Good evening, Sensei.
Ah, it's yo...
The fight has just started, you know.
Sensei, what's wrong?!
Oh my, Tatsuya. You were so happy that you fainted?
Oh, Coach!
Are you all right, Sensei?