Tatsuya!
Here!
I'm addicted to you.
Coach, come to the tennis club today.
You're going to come with me on a swimsuit play.
Um, Terashima-san?
What?
It's starting to feel a bit painful.
My heart...
My heart feels even more painful.
Sensei, you idiot!
Next day.
It's done.
Sorry about that, Shinjou.
Shinjou?
Sensei, I...
Sensei!
Won't you let me invite you?
I'm actually scared of men...
But,
if it's you, Sensei, I think I can handle it.
What's the matter?
Please tell why it is so.
So this is... your dick.
Can I lick it?
This is...
It's salty!
Your dick feels hot,
and the smell is making me feel dizzy.
Terashima!
Please listen to what I have to say!
Terashima... I!
I do not want to.
Madoka!
Did Sensei, just say Madoka?
Terashima!
It hurts.
Oh, sorry.
Pervert.
Sensei, you're a pervert!
A lecher, and an idiot!
But I love you.
I love you, Sensei!
I really do!
And yet why?
Why won't you face me?
Sensei, I'm... I'm...
I'm really in love with you.
Madoka.
I love you too.
My mind's going numb.
I...
I'm letting out a weird voice...
Don't, Sensei!
No!
Sensei, Sensei, no...!
I'm cumming!
This is... umm...
Your dick.
This will go inside me, right?
Sensei, let's do it already.
Sensei.
Sensei, make yourself feel good too.
O-Oh, oh wow...
Sensei, I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum with your dick!
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
Lots of it is coming out, Sensei.
I think, I'll be the archery club's coach.
Sensei...
Wait just a minute!
Your choice as a coach and your emotional feelings
are two completely separate things, Sensei.
Ta-tsu-ya!
Coach!
S-Sensei!
The elimination round is about to start.
Sensei, you have a lewd look on your face.
Swimming, tennis, cheerleading, and archery.
All of these clubs are really moving forward.
You sure are amazing.
Sensei.
tatsuya.
Coach.
S-Sensei.
Please coach us!
Spocon!
Part 02 The Coach Competition