Mystery Moon in the Night Sky!?
Above Ohtsuna City, right beside the actual moon, there is another
moon-like thing floating in the night sky. It radiates light just like
the real moon, but it is a different color. A meteorological research
agency was unable to detect that anything is really there.
What the hell is this? The agency will use any means possible to
determine what this is, in cooperation with other nations...
Why is that thing after me?
What is it?
It's coming!
Ow...
He's got potential.
Don't you think, Chiro?
But it seems that his powers have
not been completely revealed.
What do you think?
Should we give him a test?
Test?
Let's try it on campus.
What was that thing
that came after me?
What's going on in this city?
Was that woman just an illusion?
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Blocking the light that turns pale
Stopping the flow of time
brimming with lies
The naked words that were
thrown at the world
I'll try to gather them
and vindicate them
Happiness cannot happen unless
you decide to go after it
The repeated days of giving up
I want to go after you
more than ever
It's not sadness but
love and courage
Even a flame hints at
the beginning of life
Give a reason for minor offense
Oh, hell... two moons and wound
The sudden gust of wind
points the path to the sea
Oh, hell to sea
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Killing the souls that turn pale
Wake up from the sleep
brimming with lies
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
Waiting for the blue sky
A train is arriving on Platform 3...
Please stand behind the white line.
Uh, sorry.
Ah, you're Ryo Hamura.
Huh? Do I know you?
I need to talk to you.
Meet me at 8 PM on the
rooftop of Building #2.
You got that?
Get up!
What do you want from me?
Ow, ow! Don't be so rough!
What're you talking about?
Did she put you up to this?
Well, sorry about that, Ryo Hamura.
We wanted to test your power.
Power? What do you mean?
Your reflexes that helped you
dodge those street signs yesterday.
And the speed with which
you were able to avoid my attack.
You're using a power that
you're not even aware of yet.
A power just like ours.
Yesterday? You mean...
Hey, what are you guys
going on about?
Just bring him up.
Ryo Hamura, right?
I'm the head of the Astronomy Club.
Izumi Kagura.
We're asking you to fight with us.
What's with these guys?
Astronomy Club
Well, I don't really understand this.
You're all in the Astronomy
Club, but that's just a cover...
and you're actually a
band of warriors called "The Kasha."
You come from that blue moon
up there and you fight monsters...
like the one last night?
That's very good.
Never met anyone who
understood her explanation in one go.
I'm terrible at explaining things.
Uh, Ryo...
How about another cup of tea?
Thanks.
There's a lot here, and I
just don't know what it all means.
Just let me think about this.
Ryo!
I'm sorry about today.
But can you give us an
answer within a week?
If you really don't want anything
to do with what we talked about...
we're going to have to
erase your memory.
Erase my memory?
Shut up, you ugly nerd!
Stop it. Why let it bother you?
Don't you think it's creepy?
Oh, what am I going to do with you?
That guy doesn't deserve a lover.
Maybe I'll just break them up.
I knew it.
This rain sucks.
It sure does.
Did you hear about the hottie
who gets off in the park?
Really?
Come on, Eri!
Enough with your text messaging!
Ow!
I think she's in my class.
G-Gotoh, was it?
Hello?
Is this Ryo? It's Izumi Kagura.
Did you have time to think
about what we talked about?
Well, I haven't decided anything yet.
I see.
Um, you think you can make
it to Tamago Park tonight?
Sure.
I want you to see for yourself
what a Light Hunter is.
Here she comes.
Gotoh.
Oh...
Please be gentle.
She's been coming here for
the past two or three nights.
That's how Light Hunters
prey on their victims.
A Light Hunter is drawn to the
unfulfilled desires of people...
and they live off of that energy.
Unless we get that Light
Hunter off of her soon...
that woman will continue to
see the dreams that it projects.
Eventually she will become
too exhausted and die.
Please. Fight with us.
I understand. But how am I
supposed to fight a monster like that?
You'll need some training in
order to use your power...
but let's do it together tonight.
Come with me.
Oh, ancient fire. Your power
that banishes the filth like the wind...
Gotoh!
Ryo! This way!
Become a sword to this Kasha...
Izumi!
Ryo! Get out of here!
Izumi! Izumi!
Izumi!
We made it just in time, Chiro.
Ryo...
Thank goodness you're okay.
Thank you, Kyoka.
You're welcome.
I sensed danger in the air
around this area.
So I thought I'd
check it out just in case.
Well? Do you believe it now?
What we were telling you?
Please. Fight with us.
All right. I'll give it a shot.
Oh, ancient fire. Mend the
pain of this woman...
Does this mean her horrible
memories will disappear?
I don't know.
But this is all that we can do.
What I'm saying is that...
I don't see the motive
behind all these arson cases.
The arson cases continue.
A game arcade burns to the ground.
Was it caused by an angry
tenant with financial trouble?
The boutique where the
fire started is a total loss.
Just think about it.
Even if we were to assume that
the Light Hunters are behind all this...
as long as they're
feeding off of human desires,
we should be seeing some common
threads in where these fires are set.
According to the police, they only
hit busy areas where people gather.
I wonder if they can figure
out where they'll strike next.
Considering that they are taking
extra precautions to prevent fires,
the fact that the damage is getting
worse and worse makes me suspicious,
and I guess that the
Light Hunters are behind this.
But how could we know the motive
of someone they've possessed?
The only place they've announced
where a fire started is a boutique.
Even if we were to accept that,
the motives would be the grudges
that people had against that place.
But we can't just leave it at that.
For every fire started by the
people possessed by Light Hunters,
I'm sure there's got to
be a reason behind it.
But I guess we just need
more information.
Oh, right...
Where are Kyoka and Ryo?
It sure was a great movie.
It was so good, especially
after Megat met Tiro the Mute.
What part of this is
information gathering?
Yeah. The information
gathering begins now.
I did tell you that I have
the power of "Satori," right?
Satori people can read
the minds of others.
Even when it's all crowded like this.
Who are you?
You have an amazing power!
Just with the fluctuations in words,
you're able to make lovey-dovey
couples get into fights.
Excuse me, but are you
Manami Miwasaka?
Would you like to join our group?
- What?
We're in the process of
going after a serial arsonist.
These aren't normal arson cases.
I'm sure you realize that.
If we can count on
your power of words,
I'm sure we'll be able
to track down the arsonist.
Wow, I didn't know that.
I never knew I could do
something like that with my power.
Oh, come to think of it...
I noticed something as I
walked past that boutique last night.
Wow, how pretty.
A woman in red?
Time for the meeting.
I'm sorry, Manami.
We've got a meeting
we've got to go to.
I want to hear more
about what you saw, okay?
S-Sure.
Kyoka, about that woman
dressed in red...
That boutique where
the fire took place...
was where a lot of Goths
and witch types went.
So, I have this feeling that...
the next one will be on
the sixth floor of that same building.
Right. If the Light Hunters
have possessed a woman,
I suppose it's possible she'd
be after a boutique or something.
I'm sorry!
Ow, ow...
Are you all right?
What's the matter? What
are you doing here, Manami?
Kyoka.
I wanted to go after the arsonist, too.
What?
You want to meet that Light
Hunter woman and talk to her?
Until now, I've been
using my power of words...
for stupid, unimportant things.
But if this power of mine
can be of some use...
All right. You can come with us.
Ryo, you'll be responsible
for protecting her.
Fine.
Shit!
Ryo! I want you to go
ahead to the sixth floor!
All right!
You think they'll be all right alone?
The power of words is a rare
and highly effective power.
And Ryo is quite capable as well.
No, stop! Let me talk to her!
Just wait.
I suppose.
Thank you, Ryo.
Everyone possessed by a Light
Hunter was once a regular person.
If you want to use
the power of words,
maybe you can snap
her out of her suffering.
Leave the others to me.
Maybe I can't do this.
Maybe it's too much for me.
Wh-What's going on?
There's no end to this!
Shit!
You were lonely.
You were betrayed
by someone you loved.
And you abandoned
yourself somewhere.
You ran away from
everything, and lived all alone.
All alone.
I'm cold... I'm cold... I'm cold...
I'm sorry. How thoughtless of me.
How pretty. It's burning.
It's so pretty.
Can you be satisfied
only by burning your past?
Does that give you satisfaction?
You can burn all the places
of your past,
but your sad memories
will never go away!
They're not strangers!
And they're not family!
Nothing is going to change
unless you're willing to change!
Not everyone is good.
But still, even so...
you've got to have more strength!
Unless you can be stronger...
this will go on forever
and nothing will change!
There's no end to this, Izumi!
What is this?!
Manami!
Manami...
Ryo, I suppose I
could've expected this.
I've done terrible
things all the time.
Maybe I deserve to be...
ravaged even more.
Manami!
Are you okay?
Ryo...
Izumi...
Ryo... Manami...
Shit! The door won't open!
At this rate, we're
going to be finished!
Ryo... Manami...
Ryo. Thank you.
You're conscious. Thank God.
When I was possessed
by the Light Hunter,
I thought I was being punished.
I was toying with people's
hearts with my power of words.
I thought that I was
going to die here.
It's okay. You just take it easy.
Raisen!
Izumi!
It looks like I made it in time.
Fuck!
Manami!
Ryo!
Is everyone all right?
Thank goodness.
Makoto, you saved us. Thank you.
You have grown weak, Miss.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Who are you?
So you're Makoto Kedoin?
Just like Izumi said, that
was an amazing technique.
I wasn't able to save that person.
How could I...
It's not like that.
In the last moments,
her face was at peace.
I'm sure that she recaptured
her soul at that moment.
A happier fate than continuing to
live possessed by the Light Hunters.
It would be nice to think that. Right?
I'm sure that's how it is.
That's what I believe.
We'll meet again soon. Bye.
See ya later, Miss!
More! Fuck me harder!
More! Please, more!
More!
Oh, Haiji! Bite it!
That was great, Haiji...
That's so good...
You're boring me.
There's something
stirring inside of me.
Next Episode
The next episode of
Square of the Moon...
The Wicked Moon!
Please watch it for me!