What the hell... was that?
This happened before.
When was that?
I know them, but why?
Miss, is this really what you wanted?
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Blocking the light that turns pale
Stopping the flow of time
brimming with lies
The naked words that were
thrown at the world
I'll try to gather them
and vindicate them
Happiness cannot happen unless
you decide to go after it
The repeated days of giving up
I want to go after you
more than ever
It's not sadness but
love and courage
Even a flame hints at
the beginning of life
Give a reason for minor offense
Oh, hell... two moons and wound
The sudden gust of wind
points the path to the sea
Oh, hell to sea
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Killing the souls that turn pale
Wake up from the sleep
brimming with lies
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
Waiting for the blue sky
Just as I thought.
So, to bring the Light's world
"True Night" into this reality...
Yes... it seems we've got no other option
but to get a Kotodama user...
to call down the "Queen of the Night,"
who is said to have been the one...
to make the True Moon appear,
and ask her how.
If that man, Haiji, had done
as planned, we would have been...
able to capture the Kotodama
woman easily, but unfortunately...
We already know that
Manami Miyasaka,
the most powerful
Kotodama user in this generation,
is part of the Fire group.
But we didn't believe that the
Fire group would have enough...
power to stop the kidnapping.
We are truly sorry.
We originally constructed this tower...
to collect the power
from the light of the True Moon...
But without a Kotodama user,
we can't achieve the "True Night."
Yes.
I'll give you one more chance...
Understand?
Yes, sir.
I have a favor to ask.
Please watch Souji's actions closely.
S-sure.
Lightning Fang!
Miss, why do you
push yourself like this?
It's because of Souji, isn't it?
If we keep defeating the Light,
then my brother will appear.
That's why...
I have to stop... my brother.
Then I'll help!
Why do you go out in the
cold night and fight like...
you have nothing left to lose?
Miss! Is this some kind of atonement?
That must be it...
It's for erasing everyone's memories...
And it's for making Hamura and
Kyoka believe they're lovers...
I'm sorry, Makoto!
Please leave me alone for a while.
Miss...
Kyoka!
I was getting tired of waiting.
So, you were waiting here
the whole time?
Yeah, I wanted to meet you
that much sooner.
Weren't you cold?
Let's go inside.
Then warm me up.
While I was waiting, I was thinking about
doing this with you. Strip me, Ryo.
What is it...?
This feeling like
something's not right...
What's making me feel this way?
Ryo?
Looks like you're in quite a state.
I can feel the blood flowing.
It's so hard. What do you
want to do with it, Ryo?
I can't hear you.
Tell me what you want!
I want to cum inside you!
Go ahead. Cum inside me.
Ryo! Ryo, I'm cumming!
Don't! You want to cum inside me.
Do it... Ryo.
What's the matter...
I can't sleep... I'm too afraid.
In my dream, there's a woman
with this scary face coming at me...
trying to kill me with a blade...
For some reason,
I call her my sister,
and right when I'm about to die,
a man dressed all in black...
comes flying from the sky, and
puts her to sleep.
But then he turns to me
with this scary look and says,
"You are a sinner who betrayed
your sister, and deceived me!
You must atone for these crimes!"
But that's only a dream.
Kyoka, you're not a sinner.
Ryo...
It was probably just the sound
of the pounding rain...
giving you strange dreams.
You should try and get some more sleep.
Yeah...
The memories that Kyoka doesn't
remember... It's the same as me.
Before, I just felt like I
had to fight those monsters...
I realized that I've forgotten something.
It's been one month since
Kyoka started coming to my place...
When and where did we first meet?
At any rate, I know that I
have to be gentle and kind to her.
Be nice to Kyoka...
Looks like she's not pretending.
You erased her memory, Izumi.
Release that woman, brother.
It's you... The Kotodama user is
necessary for our plans.
Why do you help the Light and...
try to pull these people into
a world of endless dreams?
Endless dreams...
Izumi, you sound like the old men
of the Valley of Fire.
People know of
the existence of the Light, but never...
try to struggle against us,
and just go about their everyday lives.
Do you really think that such a
life can be called a reality?
Well, that's...
The dreams you show your
friends in the Astronomy Club...
the dreams that the Light show...
What's the difference?
Within each person is a demon.
The Valley of Fire does not admit this.
It will lead to their demise.
Izumi, humans feel safer
being judged.
They can not stand
to be in eternal purgatory.
Something you want to ask me?
Yes we do, traitor.
I thought you were from
a defunct holy order,
but now I find out you're
from the Valley of Fire.
Why didn't you tell us
about this earlier?
Well, no one really asked.
Excuses... Plus, yesterday's
Fire leader, Izumi Kagura,
seems to be your sister.
How do you explain all this?
Meeting her was not
really part of my plan...
But I suppose telling you to
be less nosy won't work.
Souji, what are you... scheming?
"The Day of Judgment." That's all.
Sakaki... Sakaki!
W-what should I do?
Sakaki... Sakaki's going to die!
Owww! Are you okay, miss?
S-Sakaki... he's dying.
Are you all right?
You're...
Has your memory been erased too?
I'll go and get someone!
Wait a minute!
I'm not going to last long anyway.
More importantly, I'm sorry,
but do me a favor... this woman...
Please protect her...
She has no one but me to rely on...
Sakaki!
Wait a sec. Why would
you trust a passing stranger?
Because I know you.
I knew you'd be the helpful sort...
Because you're the group
we fought. The Fire group...
The Fire? What are you...
I'm...
Sakaki!
Why don't you give up?
Everyone can't seem to remember a thing.
Be quiet. It doesn't concern you.
Maybe they're having more
fun without their memories.
Even that Shinkai guy...
hit you out of nowhere...
Ryo and Kyoka are
going out too, right?
Maybe you're just jealous.
How stupid.
It's not like that.
Why are you still here, hanging around me?
You're part of the Light!
Why don't you go back to them?
Because I don't want to.
It's gloomy, and Sakaki isn't there...
Hey, why don't we go to
a hotel instead and... do it?
Ryo Hamura, I need to talk to you.
Sorry, Hoshigawa, but we really
don't know about the Light...
or about this Fire.
And I'm telling you, it's because
your memories have been sealed.
Manami's been kidnapped by them, Ryo.
I'm sorry for the woman,
but I can't help you...
I have to protect Kyoka
as much as I can.
Kyoka! Where's Chiro?
You cared for it so much,
how can you just forget about it?
Get your hands off of Kyoka!
Ryo, your protection of Kyoka
is a spell cast by our leader, too!
That's not true!
Ouch...
Here.
Oh... thanks.
Why don't you give up?
They just don't want to remember.
Shut up! It doesn't concern you!
I'll help you.
I may have an idea of how
to get their memories back.
I never thought I'd see you
break your cool like this.
I don't like it.
Kyoka not being Kyoka.
The leader not being the leader,
Manami not being Manami...
That's all.
Come with me.
I see, so Sakaki is...
But our plans are nearly complete.
The night of the full moon,
the Kotodama user...
We have all the things we need.
The Fire group will be here soon.
Let's add some more
entertainment on such a lovely night.
Now, give us the power!
If I can save Manami and
defeat my brother, I will...
Ryo, Kyoka, Makoto, everyone...
Goodbye. Please be happy.
Kyoka, where have you been?
I've been looking for you.
Sister?
Everyone's been worried about you...
Let's go home.
Thank God.
Then all this has been a dream.
Everyone's waiting for you.
Father, mother, Souji...
Huh... Oh, Souji's coming too.
I'm sorry, sis.
I know I ruined your date.
It's okay. Why don't
the three of us go to a festival?
You wanted to meet me, right?
You wanted to sleep with me
even if you betrayed Misato.
You wanted this to happen.
N-No! Stop it!
If you just accept it,
you won't feel insecure.
If you sin,
you won't feel so insecure.
S-Sister...
Stop!
It's your first time in this hole...
S-Stop! Stop! Stop!
So that was it! I remember!
I just fought against the Light!
I had my memory wiped out...
Chiro! You came back to me...
Kyoka... you...
Yeah... I remember it all.
Kyoka...
Who is it?
Evening. Sorry it's so late.
No problem, but what's up?
Did you run away? Hold on...
I was coming home from
class and I wanted to see you.
I was just getting lonely by myself.
Izumi really went there by herself?
Ryo, trying to hog all the glory?
Hoshigawa...
We're all friends here.
We can't let you have all the fun, Senpai.
That idiot, Izumi.
Always making us worry about her.
Looks like everyone's here.
Everyone... they came after all...
Let's go save Manami and the Mistress!
Izumi!
Miss!
Leader!
Izumi!
Miss Izumi!
Everyone! Ryo!
Lightning Fang!
Sun Tegjupery!
Why are you here?
We're your friends. We won't let you
fight the Light alone, Izumi!
I think so too. Sorry, mistress,
but I broke the charm on them.
But this is my...
Izumi! Let me deal with Souji,
for my own sake.
That's why... I'll have to do this.
For us to go home alive,
we need you to rest for a while.
Hamura, I'm leaving the rest to you.
When she wakes up, catch up with us.
R-Right, I got it.
Wait, why are you looking
at me like that?
W-Well...
Just because we had sex,
it doesn't mean anything between us!
I can't believe I have to have this guy
behaving like he's my boyfriend!
What a dork!
Sorry...
Why are you apologizing?
Well, let's go.
We're counting on you, Hamura.
Unfortunately, I'll have to let
you be the knight this time.
Make sure you live up to the title, Ryo.
Yeah... You guys be careful too.
Ryo! I was a little happy that
you cared about my feelings.
Thanks.
What does this mean, Souji.
Why hasn't the Night Queen appeared?
They say the queen died
with a grudge in her soul.
Perhaps this Kotodama user
does not have enough negative energy.
How about using the Light's
power collected in the tower and...
combining it with the Kotodama
user's power to hit the True Moon?
The True Moon is the shadow
of the moon in the night sky.
If the True Moon gains its own
radiance, and loses all shadow,
then there will be no where
for the Light to live there.
The True Moon is crying?
Square of the Moon:
The Night is Coming!
I told them I wanted to wear
a yukata in the episode,
but they made me wear
this kimono instead!
Next episode: The Night is Coming!
Chapter 4: A Blurry Moon.