What is this?
What happened to me?
I know I was kidnapped...
How awful...
What the hell's going on?
What happened?
A crimson-eyed woman...
This feeling... I know her.
This... isn't going on right now...
I'm inside someone's consciousness.
This can't be... This can't be the
world of Light Sakaki mentioned.
It's just too terrible!
How dare you turn us into this!
I can turn back to normal if
I get covered in a Light's love juice.
No, stop!
No!
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Blocking the light that turns pale
Stopping the flow of time
brimming with lies
The naked words that were
thrown at the world
I'll try to gather them
and vindicate them
Happiness cannot happen unless
you decide to go after it
The repeated days of giving up
I want to go after you
more than ever
It's not sadness but
love and courage
Even a flame hints at
the beginning of life
Give a reason for minor offense
Oh, hell... two moons and wound
The sudden gust of wind
points the path to the sea
Oh, hell to sea
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Killing the souls that turn pale
Wake up from the sleep
brimming with lies
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
Waiting for the blue sky
They figured out a way to bring
True Night to the Earth's surface...
by using Miyasaka's Kotodama.
I have to hurry and
catch up with everyone...
Phew... There's no more
enemies on this floor.
I didn't even realize we
had gotten split up from the rest.
Everyone's probably okay.
Besides, we're all headed
to the same place,
so we'll all meet up sooner or later.
You're right.
Great, but if you start holding me back,
I'm leaving you behind.
That's just cold! I've been
pulling my weight the whole time!
You like sex, don't you.
Where does it feel best?
Don't hold back.
This is the last thing you'll ever feel.
No...
I can finally turn back into a human!
I'm next!
It will take a bit longer
for all the Light to move here from...
the Shadow World.
It's finally happened.
When we shall rule over this Earth!
Yes, but before
the glorious hour approaches,
I would like to make sure
that everything is in order.
Are you worried about
your sister, Kagura?
She should not even matter
to you at this point, so why?
Just wait until she comes up here.
A true Light would not understand
why this is completely unrelated.
Let us settle this, Izumi.
Before the curtain of judgment falls.
R-Ryo...
Oh, Izumi. I didn't mean to wake you.
It wasn't a dream... You really did come.
Thank you.
I've told you before, but the reason
I fight is to be with you, Izumi.
So... please, let me stay
by your side from now on, Izumi.
Yeah...
Looks like we're surrounded.
Then let me play the ace
up my sleeve. Back up, missy.
Ryo, where's everyone?
Oh, they said they would go on ahead,
and to follow them when you woke up.
I see...
Oh, and a message. Don't push yourself.
And to me, she said push myself harder.
Wonder what they meant.
Must be Makoto. Let's go, Ryo.
Where the hell did you manage
to get dynamite from?
I got a friend who loves
the dangerous stuff.
But man, it blew up those Light guys,
and all the glass out around here.
And almost blew us up in the process.
Hmm, you used explosives.
So it's not as if you came here
completely unprepared.
What the hell happened? Shit!
Guess I'll have to go with
what I'm good at.
Oh, leader. Over here. Kyoka's group
seems to be on the other side.
Yo, Hoshi, you want to
help out a little here?
Where's Momose and Makoto?
Well, we all got separated...
I'm right here.
Makoto.
Okay, it's opening!
Brother!
So you're finally here, Izumi.
We'll finish our fight from earlier.
Before everything ends, that is...
But first, I need you to talk.
Where did you hide my sister?
Then what? I put Misato inside of a deep,
eternal sleep where she rests.
No one can rest
in your deceptive world! Chiro!
You know the purgatory a person
experiences when they lose...
their memories now, don't you?
Even if she were to awaken right now,
how would Misato feel to have...
her sister, who stole her lover
away from her, being at her side?
That's...
Izumi, I didn't take this road
simply to get revenge...
against the old men
of the Valley of Fire.
I searched and I realized.
True rest can only be found
inside of ruin...
Izumi, the soul can't be saved
by the reasoning of man.
Izumi...
Then... go there by yourself.
But, avert your eyes...
from the precious memories
between you and Misato.
Brother, what you're doing is wrong!
It seems we're at an impasse.
It seems I have no choice.
Forgive me, Izumi.
Take this, brother!
Miss!
I won't tell you twice. Don't interfere!
Miss, fall back!
I told you not to interfere!
This is a problem between those
that carry on the Fire bloodline!
I can't do that. To break
the unbreakable chain of events,
that is my "purpose" in the Valley of Fire.
The one that told me
and trained a powerless me, was you.
That's right...
Lightning Fist Ultimate Technique!
Gaiha Resshin Fist!
Kitouin!
Makoto!
Calm down. It's not that bad.
Hold still Makoto. I'll heal you right away!
Thank you... Miss.
You seem pretty beat up...
But if you insist on continuing,
we'll be your opponents.
Ordinarily, I would take you both on,
but I am short on time. Move!
Chiro!
Even during my final judgment,
inside, I find myself wavering.
I don't know if you can stop
the Light's advances,
but I do remember where Misato lies.
Do what you wish with it.
Huh?
I will awaken Misato's soul.
Brother!
Souji...
Farewell.
Brother!
Brother...
I wonder... what the Light really is?
It might be the physical manifestation
of human weakness.
The Light may be within us all.
Let's go.
Where is this... A different dream?
Who is it... sleeping in such a place?
Keep it down... Leave me alone...
K-Kirara!
Welcome, Fire!
Congratulations on making it this far.
Kouichi... Why... You!
You were part of the Light!
It's been a while. You came all this way,
so I prepared a special guest.
Come on out!
Kirara!
No matter how many times
I see human despair, it's still charming.
I wouldn't move, if I were you.
You're surrounded by my servants.
Kirara's acting all weird.
What did you do to her?
You know, I don't see Souji.
Did he get beaten by you? Idiot...
Holding on to something so stupid...
Did you know? I'm the one who erased
that Misato woman's memories.
What... did you say?
You're... Oh, you're her little sister.
That was about the time
that we were trying to get Souji.
He was still wavering about you
and he fell for our plan easily.
I guess I should thank you.
His knowledge came in rather handy.
Oh, and the sleeping spell
Souji put on Misato?
I put it on this one as well.
People under this spell
are afraid to wake up, and cling...
to sleep, forever walking inside
of a shadowy world...
or something like that.
So, what will you do?
A stupid charm... Lightning! Let go, Miss!
Don't do it, Makoto!
I wouldn't try anything rough.
If you try and force her awake,
the shadows will tear up her soul,
and then there'd be no hope
to bring her back.
Only a bit more until
the cold night turns to True Night.
So stay quiet until then.
To pass the time, I'll tell you a story.
It was in the Heian Era,
when the Light came to this world as...
a form of mediation. The one born
for this was Princess Kaguya.
She had strange innate powers,
which many powerful men of the...
era desired to have, along with her beauty,
but she declined them all.
They executed her with fire, using
her mysterious powers as an excuse.
Because she was killed even though
she was innocent, her feeling of...
revenge was so strong that
it opened a rift between this world...
and the shadow world. The tunnel
only opened during the True Moon.
Before she died, she had given birth
to twins with red and blue eyes.
These became the first
of you of the Fire group.
The Fire was afraid of those
of the Light crossing over,
so they sealed away the True Moon.
And they built the Valley on the place
it was sealed, and protected it.
But due to Souji's betrayal,
the seal breaks and the True Moon revives.
Of course, my original intent
was to have both Souji Kagura and...
Izumi to become sacrifices to the Light.
My brother and I...
By the two sibling ancestors of
Princess Kaguya fighting, there...
would have been no stopping
the world from falling to darkness.
But then you meddlers
had to get in the way...
So you've been preying on
the weakness of people for so long...
You'll pay!
Senpai... should I?
Yeah, as big as possible.
You got it.
Let's go everyone!
Yeah!
Good luck everybody!
Now we're on even footing.
Oh well. Against you all
it doesn't really matter.
Sun Tegjupery!
Ah, Manami!
Izumi!
Die.
Come on, give me a bit more of a challenge.
Izumi, will you lend me your power?
Come on, let's get up, Kirara.
I don't want to. There's nothing
good out there even if I wake up.
I'm going to sleep here forever!
If you're going to say that...
I'm going to tickle you.
W-Wait, stop! Q-Quit it!
Where are we?
Not sure. I walked a long way
and ended up here...
But let's go home.
To where everyone else is.
Unless we destroy
the light gathering system,
a second or third wave
of Light might appear to do this again.
Hamura, can you do it?
Y-Yeah. Let's do it, Izumi.
Let the Night end!
It's over...
Ryo!
My body can't take anymore...
I'm sorry, Sakaki. Sorry, Hoshi...
Ryo...
Well looks like Miyasaka's safe too,
so let's get out of here.
Izumi...
Ryo, do your wounds... hurt?
I see... I was saved by your healing...
Izumi.
It's okay... Ryo.
Ryo...
Please...
Izumi...
On to the next one! Let's go everyone!