Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Blocking the light that turns pale
Stopping the flow of time
brimming with lies
The naked words that were
thrown at the world
I'll try to gather them
and vindicate them
Happiness cannot happen unless
you decide to go after it
The repeated days of giving up
I want to go after you
more than ever
It's not sadness but
love and courage
Even a flame hints
at the beginning of life
Give a reason for minor offense
Oh, hell... two moons and wound
The sudden gust of wind
points the path to the sea
Oh, hell to sea
It gently embraces us
Without averting its eyes
in this endless night
Killing the souls that turn pale
Wake up from the sleep
brimming with lies
Square of the Moon:
The Night Is Coming!
Waiting for the blue sky
Oh man, it's hot!
I can't stand being in that classroom.
Hey, Hoshikawa,
I didn't know you were here...
Izumi was looking for you.
She was complaining that she
couldn't find you even though...
you were supposed to help put the
cafe festival together.
Talent is fleeting, like the dragonfly
that skims the surface of a pond.
Huh?
My favorite band broke up last night.
The lead guitarist broke his finger
and supposedly can't play any more.
What a terrible crime...
Their music has been silenced forever.
I was going to spend the
day reminiscing about them...
You got some balls
making me mad, twice...
This time, I'm going to take
more than your finger, Hirayama!
Can you hear it?
This is the sound of
your soul breaking!
Burning Sun Strike!
Kai!
Lightning Fang!
He disappeared!
It's him...
Do you know that guy?
He's in a group called O.T.O.
And sings vocals... Tsutomu Haijima.
And the one being attacked
was the lead guitarist, Hirayama.
Yoku, please come quickly!
How awful. His finger bones
are completely destroyed...
Even with our mending powers,
this is extensive...
Switch with me, I'll try.
How is he?
I think he'll be alright...
but he's still in shock.
We'll have to erase this
person's short-term memory.
Hold on a second.
I-I just don't know... I mean,
about just erasing their memories.
Is this really in his best interest?
Yeah, but Hoshi...
What are you saying?
If we don't erase his memory,
every night he'll be crippled with fear!
Is that all right with you?
I understand... but still...
Is it okay, Hoshikawa?
I'm going to erase it.
I understand what Hoshi is saying.
But where did that guy go?
I know we injured him.
Damn it...
I'll remember this, bitch!
Who the hell are you?
We could have just let you die.
But you could prove useful to us.
We will give you new power, runt.
Take it and use it to
destroy the ones that you hate.
Starlight
Cafe/i>
Man... why do I have to
do this? Ah, here it is.
Astronomy Club
Man... why do I have to
do this? Ah, here it is.
And that's our current progress report.
Putting it bluntly, at this rate our club's
Starlight Cafe won't be ready in time.
Damn it! Manami, the uniforms
for the cafe are on schedule, right?
Y-Yes!
Shinkai, how are the decorations
for the fall constellation designs?
Leave it to me. But I could sure
use a few more people.
Well then, how about that guy
right there who isn't doing anything?
Huh! W-Wait a sec.
Why do I have to?
Ah, Momo.
Who are you?
Ah! I-I'm in Manami's class,
and we're kind of understaffed too.
I see...
And... I came to get Manami.
Is it all right if
I borrow her for a bit?
Like hell it is!
Sakuramizudai
Academy
Over here, over here!
Sakuramizudai
Academy
Did you wait long? Sorry...
Sakuramizudai
Academy
I just got here myself.
Sakuramizudai
Academy
Joe's sister's Starlight Cafe is amazing!
I'm part of it too!
Sakuramizudai
Academy
Ramune
Soda
Kyoka
Special Price
Today Only
Makoto, let's forget about the Fire
Group for today. Now take it off.
Sorry, I overslept!
Sorry to make you wait.
We're done changing.
Very nice, very nice!
Momo, when did you
join the Astronomy Club?
I guess you don't really care
about our club anymore, huh?
Astronomy Club
and Friends
Well then, I'm going to
go walk Koichi home.
Thank you very much for today.
Stay safe.
Let's go!
Sakuramizudai
Academy
Man, it is exhausting
dealing with those idiots.
Ah! Manami?
What the hell do you
think you're doing!
You!
So you finally showed up...
you Amazon woman!
Momose!
I'm taking her with me.
If you want her back, then come
to the "Live House" at the station.
Damn! It's my fault.
If I had defeated him back there...
Owww... What the hell is that guy?
Momose, are you all right?
Where's Manami?
Kidnapped. I'm going after them.
Will you be okay if I leave you here?
Yeah... I'll live...
Okay. When Ryo and the others get
back, tell them what happened.
They have to get to the "Live
House" in front of the station.
R-Roger.
I'm counting on you.
Well done. You can do whatever
you want to that bitch for revenge.
Izumi, w-wasn't that
Manami just now?
Ryo, please, don't ask questions!
Just follow me, please!
S-Sure.
Where's Manami?
She's not here.
She was just bait to lure you here.
What the hell?
Stop
Brother!
Izumi!
I didn't think you'd be in this town...
That's too bad... Die.
You don't use this too often, do you?
For a tall bitch,
you sure are tight down here.
We haven't even gotten started!
I haven't been getting
my exercise lately...
Let go of Izumi!
Your thoughts are able
to change our destiny...
Brother!
Izumi, don't involve innocents
in the war between Fire and Light.
If you don't want
any more bloodshed, that is...
And you, Kotodama user,
we will meet again.
That person was your...
I'm sorry I didn't say anything.
I'm worried about everyone else.
Let's head back.
That's two. Looks like
I expected too much.
Is that all that you got?
You arrogant fool!
We just let our guard down!
Well, well. You're the last "Satori."
I'm sure this will be a disappointing match.
Chiro!
It can't be!
You've had your memory
erased once already.
Do you even remember
why you are fighting?
I thought so... You're even
worse than your pet. Die.
Momose!
Izumi. Oh, and Manami too!
What happened? You're all beat up!
It's nothing. But Makoto
went to the "Live House"...
in front of the station to save her,
and she isn't back yet.
I have a bad feeling about this.
You're really feeling it, aren't you?
But that's not the sound
that I want to hear.
I'll put you out of your misery...
I missed... Too bad...
They'll be okay. It's not critical.
Don't worry.
They're all pretty tough...
Hey... Izumi. I don't like
watching you suffer by yourself.
Even if there's nothing I can do,
I want to make your suffering
and your destiny easier to carry.
PRACTICES
Surgery
Internal Medicine
Respiratory
Ohtsuna Hospital
I met Hirayama in there.
He said he'd continue his
music no matter what. I'm glad...
I know the deal. You're
here to wipe out my memories.
Even if I don't want you to,
I can't get far in a wheelchair.
It's okay. Go ahead.
I see...
So Dad and Mom and Izumi...
You were all pretending
like you didn't know.
Why did you erase my memories?
Who am I really? Why
am I even fighting the Light?
Give me back my memories!
Give them back...
Izumi...
I'm sorry I called so suddenly...
I went to check on
everyone this afternoon.
They don't remember anything.
Shinkai, Hoshikawa, or Kyoka.
What exactly was it
that we were fighting for?
When the Light got hold of
Emi Gotoh, I couldn't forgive them.
I wanted to destroy them
for using human sadness like that.
I thought that I was fighting
for a place that I can belong,
of my own free will.
But it's not just that.
I realized that this time.
I probably wanted to fight
because I'd be with you, Izumi...
The battle against the Light
won't end easily.
But if I can help you with your
tough decisions, and suffering...
that you may have to carry,
I want to be there for you.
And I can keep fighting for you.
Because I love you, Izumi.
Ryo...
I can finally say it.
I love you, Izumi.
Forgive me... Ryo...
Who dares disturb our slumber...
The Night Queen has graced
us with her presence...
Who dares disturb our slumber...
This is...
Who dares... disturb our...
The Queen... has returned
to the Land of the Dead.
The Kotodama user's power
was too weak!
You two make sure that this
time you get that Kotodama user.
For the sake of our "True Night."
Next Episode
Rocks, paper, scissors, shoot!
Oh no, I lost!
The next episode of
Square of the Moon...
The Rising Moon!