When I turn that corner, there she is...
Mokoto, you're late!
It's always Une.
When did you change your cell phone?
I called your house last night because
you never answer your cell phone.
What did you want to talk about?
Well...
Did you go to Karaoke with Eri, again?
Yep...
Your mom was worried because
you come back late every night.
Me and Une are not like that.
For real?
You've never kissed?
No, never.
But, you guys come to
school together every morning.
We're childhood friends.
So you're not her boyfriend.
What was that?
Well, actually...
Kitahara likes Une?
Yes, he does.
And he asked me to ask you
about you and Hasunuma's relationship.
Me and Une's relationship...
Don't...
Why?
Hasunuma doesn't
have a boyfriend, right?
You're just her good friend.
I thought that would be enough.
I thought Une would
be my closest girl forever.
Une, are you free today?
Why?
Disney Land tickets!
How unusual for you ask me out!
My dad gave me these a while ago...
...but I'd totally forgotten
and the expiration date is today.
And, I remembered you like Disney Land.
I'm sorry I can't go...
Do you have a promise with Eri?
Just cancel it.
W-Well, I have a
promise with my boyfriend.
B-Boyfriend?
Kitahara?
In our class?
Yeah...
Why do you think that's him?
Because...
You're wrong.
Then, who's your boyfriend?
You don't know him.
She's left?
She said she didn't feel good.
It's not only today.
She's been sick for a while.
Not only today?
She doesn't hang
out with us anymore...
And lately, she hasn't looked happy.
Eri!
Sorry, sorry.
I didn't realize it, at all.
I thought I knew more
about Une than anyone else...
Une was always with me...
I thought it would never change.
Une...
No...
Hold on...
Sorry, I can t wait.
It's so good, Une.
Takashi!
I-I'm coming...
T-Takashi.
I'm coming!
N-No...
Please don't come inside me...
Une!
Hey Une...
Do you wan to go to
somewhere, so we can live by ourselves?
What happened?
What about going back to school?
You want to become a doctor, right?
Not me.
My parents want me to.
Takashi...
It's impossible to escape with me, huh?
Are you serious?
I want to be with you
forever because I love you.
This morning...
When I turned that corner.
Une wasn't there...
Wait, Mak...
Hello, Hasunuma residence.
Makoto?
I'm sorry that I made you come here.
It's okay.
I'm glad, your mom
didn't answer the phone.
Yep...
What happened today?
You didn't tell me you would
be absent from school.
I was worried.
I was hung over.
Do you drink?
Kind of...
I may drop out of school.
What do you mean?
My boyfriend wants me
to go somewhere with me.
He does?
Yeah...
He asked me if I want to live with him.
He is serious, so...
What's that mean?
Makoto...
I don't want to listen such a story...
You've always given me good advice.
I can't talk about these things
to anyone except my best friend...
Best friend...
I have a question about
what men feel about something...
Goodbye!
Makoto!
I transferred money for
this month to your account.
Are you studying hard?
Your brother got into a top
medical school on his first try.
You have to try hard, too.
You should already be satisfied
because you have my brother.
Isn't that enough?
Hello, Takashi?
Tonight, I can't...
Yes, I don't feel well.
Tomorrow is fine.
Hey Takashi...
No, never mind.
See you tomorrow.
Une didn't come to school again...
I may drop out of school.
You haven't made up your
mind which school to apply to?
How come?
Don't talk like my teacher.
How about you?
My first choice is Sourin!
Sourin?
For real?
My teacher said I could probably get in.
Sourin...
Makoto, you should try.
Where?
Sourin...
Don't say that.
You know my grades, don't you?
Not many people go to
Sourin from our school...
...so I would feel much more
comfortable if you'd go with me.
You'll get a good tutor!
Professor Une Hasunuma!
Then you can give me
a ride as always, right?
Is that what you want?
That's it!
We'll start studying from today on.
Makoto...
Makoto.
Translate this English paragraph.
There is no reason for
me to be here anymore...
Midori looked upset today, didn't she?
Her boyfriend broke up with her.
Really?
She started to go to cram school
and they couldn't see each other much...
...so they had a big fight.
I hate entrance examinations.
Are you listening to us?
Y-Yep.
I said I won't go!
But Mak, you look upset.
Stop calling me Mak.
Why should I go shopping with you?
I can tell something
bad happened to you.
I have nothing to do today,
so we should go shopping together.
I can give you my strength!
Shut up!
Don't pretend that you
know what's going on!
What do you know?
Mind your own business.
Nonoka just wanted Mak...
Shut up!
You're annoying.
Leave me alone!
Hey!
How can you be so mean?
She was worried about you.
Say sorry to her!
Tell me your worries.
I'm sorry.
I'll go shopping with you, so forgive me.
But only today, okay?
Okay!
I'll have the same, please.
Are you all right?
You said you didn't like to drink.
Takashiryou like to drink, so I want
to become strong and drink with you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thank you for hanging out with me.
Did you have fun?
We didn't talk a lot...
But, I really had fun!
Let's go.
I like you, Mak!
Nonoka...
I...
I knew it.
I knew you liked someone else.
But...
If I didn't tell you,
you would never know.
And I don't want to give up on you.
I'll see you home.
Why did you drink so much?
Thank you.
I'm okay...
Are you sure?
Une!
Makoto!
Who is he?
Do you know him?
Oh, Mak!
Wait, Mak!
Mak!
Wait!
I thought I didn't need,to do anything.
I thought she knew how I felt about
her even though I've never told her...
But that was just me being a coward.
Mak, Mak.
Nonoka has been with me...
Une...
How do you feel?
I'm going back home tonight...
But you're still drunk.
It's okay.
I'm all right.
Thank you.
Une!
Are you okay?
Isn't this...
T-That's not...
Are you hurt anywhere?
Well...
That is...
I see.
So that's it.
That's why you
looked depressed lately.
I haven't seen a doctor yet.
I'll take care of you.
C-Can I have the baby?
Of course...
I love you...
I'm making love with Nonoka,
which I couldn't do with Une.
Mak...
So good, Une...
So good...
Une...
What're you doing with him?
M-Mak...
No.
More.
Please, more.
Une...
I...
Mak...
Come inside...
W-Where is it?
Une...
I...
No, that's not it.
Mak...
Is this your first time?
Your penis is big.
Kind of...
Wow!
It's pulsing.
Mak...
I'm so happy!
Dammit!
The End