Can you keep going?
Y-Yeah...
I think so.
It's my turn this time...
I wonder who it is...
I'm home!
Mizuho!
Are you in the bath?
Se-Senpai... What should we do?
We have to hide for now!
H-Hide? Where?
Under here!
Mizuho!
Y-Yes! I'm coming!
Mizuho?
No one's here.
O-Oh, really?
I'll cook something for you soon,
so can you wait, Dad?
What's going to happen to me?
G-Got it...
Tomohisa-kun?
I'll be back soon, so please wait a bit.
~ Private Lesson of Angels ~
Thanks for waiting, Dad.
I made your favorite: ramen
with matsutake mushroom.
My long-awaited matsutake ramen!
Oh, it looks delicious! It's beautiful!
Bon appetit!
I was halfway through with my bath,
so I'll go and soak for a bit longer.
S-Sure.
Tomohisa-kun, are you okay?
Tomohisa-kun?
Sorry, are you feeling dizzy?
Come on out, I'll dry you off.
Face this way.
Sure.
Do you wanna continue where we left off?
It's so hot!
Maybe I'll get you to deep throat me.
We haven't done that in a while.
Se-Senpai...
Don't hold back, go for it.
You can thrust as much as you want.
Se-Senpai, your mouth feels great-!
Does it feel good?
Yes, but isn't it difficult on you?
It feels really good when it hits my throat.
Push it further inside of me.
Senpai's mouth is slimy and...
I-I don't think I can hold back...!
Let it out! Spray it deep into my throat!
I-I'm gonna cum!
Are you feeling better now, Tomohisa-kun?
Once more?
Mizuho!
When I'm finished eating,
I'm gonna join you in bath, so wait up!
Join you?!
Tomohisa-kun, hang on...
What?!
Yes!
I'm getting out now.
Dad, you should soak on your own. Okay?
What? I was going to wash your back...
Next time, then!
This kind of outfit won't work!
It's better than going out naked, isn't it?
Then how should I escape?
Can you fit through here?
It might be a bit tight, but try your best!
Yes...
Then I shall try my best
to fit into that tight spot.
Huh?
To-Tomohisa-kun?
Right now?
No-!
A-Amazing! It's so hot!
You're still hot from the bath, huh?
You can do anything you want...
Amazing! It's so big!
So big!
Please don't make too much noise...
B-But you're doing it so roughly!
It feels so good!
I-It's-! It's reaching my deepest spots!
Amazing! You're squeezing me!
I'm gonna... Let it out like this...
You're getting hotter inside of me!
Let it out, let it out inside of me like this!
No, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum too!
To-Tomohisa-kun... Did it feel good?
Hey Mizuho, what's wrong?
What was that just now? What happened?
Mizuho...?
Geez! Don't be so mean!
You shouldn't harass a girl
who's going to the bathroom!
Close the door.
Oh, sorry.
Stringendo.
Huh?
I like Kondo?
We'll, that's the rumor.
Detective, actually...
B-Beef bowl! With mayonnaise!
I might remember if I eat something.
Sign: Broadcast room
We can make as much noise as
we want in the broadcast room.
Do me harder!
Thrust inside me until
you mess up my insides!
Miyazawa-san, Miyazawa-san!
Is that guy going to make me unhappy?
You gotta be kidding!
Miyazawa-san, you're so hot
down here. It's squeezing me!
C-Can you see?
Can you see where we're connected?
Y-Yes! I can!
Your hot cock it's-! It's,
It's entering me!
Your hard cock is entering my dirty spot!
Your cock feels great, Ono-kun!
Everyone's the same.
They just want sex.
I've had enough.
I'm sick of it!
If I pretend that I like it,
they're deceived easily enough...
Miyazawa-san! I'm gonna...!
N-Not inside!
Let your semen out inside my mouth!
S-Sorry, I didn't mean
to let it out like that...
You'll get caught instead of me?
Mi-Miyazawa-san...
I still can't believe something
like this is happening...
Hime-chan!
Good morning, Hime-chan!
Good morn!
Ami...
Mi-Miyazawa-san, shall we stop?
No, I'm fine!
Keep going!
Y-Yeah...
No! It's coming in!
His cock is entering me-!
It's hot, so hot!
Miyazawa-san, Mi-Miyazawa-san!
Miyazawa-san!
You're going out with Miyazawa-san?
R-Really?
You know, her pussy squeezes you so much!
It's great!
It's warm, and it sucks you right in!
No~!
It feels so good!
I'm getting more turned on!
Miyazawa-san, if you're too loud,
they'll hear us!
F-For some reason,
I'm getting more turned on!
I'm such a pervert.
S-Since you're so good, Ono-kun, I'm-!
Mi-Miyazawa-san, you're so warm!
It's like you're sucking me in!
Y-your cock-! It's so hot and hard!
Y-Your cock is hitting my deepest spots!
I'm gonna-!
N-Not inside, please!
Outside, release it outside!
I'm gonna cum too! I'm gonna cum,
I'm gonna cum!
No... my s-shorts are all sticky
because you came too much...
I'm sorry...
It's fine, I'm not angry.
Ono-kun...
Huh?
K-Kanda-kun would play with me every day...
I was so scared!
That bastard... He got what he deserved.
Mi-Miyazawa-san, you've done nothing wrong.
We should get back to class...
Ono-kun!
Huh?
I'll be waiting here during
the next break, okay?
...And apparently it was like that!
Isn't that funny?
Y-Yeah...
It sure was...
It's fine, you can do anything
you want to my butt and breasts...
So release your semen inside of me, okay?
Mi-Miyazawa-san!
Ono-kun... Are you listening?
Y-Yeah.
Were you... thinking about something perverted?
Ami-chan! Don't mind Ono, he doesn't talk much.
Hmm? I wonder what Mr.
Silent was thinking while he was looking at me?
Was it something like this?
H-Hey!
It's fine, everyone went back to class.
Because someone got my shorts dirty,
I'm not wearing anything beneath this.
Do you wanna go back to the classroom?
Or...
Ono-kun...
I'll be waiting here after school too...
Oh? Ono-kun!
Hime-chan...
Ami, what about club practice?
Club practice?
What good will that do?
W-What?
I'll be waiting after school...
You can let out a lot...
Hear me out, Hime-chan...
Ono-kun said that he'll
be caught instead of me!
Ono-kun said he wanted to date me.
He said that he liked me.
Isn't he just saying that
because he likes my body?
You want to date me because you want
to have sex with me, don't you?
It makes me laugh.
Oh! Ono-kun!
I was waiting for you!
Ono-kun?
Er, um, wait... Did you hear-?
O-Ono-kun...
Help me...
Help me-!
I don't want to be like you or Kanda.
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't group me together with such a person!
Hey, open up!
What was that broadcast earlier?!
Open up right now!
Hime-chan...
It's not opening...!
Damn it, is it broken?
Hi-Hime-chan...
Did you betray me?
Why? Why would you?
Aren't we friends?
You're like a crow.
Huh?
You're tainted black and you caw all day.
W-What do you mean...?
Ami... Let's wash it all off
and start again. Both of us.
I'll go with you!
Hime-chan...