~ Private Lesson of Angels ~
What?
T-Touru?
I-I'm sorry.
You didn't have to worry
about putting underwear on.
B-But...
Touru.
L-Look.
T-Tomoe?
Let's do it.
Tomoe...
I want to do it with you, Touru.
You're really hot down here, Touru.
K-Kirishima-san, are you
really okay with this movie?
I-It's fine! I like this actress.
I haven't really seen much of her work...
Maybe she's not very popular.
S-Shut up!
You're just here as my bodyguard,
so shut up and watch!
L-Lick my breasts...
Your dick is so hard!
Hey, this time, put it inside me...
I-I'm going to put it inside you, Tomoe...
N-No way! He really put
his cock inside of her...
Don't they normally just pretend?
I'm sorry that I'm such an indecent woman...
N-No, I can't. Tsuchiya will notice...!
W-What? Why is he so turned on from this?
D-Don't raise your voice!
Everyone will notice.
K-Kirishima-san-!
Y-You can't hold back
after watching this, can you?
I-I'm also... feeling good. It's in so deep-!
Really, we shouldn't
do these kinds of things here!
Even though you're so stiff here...
Did you perhaps predict
that this would happen?
Y-You did too?
T-That's right.
Can you tell?
My nipples are so stiff from this...
You're starting to like this, aren't you?
Your love juices are coming out.
It's dark in here, and there
aren't many people. We'll be fine.
No, I get too excited...
When I think of the fact that
we're doing this in public...
Maybe I'm a pervert.
If you do that so much-!
I'm...
I'm cumming again!
G-Geez! Say when you're
about to cum this much...
I-I'm sorry...
Geez.
I-I haven't cum yet!
So this time make sure that I do too.
Do whatever you like, Touru.
T-Tomoe!
Kirishima-san, do you really
want to do it here?
D-Don't move around so much, Tsuchiya.
It's dark, so I can't see very well...
It's in-!
It went in!
Kirishima-san, don't
raise your voice so much!
Thrust inside of me!
It's embarrassing for me
to be the only one moving!
It's so good! It's reaching
my deepest spots!
Thrust harder!
Kirishima-san, your voice
is more erotic than usual.
I-Idiot! Don't say such weird things!
It's embarrassing!
Could it be that you get excited when
you think that someone might be watching?
N-No! I'm not perverted like that-!
I'm just sensitive!
No-!
N-No, they'll find us...
Everyone can see me in this position-!
But... you're really squeezing me down there!
D-Don't look at me like that!
This is too perverted!
Kirishima-san, does it feel good?
Your dick is rubbing against my insides-!
It looks like they're about to finish, too!
Not yet!
Please-!
Let's cum together!
The movie's gonna finish!
Hurry up and make us cum!
Just a bit longer-!
No! Don't do it so hard!
N-Not so hard!
Kirishima-san!
C-Can I cum inside of you?!
Even if I say no, you'll do it anyway-!
Just hurry up and cum!
I'm cumming-!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Huh?
W-Wait... Huh?
N-No way...
This is actually real...
She sure is nice!
Awesome.
Looks like he came inside.
It's dribbling out!
So cute...
Hey, you guys!
What are you looking at?!
Stringendo.
One day during the summer holiday,
Mikura-san and I had to clean the pool.
We were found having sex in the infirmary,
so this is our punishment.
I'm sorry for running late, Endo-kun!
Mikura-san.
I was up late since it's the summer holiday.
It's hard get up so early in the morning.
I'll help you now, though.
Huh? What's wrong?
N-Nothing, ummm...
Geez, you really are pervert.
It's so hot.
I can't stand it...
Huh? W-Wait!
I bet you were expecting
something like this, right?
B-But, you shouldn't. Not here...
Clubs are practicing as well...
It's fine. If we stay here in the pool,
they won't see us.
B-But...
Huh?
You don't want to do it with me?
Endo-kun, you're really hot.
I-If you do it so roughly...
How about I clean here, too?
N-No, that's...
Endo-kun, you're so stiff here.
D-Don't sniff it too much.
I'm sweaty and it's dirty...
It's not dirty, Endo-kun.
But it sure emits a strong scent!
M-Mikura-san, it feels too good.
I'm going to cum-!
D-Don't cum yet, please! Do it to me first!
I-I want you to do it from behind.
I'm already soaking here, so thrust it in!
You're right, you really are wet.
How perverted of you, Mikura-san.
D-Don't say such things.
It's embarrassing...
Here I go.
My dick went all the way in!
Y-You're moaning too loudly!
Someone will hear us!
E-Even if you say so-!
S-So deep!
Mikura-san, has anyone seen us?
Can you see from there?
I-I don't know-!
E-Endo-kun, y-you're hitting me really deeply!
M-Mikura-san, I-I'm gonna...!
Your cock is quivering!
Let out a lot! Let it out inside of me!
E-Endo-kun, did it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
Mikura-san, do you like it when
people might be watching?
Huh?
I-I don't think so...
Your dick is still so big, Endo-kun.
Shall we do it again?
Okay, okay?
Hey, hey. Mikura-san and Endo-kun
are cleaning the pool today, right?
We have to hide quickly!
Why are those two cleaning?
They're not swimming club members, are they?
What? You don't know?
Those two...
What? What?
Eh?!
Seriously?
I wanna do it too!
I-It's really cramped in here.
Y-Yeah.
You still want to do it?
Y-Your hard cock is prodding me....
Hey, wait!
I might moan too loudly
if you put it in now!
B-But... It's cramped and I can't move...
W-Wait, do it with my mouth.
Your cock tastes like semen.
Mikura-san, you don't have
to lick it that much-!
If you do it so much, I might cum!
Are you about to cum?
I want you to put it in now...
I'll hold it tight, so hold
on for a bit longer, okay?
It's quivering...
I can't hold back-!
Huh? What was that?
W-Who knows...
The head of your cock is stuck
inside of me! I-It feels great!
It's so hot and narrow inside of you.
I'm gonna...
N-No!
Let me cum too!
So good-!
T-This is amazing!
It's rubbing against my deepest spots!
Mikura-san, I...
Are you about to let it out?
Are you gonna cum?
It's fine-!
B-But... Your hand is clutching it,
so I can't-!
It's coming out,
it's coming, but... it's not coming.
Your balls are quivering too!
A-Amazing-!
Amazing!
He's hitting my deepest spots! I'll break!
I'm gonna let go-!
I'm gonna let go, so let it all out!
Fill me up with your semen!
You sure let out a lot...