At the far end of the continent
is a small nation named Avon.
Due to misgovernment of the previous ruler Ragnard,
the domain fell into ruin and the economy collapsed.
The people are emigrating.
Our nation is in grave crisis.
I wonder what the princess is planning
to do, gathering everyone here.
I don't know. She seems to be
brooding over something.
People of our dear nation...
I, Ariadne upon Avon
have thought up of a way to save this nation
as a newly seated princess.
From now on, our nation of Avon
will pour all our efforts into the
establishment of the sex industry.
Huh? S-Sex industry?
Our nation is empty.
It doesn't have any life in it at all.
We don't have a choice, seeing
the current state of our country.
It might be through an unscrupulous industry,
but we have a way to survive!
Whoa... She said "unscrupulous" herself...
Your royal highness, I understand how you feel...
But to have a sex industry means that we'll need
to provide prostitutes who'll work there...
I'm well aware of that.
I already have strengthened my resolve...
If it is for the sake of this nation's revival, I-I'll also...
...work to the utmost of my strength as a prostitute!
The Making Of A Wonderful Nation
Thank you for waiting.
Oh!?
I am here today at your service.
I am Ruruka.
H-How sexy!
The personal maid of the princess
is wearing such an outfit!
These aren't my kind of clothes,
but the princess told me to wear these regardless...
No, no... Well...
They're so lewd and they look good on you...
I have a small chest, so this kind
of attire is embarrassing.
Oh?
Our dear customer...
Whoa!
I still haven't done anything to you
but you already got so hard.
D-Don't suddenly do that!
But you don't really hate this, right?
Your dick is throbbing so much and it's loving this.
That's because...
Yes... Oh!
I-If you keep rubbing that part...
W-Wait...
It's coming out! I'm coming!
No...
I'm sorry!
I-It just felt so good, so...
That's okay.
You can come as many times as you want
as long as it's within the allotted time.
Wow...
It's hot, hard, and still oozing out!
It's slimy and sticky...
Ruruka-san, don't do it so hard!
I just came...
It smells lewd!
I'll suck all of your semen out, dear customer!
You're sucking me... Wow, your
cheek walls are sticking to me!
Even though his dick just ejaculated,
it's starting to get bigger again.
Ahh... You're sucking me! This is incredible!
Ruruka-san... I-If you suck me that hard, I'll...
That's okay...
This time, I will...
...catch it with my mouth!
Yes...
Wow, you're sucking me dry!
Your mouth feels warm and soft...
Dear customer, your dick is still very lively!
H-Hey... No way...
Any more of this will be...
Huh?
Then, how about this?
Th-That's... That part would be...
Your dick is starting to get harder and bigger...
This part is squeezing my finger tightly as well!
I-I'm feeling so good again!
You're getting off from having your ass teased...
You really are a pervert, dear customer!
Th-That's because I never felt like this before!
Your body is twitching and your hips
are moving on their own, you know?
Ruruka-san!
Don't you want to shoot it out?
Don't you want to ejaculate from me servicing you?
Am I right?
Y-Yes, I want to come!
I want to spray you with semen just like this!
Yes, you don't have to hold back.
Shoot it on my face with all your might!
Coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming!
That would be enough for today.
Dear customer, thank you for your patronage.
That felt so great! I'll be requesting for you again!
Yes, I will be waiting!
The Making Of A Wonderful Nation
Thank you for selecting me.
I am Yushia.
Oh... This is incredible...
Want to strip me yourself?
For real!?
It's okay, I'll end up naked anyway.
Th-Then...
I won't be holding back...
Ahh!
D-Damn!
Wow! They're soft and smooth!
Well then, shall we enjoy
ourselves together with a bath?
I'll be giving you plenty of service today.
Okay...
I'll rub my body against yours
to make you clean.
Yushia-chan, the way you move
your hips is erotic as hell!
Doing this is kind of making me feel good as well...
Isn't being an adventurer your main job?
Why are you well-versed with hooker plays like this?
That's a secret.
Adventurers roam around the world,
so we end up learning various stuff.
Damn, that's crazy!
How is it? Are you feeling good, dear customer?
Your tits are rubbing me... Your hard
nipples are grinding against me...
That's right. The slippery lotion
is making me feel good too!
M-My nipples got so stiff!
Y-Yes! Yushia-chan!
Your thing down here became so hard.
This is seriously out of this world!
I want to put my cock down there
inside you, Yushia-chan!
I understand. Alright, then...
Shall we do it?
This is Yushia-chan's...
Wow!
You're amazing!
Damn... My hips! They won't stop!
That's okay... You can do as you please...
Your dick keeps on reaching deep inside me!
You're messing my naughty tits up!
Yushia-chan, you're damn amazing! You're so sexy!
That's right. I want you to go harder on me.
Please ram it a lot more into me! Oh!
D-Dear customer, shoot it! Please shoot it out!
If you squeeze me that hard...
I want it even harder!
I'm already...
Dear customer, thank you for ejaculating a lot.
That felt so incredible...
I'll be sure to come back here
when I saved up too much semen.
It would be my pleasure. I'll be looking
forward to it while waiting.
The Making Of A Wonderful Nation
I'll be under your care for today.
I am Avon's princess...
I'm Ariadne.
Whoa!
It's a real princess, and in a very
lewd outfit on top of that!
Was "intercrural course" what
you ordered, dear customer?
Y-Yes!
Then, umm... I'll be taking my clothes off.
I-I'm touched!
The princess is doing this for me!
Uhh... P-Please...
Please don't stare too much...
It's embarrassing...
Th-This is a man's...
It's so hot...
Y-Your highness?
It's gradually getting hard and big.
This thing will be grinding
against me down there, right?
Th-That's right.
It's my first time doing stuff like this.
I don't know if I'll be able to do a good job.
I can feel how hot you are down there.
Wow! Yes... That feels great...
Am I doing fine? Am I not hurting you?
Yes, it feels good... It feels good!
Here... Like this?
Your thing is getting bigger and harder!
I'm sorry.
Your pussy feels so soft, warm, and good...
I love this so much that I can't help it! This feels so good!
So this is what intercrural is. It feels so tingly.
That's good, your highness.
You're sopping wet down there!
No... Don't say that!
I'm starting to feel strange.
D-Dear customer, if you go that rough on me...
I'm sorry! This feels so good
that I can't stop myself!
You're so soft down there and it feels too good...
The lotion made your dick slippery.
If this goes on...
It's going in! It really is going inside!
Y-Your highness...
It's going deep inside me.
I'm begging you! Just a little longer...
I'm gonna come soon!
P-Please pull it out!
You can't! Pull it out! No, don't!
Y-You can't!
It's because your pussy feels so hot and gooey!
N-No! D-Don't!
That's why I couldn't hold myself back!
Let me go... If you keep doing any
more than this to me, I'm...
Your highness, aren't you feeling good as well?
Your pussy twitches and it's squishy!
No! No!
Don't say that.
Why... Why?
Y-Your highness, I'm begging you!
Please come with me at the same time!
Ah! Don't!
S-Something's coming... It's coming... No!
No! No! I can't!
I'm gonna come! I'm gonna come!
No! I can't!
Y-Your highness, I'm really sorry!
I-I'll pay a special fee for forcing myself upon you!
D-Don't ever tell anyone about
what happened today, alright?
A-Absolutely!
Please also make sure to come back here
and request for me as your partner.
Huh?
That's a promise.
You're the only one that I'll specially allow
to do such a thing, dear customer.
O-Okay!
Thank you for coming!
A SakuraCircle Project / Translated by: Tennouji