Lidi, stop this already!
No!
Giving up already?
I'm still hungry!
I can't come. I can't come anymore!
Try to do better in your dreams at least.
A very cute succubus like me
will suck your semen everyday.
Wait for it, I'm digging in!
It's a tight fit today as well!
Kaito, your semen is delicious!
I won't get tired of drinking it everyday!
T-This is bad!
If you suddenly do it rough—
Amazing! Amazing!
Your amazing semen is gonna come out!
Shoot it, shoot it out!
Coming! I can't take it, I'm coming!
Lidi!
Here it comes!
There's so much extraordinary semen!
Yoohoo! Good morning, Kaito!
She's always intruding in someone else's dream,
and taking away my freedom!
Succuba Mist Story
And? That childhood friend succubus classmate
is squeezing you dry of semen in a dream everyday?
Yes.
She is Melusine-sensei.
She's someone like a school nurse,
in charge of Medical Studies as well.
She has an ability to grant wishes.
But...
My wish is, to be able to get even with her!
But in return for a request,
I need to give her semen.
I'll grant your wish.
Yes.
There, all done!
It's nice to be young!
Wait for me, Kaito!
I'm hungry!
I'll indulge myself on your yummy semen today as well...
It's not always you who will have
an advantage in the dream world!
So today, I will...
This can't be!
How...
How can you fight back?
Kaito, you're an idiot!
Sigh, I couldn't suck out
his semen, It's so annoying!
What's wrong with him?!
Everything worked out!
Is that Kaito's voice?
[Medical Department Preparation Room]
That means your wish has been granted, right?
I see...
Of course, that's the way it is, Kaito.
Give it to me.
I-I can't.
I already have...
He gave it to sensei.
His semen.
He hated me that much.
I don't care anymore!
Even I can—
Lidi! What are you doing?
Oh, Kaito. Why are you here?
Why would you do such a thing?
Huh?! And why would you care?
I'm a succubus.
If I want to suck some semen,
I can get it from any guy!
Forgive me.
This misunderstanding is my fault.
I'm gonna be straightforward.
I am...
in love with you, Lidi!
I don't want you sucking any other man's semen!
Kaito...
It's nice to be young!
Sensei?!
Go in the Medical Dept.
Prep Room for the time being.
Let me take care of everything here.
I love you, Lidi.
I lovey-dovey you!
I love you!
Lidi!
Kaito!
You're way harder than inside the dream.
I wonder why?
T-That's because...
It feels very different from the dreams.
Looks like you're all ready to go.
I want to put it inside, Lidi!
Okay, then.
I'll be on the top today.
You always take the lead,
but now I'm not letting you dominate me!
Oh my...
He's so cool!
So tight! Isn't she tighter than in the dreams!
Lidi!
Your dick is so hot!
Today, I'll let you suck my semen out!
S-Suck it out!
Hearing those words
from you makes me happy!
That's so rough!
You're being rough, Kaito!
The truth is, I'm so hurt earlier.
Seeing you trying to get semen from other men...
It's unforgivable!
That's because...
you're doing it with sensei...
You're wrong!
It's true that I gave my semen to sensei.
I apologize for that.
But even so,
I love you.
I wanted to make you feel good instead,
so wished for us to get along together.
I'm sorry.
Lidi, I love you.
Sorry...
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
I love you.
I love you, Kaito!
Lidi...
Make me feel good so much!
Not my tail! I'm really sensitive there!
Well, well, Lidi. Are you not used
to being the one assaulted?
That's not—
No!
Amazing, it's so deep!
It's hitting me deep!
Our roles have always been the opposite.
You never let me do what I want!
D-Don't!
Not there!
Don't lick me there.
That's my weak spot!
From now on,
I'll be attacking you on all
the spots I couldn't in the past!
I am the one... being assaulted!
I am a succubus, yet...
I'm being intoxicated on ecstasy!
Here, I'm gonna come inside!
Take all of it!
Your dick is twitching!
It's burning!
I'm coming too! I'm gonna come!
It's flowing inside me! Kaito's semen!
So much is pouring in!
L-Lidi...
Kaito...
Did you properly sucked my semen?
Yeah, but...
I want more of it.
Kaito!
Isn't that great?
It really is nice to be young.
S-Sensei, since when did you arrive?
There are several of them so
I had to make each one come.
It took some time.
Before that, sensei...
What's with that thing?
Well then, I'd rather not get in your way but,
Lidi-chan.
After getting people involved
and causing a commotion,
next thing you're flirting with someone.
Are you properly
reflecting on your actions?
O-Of course I do!
It doesn't look like so.
But since you're so adorable,
I'll let this go if you'll undergo my punishment.
Not that hole!
I never did it there yet.
Here, pardon my intrusion!
Can you suck semen from this hole too?
I don't know!
I never tried it before, I don't know!
No, no... No!
Stop... moving!
Your pussy got so tight!
No, not my asshole!
Hey, start moving too, Kaito!
Okay.
I-Inside...
Your dicks are both wriggling inside me!
So deep!
F-Feels so great!
It feels great!
I'm feeling them inside!
T-They're rubbing against each other...
N-No good!
I'm feeling very good!
Coming... Coming!
I'm coming!
I'm coming, I'm really coming!
It's wrapping me tight! I'm being squeezed!
I-I can't anymore!
I'm really...
Lidi... Lidi!
I'm coming! Coming, coming, coming!
Having an orgasm in your first anal,
just as expected from a succubus.
I'm coming, I'm still coming...
Lidi... I'm already at my limit!
No! No more!
No more!
No!
Too much! There's so much pouring in me!
Kaito, from now on I will take
your health into consideration
when squeezing you out, okay?
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Translated by: Tennouji
A SakuraCircle Project