Lilly...
Stop!
What? You're giving up already?!
I'm just getting started though.
I can't cum anymore! I really can't!
This is a dream, so try harder.
You're getting to have a super cute succubus
like me suck out your cum every day.
I've been waiting for this.
Let's dig in!
It's a perfect fit today as well!
I love the taste of your cum, Kaito!
I don't get tired of it no matter how many times I eat it.
Seriously, this is bad.
You can't just...
You can't be so rough all of a sudden or else...
Wow. It's going so deep!
I can tell that you're about to shoot some amazing cum!
Cum!
Cum!!
I'm cumming! This is bad! This is bad!
Lilly!
It's here!
There's so much of your cum gushing out inside me!!
Heyo!
Morning, Kaito!
She always forces her way into my dreams
and plays around with me against my will!
Succubus Mist Story
Succubus mist story.
So you're saying that the little succubus who's not
only your childhood friend, but your classmate...
She's sucking out your semen night
after night without your consent?
Y-Yes.
She's Merjine-sensei.
She's the instructor of defense and also
the person in charge of medicines here.
And she has an ability that lets
her grant the wishes of others.
But...
What I want to do is get revenge on that damn succubus!
But apparently, I have to give over
some of my semen as payment...
But that's okay, right?
Yes.
Alright, all done.
It's nice to be young.
Wait up!
Kaito!
I'm starving!
I'm going to feast on your yummy cum today as well...
The dreamworld isn't a paradise for you succubi!
So today, I'm gonna...
No way! What's going on?!
How can he fight back?!
Kaito, you big dummy!
Geez, I'm cranky because I couldn't have sex.
What the heck was his problem?!
I-It went perfectly!
Was that Kaito's voice?
So your wish was granted then, correct?
Oh...
I see, so that's how it is.
Kaito...
Wanna do it?
N-No, I have a...
His semen...
He gave it to her!
You hated it that much, huh?
Fine!
Just watch!
Lilly?! What are you doing?!
Oh, Kaito? What is it now?
Why are you doing this?
Huh?!
Why do you care?!
I'm... a succubus.
I just want semen, I don't care whose it is!
Sorry.
I really misled you there.
Let me set you straight.
I...
I'm in love with you Lilly!
I don't want you sucking out other guys' semen!
Kaito...
It's so nice to be young.
Sensei?!
For the time being, why don't you
come to the medicine prep room?
I'll take care of the rest from here.
I love you, Lilly.
I love you too!
I love you so much!
Lilly...
Kaito...
Kaito!
It's even harder than it is in your dreams.
What's wrong?
I-It's because this feels totally different
than what I'm used to.
So you're already up and ready to go, huh?
I want to put it in, Lilly!
Okay, sure.
Then...
I'm on top today.
Up until now, you've been able to
have your way with me, but...
I'm turning the tables from now on!
Oh wow, Kaito's so cool right now!
It's so tight!
You're even tighter than you are in my dreams!
Lilly!
Your dick... it's so hot!
Today's the day that I make you take in my semen.
Come on, you can suck it all up!
I never thought I'd hear those words from you!
I'm so happy!
You're being so rough!
You're so rough, Kaito!
I was actually really jealous when
I saw you with all those guys.
I couldn't believe that you would try
to suck out another guys' cum!
I won't forgive you!
But...
Kaito...
You were with sensei...
No!
It's true that I gave her my semen.
And I apologize for that.
But I didn't have a choice.
I was willing to do anything because I love you!
I wanted to make you feel good so badly.
So I asked her to grant my wish.
I'm sorry.
Lilly...
I love you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I won't...
I won't do it anymore.
I love you.
I love you, Kaito!
Lilly!
Make me feel really good!
Not my tail...
It's...
It's really sensitive!
So, Lilly?
You're not used to being on the
receiving end of this, are you?
That's not...
Wow, it's going all the way in!
It's coming so deep!
Our positions have always been reversed after all.
You never let me do what I wanted.
S-Stop!
Th-That's sensitive too!
Don't lick it!
I'm really weak there!
I'm gonna repay you with all the times you've
played with me and mess you up good!
I'm the one being played with right now...
I'm a succubus, but you're the one doing the fucking.
You're making me so hot for you!
Okay, I'm gonna cum inside!
Take my cum!
Your dick's twitching!
It's getting hotter!
I'm about to cum!
I'm gonna cum!!
It's coming out!
So much... So much of your cum
is pouring out inside of me!!
Lilly...
Kaito...
Did you absorb the semen?
Yeah.
But I want more! I want so much more!
Kaito!
That's great. Being young really is great.
S-Sensei?!
When did you get here?!
There were a lot of guys out there so
it took a while to get them all off.
More importantly, sensei... that thing...
What is that?
Well, I'm sorry to bother you in
the middle of your fun, but...
Lilly-chan?
You involved so many people in your silly games.
And then you went off to have fun by yourself.
Are you really reflecting on your actions?
I-I know what I did!
Doesn't look like you do.
But because you're so cute, I'll
let you off the hook this time.
No, not that hole!
I've never done it there!
Sorry, coming in.
I wonder if this hole can absorb cum too?
I don't know!
I've never done it before, so I-I don't know!
No! No!!
Stop moving!
You're getting so tight!
No! My ass...
Come on, Kaito-kun, you should move too!
R-Right.
You're really moving two of those things inside me at once?!
It's good! It feels so good!
I'm getting so turned on!
They're rubbing... They're rubbing so hard against me!
Th-This isn't good!
It feels so amazing!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
I'm gonna cum!
No!
I'm cumming!!
I just came, but...
I'm really... I'm really...
Lilly! Lilly!!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
Cumming from your first anal? That's a succubus for you.
I'm cumming... I'm already cumming, but...
Lilly, I'm already at my limit!
No! No more!
I...
I can't...
There's... There's so much cum flooding into me!
Kaito? From now on, I'll always think about your stamina
before I try to suck out your semen, okay?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч