SubDESU-H.net
Hey, are you seriously asleep?
So it really worked?
Well, this means that the nuisance is gone...
Today, at last...
No more...
Yes!
Is this what I think it is...? Just because I'm always in your room...
Doesn't mean you have to drug me so you can watch porn, stupid bro.
And why did you put the whole pill in? That’s so obvious...
He really is such an idiot when it comes to this sort of thing.
Geez... he doesn't even know how I feel...
W
I love you I love you,
I love you
「One Step Ahead」&「Floating Sky」
I love you... I love you... I love you.
So... are you really asleep?
One
Step
Ahead...
He’s worried I’m faking? Fine.
How is this? This should be enough to get jerking off out of his mind.
Oh, how I love to see his uneasy face...
Slowly open my eyes a little... Okay, now let’s scare him.
Wh-What?! Is that a...?
This can't be happening! Wasn't he watching porn?
Don't rub it in my face...
It’s warm... wh-what?!
What are you...?
What is he doing...?
Could it be...?
Just as I thought!
No... don't start grinding with it... you idiot... pervert!
This feels... kinda... weird...
Okay.
Even this didn’t wake her up...
Then...
What? How far are you going to go?
Th-This is a pussy...
This is embarrassing even for me...
Don't stare with a straight face!
If you wanna do it... now's your chance...
Because once I open my eyes you won't be able to disobey me.
Ooh... don't get cocky...
Wow, it coils around your finger.
Shit, I can't stop!
Wait! Doing both boobs and crotch at once...
is bad...
Wait, not there...
Wow... it feels so good...
No... no... no no no!
If this carries on, my stupid brother will have his way with me...
No... I can't...
I can't give in. I have to endure it.
His face is too red...
Stupid brother, so persistent...
Stupid brother...
Eh? What?!
I'm about to cum...!
He's making me cum!
I've never...
Kissed anyone before...
I can't take it anymore... don't stare with such an anxious face.
Eh?
It can't be...!
This is bad!
No! It’s still all right!
It’s not like he knew I was awake all along...
That's right!
I just woke up right now.
That's right... really...
Lick it.
Wait! He closed my mouth!
He wants me to keep quiet!
But no matter how you look at it...
This looks like a brother forcing his sister into this.
After this he won't be able to disobey me!
Yes, it’s so easy to gain control of him!
Amazing!
It’s so wet...
I want to stick my dick in there...
Do what you want...
I see...
Then I'm gonna stop.
What?!
This is bad!
This reaction makes it so obvious that I want it!
Don’t make that face...
You want it, right?
No I don’t!
You know, I realized...
That you were awake from the start.
What did he just say?
No way... this is bad!
He knew I was awake!
My brother is inside!
You tried your best to look like you were asleep...
So cute...
I was testing how far you would let me go, but...
No way! No!
I didn't expect you to suck my dick, though.
He knows everything!
That's because you...
Forcefully...
Except you let me do it – you didn’t resist at all...
I have to act fast!
You're letting me do everything...
No!
I can't say anything!
You wanted it so much that you faked being asleep.
Idiot!
Impossible... how can I... lose to him... like this...?
Stupid brother...
Do you think it’s okay for siblings to do it?
Whether it is or not, I can't stop when I’ve gone this far...
What are you...?
Wow, he's hotter and harder than before!
Could it be because of me?
No!
Kissing is against the rules!
You like me more than you thought, don't you?
No!
Say it!
Go on.
I...
Love you.
That doesn’t exactly count as "saying" it, but...
Here's your reward.
No, don’t!
You have to cum inside for the finale, right?
No!
If you do it that hard...
I'll cum!
Cumming...
Me too!
I'm cumming, cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming...
Aww!
I never thought I would get fucked so much!
No... No... No!
It’s not that he fucked me - I let him do it!
What was that supposed to be?
Didn't you say you had a girlfriend?
Um... that was, well...
That was obviously a lie...
All my firsts were with you...
Even though I should be angry...
Thump Thump
Didn't you say you were popular in class? Even though that was your first time...
This release was done by SubDESU-H, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
Thump Thump
I'm a girl so I'd obviously give my first time to someone I love!
Eh? What?!
I'm gonna destroy you!
Stop it!
It’s always the greater lover who suffers the most...
W
I love you, I love you,
I love you!
I love you, I love you, I love you!
Mom!
Is bro back?
Not yet.
His bus should arrive soon.
I'm gonna go welcome him!
After being away at university in the city, I've finally returned home.
I only call once in a while...
And I haven't come back before now.
I left this place because I was trying to avoid love.
Because this place has...
Floating Sky
Exit
It hasn’t changed at all.
Bro!
I'm so glad I made it in time!
I ran all the way here.
And who are you, miss?
S-So mean!
Did you forget your little sister's face?!
I'm just kidding!
That's because the last time I saw you,
you were only this high.
Hey! How much time do you think has passed?
I never thought you'd get this big, Aki.
Look... I'm not a child any more.
Mom's waiting, so let’s go home.
I found my grown-up sister pretty attractive.
Today’s meal looks delicious.
I prepared it with mom.
A home cooked meal!
It's been a while.
What?!
Don't you have anyone to cook for you?
What's this all of a sudden...?
Don’t you have a girlfriend?
Well... it’s not that I don't have one.
Why can't you say it straight out?
Well? Do you plan on marrying her?
Anyway...
Please get married soon and don't make us worry too much.
I'll try...
Brother, are you getting married?
Um... well... no, I don't have any plans for that.
It’s just that mom is celebrating all by herself...
You’re lying...
Whenever you lie...
You always look away.
Would it have been better if I hadn’t come back?
Bro...
Is it okay if I sleep next to you?
He fell asleep.
I love you.
Bro!
Aki.
I always loved you.
And I got to see you at last.
And I can't stand knowing that you're going to be gone again.
Aki... you can't...
There's a line we can't cross.
He... touches... me...
There's a man who comes to see mom...
He's normally a nice guy, but...
He touches me sometimes...
He said he wanted to get in the bath with me.
But I can't tell anyone because mom looks so happy with him.
If this keeps on, I’m worried something will happen that I can’t take back...
I...
Wanted to give my first time to the person I loved...
Aki...
Aren't you scared?
No, I'm okay.
Bro.
Touch me all over.
Bro's fingers are churning me deep inside!
This is bad... I'm about to cum!
Wait... wait...!
I want to cum with your dick...
Is it really okay?
I want my first time to be with bro. No one else.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Ouch!
You want to stop?
No! I'm finally one with my brother! Please keep going!
Then just bear with it for a little while.
Are you okay?
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Come... come closer to me.
I can feel it. I can feel his penis throbbing inside me.
Oh yes! Bro, yes!
I can feel your thing deep inside me... going all the way to my uterus...
Bro!
If you move so much then... bro!
I can't hold on much longer!
Bro! This is bad!
Cum! Let it all out!
It’s okay, so please let it out!
But I... inside...?
Bro!
This is what she wanted.
All I did...
was grant that wish.
Bro...
Is she still sleeping?
If you're looking for mom, she went to work.
She won’t be back until the evening.
It’s only us two, right?
After this...
I won’t be able to make up excuses to justify my actions...
SubDESU-H.net
I went to watch the voice recording for this show.
Professional voice actors are awesome!
May 23rd, 2012 Okada Tsuu
Be sure to check out part two!
Ahaha!
Do I get to be
in the next episode?
Hahaha!
I went to watch the voice recording for this show.
Professional voice actors are awesome!
May 23rd, 2012 Okada Tsuu
Be sure to check out part two!
Ahaha!
Do I get to be
in the next episode?
Hahaha!