SubDESU-H.net
Kasumi, do you...
have someone that you like?
Onii-chan...
You already know...
... who I like.
Could it be... that Onii-chan likes me as well?
W
I love you I love you,
I love you
「Fabrications」&「Double Faced」
Now, open up and let me see it.
I-I can't just...
You can't?
Aren't you doing this for your brother's sake?
Take a look.
If this picture of you siblings get released in school,
his recommendation will instantly fly away.
I-Is this okay?
That’s right.
Stay like that for a while.
Why Kouji-kun? For what reason are you doing this?
You were my brother's kind and best friend.
No, no. Don't touch it too much.
Are you thinking about your brother every night?
Ah... or is your brother doing it for you?
No way!
Huh?
Could this be... your first time?
I see.
And I thought you were doing it with Seiichi-kun.
See, my fingers got in easily.
Have you been masturbating too much, Kasumi-chan?
No!
If I do this...
No, stop.
Don’t do that!
It's okay.
This will be pleasurable for you.
You're quite wet already Kasumi-chan,
from inside out.
Are you about to cum already?
No, no!
Is this what "feeling good" means?
Anymore of this...
... is beyond me!
So this was your first time having an orgasm too, eh?
That's cute.
No!
You don't want to kiss?
Then, I'll have you kiss this instead.
Kasumi-chan, you don't have to move.
Just stay right there.
Seiichi, you don’t think of Kasumi-chan in that way, do you?
No way. We're siblings...
Then, is it okay if I...
Ah, you didn't drink it properly.
Now your face and clothes are a mess.
Oh, well.
You're about to get more dirtier anyway.
Stop this...
So you do understand what is about to happen.
No way! No way!
I really can't!
No don't, not that...
Don’t worry. I got it covered.
Why is it not my brother here instead?
Onii-chan
Oh, it's from Seiichi.
Since we're doing this,
why don't we let him join too?
Hello?
No way, no way, no way.
What are you thinking?
Hello?!
Kasumi?
Thank goodness the call went through.
I thought you were ignoring me.
What's wrong, Kasumi?
Is the signal bad there?
Hey!
Now, if you don't talk soon,
he'll take notice.
Onii-chan...
Heard you at last.
You left home early this morning, right?
I didn't see you after that,
and I was worried.
Are you still pondering over what happened yesterday?
I'm not...
that upset...
about it...
Kasumi?
I was just...
A little afraid.
I can't moan at this time.
It hurts!
Hello? What happened?
So you're taking in his best friend's cock
while talking with him over the phone.
Hello? What's wrong, Kasumi?
Do you feel unwell or something?
I think I won't come to school today.
Are you okay?
Should I skip club activities and go straight home?
N-No!
I'll feel better in time.
Are you really okay?
Like I said...
Gonna end the call now...
Then I'll just leave it to Kouji.
He seems to be absent, too.
I'll let him check on you if he has time.
Onii-chan, you really have no clue that
this Kouji-kun is doing something like this to me.
Hello?
Kasumi?
Hello?!
Did she really hate it that much?
A message?
Battery ran out.
I'm going to sleep a bit,
so don’t worry.
I understand. Sleep tight then.
I'll be home as soon as possible.
Is what it says.
Isn’t that great, Kasumi-chan?
Your brother is such a thickhead.
He didn’t notice even after you moaned like that.
I already knew that he was dense,
but to such an extent...
Now I'm the one who's getting worried.
It's hard for you too, right?
There's no progress between you two,
and yet you're forced to have your first time like this.
Your body is awesome, Kasumi-chan.
Getting your pussy wet like this...
As if it's saying that my cock still isn't enough.
This is unfair.
It was already over, right?
No one said this was finished already.
Besides, I have yet to cum.
So it feels better than before, right?
Becoming a perverted girl like this,
I bet you won't be able to face your brother.
No! It feels good...
Seriously my body's getting hornier.
Could it be that you finally realized?
Eh? No way, no way, no way! Is that...?
Doing it raw is a whole lot better, right?
No don't, don't... use proper protection.
No, no!
There's no turning back now.
Can you feel it?
I'm hitting your innermost part.
I'm going to release a whole lot of it there.
No, this can't be. This can't be!
We don't know what will happen if you release it inside now.
Well, I still plan on releasing it even if you say no.
No! No!
No.
No!
Something warm is inside...
Seiichi, then is it okay for me to confess to Kasumi-chan?
Yeah.
What happened to you today?
Got a cold or something?
No, I just had something to do.
But I'm already done.
Then I need to ask you a favor.
Kasumi is not feeling well today and is currently resting at home.
Could you check on her for me?
Okay sure, just leave Kasumi-chan to me.
Sorry about that.
Don’t be.
We're childhood friends, ain't we?
Yeah, okay. See you then.
Kobayashi
Seiichi
Seiichi, it's all your fault.
You're the one who betrayed me first.
W
I love you, I love you,
I love you!
I love you, I love you, I love you!
After being away at a university in the city,
I have finally returned home after a couple of years.
I'm no longer a kid...
A-Aki...
Don't you have anyone to cook for you?
Well... it's not that I don’t have one, but...
Onii-chan, are you getting married?
Well... no, I don’t have any plans for that yet.
You are lying.
Whenever you lie, you always face away.
Onii-chan!
It's so intense.
Are going to do it to me?
Are you going to do it like that guy Mom's dating?
I want to at least do my first time with someone that I like.
Aki...
Aki!
Onii-chan.
No, I'm going to lose it!
I'm cumming!
We connected with each other... as if we were catching up on the lost time.
Fabrications
Is it good?
It's bad.
But we did not have much time to prepare.
Well, I don't care as long as it's palatable.
Is the taste okay for you? You haven't eaten anything, right?
As for me...
Hey, I'm still eating!
It feels good this way, right?
Yeah, it feels very good.
Doing something like that...
This one can't endure, can she?
I don't...
...want to endure at all!
Onii-chan!
Hurry!
Hurry!!
I never knew that you were this perverted.
I have to make up for the lost moments.
Aki!
You tease.
You're really perverted.
Onii-chan... amazing!
Wait, wait!
No, I can’t stop anymore.
I'm losing it.
Aki.
Aki!
I'll be cumming like this.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan!
No, I'll lose it.
Don't do it so aggressively.
It's wrapping me really tight.
No, no!
It’s tight!
This is bad.
Together...
Together!
It's wrapping me tight.
I can't hold it in. I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Aki!
It seems to have left a mark.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It didn't hurt.
Let's do it again when I get better.
What time is it?
Oh, no! Mom's going to be home any minute!
Quick, wear some clothes!
Aerate, aerate the room!
I'll try to slow Mom down.
Okay!
Welcome home, Mom!
Oh Aki. What's up with the excitement?
What's for dinner today?
That was really close.
Want to make it together?
Yes!
This is bad.
I'm just going to get a few things that I forgot in the classroom,
so you don’t have to come along.
I have nothing else to do myself anyway.
Is Mom working on a night shift later?
Yeah.
That's what she said.
But, it could be that she's going on a date or something.
Is it with that guy who she has been dating?
The man that you said tried to do something to you.
Yes.
I think you really need to tell Mom about this.
I'm fine, don't worry.
But...
I don't care about that anymore.
Because you're here with me.
That's all that matters.
Onii-chan, let's do it already.
I can’t make a fair judgment.
Is it some wound that I should not touch?
Or a fabrication that I can never really unravel?
Aki!
Sorry, I won't ask about it anymore.
You're already awake?
Yeah.
Coming home early morning, Mom?
Don't say it like that. I was on a night shift.
I still have to pay for Aki's schooling, you know. Gotta work hard.
Should I help out as well?
You don't need to worry about that.
Just focus on settling down and getting a wife.
'Kay.
It might be a little too early,
but do you want to eat breakfast?
Hey, Mom.
What is it?
What kind of person is the one that you’re going out with?
Eh?
Wait, where did that idea come from?
I can't possibly have such a person, you know.
No need to worry about me for now.
Really? Of course.
Why?
Why are you leaving without saying anything?
Sorry...
I need to go back due to an emergency work.
Onii-chan?
No, I don't want you to leave!
I need to go now.
Are you going to come back again?
I will.
That's a lie.
Onii-chan, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan!
So it was a lie after all.
Part of the reason why I easily accepted that lie,
was that I also wanted to do it with her.
Even if what Mom said was a lie...
No, I don’t care about the truth.
Even if I knew it, I would no longer be able to fix the time that I had with Aki.
Liar.
Onii-chan, I'm no longer a kid...
Onii-chan, are you getting married?
Onii-chan, I love you.
I want my first time to be with you.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan!
SubDESU-H.net