Hey,
does sex actually feel good?
Well it should if your guy is experienced.
Experienced, such as?
I don't know. Someone like Hashimoto, maybe?
Oh, that playboy?
– Hajimoto's not like that!
– Sex. People say it hurts or it feels good, but.
– Sex. People say it hurts or it feels good, but
everyone seems so engrossed in it.
Everyone's talking about him. They say he's
always having sex with other students.
I can't say I like that part of him, but
for someone to teach me, a virgin,
about sex as soon as possible
after all...
a playboy is just who I need.
Teach me about sex.
What's this?
Hashimoto's always cutting class, but Nishima too?
They're totally doing it! That Nishana's doing it!
Settle down, class.
My dick,
how do you like it?
This is my first time seeing one.
This looks different than it does in movies.
This is the dick that will take my virginity?
Virginity? You haven't had sex yet?
I haven't, so I wanted to try it.
What a waste.
If you don't have sex,
you're missing out on life.
I'll make you feel good,
so listen to what I say.
Of corse. Follow those who are experienced.
First of all, spread your legs,
and show me your pussy.
Like this?
What are you doing?
Just 5 minutes after we met♪
Fastest time ever♪
Now I'm going in there♪
Don't worry about it. Don't worry!
OK, here we go.
I'm putting it in.
Already?
What about foreplay or a condom?
What? Condoms hurt and don't
feel good, so I don't use them.
Condoms hurt?
Oh, I see. Since I'm a virgin, he doesn't
want to hurt me by using a condom.
Well, once I get used to it, I'll.
Virgin pussy feels so good!
He won't cum inside me.
I'm trusting him not to.
I'm popping your cherry.
Wow, that feels good!
I broke your hymen! The blood's making
it nice and slippery inside.
I thought a virgin would be a pain in the ass,
but doing it with a girl like you is just fine!
It doesn't hurt more than expected, but
It feels like he's being too rough. Is that because
this is my first time, and I'm too sensitive?
This is kind of a let down.
I-I'm cumming!
What is this feeling?
Is he cumming, inside me?
He's cumming! It's seeping into my womb!
I feel so full inside!
It hurt when he put his dick inside,
but I think I might like this feeling!
I really came a lot.
Come on, lick it.
Fellatio comes after sex?
You have to lick it clean. It's common sense.
This tastes strange.
So this is my blood and cum mixed together?
I wonder where it feels good to be licked.
I hope he teaches me.
How was your first time having sex?
At first it hurt, but it felt good after that.
You're good at this, aren't you, Hashimoto?
Nishina-chan. That's your name, right? You've
really gotten attached to me, haven't you?
Hey, hey, hey! You're taking my dick really well.
Nobody'd guess you were a virgin until just yesterday.
Does it feel good. Come on, say it.
Say you want me to cum inside you.
It'll feel even better if you do.
But if you cum inside me...
It's fine. You won't get pregnant that easily. Even
if you do, there are plenty of ways to handle it.
You should trust those who are experienced.
I understand.
Hashimoto-kun, cum inside me until you're satisfied!
I'll call you when I want to do this again.
Let's do this again, OK?
No message
He's doing it with other girls...
To him, I'm just one of his many girls.
It can't be helped.
Idiot.
It kind of hurts.
And sex with him really isn't anything special.
Is that just how sex is?
Don't people touch each other or kiss?
There's much more, right?
All he did was put it in and cum.
Sex with someone else
Please teach me how to do it
I live in District 3, Tsubasa subprovince. Kindly teach me how to have sex. Please contact me if you live close by. Specifically, I would like to learn fellatio and the like. My contact information is below.
Cancel       Submit
might feel completely different.
Nishina, this is no good.
Using dating sites at your age? And
what's with this description?
Just look at this.
Even though your account is frozen,
people keep messaging you.
Even though you look so tempting
I'm disappointed in you, Nishina.
To think you were so stupid and debauched!
How does this feel? With that blindfold, you should be able
to focus on my voice and the feeling of my fingers oh you.
Fellatio and what good sex really feels like...
Just as you wanted, I'll teach you all about them.
Alright, fellatio.
What a powerful smell.
First, you gently pull the foreskin back.
Then, the glans is where it's especially sensitive
so focus on that part, and squeeze your lips around it.
While stimulating the tip, lick the
underside with your tongue.
Even if it's difficult, push through it and keep going.
Your mouth is a cock-sucking precision machine!
Use your mouth-pussy and become a cum-sucking tool!
I'm going to cum. Don't spill.
Nishina, you're a fast learner when it comes to sex too.
These experiences of sex gave me a realization.
All guys have dicks and are looking
for a chance to cum inside girls.
I really liked you, Nishina.
Even though you're ordinary, you're vulnerable,
and you show off your lewd body.
But why'd you have to get raped by that kid?
Looks like I have to thoroughly teach
you a woman's pleasures.
Yes, yes! Why does that feel so good?
Sensei, quickly, put your dick inside me! I'm going crazy!
Sensei was very skilled.
An older man teasing me to his heart's content...
Compared to before, this pleasure
was completely different.
He stimulated my perfectly sensitive pussy.
The pleasure mixed with the feeling from just before.
And so I was thoroughly taught how adults have sex.
Damn, wait a sec. Wait!
Wow, you've gotten really good at this.
What, were you practicing on sausages or something?
Yes. I tried all kinds of sausage.
Hey, why won't you let me put it in today?
You always cum inside. If someone
finds out, you'd be in trouble.
It's fine.
You're so cute and sexy. It makes me want to.
You can't.
That's 250,000 yen.
Where there's money, there's money all right.
Even though taking this makes it more
likely my parents'll find out...
Well, that guy needs money right now, so...
It comes at a good time.
After I was thoroughly used to sex, I happened
upon this man in an alleyway.
He was right in the middle of raping someone.
Normally, I'd start running away, but
for some reason, it didn't bother me, and I saw
him as especially masculine and attractive.
Oh, you were awake. I brought some lunch so...
It's so...
It's so big. But I'm used to it now!
It's kind of early for this, but why don't we use my pussy?
It's so thick.
Black people's dicks are so big! They reach
all the places that normal penises don't!
The first time we had sex, all I could
think about was his dick.
Ever since then, I've been seeing him frequently. I've
been taking his sperm in exchange for money.
Yes! That's it! That's the dick I can't live without!
He doesn't understand Japanese.
But he seems to like the things I say.
Your dick's so big! It's stretching my pussy!
It feels so good!
And now talking dirty has started to arouse me!
You want to see my breasts? Go ahead.
I can't get enough of your dick, so
I'll even let you do this.
Nipple piercings are amazing, you know.
They always make my sensitive spots tingle.
I can't help but feel sexy all the time.
It's the same with tattoos.
Every time I look in a mirror, it reminds
me that I'm a guy's property.
This body isn't my own.
I need a guy to tease and to please me.
But it can't be helped, can it?
I want to feel even sexier!
I want to become a sexy, cute woman!
No matter what the cost!
I'm going to cum!
I can feel it! I know it's coming. I'm going to cum!
It's going to feel so good!
I can't go back from this wild sex!
I looked into this. Today is an extremely dangerous
day. I'm super likely to get pregnant from this!
But I'm doing it anyway!
I can't resist having sex with this guy's cock!
But there's no way you could understand that.
You don't understand Japanese.
There's nothing I could say that would get you to stop.
What should I do in a situation like this?!
He can't understand Japanese, so he can't understand me!
He's the kind of person who rapes people in alleyways!
He's thrusting deep inside me so forcefully!
This feels so good!
What do I do? If he cums this much inside me,
I'm going to have his baby!
She's not picking up.
Geez.
I told her to pick up the phone.
Hashimoto-kun.
Are you OK?
I wanted to ask you about something,
but are those injuries...
I'm fine.
Hey...
Go out with me.
I don't want to lose you.
All right.
Are you sure?
If you go out with a guy like me, there'll
be strange rumors about you.
Rumors?
Ha, rumors.
It's too late to worry.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч