Hey, do you think sex actually feels good?
If the guy knows what he's doing, sure.
Otherwise, probably not.
Does anybody know someone who does?
Not sure... Maybe someone like Hashimoto?
Oh, that hornball?
Sex...
Apparently it's either very painful or very pleasant,
but it seems like people get really into it.
I've heard that Hashimoto guy sleeps with
any girl in the school who'll agree to it.
It's hard to believe a guy like him exists, but...
If I'm looking for a quick experience
with sex, despite being a virgin...
It's better to ask a guy who likes to fool around.
Teach me about sex.
Oh? Hashimoto I'm not surprised about,
but Nishina's skipping class too?
They're definitely doing it.
I can't believe it. Nishina-san of all people!
Seriously, I can't believe it!
Hey, focus on class.
So, what do you think of my dick?
This is the first time I've seen
one up close and personal.
It's completely different to the ones
I've seen in books and videos.
So this is the dick that's gonna take my virginity?
You're a virgin?
So wait, this is your first time?
Yeah, that's why I wanted to find out what it was like.
You've been missing out.
Not having sex is a real shame.
I'll make you feel real good,
so listen to what I say, okay?
Sure. You're the one with the experience.
Right. First up, spread your legs and show me your pussy.
Like this?
What are you doing?
Don't sweat it.
Aite, I'm all good. I'm gonna put it in now.
You're putting it in already?
What about foreplay? What about a condom?
Why in the hell would I carry condoms around
when they just hurt and don't feel good at all?
Condoms hurt?
Oh, I see. He's trying to be nice because I'm a virgin?
Well, he has experience, so I guess it's fine.
Your virgin hole is so small!
He won't cum inside me.
I'll just leave everything to him.
Okay, I'm all the way in.
Damn, this feels so good.
Shit, you're so tight!
Everything feels good.
I thought doing it with virgins would suck,
but if it's with a girl like you, I couldn't care less.
It doesn't hurt as much as I thought it would,
but is it just because it's my first time that I feel
this sensitive or is he actually being rough?
This is honestly kind of disappointing.
I-I'm cumming!
Wait. What is this feeling?
Hold on. Is he ejaculating inside me?
His semen's flowing out inside my vagina
and it's being sucked into my womb.
Wow I feel so filled up.
It hurt a little when he put his dick inside me,
but this... might actually feel kinda good.
Whew, I came a lot.
Come on, hurry up and suck it already.
Fellatios come after sex?
It's a cleaning fellatio.
It's common knowledge.
What a strange taste.
Is this a mixture of my blood and love juices?
Where should I suck to make him feel good?
I wish he would tell me.
So how was your first time?
I heard that a girl's first time would hurt, but it felt good for me.
You really are good at this aren't you, Hashimoto-kun?
Nishina-chan, was it? You're my woman now.
Come on, keep it up!
Your pussy's swallowing my dick like it's nothing.
Hard to believe you were a virgin not too long ago.
Feel good?
Come on, you gotta say it yourself.
Tell me to cum inside you.
If you do, it'll feel even better.
But if you cum in me again...
Don't worry, you won't get pregnant that easily.
And even if you do, there are still ways to get around it.
You need to listen to the guy with experience, right?
Okay...
Keep cumming in me until you're satisfied, Hashimoto-kun!
I'll call you when I wanna do it, okay?
So keep your schedule open, you hear me?
No new calls
He's probably doing it with other girls right now.
To him, I'm probably just another girl.
Nothing I can do about that.
I'm so stupid.
I feel kinda tingly.
I'm getting the impression that
the sex we're having is really basic.
Was that the right way to do it?
I feel like there's more to sex,
like kissing and caressing each others's bodies...
All he did was put it in and cum.
But maybe if I change partners, I'll change as well.
Nishina, you can't do this.
You're looking for sex like this at your age?
The ad you put out is also really weird.
Look, even though your account's been frozen,
the emails just keep coming.
This kinda thing is irresistible to guys.
I'm so disappointed in you, Nishina.
I had no idea that you were
this stupid and horny of a student.
How's it feel?
Being blindfolded makes you focus
on my voice and my fingers, doesn't it?
I'm gonna teach you about fellatios,
and just how good sex can feel, just like you wanted.
Okay, here it is.
It has such a strong smell.
First, peel back the skin with your hands.
And then take just the tip into your mouth.
That's the most sensitive part.
Make sure to rub your tongue around all of it evenly.
Keep your lips firmly around it and
use your tongue to stimulate the glands.
You gotta stick it out and make it feel good,
no matter how uncomfortable it is.
Your mouth is only a tool for guys to dump their cum in.
Make your mouth become a tool that sucks out cum!
I'm cumming.
Don't spill a single drop, okay?
You really are a fast learner, Nishina.
My sex experience enlightened me to a certain truth.
All guys have a dick and they're
all looking for an opportunity
to put it in a girl's hole and shoot their genes inside.
Let me tell you something. I always liked you, Nishina.
You might be plain, but I liked you and your dirty body.
But then that kid got the jump on me.
But now I can really teach you about
the pleasures a woman can feel.
Oh my god, why? Why does this feel so good?
Sensei, please hurry.
Your dick...
Your dick... put it in!
I'm already loosened up!
Sensei was great at sex.
Having an older man make love to me however
he pleased was a type of pleasure that I've never felt.
He hit all the spots that made me feel pleasure perfectly
and helped me taste and get
accustomed to the ecstasy of it all.
And just like that, adult sex was drilled into me.
Holy shit. Wait a sec!
You serious? You've gotten so damn good.
What are you doing? Practicing with sausages?
Yep, with a lot of different sausages.
So why aren't we having sex today?
I'm on my period and you always cum inside me,
so I thought you'd get mad if you found out.
That's not a problem.
You're cute and hot, of course I'd be in the mood.
Not happening.
250,000 total.
I guess it's not too hard to make this much money.
Making this much is gonna make it harder
for me to hide it from my parents, but...
I guess now I have money to give him, so it all works out.
After I became accustomed to sex, I ran into this guy.
He was in the middle of raping someone.
Anyone's first instinct would've been to run away, but...
I was taken in by the fantasy of being raped
by a guy with an even bigger dick than I've ever seen.
You woke up?
I bought lunch, so eat...
You're being too rough...
You're so big. Morning wood, maybe?
But I'm pretty wet too!
How about we get to using this hole right now?
Oh, shit.
It's so big.
A black guy's dick really is beast-like.
It's reaching places that most dicks can't!
The first time I had sex with him,
I was completely enthralled by his dick.
After that, I became his girl on the
side while getting money in return.
I take in his insatiable lust.
Right there! Yes!
I can't bring myself to leave this dick!
We don't speak the same language.
But he seems to tike it when I try
my hardest to talk dirty to him.
Your huge dick is spreading me so wide...
This is amazing!
And when I do that,
I get turned on by the dirty things I say.
You wanna see my boobs?
Go ahead.
I can't get enough of your dick,
so I even let you do this to me.
Hey, having your nipples pierced feels really great.
The sensitive spots are always tingling.
The feeling of arousal never leaves my head!
These tattoos are the same.
Whenever I look at myself in the mirror,
it reminds me that I'm some guy's property.
This body's not mine anymore.
There's a guy out there who'll play
with my body however he wants!
But that's just how it is.
I want to have more sex, after all.
I want to become a cute and sexy girl!
I need to live up to my potential!
It's coming! It's coming!
I can tell!
You're gonna fill me with your irresponsible cum again!
It's definitely going to feel good!
Sex like this will definitely get me pregnant!
I looked it up.
Today's definitely not a safe day for me.
But I'm still having raw sex even though I shouldn't be!
I just can't resist having sex with this dick, so I came here!
It's not like you understand anyway.
We don't speak the same language, after all.
No matter what I say, there's no way you're gonna stop!
This is too good! I love this!
We don't understand each other
or even know each others's names.
He's a guy who rapes girls in alleys...
He's even giving me money to have sex with him,
but this just feels too good!
With all the cum he's shooting inside me,
I'm definitely going to get pregnant with his kid.
Nishina
Calling...
No luck, huh?
Christ, I told her to pick up the phone when I call.
Hashimoto-kun?
Are you okay?
I wanted to ask you something, but what happened to you?
Nothing really.
You... should go out with me.
I can't think of anyone else but you.
Sure.
Really?
If you go out with me, weird rumors about you might start.
Rumors, huh?
It's a little late for that.
This is my sexfriend, Nishina-chan!
She let me cum inside her for just 3.000 yen
(limited time deal) as long as I followed two rules!
1. Cumming inside as not allowed on any day but her safe days.
2. Don't tell Hashimoto lol
Any kind role play is okay! You can only cum inside her for this limited time so let's all have fun shouldn't I leave her!
хз, что тут, мелко и размыто, у HH ссылки сдохли, 720 версию брать негде :(...
translation: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: olynn
quality control: olynn
softsub: торрент иваниваныч