Hey...
does sex actually feel good?
Well, if the guy is not experienced, it won't?
Who would be experienced?
I don't know either.
Hashimoto maybe?
Oh, that playboy?
Hashimoto is not like that!
Sex. People say it hurts or feel good, but...
everyone seems to be
so engrossed in it.
The guy they're talking about...
Seems like he's always having sex with girls within our school.
A terrible guy, but...
For someone to teach me, a virgin, about sex as soon as possible...
afterall...
a playboy is just who I need.
Teach me about sex.
What the...
Hashimoto is not a surprise, but Nishina is skipping out as well?
They're doing it for sure!
That Nishina's doing it!
Settle down, class.
There...
My dick.
This is my first time seeing one.
Totally different than those in books and movies...
Is this the dick that will take my virginity?
Virginity? You've never done it?
Yeah. That's why I wanted to try it.
What a waste.
For not having sex, you're missing out on life.
I'll make you feel good,
so listen to what I say.
Of course. Follow those who are experienced.
For starters, spread them wider.
Show me your pussy.
Like this?
What are you doing?
Just 5 minutes after we met ♪
Fastest time ever ♪
Now I'm going in there ♪
Nothing to worry.
OK. Here we go.
I'm putting it in.
You're putting it in already?
What about foreplay or the condom?
Huh?
Comdoms hurt and don't feel good,
so I don't use them.
Condoms hurt?
I see... Since I'm a virgin, he doesn't want to hurt me by using a condom.
Well, since he's experienced, I'll...
Virgin pussy feels so good
I'll trust him not to cum inside.
There... you... go.
Wow, that feels good!
There goes your hymen. The blood's making it nice and slippery.
I thought a virgin would be a pain in the ass,
but doing it with a girl like you is just fine.
It doesn't hurt more than
I imagined it would, but...
...it feels rough. Is it because
it's my first time, I'm too sensitive?
It's kind of a let down.
I- I'm cumming!
What is this... feeling?
Is he cumming... inside?
His cum is seeping in and filling up my womb!
It's filled up so much!
It hurt when he put his dick inside,
but I think I might like this feeling!
I really came a lot.
There. Hurry up and lick it.
Is fellatio what you do after sex?
It's to clean it up. That's common sense.
What a strange taste.
Is this my blood and
his cum mixed together?
I wonder where it feel good to be licked at.
I hope he would teach me.
How was it? Your first sex?
At first it hurt, but it felt good after that.
You really are good at this,
aren't you, Hashimoto?
Nishina was it?
Seems like you're totally mine now.
There!
You're taking my dick really well!
Nobody would guess
you're a virgin until recently.
Does it feel good?
Come on, say it!
Say "Cum inside please".
It'll feel even better if you do.
But, if you cum inside me...
It's okay. You won't get pregnant that easily.
Even if you do, there are
lots of ways to handle it.
You have to follow the experienced one, right?
Got it.
Hashimoto, cum inside,
as much as you want!
I'll call you when I want to do this again.
Let's do this again, OK?
No messages
He must be doing it with other girls...
To him, I'm just one of his many girls.
Can't be helped I guess.
Idiot.
It kind of hurts.
Even so, sex with him seems awfully dull.
Is that just how sex is?
Don't you normally touch each other or kiss?
There's much more, right?
All he did was put it in and cum.
If I do it with a different guy...
would it feel different as well?
I live in district 3, Tsubasa subprovince.
Kindly teach me how to have sex.
Please contact me if you live close by.
Specifically, I'd like to learn fellatio
and the likes.
Below is my e-mail address.
Please teach me how to do it
Post
Cancel
Nishina, this isn't good you know.
For you to use a dating site at your age.
Seriously, what's with this post?
Just look at this.
Even though your account is frozen,
the replies won't stop coming.
Those men that keep coming shouldn't be seeing this.
What a disappointment, Nishina.
For you to be this stupid
and slutty of a student.
How is it?
With your sight blocked, you can just concentrate on my voice and the feeling of my fingers, right?
How to do fellatio and
what good sex really feels like...
as you wish, I'll teach you all about them.
Alright, fellatio.
What a powerful smell.4
First, gently pull the foreskin with your hand.
Then, the glans is where it's especially sensitive...
so focus on that part and
squeeze your lips around it.
While stimulating the tip,
lick the underside with your tongue.
Even if it's difficult, just
bear with it and keep going.
Your mouth is a cock-sucking machine!
With your mouth-pussy,
become  a cum-sucking tool!
I'm going to cum.
Don't spill the cum that came out.
Nishina, when it comes to sex,
you're a fast learner too.
These experiences with sex
gave me a realization.
No matter who, guys have dicks and are looking for a chance to cum inside girls.
You know... I liked you, Nishina.
Eventhough you're a plain girl,
you're showing off your lewd body like nothing.
But why'd you have to get raped by that brat?
Looks like I have to thoroughly teach you a woman's pleasures.
Oh yes! Why does that feel so good?
Teach, hurry up!
Your dick! Your dirty dick!
Put it in already! I'm going crazy!
Teacher was very skilled with sex.
An older man teasing me to his heart's content...
still feels completely different.
He stimulated my perfectly sensitive pussy...
The pleasures mixed with the feelings from just before.
That's how I was thoroughly taught of adult sex.
Shit. Slow it down.
Damn, you've gotten really good at this.
What, were you practicing on sausages or something?
Yeah. I tried all kinds of sausages.
Say, why won't you let me put in in today?
You always cum inside. If someone finds out, we'd be in trouble.
It's fine. You're just so cute and sexy, it makes me want to.
You can't.
250,000 yen, the full amount.
Where there's money, there's money alright.
Even though taking this will increase the risk of my parents finding out...
Well, I need to give him the money now, so...
the time is just right.
After I was completely used to sex, I met this guy in some back alley.
He was in the midde of raping someone.
Normally, I'd start running away, but...
I was fascinated by
the manly dick, hard from raping.
You were awake?
I brought some lunch, so-
It's so-
It's so big. But I'm already so wet!
Should we use this hole already?
It really is damn thick!
Black dicks... are so big!
They reach all the places
that normal dicks don't!
The first time I had sex with him, all I could think was this dick.
Since then I've become his woman,
taking care of his sexual urges in exchange for money.
Yes! This is it!
I can't get enough of this dick!
He don't get what I'm saying.
But he seems to like the things I say.
Your thick dick is stretching my pussy!
It feels so good.
And now talking dirty has started to arouse me.
You wanna see my boobs? Go ahead.
I can't get enough of your black dick already,
so I'll let you do this.
You know... nipple piercings are awesome.
They always make my sensitive spot tingles.
I can't stop feeling lewd all the time.
It's the same with the tattoos.
Every time I look in a mirror, it reminds me that I'm a guy's property,
this body isn't my own, and a guy is playing around with it all he wants.
But... it can't be helped.
I wanna be more lewd!
I wanna be a cute and sexy girl!
No matter what!
I'm going to cum!
I can feel it. He'll cum inside without any care!
It's gonna feel so good!
I can't go back from this wild sex!
I've looked into it.
Today is an extremely dangerous day.
I shouldn't let him cum inside!
But I can't resist having sex
with this dick, I might just let him.
But, you don't get it, do you?
Cause you don't get what I'm saying.
Of course, no matter what I say, you won't stop.
Holy shit!
What should I do?!
He don't get what I'm saying!
He's the kind of person
who rapes at back alley.
He's thrusting deep inside me so forcefully!
This feels so good!
What do I do? With this much cum
flowing inside, I'm going to have his baby!
She's not picking it up...
Geez, I've told her to pick up my calls.
Hashimoto...
You're okay?
I was going to ask for some advice,
but... those injuries...
It's nothing.
Hey...
go out with me.
You're the only one I don't want to lose.
Sure.
Are you sure?
If you go out with someone like me,
there will be weird rumors about you.
Rumors?
Rumors huh...
It's too late already.