Yu... Yuu-kun!?
Your sister is already in here you know.
What're you saying? Didn't we're also take a bath together yesterday?
Eh?
Here, do it the way you always do.
Yu... Yuu-kun.
"Do" what?
What's the matter? Didn't you always wash it with your breasts?
Is... Is that so?
That's right, It wouldn't be like this with Natsu-nee breasts.
Yes, the one who's gonna clean up Yuu-kun's penis will be me.
When I cum... you're going to get dirty from it.
It's alright, I'll rub it up till you can let it out.
It's not healthy if a boy like you doesn't ejaculate too often.
Come on, release it on your sister.
There.
Chiyo-nee...
Come on, release all of it for me.
I have to clean it up again.
Yuu-kun...
Yuu-kun, what're you making your sister do this time?
Until Green Creation Festival
Green Creation
Just like Chiyo-nee said.
Yuuta, you brought your umbrella?
Yeah.
It seems like it's going to be rain, you should bring your umbrella.
Ah... sure, thank you Chiyo-nee.
You haven't changed at all...
Oh!
Oh right, don't forget about what we're going to do this Sunday.
Ah?
Sure, I got that.
For sure, okay?
If you're not coming, then that person won't come either.
I don't really care about that...
If I just could watch soccer...
That's not the way it works!
Don't you know that we're trying to fix your sister-complex?
Mind your own business.
What are you two talking about?
Natsu-nee...
You're going to do something fun?
No... I was talking about inviting Yuuta to watch the soccer game.
Just the two of you?
N... No... with a few other people.
Hm?
With the other... girls too...
Hm...?
Well, that's alright.
My umbrella!?
Good job, little brother!
Hey, let's go home!
Wait for me!
No, my laundry!
It's already this late?
Yuu-kun... Chinatsu.
I'm home, Chiyo-nee.
Are you having a late night today?
I'll be home before dinner time.
Yuu-kun, I've left the laundry in the living room,
could you fold it for me?
Sure!
Okay, see you.
Take care~!
She said "for me", eh?
What's your problem?
You cheeky bastard.
Drop it, okay.
Yuu-kun, I wonder what he wants to eat today...
Even though she said it like that, Chiyo-nee is always so strict with me.
What's with this piece of cloth?
It wouldn't be Natsu-nee's thing...
Then it would be...
No way, that couldn't be~!
Tell me that this isn't yours, Chiyo-nee!
You-per-vert!
That's mine, you know?
If you want, I can give it to you.
Natsu-nee...
Let's stop doing something like this.
You're...
It's okay to touch me... do as you'd like...
You can be rough with me...
It's okay to let it out in my mouth.
You're not going to be satisfied just with this, are you?
Let's go all the way to the end today.
Natsu-nee.
Didn't I said that you can do as you'd like it?
Even things I don't normally like.
Hey.
Let's do it?
Let's stop this.
Would you have done this with Chiyo-nee?
Eh?
Natsu-nee...
Why're you making that face?
You're always happy to tease me all the time...
That's wrong!
You're always getting closer with Chiyo-nee,
now I don't know what to do.
Natsu-nee...
That's why...
Natsu-nee.
Gimme attention!
That's why I've been teasing you all this time~!
This worries me in many different ways...
Sorry... I'm so sorry, Yuuta.
Gimme attention!
The thing is...
I thought you hated me... but now that I know that's not true, I feel better..
You're up for this?
That's because you're so cute...
Don't you talk back to me.
If you talk back to me...
This happens~!
Natsu-nee, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Tease your sister a lot, take your revenge on me.
Yuuta...
My body is...
falling... apart~!
Make me fall apart...
Yuu-kun?
Yuu-kun... Chinatsu... what are you two doing?
Yuu-kun!
Yes!
I have something to talk to you about.
Chinatsu can go back to her room.
It's not true... Chiyo-nee is not being herself...
Chinatsu couldn't do something like this, right?
Wait, If you do something like that right now...
Do you like it?
Just leave it to your sister.
It's okay if you want to touch it.
Chiyo-nee!
Does it really feel that good?
Do you and Natsu-nee have a bad relationship?
What is that supposed to mean?
Me and Chinatsu just both like you very much.
Each of us just wants to keep you for herself.
I want to do it with Yuu-kun as well.
Yuu-kun's hard thing... is inside of me...
It's great, I'm so sensitive I can feel it!
Yuu-kun...
No... you're going to make your sister go crazy~!
Yuu-kun.
Yuu-kun~!
Yuu-kun?
I'm exhausted, but I still can do it.
He collapsed from folding the laundry and I found him with a bloody nose, did something happen before?
I might've kicked him a little...
But a little kick wouldn't have put him in this condition...
Is your head okay now?
It's alright.
Is that so? That's a relief.
If you don't go right now, you'll be late for the soccer game.
No way!
I'll be going now!
Take care!
He's really attached to you.
Is that how it looks? I thought that he was always playing around with you.
Is that so?
That's true.
Ever since he graduated from primary school,
he's always chasing you everywhere.
I'm done with the whites.
Thank you.
Chinatsu, what do you want to eat for today's dinner?
Hm... You never ask me that unless we're dining with Yuuta.
Of course I would.
He's really lucky to be loved by us, lucky bastard.
Even though that boy is leaving his sisters at home and having a date.
Date?
Didn't he say he was going to watch a soccer game with his friends?
Yuuta might not realize it, but it won't be over
after they watch the soccer game.
Then I won't forgive him for not bringing me with him.
Eh, what should I do!?
Thanks for the meal~!
Chiyo-nee?
Hm, Ah... please put the dishes in the sink.
Sure.
I beg you, didn't Chinatsu-san already give you permission?
No way, I'm gonna be late for the last train.
What are you two boys talking about!?
Let's go right away!
Chiyo-nee would be worried about me.
I'm trying to fix your sister complex.
Mind your own business.
Anyway I appreciate that it's a great opportunity, but...
You're so right-
You're telling secrets, aren't you!?
Well then, I'm sorry.
Eh, you're going home?
Hey... hey... I'm also here, right?
Heh~ that's boring!
It's already this late...
I'm home~
I'm so tired~
Huh?
Chiyo-nee!
Welcome home.
I... I'm home.
And then the goal finally came in the last minute,
then all people in the stadium were shouting together.
It was hard to leave the stadium after that goal.
It was good match, then?
Yes... yes... It was really great~
I'm glad.
I'm sorry for making you listen my story,
I guess it's already bedtime.
Ah... how about another cup of tea?
That's enough, thanks for the tea.
Is that so? Then, I shall sleep as well.
Fluff
Yuu-kun, have a good dream.
Why... Why're you sleeping with me!?
What's wrong with your sister sleeping with her little brother?
Even though you've grown up, for me you're still my cute little brother.
Is that so? Maybe it is...
You're weird, Yuu-kun.
The... then, good night.
Yes, good night.
I can't sleep at all.
Your back has gotten wider, hasn't it?
Chiyo-nee, what are you doing?
Yuu-kun, you're already asleep? I'm going to be lonely.
There's no way I could sleep like this!
Let me smell Yuu-kun's scent.
Chiyo-nee~
You're a bit sweaty.
Is this a dream? This must be a dream
You couldn't take a bath this late at night, could you?
If I touch it, I'm going to go crazy.
What are you doing, Chiyo-nee!?
No...
Yuu-kun, you've gotten like this?
Chi... Chiyo-nee...
You don't have to hold back, just let it out.
It's not good for your health you know.
Wait... st-stop...
What are you ashamed of?
Haven't you seen your own thing?
Yuu-kun... what a splendid thing you have.
That thing is...
I'm gonna cum...
I'm gonna cum... you're going to be covered with it, Chiyo-nee.
It's okay, as long as it's Yuu-kun.
But at a time like this...
At a time like this, I want you to let it out inside of me.
Bu... But...
Your onee-chan already said okay.
Okay?
Chiyo-nee!
Yuu-kun~!
Chiyo-nee...
Inside of Chiyo-nee.
Yes... Does it feel good, Yuu-kun?
I'm... having sex with Chiyo-nee!
Yuu... kun... Yuu-kun~!
You can't do it with other girls, okay?
You can't do it!
It's coming...
No, Yuu-kun~!!
Chiyo-nee!
Yuu-kun~!!!
There's a lot inside of me...
Yuu-kun.
Stand still, okay?
I'll clean it up for you.
Chiyo-nee...
Yes, It's all clean.
Chiyo-nee.
Yes, what's the matter?
Chiyo-nee, the truth is I'm...
I've always...
The thing...
is...
Listen to me, Yuu-kun.
If I didn't have the same feelings for you, then there's no way
I would do something like this.
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
Then shall we go together?
Sure!
What does this mean?
What's that?
Here you go, Yuu-kun.
Open your mouth~
Eh... It's embarrassing.
He's way more attached to Chiyo-nee!
Chiyo-nee?!
You're waking me up this way again...?
You do it almost everyday you know.
Good morning, Yuu-kun.
Let's do our best today, okay?
It's finally the day of the Green Creation Festival,
I'll go together with Chiyo-nee.
Green
Creation
Festival
Chiyo-nee...
Shall we go then!?
Eh!? Natsu-nee... No... I'm... going to be... with Chiyo-nee...
Stop blabbing and come with me!
Huff... I'm so tired~
I didn't end up getting to walk around with Chiyo-nee...
Good work for today, Master.
Chiyo-nee...
I'll be Yuu-kun's personal maid when we're at home.
Because I couldn't be with Yuu-kun today.
Right?
Onee-chan~!
Why're you crying, Yuu-kun?
But, those clothes?
I brought them home to have them washed.
I'll do whatever Yuu-kun wants, so tell me about it.
Is that so?
Then would it be okay to get it dirty before washing it, right?
Pervert.
Did you enjoy the cultural festival?
It was a bit lonely when I couldn't walk around with you, Chiyo-nee...
But with Natsu-nee... I somehow ended up having fun.
The last Green Creation Festival with Yuu-kun...
I wanted to walk around together with you too.
Chiyo-nee.
From now on... let's have fun, just for the two of us, okay?
Sure.
Chiyo-nee.
I love you.
Chiyo-nee really likes to suck on my penis, doesn't she?
That's because Yuu-kun's penis is tasty.
But today, I'm the one who's...
You can't do that. A maid's duty is...
to always obey her master, right?
Chiyo-nee!
Hm... ahhhh, you're hopeless.
What are you doing, Yuu-kun!?
I can do whatever I want, right?
That's not right, I'm the one who's going to do it.
Punishment is important for the Maid-san who talks back to her master.
Yuu... kun.
It's way harder than before!
This won't be good punishment for you.
Then... then, do it more intense.
Chiyo-nee!
Is it over?
Far from it.
No... It's still this hard...
Master... Master~!!!
Master...
Is the punishment already over?
Next time, I should put it inside here~
Sure, please punish me with my ass.
It's tight...
It's inside of my ass...
It's too tight...
I'll take it out after I cum.
Sto... Stop it please, master.
Chiyo-nee!
No~! You can't... you can't do this, master!
If you thrust that deep to my stomach, It's going to come out!
No, I can't hold it anymore~!
No, you can't... you can't do this.
You can't!
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
I want you...
to punish me more.
Eh~!?
Yuu-kun, move it... more... punish me more!
Chiyo-nee...
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Onee-chan...
Yuuta...
Asahi no ijou na biki
The morning of an abnormal beauty.
Hayaku oide to yondeiru kimi no koe
Your voice calls "Come down quickly!"
Kodomo no koro kara zutto
Your unchanged stance from childhood
Kawaranai sutansu na ima wa modokashi
Has me impatient right now
Hanicoumu you ni ukaberu
Your smile is just like a honeycomb
Egao ga totemo tamaranai no
It's something I can't bear.
Can't stop ai no SOS
Can't stop love's SOS
An unstoppable SOS
Tomaranai SOS
Kimi ga nozomu nara donna watashi ni mo naru
If it's what you're aiming for, I'll become whichever "me."
Suki nante SOS
This is love, SOS
Sasayaide SOS
Whisper it, SOS
Afuredashisou na omoi ga
These feelings about to overflow are
the love of my beating heart.
Tokimeki to Ai wo
SOS SOS