Y-Yuu-kun!
I'm already in the bath!
Oh come on, we bathed together yesterday, didn't we?
Here, do it as you always do.
Yuu-kun, what are you...?
What's wrong?
You always clean it using your breasts, right?
I do?
Yep.
Natsu-nee can't do it this way, you know.
You're right, I'm the only one who can clean your dick this way.
It's going to get dirty again if I cum.
It's okay.
I'm going to clean it until it runs dry.
It's always healthy for a man to cum.
Here, just cum when you want to.
Chiyo-nee.
There, I’m going to rubiit even harder.
I have to clean it again.
Yuu-kun.
Oh Yuu-kun, what are you making me do?
It's as Chiyo-nee said.
Yuuta, you have an umbrella with you?
Yup.
There's a chance it's going to rain, so take this umbrella with you.
Oh okay, thanks Chiyo-nee.
Just the usual routine again, huh?
By the way, don't forget this Sunday.
Okay, I understand.
Don't forget!
They won't tag along if you're not with us.
I'm not really concerned about them.
I just want to see the soccer game.
This isn't a trivial issue.
Besides, you really need to fix that sister complex of yours.
That's none of your business.
What are you guys talking about?
Natsu-nee.
You boys planning on doing something fun?
Well, we're just talking about our plan to see a soccer game.
Just you two?
No, there's more.
A few girls will be there as well.
I guess it's alright.
My umbrella!
Good for you, my brother!
Come on, let's go home!
Wait up!
Oh no, the laundry!
It's this late already?
Yuu-kun, Chinatsu.
We're home, Chiyo-nee!
Will you be home late tonight?
I'll be back in time to prepare dinner.
Yuu-kun, I've sent the laundry inside.
Fold them properly, okay?
Got it.
I'm off then.
Take care.
Getting more intimate, eh?
What are you talking about?
You cheeky boy.
Just forget it.
I wonder what Yuu-kun wants to eat tonight.
Though,
it's really quite difficult when she goes out like this.
What's with this underwear?
It's definitely not Natsu-nee's.
Which means, could it be...
Please tell me this isn't yours, Chiyo-nee!
Take this!
Pervert!
That's mine.
Do you want to have it?
Natsu-nee...
Let's stop this already.
Hey...!
You can touch me.
You can do whatever you want.
Be intense if you want to.
You can even cum in my mouth.
You're not satisfied with just this, right?
Let's go all the way.
Natsu-nee.
I told you, you can do whatever you want.
You can even force me to do things.
Hey, let's do it.
Let's stop this already.
Would you be willing if I were Chiyo-nee?
Natsu-nee...
What's with that expression?
You just enjoy teasing me like this, right?
No!
You're always close to Chiyo-nee.
So I didn't know what else to do.
Natsu-nee...
That's why...
I just get pissed off and end up teasing you!
I'm getting worried now for a whole different reason.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Yuuta.
umm...
I thought you hated me.
I'm relieved to know that you don't.
So you want to do it after all?
You're just too cute so...
Don't make excuses.
If you keep doing that,
this will happen.
Natsu-nee, are you alright?
It's alright tease me.
Get revenge on me.
Yuuta.
My body is...
It's going crazy!
I'm going wild.
Yuu-kun?
Yuu-kun, Chinatsu, what on earth are you...?
Yuu-kun.
Yes?
We need to talk.
Chinatsu, go back to your room.
No way, Chiyo-nee's actually...
Chinatsu can't do this, right?
Stop, if you keep doing that, I'll...
Do you like it?
Leave this to me.
You can also touch me if you want.
Chiyo-nee!
Did it feel really good?
Are you two on bad terms with each other?
Why do you say that?
Chinatsu and I love you very much.
So much that we like to keep you to ourselves.
I want you to move too Yuu-kun.
Your thing is... inside me...
Wow, it's filling me.
Yuu-kun...
Oh no, my mind's going blank...
Yuu-kun!
Yuu-kun, Yuu-kun!
Did I get too tired?
I can still do it, right?
He left the clothes undone, was covered
in blood and unconscious...
Did you do something to him?
Just a bit, I guess.
This is too weird to be "just a bit" though.
Is your head feeling okay now?
I'm fine now.
I see, that's good.
You're going to be late for the game if you don't hurry.
Oh crap!
I'm going!
Take care.
He's really clingy to you, Chiyo-nee.
Really?
You often play with him too, right?
Do I?
Yes you do.
He kept following you around right after
he finished elementary school.
That's all of the white clothes.
Thank you.
What do you want to eat for dinner?
You only ever ask me that when he's out.
My, my, but that's true.
Dang, you're really doting on him.
Though, he left us today and is out on a date.
A date?
Oh my, he went out with his friends to watch a soccer game, right?
He might not notice it,
but there's no way it will simply end with just watching the game.
If it would, I wouldn't have allowed him to go without me.
Oh no, what should I do?
Thanks for the food.
Chiyo-nee?
Just put the dishes in the sink, okay?
Got it.
Come on.
Chinatsu even allowed you to come with us.
No way, I'm going to miss the last train.
What are you two boys whispering about?
Let's go already!
Chiyo-nee will be worried.
I told you to fix that complex of yours already!
That's none of your business!
Anyway, sorry for missing the chance, but...
Jeez.
Talking secretly now are you?
Sorry, but I got to go.
You're going home already?
Well, I'm still here you know.
It's boring now.
It's late already.
I'm home.
I'm tired.
Chiyo-nee.
Welcome home.
I-I'm home.
Then, they hit the goal just right before the last minute.
And the crowd Went absolutely wild!
We were totally glued to our seats.
So it was a good game.
Yeah, it was really amazing.
Thank goodness.
Sorry, for making you listen to me.
I'm going to sleep now.
Oh, had enough tea?
Yeah, thanks for the drink.
I see, then I'm going to sleep as well.
Yuu-kun.
Have a nice dream.
Why are we sleeping together?!
Is there something wrong with siblings sleeping together?
Even if we grow up, you'll always be my cute little brother.
Is that how it works?
I guess it is.
Silly Yuu-kun.
Good night then.
Good night.
I can't sleep.
Your back feels wide now.
Chiyo-nee, what are you doing?
Asleep already, Yuu-kun?
I'm a bit lonely here.
I can't sleep!
Let me take a sniff of you.
Chiyo-nee!
Smells a bit of sweat.
Is this a dream?
This is just a dream, right?
You were home late, so you weren't able to take a bath.
I don't think I will be able to control myself if I touch it.
What are you doing Chiyo-nee?!
No...
Oh Yuu-kun, it's already like this.
Chi-Chiyo-nee.
No need to hold it in, just cum.
It'd be bad for your body if you don't.
Wait, stop.
Why are you embarrassed?
It's not like I haven’t seen it before.
Yuu-kun, since when did it become this big?
I'm going to cum.
It's going to come out.
It'll spray all over you, Chiyo-nee.
It's okay, as long as it's yours.
But, since we're at it already...
...since we're at it already,
I want you to cum inside me instead.
B-But...
I said it's okay.
Please?
Chiyo-nee!
Yuu-kun!
Chiyo-nee, it's Chiyo-nee's insides.
So, does it feel good Yuu-kun?
I'm really doing it with her!
Yuu-kun!
You can't do it with anyone else,
only me!
I'm cumming.
Yuu-kun.
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun!
It's filling me inside!
Yuu-kun,
I'm going to clean it.
Chiyo-nee.
Okay, it's clean now.
Chiyo-nee...
What is it?
I... for a long time now...
Yuu-kun,
I wouldn't do this with you if I didn't feel the same way.
Chiyo-nee...
Yuu-kun.
Let’s go together then.
Okay.
What's the meaning of this?
Why?
Here Yuu-kun, say ah.
But it's embarrassing.
He s dinging to her even more than before!
Chiyo-nee!
You're waking me up this way again.
It's like this every single day.
Good morning, Yuu-kun.
Let's do our best today.
The school festival is happening soon.
Tomorrow Chiyo-nee and I will...
Chiyo-nee.
Come on, let's go.
Natsu-nee!
Umm, well... I'm actually going with Chiyo-nee...
Stop complaining and just come with me.
Whew, I'm tired.
I wasn't able to go around with Chiyo-nee.
Welcome and good evening master.
Chiyo-nee.
Please make me your exclusive maid.
Since I wasn't able to be with you today.
Okay?
Onee-chan!
Oh my, Yuu-kun.
But those clothes...
I brought it home to wash it.
I will do whatever you want, so just say it.
I see.
Since it's going to the laundry, it's okay for it to get dirty, right?
Pervert.
Did you enjoy the school festival?
It was a bit lone not going around with you,
but Natsu-nee was there, so it was quite fun.
This was the last school festival that I could have with you.
I really wanted to go around with you.
Chiyo-nee.
Let's enjoy ourselves now, okay?
Okay.
Chiyo-nee, I love you.
You really love to suck that.
Because it's delicious.
But, tonight I'll be the one to...
Nope, maids are supposed to be submissive, right?
Chiyo-nee.
Jeez, it can't be helped then.
What are you doing, Yuu-kun?
You said I could do whatever I wanted, right?
That's not what I meant.
I'm the one who'll do it for you.
Maids who complain will be punished.
Yuu-kun...
It's in deeper than normal!
This can't be your punishment now.
Th-Then, please do it faster.
Chiyo-nee.
Done already?
Not yet.
Oh no, it's still stiff.
Master, master!
Master...
Is my punishment over now?
I think I'll put it in here next.
Okay, please punish my ass.
My ass, it feels weird.
It hurts a bit.
I'll stop after I cum.
Oh no, master.
Chiyo-nee.
No, please don't master!
I'll lose control if it continues to rub like this.
Oh no, I don't think I can hold it anymore.
Don't, please don't!
Oh no!
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
Please... punish me more.
Yuu-kun, move more.
Punish me more.
Chiyo-nee.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Onee-chan, Yuuta...
Here, Yuu-kun.
This is embarrassing.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's very tasty.
Tests are coming soon, so keep your
nutritional intake balanced, okay?
Ow!
What?
Are you okay, Yuu-kun?
Chinatsu?
I'm home.
Yuuta!
Die, die right now!
Hey, you beast!
How dare you do that to Chiyo-nee!
That doesn't concern you.
It does!
You thief.
Wait, I get it already, so get off me!
Stop already...!
You're...
This, this isn't what you think.
Per-vert.
Sign: Pervert
So it gets stiff on me too.
You pervert.
Any boy would get stiff if it gets rubbed like that.
Let me see for a bit.
What are you saying?
Just do it.
Show it to me already.
Natsu-nee.
Maybe you’re actually looking forward to this.
No way...
No way I'd look forward to it.
Here, here.
I hate you, Natsu-nee.
Is it really okay for you to say that?
Then why do you continue to feel pleasure as I rub it?
I can't help it.
Someone's been rubbing it that way.
So stop it already.
So anyone's okay as long as it's a girl.
Stop, I'm going to cum.
Really? I want to see it!
Chiyo-nee, I'm sorry.
Lots came out.
Was that all of it?
Hey, want to cum some more?
You're just unfair.
You eventually stopped resisting.
Natsu-nee.
Yuuta.
I'm starting to feel crazy too.
Hey, Yuuta,
do you really hate me?
I was just kidding.
Even so, it still hurts to hear you say it.
I'm sorry.
Why?
Why does it feel good?
You're heavy.
Oh, sorry.
Chinatsu-chan.
W-Why are you calling me by that old name all of a sudden?
I'm 8 months older than you, you know!
Chinatsu-chan.
You're saying it again.
Oh, it slipped out.
Yuuta, Yuuta,
put it deep inside so that it won't slip out.
It feels good.
Oh wow.
Even my mind's starting to feel tingly.
Your erotic voice...
Stupid!
Yuuta, does it feel good?
It's okay, Yuuta.
Cum all you want inside me.
Chinatsu-chan.
I'm about to...
Yuuta, Yuuta!
Yuuta.
What is it, Natsu-nee.
What? You were calling me Chinatsu-chan earlier!
Well...
You're the one who made me like this.
You came inside a lot.
I'm sorry.
Let's do it again.
Yuu-kun, are you okay?
Don't feel like eating?
I'm fine, Chiyo-nee.
Is that so?
I'm off then!
Will you be okay for your tests today?
For real?
Yeah, so the answer should be C.
I think I just completely flunked it.
Hang in there.
Oh well!
You've recovered already.
You people sure are easy-going.
Natsu-nee.
So you're checking answers together.
What did you come here for?
What's that?
I even came here to see you.
See ya!
I remember that when she's in a really good mood,
she's up for another one of her games.
Games that would make Yuuta her toy.
Now, open it!
What's written in it?
I have a bad feeling about this.
No, no way...
You're late!
It's impossible for me to complete it in under 10 minutes!
25 minutes, huh?
I'll commend you for coming anyway.
It's scary to think what'll happen if I ignore this.
Fine then.
Now come with me.
Hey, where are we going.
Just follow me.
This place is.
The underground path that no one dares to take.
What?
Are you scared?
No one's going to come here at this hour.
Not even Chiyo-nee.
Chiyo-nee I'm sorry, Chiyo-nee I'm sorry, Chiyo-nee I'm sorry...
It's too late to take back what you've done, you know.
Let's see...
Just how lively is our Yuuta today?
I don't think we can do this here.
I want to do it.
Any complaints about that?
No.
Besides, if you're happy with Chiyo-nee, then why not with me?
You already came lots inside me, you know.
I'm sorry.
Stop apologizing.
Does it feel good?
That's good.
I'm not going to lose to Chiyo-nee.
I'm cumming.
It's coming out!
I can't let my uniform get soiled.
Yeah.
Yuuta, kiss me.
You don't want to?
That's not it.
Natsu-nee, you're just having fun teasing me.
Did I tease you too much?
True, it's fun to tease you,
but I'd never do something like this just for that.
You can do whatever you want today.
Here, it feels good, right?
Here, you can put it in Yuuta.
Stir me up completely.
Yuuta.
Hey, make me feel good!
I’m sorry Chiyo-nee!
So you're finally up for it.
Your thing is twitching.
That's good.
Just pour everything inside me!
Chinatsu-chan.
Yuuta.
Yuuta!
It feels hot.
And it's all sticky.
It's all sticky.
Hey, were not done yet, right?
Yu-u-ta.
But, we don't have much time.
Then, come here quickly.
Here, Yuuta.
Yuuta, no need to hold back.
Chinatsu-chan, I'm cumming inside again.
It's okay.
Just cum whenever you want to.
Your thing is getting twitchy again!
We're not done yet.
I'm going to move for you.
Natsu-nee, the bell.
Let's keep this up a little longer.
We can't!
Oh yeah, we can just ditch class!
What are you saying?
Don’t!
Wait, Natsu-nee!
What's wrong?
He came late, and rushed his answers.
He got the order of his answers wrong by one question.
Hang in there.
Yuu-kun.
Let's go home.
Yuu-kun, is there something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Is that so?
Is it alright for you to skip checking your answers?
It's okay.
The answers themselves aren't wrong anyway.
Really?
But you still look a little unwell.
If you're worried about something, just tell me.
I'm just feeling a bit stressed.
Yuu-kun, I love you.
Your dick can't hold itself anymore.
Do me please.
Chiyo-nee.
More, touch me more!
Yuu-kun.
Chiyo-nee.
That's good.
Yuu-kun, Yuu-kun!
Yuuta!
Chiyo-nee!
Yes.
That's good.
I'm going to cum!
Chiyo-nee...
Yuu-kun, more...
Chiyo-nee!
Yuu-kun, I love you.
I couldn't live anymore if you ever got a girlfriend.
I'll be home late.
So just eat without me, okay?
Okay.
Let's do it again once I get home.
OK, I'm off.
Yuuta, the bath’s ready.
Chiyo-nee's going to be late.
Wanna sleep together?
Yuuta, I'm your elder sister too.
Yuuta...
Yuuta.
Why did you try to escape?
B-But...
Jeez, you really make this difficult for me.
This is our chance to do it at home, you know?
I'm going to do anything that you want.
Come on, just say it.
Hey, I don't want to betray Chiyo-nee any further.
That's why...
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
This is our last time, huh?
I just did it for fun so I guess it's alright.
What's with that face?
You're my toy.
It's been that way for a while, right?
It's okay, this will be my last time.
What are you doing? Lick it already.
It's good that your body's honest about it.
I'll be sure to hit your soft spots.
Oops, not yet.
It'd be a waste for you to cum this early.
I'm going to let you do it later.
It's okay if you don't want to do it.
If you think I'm going to stop with that, then you're mistaken.
I'm digging in.
This feels good.
Yuuta, control it for a bit will you?
Idiot.
Next round!
I'm sorry, but please stop.
I'll stop when I feel good enough.
Does it really feel good?
Would this really make you feel good?
Of course.
Of course it'd feel good.
Because you're my favorite toy.
Chinatsu-chan, can you let me go now?
Okay, I'm sorry.
Yuuta, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Chinatsu-chan.
Idiot.
Don't be gentle with me now.
I'm sorry Chinatsu-chan, but I...
Idiot.
If you keep acting like that...
I'm sorry.
But, I can't just leave you here.
I won't be able to stop myself.
Yuuta.
Yuuta, Yuuta.
Yuuta!
Chinatsu-chan, your voice is too loud.
Yuuta.
It's your flavor.
I'm completely stained, inside and out.
Chinatsu-chan...
Did it feel good.
Yeah, I don't know what to do anymore.
I'm sorry Yuuta.
It feels so good, I don't even know what I'm feeling.
That's why I don't ever want to be separated from you.
How many times have we done it already?
It's the seventh or eighth time I think.
You're actually counting?
That's just so like you.
I'm late already.
I wonder if Yuu-kun ate a proper dinner.
I'm home.
Don't stop.
Chinatsu-chan, Chiyo-nee's already home.
What are you so worried about?
Wait...
Yuu-kun.
My, oh my.
Chinatsu.
Welcome home, Onee-chan.
This isn't what you think!
Don't misunderstand, Chiyo-nee!
So this is a misunderstanding, huh?
My, you two get along well together.
You two finish that off and take a bath now.
Chiyo-nee, you're not mad?
Why should I?
Just when I thought that Yuu-kun was feeling a bit down,
you were actually playing with him the whole time, Chinatsu?
I wasn't playing!
I was serious about it!
You were serious about it too, right?
I can't just like you both?
What? That's not fair.
I can't accept that!
Chinatsu.
We're all siblings.
So let's all get along, okay?
Onee-chan.
You don't want us to be together?
It looks red, does it hurt?
You're really not angry about it?
Knowing you,
I'm sure you felt left out because you were
thinking about me and Yuu-kun, right?
I'm sorry if I wasn't able to notice my cute
little sister's feelings immediately.
Onee-chan.
Yuu-kun, are you just going to watch from there?
Chinatsu, he loves being rubbed by breasts like this.
Oh...
What's that?
He also likes doing it this way.
Oh, that looks interesting.
No, my nipples feel good.
This position feels like you're forcing yourself on me.
Chinatsu, how many times have you done it already?
About ten times I think.
Oh my, then let's do it many times together as well.
Hey, you're not going anywhere.
Chinatsu, I'll be first okay?
Leave a few turns for me.
I'm happy, but any more and I might die.
It's not coming out.
You're right.
Here.
My, oh my.
Pull it out!
Nope.
Wow it came out.
This looks really fun.
Spray more of it on me!
I think it has reached its limit.
I'm a bit worried now.
It's still this stiff so you can still do it.
Yuu-kun, this is wonderful.
Here, you can do whatever you want to your big sisters.
Yuu-kun.
Yuuta.
I wonder if I'm going to die today.
Chiyo-nee, congratulations!
Chiyo-nee?!
What's going on?
Chiyo-nee, you look really beautiful!
You're next Chinatsu.
Why?
Onee-chan?
What's this?
Thank goodness.
You finally smiled again after Yuuta passed away.
I won't forget Yuu-kun.
Congratulations!
Chiyo-nee, I'm still alive!
Yuu-kun?
Chiyo-nee.
I see, you had a bad dream.
Yeah.
It's alright.
We're not going to leave you.
But, about weddings and stuff.
Well,
I think I want to be in one.
But...
...we're siblings, so we can't get married.
Chiyo-nee.
Natsu-nee? Natsu-nee?
Yuu-kun.
Come to my room later.
Eh? O-okay.
Chiyo-nee, that dress...
Please let me be your wife from now on.
Chiyo-nee.
So that you won't have that bad dream again.
Oh my, silly Yuu-kun.
It's already this stiff.
The sensation of her gloves...
Does it feel good.
It feels very good.
If you keep doing that, I'll cum.
It's alright.
Just cum whenever you want.
I'll take all of it.
Does it feel good?
It feels good.
It feels too good.
This time, I want you to do it.
Yuu-kun, please.
It's already dripping wet.
Your tongue is inside me.
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
Chiyo-nee, you look beautiful.
Oh Yuu-kun, you...
I love you too Yuu-kun.
Chiyo-nee, I'm putting it in.
Okay...
It's gripping me tight.
You're filling me up.
Yuu-kun, you can move more if you want to.
You want me to?
Yuu-kun, you're such a...
Yuu-kun, you’re such a...
You’re suddenly so intense.
It feels good inside you Chiyo-nee.
It feels good Yuu-kun.
More, push it more!
Amazing.
Your insides are wrapping me tightly.
Cum anywhere you want.
I'm going to cum quickly if We keep this up.
It's okay.
Cum as many times as you want.
Just pour it all inside me.
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
No, don't fill me so deeply.
I can't?
No I mean, do it more.
Please, release all of your cum inside me.
I'm about to...!
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
Your thing is still this stiff.
It's still okay, right?
Put it in here this time, okay?
Does it feel good?
Yes, it does.
Yuu-kun.
What is it Chiyo-nee?
I can't wait any longer.
Put it in already.
This one?
No, not that one.
I want...
I want you to insert your dick inside my ass.
Chiyo-nee, you're really craving for it, huh?
No, please don't tease me.
It can't be helped then.
It's going in.
Your thing is going inside.
It's really tight.
I think I'm going to cum already.
Yuu-kun.
You can move more faster if you want to.
But, I'll cum immediately.
It's alright.
Just cum whenever, however, and as many times as you want to.
I'm always going to take it all.
If you keep moving like that, I'll...
Yuu-kun, cum lots inside me!
It's filling me inside.
Oh wow, you just came and you’re already doing it again.
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
Yuu-kun!
Did it feel good?
Yeah, it's the best Natsu-nee.
Natsu-nee, that outfit...
What?
It doesn't suit me?
No, that's not it.
Oh my, Yuu-kun.
No, wait this is...
It's just too easy to see what you're thinking.
It's okay, I'm going to make you feel good this time.
But, I want to end this for today already.
I'm tired already.
Onee-chanrYuuta is...
Yuuta is acting weird!
Yuu-kun, what's the meaning of this?
How did she hear that?
I'm sorry.
Alright.
This time, do it with Chinatsu okay?
What's wrong?
Natsu-nee, you look beautiful.
What are you saying? Jeez.
Here Yuuta.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I can't see it well.
Natsu-nee, it's wet already.
Don't say it!
Natsu-nee.
Come.
It's alright.
Just move however you want to.
Natsu-nee.
You’re really getting excited there.
Does it feel really good inside me?
It's amazing.
It's wrapping me inside and I can't resist it.
It's fine, no need to hold it in.
I want it all inside me.
Natsu-nee.
Yuuta, Yuuta!
Here, you can still do it right?
Natsu-nee...
I think I'm really going to die this time.
I'm sorry Yuuta.
Let's end this now.
Natsu-nee.
Thanks, it was really fun today.
Natsu-nee, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yuuta...
I want to make both of you feel good, always!
Don't start complaining after you've said that.
You're going to do it with me until you have completely run dry.
Come, Yuuta.
Natsu-nee!
Wow.
It's like she's trying to suck me in.
I'm going to cum quickly if I'm not careful.
Oh wow, that feels great.
My insides feel all tingly.
More, do it more.
I want more of your hot stuff!
Natsu-nee, this is amazing!
It's wrapping me inside, and it feels good.
I feel like cumming immediately whenever it hits deeply.
Yuuta!
Your thing,
it's going deep inside me.
Natsu-nee, are you alright?
I'm okay, it feels good.
Just move, just stir me up more!
Natsu-nee.
Yuu-kun.
His thing is deep inside Chinatsu.
I want him to make a mess of me.
Yuuta, Yuuta.
Natsu-nee.
Chinatsu, Yuu-kun.
Natsu-nee, I'm about to cum.
Me too, I'm about to...
Yuuta, let's cum together!
Natsu-nee!
Chinatsu, Yuu-kun.
Your thing is getting bigger inside.
Cum.
Cum lots inside me.
Natsu-nee.
Yuuta, Yuuta!
Natsu-nee, Natsu-nee!
Me too, I want to be together with them.
Yuu-kun, Yuu-kun.
Yuuta, Yuuta.
Yuuta!
Awake already?
Natsu-nee.
Did it feel good?
Yeah.
Then let's all do it together, okay?
Eh?
Let's do it more!
Yes, I'm excited to do it.
But, I'm already...
Okay?
Okay.
Here Yuuta, come.
We're ready.
It's getting stiff again.
Wait, stop...
It's wonderful.
Let's do it again and again.
Well? Does my breasts feel good?
Chinatsu can't do this, right?
That's not true.
Here now, I'm going to do it more.
Natsu-nee.
Yuuta.
Chiyo-nee.
Yuu-kun.
Let's do it again, okay?
Chiyo-nee.
Natsu-nee.
Me too.
I see, so that's what he's been dreaming about.
He was really distressed about it.
That we might get married to someone else and leave.
So, what do you think?
Wait a minute.
Let’s see, about 22 hours before a complete recovery I think.
You're really amazing as always.
Then, that's it for now.
Let's do it again tomorrow.
Natsu-nee, Chiyo-nee.
My, oh my, Yuu-kun.
Now, now, we're not going anywhere.
Good night.