Tokyo Kingdom, the artificial island
built not far off from Tokyo's coast.
The terrorist organization Ryuumon was
confirmed to be based on the island.
With Oboro's clone acting as its head.
Sakura and I were then eventually captured by a woman
named Saya, who claims to have also been
using her powers as a Taima-nin.
The Oboro clone, who plans to wield the
power of the Taima-nin as a weapon,
have started modifying and training us to her desires.
Taima-nin Asagi
The Conspilascivious Tokyo kingdom
Episode 02: The Beginning of Debauchery and Conspiracy
Oboro-sama!
Oboro, oh our high ruler!
Everyone, thank you for gathering.
Come, Asagi-oneesama, Sakura-oneechan,
over here.
Those women... could they be Taima-nin?
Correct.
They are indeed our sworn enemies
Igawa Asagi and Igawa Sakura.
Behold this form well,
and the one who defeated them is Ryuumon.
No, they willingly submitted themselves to me!
Looks like they're already drenched in white!
It's cum!
The Taima-nm are drenched in semen!
From now on they will serve us as prostitutes.
Come now, greet all of them.
Here, stancl in front of all of them.
I'm Asagi, the newbie slut.
I've been modified for pleasure.
My breasts and nipples are also modified to work as sex tools.
Anything goes.
20,000 yen per person.
That's kinda cheap!
Modified? In what way?
I plan to take further modification training in
order for my nipples to feel further pleasure.
Everyone, I hope we can all get along.
Come on now, it's your turn next, Sakura-oneechan!
I'm Sakura, also a newbie slut.
Modified for maximum pleasure.
Anything goes, and it's 15,000 yen per night.
Raise your face more!
I can't see!
I've been trained to consume only semen.
Also,
I can climax with my throat.
In my mouth pussy.
I'll work hard, so I hope we can all get along.
Seems everyone is cheering.
Onee-sama,
shall we move on to the next step?
I shall now leave these two Taima-nin here.
For three days straight.
Complete this punishment, and you shall be forgiven.
I shall then award you full citizenship within
the Tokyo Kingdom as official harlots!
Onee-chan...
I'm sure help will arrive soon.
Don't lose.
Hold on until the end.
Okay.
Can you still stay sane after getting raped continuously
for three days with that modified body of yours?
It'll be troublesome for me if you don't
break down soon, you know.
Saya also worked hard.
Because so long as the consciousness
isn't destroyed completely,
we won't be able to awaken the power of those genes.
Karma will definitely bite your hand, and your demonic actions!
That's too bad, Asagi.
It will soon be over.
Because you'll be completely reborn
as soon as the process completes.
No worry, I shall make sure your body
still remains as lovely as it is.
That's why please... let yourself break down completely.
Now, let's get started with the punishment.
Who would like to rape these sluts first?
Me, let me do it!
No, wait, me!
I'm going to get my revenge on the damned Taima-nin!
These nipples sure are huge.
It also feels so hard.
They said the nipples were modified to become clits.
Which means...
She already came!
It really does act like a clit!
You said you're aroused in your mouth pussy, right?
I-It stinks...
Whoops, sorry.
Haven't bathed for a while.
Then this is...
So intense!
The dicks are rubbing hard.
We're not even getting started yet!
I'm going to rip your asshole apart!
Let me rest!
Even if we did finish, this entire thing will still be far from over.
Just take a look around.
There are still about fifty thousand men
here waiting in line while fapping.
I-I can't do it!
I can't!
It's too hard!
Oh no...!
You say that, but look at how you move your hips.
You slut!
I'm going to cum now!
No one said anything about impregnating
being prohibited, right?
Get pregnant, you swine!
No, please, anything but that...!
They're really cumming,
and yet it feels so good.
You? A Taima-nin?
You just came when you were cummed inside earlier!
You swine!
No, I'm not...
I lost.
I lost to two dicks in my ass and pussy...
Oh no, cum's going to burst out...
It's gushing out like a fountain!
Sakura,
do your best.
And I will do my part as well.
I never thought that I'd be able to rape Sakura, the Taima-nin.
We're really lucky.
It's drilling so deep within me!
Feels good for you too, eh.
Yes, it does.
It feels great as it rubs inside my pussy,
as it penetrates at the very end,
at the very end of my vagina!
The tip of the dick is hitting it!
Sakura-chan, don't forget this one too.
Smegma tastes great.
It all sticks behind as I suck on it.
It stinks, and it's bitter.
And it makes me feel good!
It feels good to have both dicks rubbing in my throat and pussy!
This is such a turn on.
This Sakura is the best!
We're about to rape you till you drop dead!
No need to drink, just pump it straight to the throat!
She's cumming while being pumped with cum!
Taima-nin sure make good cum dumpsters.
It's going in my womb...!
Cum is getting pumped in my womb!
Onee-chan...
I can't... hold on...
This is just...
I can't wait to see them after three days.
Asagi-oneesama, Sakura-oneechan,
I want you all to become like me soon!
This is amazing!
I think even a Taima-nin would die from that!
Fuck her, fuck her!
I beg of you... spare me.
Please! I'm going to die if I get fucked by a dick that big!
Just get done with your sex rituals already, you swine!
Get totally wrecked! Until it becomes satisfied!
It hurts!
Hey look, her tits are jiggling.
Maybe it's just her body twitching as she gets fucked deeper.
No... don't push it in there...
It's at the very end already.
Feels good, right, Ms. Swine?
Being able to copulate with livestock like you.
I don't want to copulate!
Stop... I don't want to be impregnated like this...
Please don't release your big dick's fluids inside.
I don't want this monster's cum.
I don't want to get pregnant with this monster.
Please, I beg of you... I don't want to...
I beg of you!
My insides hurt.
My insides are...!
I'm peeing...
She just peed herself!
And what a pathetic expression while doing it!
Serves you right!
3 Days Later
Please... look, madam.
They came this much inside this swine cum dumpster.
My insides are completely filled with cum.
Thinking about the modification,
I'm actually happy...
That I became a sex swine.
I get really aroused whenever I think that
you two are about to become my pets.
Thank you very much-
Sex swines that are raped for three days straight.
Now show it to me!
Just how much cum have you collected?
That's cute, Asagi.
You're the best sex swine ever.
Such an unsightly form.
You... again...
I can no longer stand by and watch.
Now Asagi,
the time has come for our union.
What?
This phantasmal energy, could it be...?!
Asagi's form,
was able to awaken the power of her genes all on her own?
How dare you do that to Oboro-oneesama!
Amazing, amazing, Asagi-oneesama!
That's really cool!
I wanted to play more...
Because I finally feel like having a real big sister.
Even for just a second... beyond that island... you and me...
She was just another hapless victim.
Oboro!
It's really too bad until the end,
as it seems that your awakening isn't complete.
Your awakened body cannot keep up.
I can do the necessary modifications for that.
Modifications to become the best sex swine, of course!
I'm looking forward to that as well.
Your usurpation ends here, my fake self.
It can't be... the Original?!
Aren't you dead already?
A vampire?
I was resurrected,
into a body that could no longer walk under the sun.
This can't be...
Three Months Later
ETA in thirty minutes.
Got it.
We shall proceed as planned.
Oboro's life is just one.
Let's complete our mission this time.
Indeed, let's both execute our plans well.
Who will come, Onee-chan?
A Taima-nin, Rinto Murasaki.
My womb is filled with cum already.
There's no room anymore!
Your dick is too huge!
My insides are getting ripped apart!
How wonderful, Asagi.
Your screams are the one thing I love best.
I hope they'll continue to be tricked by it all the way.
Do not underestimate another Taima-nin.
Are you referring to the original one's memories?
You're going to get really hurt if you get too cocky.
I know!
We'll capture, and then replace her with a clone, right?
Yes.
Everything is for Oboro-sama's will.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Such unsightly faces.
This is all too wonderful.
One more guest will soon arrive.
And the day that all kunoichis will be
under my army draws ever nearer.
I shall awaken the power asleep in you with my own hands.
It will surely succeed this time... once
you become my fine sex swine.
Th-Thank you very much.
I'll do my best to become Oboro-sama's number one sex swine.
My oh my, your objective is becoming different,
my cute sex swine.