An entity of darkness.
A Japan of the near-future tainted with violence and corruption.
Under it's belly,
Rinko-senpai and us were tasked to infiltrate and rescue my mom.
Provided with a means of infiltrating as slave prostitutes,
However, we were betrayed by our very ally, Zokuto,
and our minds were promptly altered to
prepare us to become real slave prostitutes.
We had our virginity bruttally taken.
We were completely tortured.
We are obligated to be violated every day of our lives.
"Something could be in her womb six months later..."
Tatsuro.
This will be a test of our love.
Mmmh.
Yukikaze, I will protect you with my life.
It doesn't matter what happened, I will never forget you.
I believe in you, Yukikaze.
Don't worry Tatsuro, I still remember you.
Yukikaze.
How are you feeling?
Don't worry, I've been alright after all.
Have you heard of "Real"?
The gala that will happen tonight will be
scene where many brothel owners will meet.
Which means that many slave prostitutes
from many different brothels will be there.
Does that mean my mom will be there?
I'm not sure.
It's time.
It is really a group of uncontrollable beasts.
Mom, where are you?
The rumors are true about the Taimanin.
You are Yukikaze? Rinko?
Yes!
We are very pleased to have been picked
I'm Taimanin slave Yukikaze.
I'm Rinko, another slave prostitute, I apologize for the wait.
We have to serve you no matter who you are.
Without knowing, I could serve men like a prostitute.
Sir, it's already so hard...
Do you want me to start sucking it?
You can't hold back? Do it.
Yes, thank you for the meal.
His dick stinks a lot.
It also has some semen on it.
It makes me want to vomit.
But I don't hate it.
So good... his semen is so good.
It started to flow a little bit.
It's bitter and salty.
It feels so good that I want to drink it.
Show me your vagina.
Alright.
Look sir.
This is the pussy of Yukikaze.
You can see all the way inside.
I'm a little wet because I want you to stick your dick inside.
I want to feel all of your dick.
My dirty and perverted is really very hot.
But don't worry, I've probably done it a thousand times and,
everyone says that it feels great.
You're rubbing my clitoris.
It feels so good when you rub my clitoris.
Hey, you could cum if you want.
Do you want me to stick it in?
Yes, I want your penis.
I can't hold out anymore.
Sir, please use your immense dick
and stick it in my perverted pussy.
Your penis is so big and hard.
My small and tight pussy adjusts perfectly.
It's grabbing your penis firmly.
The tip, the tip is touching so deep.
You're moving all of my insides.
Oh my pussy, my pussy feels soooo good.
More! More! Stick it more!
I'm about to cum.
More! I want you to cum all over my pussy!
Do it! I'm no more than just a slave whore.
I feel like you're about to rip my pussy appart.
Like that! Do it harder!
Dick feels so good! (X3)
My pussy feels so good! (X6)
I'm feeling it in my pussy! (X6)
Give me more dick! (X9)
My pussy is about to cum! (X6)
I'm cumming! (X6)
Give me all your semen!
Fill this perverted pussy with all your semen, impregnate me!
Cum! Cum! Cum!
Cum! It's so hot...
You've filled all of my womb with your semen.
Incredible, your penis has filled me completely.
Master, you're so good at this that I'm all wet.
My fluids feel so good.
Ah! Incredible!
I feel how you're sucking my clitoris.
More! Keep biting my clitoris.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Let me suck your penis.
What incredible penis, will it fit in my mouth?
Excuse me.
You're going to cum?
It's alright, you can cum whenever you want in my mouth.
Give me all your semen please.
I want to cum in your pussy.
So you want to cum inside my pussy? That makes me so happy.
I'll do it slowly alright? Your penis is so big.
What is this? It's so big that it's filling.
My pussy is full.
So big! So big!
It's so big and thick that it fills my entire pussy.
I feel how it's feeling my stomach!
Incredible, it feel so good.
My pussy, my pussy feels so good.
The Taimanin are whores that are addicted to dicks.
That's right, I'm a whore that is adicted to dicks.
Give me all your penis, give me it all, all!
You also like it in your ass.
That is my ass! It's inside my ass!
This feels incredible!
You're sticking it in my pussy and in my ass.
I can feel how it moves inside my pussy and ass.
I can feel how it expands.
This ass feels like she is sucking my off.
I can feel how this whore squeezes her pussy.
Come on! Come on! Give me more!
You're penetrating this whore Taimanin from both ends.
I'm cumming!!
I'm cumming!!!
I can feel how you're filling me up.
I feel it fill me, it's so hot.
The faimous Taimanin, to what point will they ruin themselves?
Delicious.
How good my pussy feels.
It feels so good to fuck a Taimanin.
Taimanin?
Disappear, disappear, disappear!
Now I'm only a prostitute slave.
Now I'm only a human waste serving these pigs.
I'm gonna cum.
Here too.
I'm cumming!
It's coming! It's coming!
Really admirable Yukikaze.
Really worthy of first class whores.
Are you happy to do it?
Tatsuro.
How?
I see, Tatsuro doesn't know yet.
As you can see, Taimanin Yukikaze is now our whore.
Nooo!
Many dicks have filled her pussy.
Tatsuro, don't look!
Don't look!
It seems that her pussy finally emptied.
With my dick, I took her virginity.
Something her boyfriend didn't do.
Now I'll repeat it here, the moment I broke her hymen.
I'm sorry for doing something that you should have done...
No! Yazaki stop, I don't want to do it in front of Tatsuro.
I don't want you to fuck me now.
I don't want him to see how I lost my virginity.
Shut up whore!
Tatsuro please, don't look how dirty I am.
Watch, I urge you to watch.
Watch how he shoves it in and out.
Watch how he makes me happy every time his dick fills my pussy.
Tatsuro look at me, look well.
Yazaki has a fantastic dick that makes my
pussy feel good every time he sticks it in.
He has a dick of the gods.
Marvelous penis, good in my pussy! (X3)
Look Tatsuro, look how my pussy enjoys it.
Open your eyes, watch well and never forget.
It will be an unforgettable scar in your memory Tatsuro.
I will fill you up.
Give me your semen, give me all your semen.
Shoot it and fill my womb.
Let it all go and fill me up. Impregnate me!
Yazaki, I want to have your son!
Give me your semen.
It hasn't stopped filling me completely.
You've completely filled me with your sperm.
All of my womb is full.
You've left your seed inside of me.
You're the first man to make me this happy.
You are a complete pervert as well...
How was it? First time seeing Yukikaze in this form?
It feels weird with my fluids and your semen Yazaki.
Wow, you've gotten hard again.
I want you to fuck me again.
Tatsuro, I knew you'd come here.
Are you alright?
Hey, why did you leave in the middle of everything?
I told you that you don't have the last word.
After Yazaki filled my pussy up, he fucked me in the ass.
He gave it to me continously in the ass.
I want to take your dick's virginity Tatsuro.
It will feel just as good as Yazaki's penis.
Do you want to put it in my pussy?
Do you want to? Do you want to? Do you want to?
Hey, answer me fast.
Why are you putting that such a weird face?
Wow, you stink.
You're probably watching my videos online.
How are you Tatsuro?
Who do you think is the father of this child?
Today is the anniversary of when I became a sexual slave.
I've become addicted to dicks.
After being fucked so many times in public in a degrading form.
Please, I want you to fill me with your semen.
I want you to stick your dick in me please.
Today is probably a dangerous day.
Probably I'm not pregnant.
I'm very happy for that.
Watch me please.
My pussy is already so wet.
Could you forgive this perverted pussy?
God, I can't hold out anymore.
Quick, someone stick your dick in me!