Begone!
I'll have orc-kun punish you later.
Yukikaze
Anti Demon Ninja
~Sow Trainings~ Shiranui
Yukikaze
Anti Demon Ninja
Dye the colorless night
sore ha iro no nai yoru wo someru
tada mukishitsu naru yoru wo someru
Illuminated by the waning moon
sore ha kagen to tsuki ga terashita
Reflected color of a façade
me ni mieru omote no kao no iro yeah iya iyaaaa
Dye the colorless night
sore ha iro no nai yoru wo someru
Dye the true face behind the façade
me ni mienu ura no kao wo someru
Buried in the farthest end of the sky
saihate no sora mo umete nidoto
Inescapable destiny
kesenai sadame
This body beyond salvation
sukui no nai kono mi ha
Waver inside somebody's consciousness
dare ka no ishiki no naka de yurameku
Flounshing world dyed in crimson
aka ni somari sazameku sekai
Two overlapping memories
kasanariau futatsu no kioku
Shadow of the night with hidden determination
ketsui wo himeta yoru no kage ni
A fluttering moment
setsuna no yurameki
You pussy is twitching
like you're on heat.
What a nice view.
You can't move because of the
aphrodisiac, right Shiranui?
I will train you whole lots from now on.
Stop it.
Your pussy is drenched right now.
No!
So big!
It's scraping my inside.
What is this feeling.
Noooo!!!
No good! Don't! Stop!
Amazing!
So deep!
His dick is stirring the inside of my pussy.
Nooo!!!
Sonething big is coming!
I'm gonna cum!
Cumming! I'm cumming!
So amazing!
I'm creampied so deep in my womb!
I'M CUMMING!!!
No good, he cummed buckets inside me.
His semen overflowing from my pussy.
He shoved his orc dick forcefully
inside me and made me cum so hard.
I cummed so hard!
More! Shove your dick more
inside my pussy!