A year had passed since the decimation of Chaos Arena.
And yet, Chaos's existence still plagues the world.
In the man made tower near Tokyo bay, of Tokyo kingdom,
lies an abandoned town afloat on the water.
It has become a town of shadows, infested by scum of the Earth.
In order to deal with the terrorist organization, Dragon, hiding there,
and to find the whereabouts of our undercover agent on the island,
my little sister and I infiltrated Tokyo Kingdom.
The Anti-Demon Shinobi clan?
Our comrades?
Saya. I'm Saya.
And you two are Asagi-onee-chan and Sakura-onee-chan, right?
How do you know our names?
Well, like, you guys are Oboro-onee-sama's enemies.
Oboro?!
A monster?
I hate spiders!
That's so mean! I only look like this because of that Anti-Demon power.
Anti-Demon power?
Asagi-onee-sama, Sakura-onee-chan, even you can transform!
We can?
You're crazy!
You don't even know about your own bodies?
Then, I'll teach you all about Anti-Demon power!
Bordering Crisis!
Anti Demon Shinobi Asagi
The Lewd Stratagem of Tokyo Kingdom
Episode 1 Rebuild, Once More
Where am I?
A hundred warriors defeated, without so much
as a scratch. Unmatched on the battlefield.
Yet, I feel no joy whatsoever.
I've lost as many comrades as I've killed enemies.
We had no anger, no sorrow, no hopes.
Yearn for this power! Drown in the darkness
within you, Asagi of the Iga clan.
Get away from me!
Good morning, Asagi-onee-sama!
You look like you're doing well.
If you're worried about Sakura-onee-sama,
she's sleeping soundly in my room.
Oh? You seem to be in a good mood too, Saya-chan.
I get to interrogate you now, after all!
I'm going to exact Oboro-onee-sama's revenge.
Saya, who do you work for?
That would be me.
I'm sure I killed you that time!
A pleasure to make your acquaintance, Asagi.
A pleasure?
I'm a clone of Oboro, a product of human
and demon realm's technology.
A clone?
I am also the boss of Dragon.
Since you so kindly killed the original, I was able to seize power here.
Thanks.
I was born here, too!
Oh, she's an artificially created being.
Using a kunoichi's body as the base, we were able to awaken the
hidden potential within her, making her the ultimate warrior!
Sleeping within the bodies of Shinobi is a power
that is hidden and difficult to tap into.
She is the embodiment of that power!
Are you trying to say that's what a Shinobi really is?
She is the true form of the Shinobi that lies dormant within you all.
That goes for you too, Asagi.
If I use the genes of the person who killed my original,
I know I'll be able to create an even stronger being!
It'll surely be the most splendid weapon ever.
I will never let you do that!
I knew you'd say that.
If I don't get you to submit, I won't be able to use your genes.
So I'll just have to train you until you become a subservient bitch.
You little bitch!
First, I'll augment those tits for you.
Augment! Training! Sex slave!
What are you doing?
Your body hasn't changed since Chaos Arena, has it?
Your body's sensitivity has been dialed up to the max.
Did you just cum from having those needles inserted?
I can suppress my body's impulses!
Doesn't seem that way to me.
What a dirty voice you're letting out. Are you already getting turned on?
What a slut! Slut!
I can't let myself feel aroused. I can't!
End this already!
Now you're just jumping the gun. We're not
done until all that fluid has been injected.
What do you think it is?
What indeed.
It's something to forcefully alter your cells and
allocate more potency to your other organs.
Your nipples shall now become clitorises!
Two huge clits made just for you!
Aren't you glad that your baby nurturing
parts are turning into sex parts?
If you get fondled, you'll climax, if you get injected, you'll
climax! You're gonna be the best mother ever!
It's filling me up inside! It feels so hot!
Hm? Is the drug finally kicking in?
You're already getting off from this? You're such a slut!
Look, it's almost empty.
There, all gone.
Augmentation complete!
Your nipples are so huge now!
Kind of obscene if you ask me.
R-Really? I kinda like them.
Staying strong is just like you.
But, you know...
You're getting off from being whipped?
Your nipples are quivering.
As if I would get aroused from something like this!
Again with that attitude. You're really pissing me off, you piece of shit.
I'll give you an even better present.
No! No way!
Sto...
This should hurt, but it feels so good!
No! Stop! No!!
No!!
Oboro! How dare you do this to me!
This is where babies are supposed to suck,
they're not for your disgusting tentacles!
My nipples will be like this forever!
I'm gonna kill you!
Yes! That's the face I wanted to see. A face twisted with anger!
The memories of being killed by you have been
transmitted from my original's brain.
What an extremely painful memory.
Asagi, I despise you more than anything, so
seeing your pathetic face gets me so wet!
Just like your twisted original.
You're both perverts!
That's it, Asagi. Your stubbornness is just right.
Show me more of that!
Oboro! I will definitely get you for this!
That's not something you say with an ecstatic face, is it?
No, I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!!
Don't let yourself be satisfied with that.
We still have more presents for you.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming with my nipples!
So much milk is flowing out!
It should feel just as good as having a man cum inside you.
I can't stop it!
It won't sto...
Thi...
No! No more! I can't...
That's it. Show me more of your disgraceful face,
wound up in ecstasy.
No!!
We're going to milk every last drop out.
We'll be sure to milk you until your tits
are completely and utterly empty!
No!!
I'm cumming! No!!
You're making a great face.
I can understand why my original obsessed
over trying to see your face like this.
Wow, Sakura-onee-chan, you're so perverted!
You've been cumming so much!
My body that's augmented by Chaos Arena,
my pussy that won't stop throbbing...
The sexual stimulation suppressors are about to run out!
I have to brace myself!
It's so big!
No!
You're so dirty! I thought you'd be able to hold back for a little longer!
My pussy and my asshole are so hot!
Are you gonna cum again? Are you really gonna?
You said you'd never forgive me, didn't you?
This is your punishment!
Oh, no! I'm gonna cum again!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
You came again?!
No, I d-didn't...
Yeah, you did! Wow, you're such a slut!
Wh-What are you doing?
I'm gonna slap your ass twenty times as punishment.
No! Don't do it!
Even if you don't want it, I'm gonna!
Wow, your face looks horrible, Sakura-onee-chan!
I'll make your ass shine red!
No, no more! Forgive me!
No can do!
You lied to me, so I'm gonna spank you!
You look like you're having a blast!
I'm tired of spanking you little by little, so let's do it all at once.
No, no, no!
I can't understand a thing you're saying.
No more!
Come on, no matter how good it feels,
you can't just pee on me like that.
Delicious! Your pee tastes so sweet!
No, don't say that!
Um... how many times have I spanked you so far?
I don't remember at all.
Let's start over again!
Now that you've peed, I wonder what's gonna come out next.
Onee-chan, I'm gonna do my best!
But... But...
Okay, here we go! One slap, coming up!
No more! I'm gonna cum!
Onee-chan, this might be it for me.
If it is, I wonder if you'll forgive me.
Here comes round two!
I'm cumming!
You came again?! I'm done giving you chances to redeem yourself.
Here come two hundred more!
No, you're going to destroy my butt!
How's that?!
This dream again...
Looks like you've hit a wall, huh?
You look pathetic. And people call you
the strongest Anti-Demon Shinobi?
Who the hell are you?
I am you.
Wha...
Yearn for power, Asagi.
Power?
If you call on my power, you'll be able to release
yourself from this pain in an instant.
What are you mumbling about?
Have you finally lost your mind?
Let... me go.
Let me go.
Go, my pets. Show me what you can do.
Make this useless pile of meat into a pathetic,
dirty slut who only lives for sex.
I can't take this! I'm cumming!
Stop!
This is quite the dirty spectacle.
You're the best, Asagi.
You make me want to masturbate.
No, wait!
If I get any more milk inside me...
No!
No! No! I'm going to go crazy!
I'm really going to go crazy!
Shatter to pieces, Asagi!
I'll get you, Oboro!
No! No more!
My nipples, my pussy, my asshole... everything feels so good!
I'm cumming!
I feel so good!
In the man made tower, Chaos Kingdom, that lies in Tokyo Bay,
resided a terrorist organization named
Dragon, led by the woman Oboro.
She was, in fact, the clone of the original Oboro.
My younger sister and I were captured by a girl who could manipulate
her genetic makeup and unlock her dormant Anti-Demon power.
In order to awaken the dormant Anti-Demon
power within us and weaponize it,
Sakura and I were taken by the clone of Oboro,
who began to try and break us.
The Lewd Stratagem of Tokyo Kingdom
Anti Demon Shinobi Asagi
Episode 2 The Lewd Stratagem Begins
Oboro-sama!
Oboro, our liberator!
Thank you for being here today.
Sakura-onee-chan, Asagi-onee-sama, come here.
Are those women, Anti-Demon Shinobis?
Yes. They're our mortal enemies. Sakura and Asagi of the Iga clan.
Engrave this into your eyes.
Our mortal enemies have submitted to Dragon.
No, to me, Oboro.
There's some kind of white liquid dripping down on them!
It's semen! They're covered in semen!
I've employed them as prostitutes.
Come on, say hello.
Come up here, you two.
I'm the new slutty prostitute, Asagi.
My sensitive spots have finished being augmented.
My nipples have also been altered for your sexual pleasure.
I'm good for anything. One night is 20,000 yen.
Oh, she's pretty hot. What else have you done to her body?
I'm gonna be trained so that you can
fuck me through my nipples.
Please, take good care of me.
Alright, you're up next, Sakura-onee-chan.
I'm the new slutty prostitute, Sakura.
My sensitive spots have finished being augmented.
I'm good for anything. One night is 5,000 yen.
Hey, let us see more of your face!
Can't see it at all!
I've been modified so that I can't live unless I consume semen.
Also, I can make you cum in my throat.
I have a mouth pussy.
Um... I'll try my hardest, so please take care of me.
Looks like everyone is happy about this.
Onee-sama, can we do this next?
We will leave these slutty Anti-Demon Shinobis here for three days.
Through this punishment we will forgive them of all their sins.
We will also let them live happily ever after
here in the Tokyo Kindgom, as prostitutes.
Onee-chan?
Help will come. Try and control your feelings.
Y-Yeah.
With your augmented body, do you really think you
can last three days of being fucked nonstop?
You're almost there, aren't you?
You need to break completely for this to work.
Saya had to endure a lot. If you don't completely destroy your,
ego, it's impossible to draw out the power within yourself.
I'll make sure you pay for these bestial things you're making us do!
That's too bad, Asagi. It's over.
You're going to forget everything and be reborn.
I'll let you be reborn with your amazing body.
Just sit back and allow yourself to be broken into pieces.
All right! Let's start punishing these two!
Who wants to fuck these sluts first?
Please, let me do them!
No, let me!
Let me show those Anti-Demon bitches who's boss!
You've got pretty big nipples, and the boobs to match.
I heard your tits have turned into clitorises?
That means...
No!
You came already? Shit, it really is a clitoris.
Does your mouth-pussy feel good, Sakura-chan?
It stinks!
Sorry! I haven't really showered or anything.
No, please!
This is so intense! Their cocks are messing me up!
This isn't nearly enough!
I'm gonna break your ass!
Let me rest!
There are still more people behind us!
Look around you. You're surrounded by cocks!
All these people! I can't!
This is too rough! No!!
You say that, but you're moving your hips, you fucking whore!
I'm gonna cum soon. Let's see if I can get you pregnant.
Get pregnant, you slut!
No! Please, anything but that!
They came inside me!
Their cum feels so good!
You call yourself an Anti-Demon Shinobi?
You're just a whore who cums while being creampied.
You fucking slut!
No, I'm not a slut!
They're out!
Their cocks came out of my pussy and asshole.
I can't hold it in. Their cum is gonna gush out!
No!
Looks like she's shitting herself!
Stay strong, Sakura. I'm gonna do my best too!
I never thought the day I get to fuck you would come.
We're totally inside her.
Their cocks are so deep inside me!
It feels good, it feels good, doesn't it?!
It feels so good! Both my mouth and pussy are being fucked so hard!
Your cock is so deep inside my pussy! So deep!
I can feel your balls touching my pussy...
Sakura-chan, take care of this too.
Yes...
It tastes so good! It tastes kind of like chocolate.
It smells, it's so hard, and it feels so good!
There are dicks so deep inside my mouth
and my pussy... It feels so good!
Your reactions are great. I love how you're
getting so turned on from this!
We'll fuck you until you break!
You don't need to drink it, I'll just pour it straight down your throat.
My cum just won't stop flowing out!
Anti-Demon Shinobis are actually good cum dumpsters, huh?
Semen is flowing into my womb! Oh, no, it's coming! No! Don't!
Onee-chan, I think I'm done for.
I'm so sorry...
I can't wait to see what will happen on the third day.
Asagi-onee-sama, Sakura-onee-chan, I can't
wait until you two become like me!
I'm cumming!
This is amazing!
They're really living up to their reputations as Anti-Demon Shinobis!
Do it! Do her!!
Please, don't!
If you put a cock that big inside me, I'll die!
Get on with it, you slut!
Get fucked! Get fucked until you become a complete slut!
It hurts!!
Look! She's even moving her hips!
She's actually getting turned on from taking that cock in?
I won't let myself cum from this!
Isn't it great? You got to breed with one of your kind, you filthy animal!
No!
No, don't! I don't want to bear your child!
Your dick is exploding inside me!
No, please! I don't want your semen!
I don't want to bear a demon's child! Please, don't do it!
Please, I beg you!
It's shooting out inside!
It's coming!
No!
I'm peeing...
She peed herself!
What a pathetic bitch!
So pathetic!
3 days later —
Look at me.
I got so much semen inside me for being your bitch.
My stomach is so full... I'm so thankful...
I'm so happy to have become your bitch.
You make me so wet when you say you're my bitches.
Thank you so much!
You've been everyone's bitch for three days. Come on.
Show me how much cum you have in you.
You're so cute, Asagi. You're the best whore.
You're a disgrace.
You again...
I can't sit around and watch any longer. Come, Asagi, it's time.
What's happening?
This demonic aura... It can't be!
Asagi, you...
You awakened your dormant power by yourself...?!
How dare you do that to her!
You're amazing! You're so amazing, Asagi-onee-sama!
You're so cool!
So you wanted to play with me?
It's like you're that sister I always wanted.
Just once, just once, I hope that the three of
us can play together again on that island...
So she was also a victim.
Oboro!
In the end, it looks like you still lose.
Your transformation was incomplete.
Your body can't keep up with your awakened self.
Don't worry, I'll help change your body into the best slut in the world!
I'm also looking forward to this.
How dare you usurp me, imposter!
It can't be! The original?!
You're supposed to be dead!
You're a vampire?!
I was reborn, you see. Reborn into a body that cannot bathe in sunlight.
Th-This can't be...
3 months later —
Thirty minutes until we reach the shore.
Understood. Everything is proceeding as planned over here.
We'll take Oboro's life. This time, for sure.
Indeed. Let's both fulfill our missions.
Who's coming, onee-chan?
Rinto Murasaki, another Anti-Demon Shinobi.
There's so much semen flowing into my womb! It won't stop!
Your dick is too big! It's gonna rip me apart!
You're wonderful, Asagi. Out of everyone, you're my favourite.
It'd be great if we can fool them just like we planned to.
We shouldn't underestimate them.
Is that from your original's memory?
If we underestimate them, we'll be in for a world of hurt.
I know, we have to make sure we take them alive, right?
Everything is for Oboro-sama's plan.
We're going.
How beautiful. Your faces are disgraceful.
Don't worry, you'll have some new friends soon.
I'm going to make every Kunoichi part of my army.
I'll draw out the power sleeping within all of you.
If you become my good little whores, I'll definitely succeed.
Yes, thank you very much!
I'll work hard to become the perfect sex slave for you!
What's this? Looks like your objective has changed, my cute slut.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: bis | punk4real