SubDESU-H Present.
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
To dyeing the night without color
tada mu kijun naru yoru o someru
I simply painted the ever-changing moon,
sore wa kagen no tsuki ga terashita
and it shone at the moon's last quarter.
menimieru omote no kao no iro
The color of these shown faces which I can see,
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
is painting the colorless night,
meni﻿meimu ura na kao o someru
and also smears the hidden faces which I can't see.
saihate no sora mo umete nidoto
It even filled the ends of the skies and sealed.
kesenai sadame
the fate which would never be erased.
sukui no nai kono mi wa
My own self, which cannot reach salvation,
dereka no ishiki no naka de yurameku
wavers within someone else's consciousness.
aka ni somari sazameku sekai
This world, which will be covered completely in red,
kasanariau futatsu no kioku
with these two overlapping memories,
ketsui o himeta yoru no kage ni setsuna no yurameki
and my momentary hesitation that hides my determination In the night.
Entities of darkness.
A near future version of Japan where all earthly "demons" run rampant.
The tacit rule from long ago of non-interference
between humans and demons,
is now starting to show how humans eventually
degenerated into corruption,
and now many criminal organizations and
businesses by humans and demons...
...﻿lurk in the darkness.
With the current age falling into chaos and decay.
However,
this doesn't mean that people who have strayed are weak.
The current government,
has established an organization consisting of "shadow agents",
to counter this "evil",
and to oppose the wickedness of these decadents.
People call them,
TL Note: Taima-nin = Anti Evil Shadows
the "Taima-nin".
Rinko-senpai,
Tatsurou...
shall we fly?
No.
There are too many guards.
Let's try to observe a little longer.
Understood.
Tatsurou?
How about calming down a little bit?
O-Okay.
Pull yourself together.
You want to act cool in front of her, right?
N-Nee-san!
Senpai, I don't really need to...
You say that, but that pendant...
I remember a certain "childhood friend" giving you that.
How did you know about that?
I already knew everything.
Senpai...
My brother might seem a bit cowardly,
out I leave him to you.
Senpai!
We're on a mission right now!
That's right, Nee-san!
Leave the room if you've already finished preparing.
I understand.
Excuse me, and sorry to keep you waiting.
You're...!
Yukikaze, you're looking quite pathetic there.
Yazaki!
My, my,
what a lively slave we have here.
I deeply apologize for her actions, Yazaki-sama.
YuKiKaze.
I will not allow any more acts of rudeness.
If you activate the power of that seal,
your body will suffer a great deal of torture.
Will that be okay with you?
I think that would just be great, am I right, Dial?
My gratitude for your reassurance.
Yukikaze.
Yazaki-sama is a high-level VIP here.
Never do what you just did again.
What's wrong, Yukikaze?
Senpai, I...
I...
We're going to be slave prostitutes for this mission.
I understand that.
Then you also already understand,
purity is not what's important here,
it's your heart.
Tatsurou will also understand.
What?
Now, don't you have anything to say?
If not for the mission, I wouldn't have
I'm happy that we met again, Yukikaze.
I'm very sorry for what happened earlier.
I'm Yukikaze, your slave prostitute.
You know, I remember you from time to time.
Whenever I see this on my face,
I think that I would've been able to clean
it properly with the right technology.
Do you understand why I didn't?
Because I was thinking of repaying you one day, for doing this to me.
One day, I heard a certain rumor.
That you'd been captured, and being "tamed"
to become a slave prostitute.
Do you understand how happy I was when I heard that?
I'm prepared for this.
Sir.
Well said, Yukikaze!
I'll take my sweet time to exact my revenge on you.
I'll corrupt you to the point that you'll even plead to bear my children.
Stop fucking aro-
Stop fucking around, eh?
I'm serious here.
You're going to bear my child.
Don't you think that's the best revenge I could ever get?
This garbage...
And just who would want your children...
Just who would..
But why?
My body feels hot..
What's wrong with me?
My heart won't stop throbbing!
You're going to give birth to my child, Yukikaze.
This guy's child...
Why is my heart throbbing from the words of this despicable guy?
No!
That's...
That's just not possible!
Why don't you come closer?
Oh, do you have a sweetheart?
I don't have one!
...﻿I have...
Is that so?
Being kissed,
by this disgusting old man...
His tongue...
It's stinky and feels slimy.
It's gross.
Now, why don't you start servicing this?
It's this big?
Fine then.
I'm going to make you cum quickly.
Hey, hey,
with that hand technique, you won't be able to satisfy me,
no matter how long we stay here.
Hmm...
You don't seem to know how to do it.
When you're stroking a man's dick, you
should also stroke your own pussy.
That's the basics.
YuKiKaze,
how's your new body?
New body?
It's not just the aphrodisiac lotion that is spread all over your body.
Your brain's circuitry has been rewired,
and you're now able to feel pleasure many times more than normal.
Which means your sexual arousal no longer has a limit.
My brain is...
No way.
If that was your previous body,
you wouldn't have been able to masturbate in
front of anyone, even when ordered to do so.
Hey, swine woman.
Your stroking here is getting lighter.
Oh, you're concentrating on your pussy, eh?
Hey, are you even listening you bitch?
Now, suck on my tongue.
Oh no.
He's such a despicable guy and yet,
if this continues...
Are you at your limit already?
You won't be able to do well forever, with that stroking.
Do you want to put it in?
I...
I am asking if you want to put it in?
It won't fit.
That's just...
Say what you really want.
Say yes!
What a pathetic sight, Yukikaze!
But this is far from the end.
Tatsurou, I...
Why did this have to happen?
There are only five guards around, which we can target easily.
It's within our sights.
Let's fly!
But,
it'd be dangerous to leap across high buildings from this point.
One mistake, and we'll be splatted all over the wall.
It'll be okay with your wind tunnel technique Rinko-senpai.
So she says.
What are you going to do, Tatsurou?
I believe in you, Nee-san!
Okay, thanks.
Then, let's head out!
Well then,
it's a mutual agreement on what we discussed earlier, correct?
Yes, of course.
Just leave all the other things to us.
What?
Taima-nins?
It's an attack by Taima-nins!
Electric shot!
All targets, elimination complete.
Did she do this?
A lightning gun user,
and that peculiar flat chest.
She's the Lightning Taima-nin!
Beside her,
the big boobs bitch known as,
the Slasher Taima-nin!
Who are you calling flat chested?!
Who are you calling big boobs bitch?!
Chief Secretary of Civilian Affairs.
You're Yazaki Souichi, correct?
That's right.
I also know you people very well.
It's a real honor to be known by a shitty politician.
You cheeky little brat.
What's with that attitude?
Just wait!
Yukikaze, he's not our target.
It'd be bad if we kill him here.
I know.
But it'd be a lot better for this country if this man...
Yukikaze!
Are you going to kill me?
But you can't, right?
You won't just get away with it if you do that.
Threatening me now, eh?
Even though you’re just a traitor to the country.
Let me tell you this,
the truth isn't as beautiful as it looks.
This country you see,
for hundreds, no thousands of years,
has been governed by the fact that the weak fall to the strong!
Don't you even understand that?
Such logic is most suited for villains such as you.
Then it'd also be logical for you do die at my hands, correct?
Are you crazy, little brat?!
Stop that already.
They told us not to lay a hand on him.
Justice will be served to him sooner or later.
I understand.
I just wanted to see this old guy's cold sweat.
Making a fool out of me...
Don't think you can easily get away with this.
Anything can happen to you if I just order my men to do so.
Are you listening?!
Oh yes, your mother was once a powerful Taima-nin.
But I've heard she disappeared in the middle of one of her missions.
Remember this.
You won't just be ensnared and eliminated
by the traps your enemies set.
People like you will...!
Shut your damn mouth!
I'm actually going to kill you if you speak about my mother again.
Hey now.
I didn't kill him.
Look, he's still alive.
My blood just boiled a little bit.
That's some hard guts there.
Jeez, you're such a...
Rinko-senpai.
Well, let's just leave it at that.
It's mission complete, right?
Seems so.
Though, it seems you didn't do anything.
I'm sorry.
Let's withdraw now.
The guards below should have noticed the ruckus here already.
Roger!
Wake up, Yukikaze.
The real thing starts now.
Now, do your work as a slave prostitute and serve my dick.
He's a worse than trash politician.
I want to kill this guy so badly.
But, I need to act as a slave prostitute to finish my mission.
In order to find mother, and save her.
Hey, are you listening swine?
Yes, I understand.
Spread your legs.
You need to clearly show me your aroused pussy.
Is this okay?
It's still wet...
Now, act like a slave prostitute and suck up.
Yes.
I am a slave prostitute.
I'm now going to serve you,
with my swine mouth pussy.
What a dirty dick.
There's lot of dirt on it.
My nose feels irritated from its stench.
I haven't taken a bath in days.
I did it all for you.
Thank you very much.
If feels weird.
It's so gross, but...
Why?
It smells and tastes so good...
Does my dirt covered dick taste that good?
That's not...
But you seem quite passionate there.
Does it feel good, sir?
Does my mouth pussy feel good, sir?
It feels good.
Swallow more of it.
Suck it till you reach the tip.
Yes.
Does it really feel good to get it rubbed inside your mouth pussy?
Then I'll do this for you.
Is that good?
You perverted blowjob swine!
I'll do this for you.
I'm going to break you with this!
It's about to come out.
I'm about to... cum!
You blowjob swine!
Don't swallow it yet.
Show me all the cum in there.
Now close your mouth.
then try to savor it.
Open your mouth again.
Okay, you can swallow it now swine.
From now on you'll be bathing in my cum every day.
For that little brat before to now be a slave
prostitute, it sure looks quite miserable.
Oh, you came just from drinking of my cum.
How does the cum of the man you hate taste?
Let me hear your thoughts.
I can't just tell you that...
Let me hear it!
It's very sticky.
It gets stuck in my mouth.
It stinks, and feels gross.
That's all?
That's...
Tell me the truth.
I'll now if you're lying.
It tastes good.
Your cum tastes great.
I hated it,
but with the smell, and its taste...
I got so aroused from it.
Your thoughts were just realistically perfect.
Now then Yukikaze, stand up.
Yes.
From just a little touch, you're already reacting like that?
It looks like your nipples are about to burst.
They have perfect sensitivity,
as if you've got extra clitoris' here.
Resistance is futile.
Your mind is already perfectly reformed so that your body,
will take any form of stimulation as pleasure.
Don't.
I can't take it anymore!
You also received pain as pleasure, right?
How's the feeling of having a very horny body?
Are you getting aroused from being spanked?
You shitty swine!
No, this is...!
What are you denying it for?
This is the finishing blow!
I'm cumming!
Don't just sit there, stand up!
You already want a dick inside, right?
That's not...
I don't want any dick...
Stop lying.
Your mind will break if you keep on defying your instincts.
I'm not lying...
I'm so aroused,
but that's not it...
Let's start our virgin piercing session.
There's no other way for you to live but as a slave prostitute anyway.
Isn't that right, Yukikaze?
Can I put it in now?
You'll put it inside raw?
No need for any contraceptives.
Because slave prostitutes need to enjoy this raw.
Are you remembering your sweetheart?
Oh yes, his name is Tatsurou, right?
I've heard that he's the brother of Akiyama Rinko.
How do you know him?
He seems like a bashful person.
Then it can't be helped.
I'll just report to him how your pussy feels.
Stop joking around!
I'll seriously kill you if you do that!
I'm looking forward to it.
I don't like this, but I just came.
He made me cum.
Savor the sensation well,
and become a swine that can easily feel
ecstasy no matter who is fucking you!
Here, look at where it's connected.
No, I don't want any more of this obscene stuff!
Oh no...!
I'm losing it.
That won't do, you need to look at it well.
Look at how your pussy and my dick are making love to each other.
That's not true!
We're not making love to each other!
Your body is telling me otherwise.
It's hitting deep inside my pussy.
It feels good...
Yukikaze, let's kiss.
Put out your tongue, and drink my saliva.
Is my saliva delicious?
Yes, it's delicious.
This is called hit-the-womb sex.
Every woman who receives this becomes a sex swine,
and now that includes you!
Not that!
It feels good.
Tatsurou-kun is yet to pierce through your womb, right?
No, he hasn't even had sex with you yet!
Shut up!
I don't care about th-
Oh no...
This can't be...
He's kissing me while it keeps getting pierced.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm about to cum now.
I'm going to cum inside.
No!
Don't cum inside!
I'm cumming!
It feels good...
My pussy just came...
It feels hot...
It feels hot inside.
It's still coming out.
Does that much really come out?
My womb is getting filled.
Your womb is now my cum tank.
Do you understand?
Yes, I'm now your personal cum tank.
I still came a lot even though it's my second shot.
Don't worry if you get pregnant.
I'll properly take care of it,
because slave prostitutes aren't allowed to abort.
My, oh my,
even though you're a Taima-nin,
you're still just a little brat after all.
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
To dyeing the night without color
tada mu kijun naru yoru o someru
I simply painted the ever-changing moon,
sore wa kagen no tsuki ga terashita
and it shone at the moon's last quarter.
menimieru omote no kao no iro
The color of these shown faces which I can see,
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
is painting the colorless night,
meni﻿meimu ura na kao o someru
and also smears the hidden faces which I can't see.
saihate no sora mo umete nidoto
It even filled the ends of the skies and sealed.
kesenai sadame
the fate which would never be erased.
sukui no nai kono mi wa
My own self, which cannot reach salvation,
dereka no ishiki no naka de yurameku
wavers within someone else's consciousness.
aka ni somari sazameku sekai
This world, which will be covered completely in red,
kasanariau futatsu no kioku
with these two overlapping memories,
ketsui o himeta yoru no kage ni setsuna no yurameki
and my momentary hesitation that hides my determination in the night.
It feels lonely without a dick in there, right? This﻿
is also an important job for a slave prostitute.
So you can do it if you try.
I'm about to cum.
Taste all of it.
You seem to have properly learned to cum during a blowjob.
What a pitiful sight there,
Taima-nin, Yukikaze.
The road that these girls tread,
is the road that continues to the realm of debauchery.
What awaits them there? Heaven? Hell?
The true objective that they had as they dove into the darkness,
and Tatsurou's feelings.
Next time:
Rinko, Falls Down.
The decayed body sadly dances on the bed.