It's been one year after the destruction of the Chaos Arena,
but the chaos itself is yet to be quelled.
Not far from Tokyo's waters, lies an
artificial island named Tokyo Kingdom.
On that island, everything is forsaken and shunned by society.
A populated area of those who embraced the
darkness and allied themselves to the jinma. (demons)
I, as well as my sister Sakura, have
decided to infiltrate the Tokyo Kingdom island,
to investigate the possibility of the
existence of the terrorist organization Ryuumon.
As well as to find the whereabouts of the
Taima-nin that was previously sent here.
That distinct aura,
a Taima-nin?
So, our ally?
Saya. My name is Saya.
Asagi-oneesama and Sakura-oneechan, I presume?
Why do you know our names?
That's because.... You're the ones I
have to avenge Oboro-oneesama for!
Oboro, you say?!
A fiend.
I'm not very fond of spiders!
How terrible!
This form you see,
came from tapping into the powers of a Taima-nin!
The powers of a Taima-nin?
Even both of you can transform!
Me and Onee-chan?
Stop such foolish nonsense!
You don't know? Even though it's about your own selves?
Then let me teach you all about it.
All about the powers of a Taima-nin!
Holding Crisis!
Taima-nin Asagi
The Conspilascivious Tokyo kingdom
Episode 01: Rebuild, Once Again
This place is...
Slay a hundred men I did,
rose from the battlefield I came,
but joy was nowhere to be felt.
Friends lost in battle,
no matter how many more I slay,
anger was nowhere to be felt.
Thus,
neither sadness, nor hope can be felt.
Do you desire me?
Call upon your wicked powers, Igawa Asagi!
Begone!
Good morning, Asagi-oneesama.
You look quite upset.
If you're looking for
Sakura-oneechan, she's sleeping at my quarters.
I see, and you look quite happy,
Saya-chan.
That's because... I'm about to mold and train you right here!
All while avenging Oboro-oneesama.
Saya, who are you working for?
It's me.
I already terminated you when the Chaos Arena fell to its ruin!
Pleased to meet you, Asagi.
Pleased to meet me...?
I am Oboro's clone.
A product of the fusion between
human and demon technologies.
A clone, you say?
I am also the head of Ryuumon.
My position here now is all thanks to you killing the original.
You have my gratitude.
I was also born here!
No, this girl is an artificial human.
Using a kunoichi's body as a base,
they awakened her shinobi genes,
thus creating the ultimate warrior.
Kunoichi's genes have dormant yet
great survival and preservation abilities.
She is the very essence of that potential.
You dare say that she's a real shinobi?!
All Shinobis have their true forms within them, asleep.
That of course includes you, Asagi.
Using you, who killed the original as a nucleus,
we are bound to see even greater feats of power.
I am sure it will become a very wonderful living weapon.
I'll never let that happen!
I knew you were going to say that.
We can't use someone as a nucleus if
they do not completely submit themselves.
So I'm going to train you.
Completely, thoroughly, until you simply
become an obedient swine that does nothing but squeal.
You damned bitch!
First, we'll modify those lewd breasts of yours.
Modify, train,
then a swine slave!
What are you doing?
You body is still the same as it was
when modified at the Chaos Arena, right?
The pleasure intensity is now
increased many thousand times more,
so you probably already came as the needles pierced your body.
I can hold and stop my own sensations!
Onee-sama, you're twitching all over.
Such a lovingly slutty voice.
Have you gotten horny already?
How lewd, how lewd!
No, I must not get aroused.
Finish this already!
What an impatient woman.
We still have to inject the fluids till the last drop.
Do you any idea what kind of fluid this is?
I wonder.
This fluid has the ability to change cellular properties,
allowing the addition of more functions to the cells it changes.
In this case, your nipples will become clitorises!
Two huge clits done!
How fortunate for you, don't you think?
Changing the organs used to support an infant into a sex tool.
Cums when fondled.
Cums when sucked!
You'll definitely become a wonderful mom!
It's seeping inside...
It feels hot...!
Oh? The drug seems to be working already.
Getting aroused from something like
this... Onee-sama, you really are lewd!
See? Just a little more before it's all gone.
She finally took the last drop.
Modification complete!
Her nipples have become really big~!
Oh my, how obscene.
O-Oh eah?
Well, I actually like it, you know.
That defiant fervor really defines you, Asagi.
But you see...
Getting aroused while being lashed?
Your clit-nipples are shaking right now.
I can't possibly... get aroused from this!
You're speaking such bland defiance again.
This damned bitch is really getting on my nerves.
I'll give you something even better, then.
No way!
Stop...!
It feels too.. it feels too good!
It should hurt and yet...
No!
No, stop!
Oboro, how dare you try to modify me!
Don't just let some tentacle poke at
something precious as this organ for child rearing!
I can no longer turn back.
I will kill you!
That's it!
I've always wanted to see this rage-filled expression!
It is still within me as well.
The memories of the original just
before she was terminated by you.
That very painful memory...
Asagi, I hate you so much that I just can't help myself.
Seeing you torn and miserable like this
totally arouses me, and makes me wet!
You're every bit the same as the original.
You degenerate!
That's good Asagi.
That defiance is absolutely wonderful.
Show it to me more.
Show me your expression as you defy me!
Oboro!
I-I'm never going to forgive you!
That's not what you say wit that pleasure-filled face.
Oh no, oh no!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
You must not feel satisfaction,
as I still have more to give you.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming hard in my nipples!
Her milk is literally gushing out!
Its sensation should be about the same as a man ejaculating.
I can't stop cumming!
It just won't stop!
This is... stop...!
Stop already!
It's moving in all sorts of directions...
And now for the finisher.
Show me more. The shameless,
stupefied expression you are wearing!
We're going to squeeze every last drop.
Every-last-drop, until your breasts go perfectly dry.
No... don't...!
Such a priceless expression.
The face of misery.
Now I understand why my original craved so much for it.
Sakura-oneesan, you're so slutty!
You've cum countlessly since earlier!
My body's been modified before at the Chaose Arena.
As such, my pussy is craving for it constantly.
The drug I've been taking to counter its effect has worn off.
I have to take one fast!
Stop...!
How sloppy.
Asagi-oneesama would have been able to resist that a bit more.
Both my ass and pussy feel so hot!
Cumming again?
About to cum again?
Try cumming without my permission,
and I'll deliver you some good punishment.
No good...
I'm cumming again.
I'm going to cum again!
I'm cumming!
Sakura-oneechan, you came again!
I... did not...
You did!
You really are such a slut!
What are you...?
What are you going to do?
Punishment: twenty slaps in the butt!
No, please don't!
Oh, but I'm going to do it anyway!
What a terrible expression you have there.
I'm going to make your butt bright red again!
No...
No more, please!
Please forgive me!
Too bad.
You lied, so I'm going to slap you lots instead!
You look like you're having so much fun with this.
Alright then,
one by one is tiring, so I'll go all out at once!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Can't hear what you're saying~.
I beg of you stop this already!
Oh my.
I know that it felt good, but to actually piss from the pleasure?
Delicious!
Sakura-oneechan, I never knew your pee tasted this sweet.
No, don't say that...
Oh, how many times have I slapped you already?
I don't know anymore!
Okay, let's start from twenty!
I wonder what else will come out besides pee?
Onee-chan, I'm going to endure this!
But, but...
Here we go!
First, one slap!
No, this can't be...
I might just come out!
Onee-chan, I think I'm done for.
I wonder if, Onee-chan will will forgive me if I say this...
Second!
I'm cumming!
You came again!
Okay, no forgiving now!
Two hundred slaps!
No, my ass... will be torn apart...!
Have some more!
This dream again.
You seem to be in a total bind.
What a pathetic face.
And people really call you the strongest Taima-nin?
Who are you?
I... am you.
Lust for power, Asagi.
Power?
Ask me to lend you power, and you
shall be easily freed from this predicament.
What are you mumbling about?
Or have you indeed gone crazy?
Forgive me... already...
Forgive me...
...forgive... me...
Now, my Inmas, show it to me more.
The miserable and pathetic self to
which she is now currently falling down into.
No, I can't take any more of this!
Stop!
What a totally lewd sight.
This is perfect, Asagi.
Now I want to play with myself.
Wait!
If you try to suck milk from me now...!
Don't!
Stop, stop!
I'm going crazy!
I'm really going crazy!
Then go crazy!
Oboro...!
Remember this!
It's no good.
No good...
My nipples, my pussy,
even my ass and pussy,
every single one of them is cumming!
And my whole body is cumming with it!