Beings of the dark.
In the future where evil spirits of the rivers
and mountains run rampant around Japan.
They have broken the mutual agreement
to not interfere with the lives of humans.
And the organization that led this charge, Annyaku,
slowly dragged this era into chaos.
But the humans who would resist this are by no means weak.
The humans who could fight against the demons banded
together to form an organization of ninjas.
And the people called them the Anti-Demon Shinobis.
Asuka!
Did you do this?
Answer me!
You don't understand anything.
I'm going to save my younger brother, Kousuke.
Kou-kun?
Did something happen to him?
Wind Technique! Rising wind!
What did she mean by she was going to save him?
You're late, Asagi.
Oboro!
Taimanin Asagi 3 01
Near future kunoichi adventure
Anti-Demon Shinobi Asagi
「Unfulfilled Wish」
Wait... Kou-kun?!
I-I'm so sorry!
That surprised me.
I didn't know you were taking a morning shower, Asagi.
– Hey, Kousuke!
– Sakura-nee!
How brave of you to be peeping in
on her this early in the morning.
– I didn't mean to...
– Wow, so you've finally gotten an interest in a woman's body, huh?
– It was an accident! I swear!
– You sure?
You're not just a huge pervert, are you?
My older brother, Kyousuke, was engaged to Asagi-san.
But he lost his life while on a mission.
And so I was raised by her in the stead of
my brother, saving me from loneliness.
In a sense, she's my parent.
But even so, I...
I can't... I want this woman.
I want to make her mine.
Asagi-san, please get turned on by my ninja technique!
Kou-kun? What was that?
You just did something, didn't you?
Uh...
Was that one of your ninja skills?
What kind was it?
Tell me.
It was a skill to seduce women.
A seduction technique? More precisely
a skill that arouses a woman.
It's a technique that arouses the womb, right?
I'm sorry.
What a bad boy. Did you want to test it out?
I didn't want to test it...
I wanted to use it on you, Asagi-san.
I wanted you to see me like more of a man.
I'm really sorry.
I won't do it again, so please don't kick me out!
Kick you out?
Silly, you're an important part of this family, Kou-kun.
Also, that technique is very effective.
My body's really hot.
Kou-kun...
Asagi-san, I...
No, Kou-kun! Don't hit my butt!
Do you get turned on by getting spanked?
What are you planning on doing to me?
I'm going to make you dirty. I'm gonna
make your body dirty just for me.
It hurts when you smack me like that!
But it feels good, doesn't it?
It does! It feels good when you smack my butt!
Asagi-san, you're mine now.
No, don't...
Now get turned on!
Kou-kun!
Wow, Asagi-san, you're getting more and more turned on!
Something amazing keeps pushing into my womb!
I did it!
I made you cum for the first time!
I did!
Asagi-san, I'm going to make you my woman tonight.
Your woman?
I've raised you as my son all this time,
but now I'm going to be your woman?
Right now, this dick is going to go inside you, Asagi-san.
Is that okay?
Come in slowly.
It's coming inside!
Kou-kun, your dick is inside me!
My nipples feel good!
Lick them more!
You moan nicely.
I wonder if that one just woke up Sakura-nee.
Let's show her how we make love together!
No! What we're doing isn't right!
No!
Your pussy's so tight!
My Asagi-san is so erotic... She's the best!
No! My pussy... I...
I feel like I'm becoming one with you!
It's okay if I cum inside, right?
I'm going to plant my seed inside you, okay?
No, don't! I'm going to get pregnant!
Not inside!
Your semen's flowing out!
My womb's climaxing! I'm cumming!
Don't! Don't play with it right now!
This is amazing! Your pussy's so wet with your juices and mine!
I'm going to lose it. Please! Stop!
Anymore and I...
I'm gonna break!
Then promise me, Asagi-san. Promise
me that you'll be my sex slave.
Sex slave?
Why are you saying that?
Because I love you, Asagi-san!
Now promise me, Asagi-san, or I'll keep
making you cum until the sun rises!
I promise.
I promise I'll do it!
So please stop!
You're not lying, right?
You're going to be my sex slave, right?
I will!
I'll be your sex slave, so...
Please, stop already!
Thank you, Asagi-san!
Okay now, cum from this!
I'm cumming!
My wish has finally been granted!
Asagi-san is my sex slave!
Sex slave...
What are you doing, Sawaki Kousuke?
Asagi-sama isn't here.
Come back later.
But I haven't seen her since this mor...
Come back later!
You always love to bare your fangs
at Kousuke, don't you Mu-chan?
That's not what this is.
I was trying to swat this fly that kept
trying to buzz around Asagi-sama.
You're so gung-ho this early in the morning.
Sakura-nee, I...
Onee-chan's on a mission right now.
She's going to Tokyo Kingdom.
Tokyo Kingdom?
You fell into my trap so easily, Asagi.
Trap?!
Right about now, your precious Gosha Academy should be...
There's no end to them!
Mu-chan, have you seen Kousuke?
Wasn't he with you?
Crap, I'm supposed to be protecting him, but...
It's the Ground and Air forces' new weapon.
The PX-887 Kai Raiden.
I never thought we'd be betrayed by our own government!
It's formidable.
Focus on the enemies in front of us!
The red aphrodisiac is a specially made drug
just for Anti-Demon Ninjas like yourselves.
You're all going to become beautiful sex slaves.
We're gonna make you all regret this!
Even if you beg us in tears to forgive you, we won't!
Why would we apologize?
You're already so turned on now.
Mu-chan!
I'm going to make you feel good too!
So this is the real form of the honorable Anti-Demon
Ninjas? They're just prostitutes!
It's really wet down here too!
Mine just might slip in!
It's inside me!
I can't stop my lactation or my pee!
It's okay if you do the same as her, you know?
Why would I?
Okay, it's getting pretty wet back here.
It's so slippery now.
Let's seal the deal!
Mu-chan, what was that moan right now?
Are you turned on?
O-Of course I'm not. I'm not you!
Don't come inside me!
I'm cumming!!
Do you want semen?
Your pussy's starting to get tight!
I'll give you a huge serving of my cum!
I don't need your filthy semen!
It's cumming inside me! It's defiling me!
I'm going to get pregnant with this much cum!
This is a beautiful sight, Sakura-chan.
Stop looking!
Murasaki-chan is getting so wet just by being touched.
Die! You're all perverted scum!
I'll put this here for Sakura-chan.
Why does this feel good?!
There's so much coming out! I can't stop it!
It won't stop!
Please, stop! I'm going to lose my mind!
No... I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum!!
Don't say that!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming at the same time as his dick!
Looks like we've completed making you
into the perfect cum dumpsters,
I guess that just shows how strong you guys really are.
No! I'm going to break! I'm going to break!!
Even your asshole is completely drenched.
Looks like it wants in on the fun too.
Come on junior, you want it too, don't you?
Don't say that!
My ass doesn't want your dick!
It just went into my ass!
I'll never forgive you if you cum inside me!
They're moving!
They're moving in my ass!
Both of them are moving at the same time!
I'm going to lose it. If this keeps going on...
I told you not to cum in me!
Shut up! Just be quiet and suck my dick!
Your clitoris is so big right now.
It's so easy to pinch now.
I'll let you drink the thing that you love.
I'm going to fill you up!
Yeah!
I'm cumming!
She's starting to really suck me in!
I'm cumming from the cum being sprayed inside me!
Alright, let's go with the finishing touches!
I love cock
Public Urinal
The brandings fit you two perfectly.
So how's it feel?
Thanks for letting me know.
As thanks, I'll give you a swift death.
Don't you care about what happens to Sawaki Kousuke?
A-Asagi-san...
Kou-kun? You don't mean...
We used a technique from the demon realm.
Stand down.
If you don't...
Stop!
I'll save all of you.
Sakura, Murasaki...
And Kou-kun too!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч