An entity of darkness.
A Japan of the near future,
tainted with violence and corruption.
Under its belly,
we were tasked to infiltrate the place,
and rescue Yukikaze's mother, Shiranui.
Provided with a means of infiltrating as slave prostitutes,
we then proceeded to go deeper within.
However,
we were betrayed by our very ally, Zokuto,
and our minds were promptly altered to
prepare us to become real slave prostitutes.
My brother Tatsuro's sweetheart, Yukikaze,
had her virginity inevitably and
brutally taken away by Yazaki Muneichi,
completing her transformation into a slave prostitute.
Now I,
Akiyama Rinko,
am about to face the underworld's known master and head.
My purity is about to be taken,
...by none other than Ryal.
So hot...
My body feels hot.
My part down there is itching for it.
I can feel it becoming really wet.
How's your pussy now Rinko?
How does it feel to have your senses
slowly but surely take over your rational mind?
Shut your mouth, Ryal!
I won't let myself be overpowered by such fabrication!
Do you know what happens to women
we have metally altered as slave prostitutes?
Perhaps you've already forgotten the unsightly
virgin orgasm your dear Yukikaze has shown us?
Now it's your turn to show how
shameless and pathetic you can be.
Behold.
That seal is proof that you're now a slave prostitute.
Trying to resist is utterly useless.
Ryal!
I'm going to kill you!
At the cost of your arms and legs getting blown off?
You beast!
That's my girl.
Let's start then, shall we?
The end of the Slashing Taima-nin Rinko's virginity.
What's wrong?
You're shaking.
Don't touch me with your gross hands.
Your nipples are now getting hard.
Shut up.
Hey...!
Let me go.
I'll fondle it directly.
Stop!
It's my first time being touched by a man like this.
I feel so humiliated, and yet,
and yet...
Is this due to my alteration?
No, I don't like this.
I don't like getting aroused like this!
Good reaction.
I'm going to examine your virgin pussy next.
Stop playing with me...!
Your slit is completely exposed.
What's wrong? Part those legs already.
More.
Lower your hips more and further expose your pussy.
How is this humiliating pose for you?
Getting a clearer idea now of your status as a slave prostitute?
You degenerate!
Your love juices are already overflowing
after having it exposed for a short while.
I'm being pathetically forced to do this,
and yet I'm feeling more and more hot down there.
Hey, don't touch it!
Why it's already very wet.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Stop, don't put your finger there!
As expected of your virgin pussy.
Even with one finger it still feels quite tight.
Your lips are also wrapping around my finger well.
How about here?
No, not there!
It's rubbing.
He's touching me where I'm most sensitive.
His finger's just swirling around it!
I'm going in.
This is quite tight.
It's cramped, and wraps very well.
It feels as if my finger is about to be squeezed and torn off.
How about this rough part over here?
Looks like it's ready.
Alright, three fingers, then.
What is this?
I can't take this.
I can't endure this kind of pleasure!
Something's weird.
I feel hot.
My insides feel hot.
Something's coming.
Something deep inside me.
I'm scared.
I'm scared,
but it feels so good.
It's done.
Rinko.
It's still too early for you to pass out.
Next, we shall finally start the intercourse.
Inter... course...
Look.
The very dick that will take your virginity,
the dick that you ought to remember.
First, you must properly service its tip with your mouth.
A dick, this is a dick.
This length, thickness, and overall appearance,
what a grotesque looking thing.
So this dick will be the one to take my
virginity and make me into a woman?
It stiffened!
It's big.
Something's coming.. so this is a cowper secretion?
Now, suck it.
What's this smell?
It stinks so much that I'm about to puke.
But, I don't hate it.
My mind starts to get all fuzzy as I lick it.
Suck it in.
Looks like you've already taken a liking to this dick.
Alright then.
I'll pump every last bit into your virgin pussy, then.
A wet female's scent...
Your pussy is overflowing, craving for a dick that will fuck it.
Say that you want it.
I want it... in me.
No.
I, Rinko, as a Taima-nin, would like her perverted virgin pussy,
to be completely fucked by Master Ryal's magnificent dick.
It's all because of my alterations as a slave prostitute.
No matter how my body reacts,
my heart will still defy it.
I, Rinko, as a Taima-nin,
would like her perverted virgin pussy,
to be completely fucked,
by... by Master Ryal's magnificent dick.
Once more.
Completely fuck me with your dick!
Completely fuck me with-
Feeling tight?
We're still just at the tip.
Here we go.
Complete penetration.
Very tight.
It's very tight, Rinko.
Tell me, how does it feel for your hymen to finally break?
It feels like my very depths are being ripped apart!
It's stretching it, this dick is just too thick!
Too big, it's just too big!
This is a dick.
Savor its taste.
It doesn't hurt.
He broke through my hymen,
and yet it doesn't hurt.
It rather...
I see, it's wraping around me veru well.
Did you cum with your first dick?
Now that's my cum dumpster.
I shall fuck you from behind next, then.
Wow...
Amazing, this is totally different.
It's rubbing completely different spots than earlier.
The tip is getting caught between them.
It's really stirring my pussy hard!
Oh no...
Why... why is it...
Why is this dick so pleasurable?
My mind is going blank.
I'm going crazy.
Going crazy for dicks!
Dicks are great.
Dicks feel great.
Dicks are the best.
Dicks are the toughest!
Dicks are godly.
Fuck this crazy for dicks girl more!
Push it all the way!
Just keep on fucking me!
I shall use my finishing
penetration deep inside your womb, then.
Amazing.
Just amazing... too amazing!
Your dick pushing me deep through my womb!
It's at the very, very end.
It's hitting, hitting.
My womb feels like it's about to be pierced through.
It's getting ripped apart!
Getting torn to shreds!
Getting penetrated all the way through!
Feel nothing else but my dick.
Taste nothing else but my dick.
Remember nothing else but my dick!
Don't forget, etch it into your mind!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm going to die, I'm going to die.
I'll cum with this dick, I'll cum with this dick.
Dick, dick, dick, dicks, dick, dicks, dicks, dicks, dick, dicks...!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum inside.
I'll have your womb take every lats drop of your very first cum.
It feels hot.
It's pumping in me.
So warm...
We're not done yet.
Just like Yukikaze, don't for once think that you can rest.
This smell...
...it's cum.
What... is this?
Are you finally awake, Rinko?
Ryal!
What in the world is this?
You're now about to commence
special training as a slave prostitute.
Training?
It's a special tool that's used to
continually release and disperse cum.
A flesh vessel created with the
culmination of our demonic technology.
In a few moments, you shall be
continually impregnated with a monster's cum.
I would advice bracing yourself mentally.
If you lose your mind here, then all of
what you've one to this point will be in vain.
Judging from how shamelessly
you came in our earlier intercourse,
are you capable of surviving this?
Just who's going to get crazy here?
Don't underestimate a Taima-nin!
Good.
Enjoy yourself, then.
My breasts... they're going to get ripped apart!
For me to be raped by such monstrosities...
But, now that I've smelled the scent of their cum I...
What?
It's going in!
It's pushing more and more inside my ass.
It's getting stretched.
Feels like it's going to be torn to shreds.
It's tearing me!
Breaking me!
It's penetrating me.
It's penetrating me deeply.
What's this sensation?
It feels like it's building up.
It hurts, and I feel like dumping it all and yet I can't.
I-It feels good!
My ass feels good.
It hurts, and yet I get aroused.
My ass, my ass is being stirred really hard.
My ass feels good.
Now I'm being penetrated in my pussy as well!
By something really big!
One totally big tentacle is now fucking my pussy.
I-I'm being fucked in both holes.
Oh yes, oh yes, oh yes!
My pussy is being stretched beyond its limits!
All of these dicks...
It feels like every dick is fucking my pussy!
It's being burst open,
and it's the same in my ass too!
And these monstrosities just continue stirring me deeper!
My pussy feels great, my ass feels great!
Pussy feels great, ass feels great!
Ass feels great, pussy feels great!
My ass wants to drink cum.
My womb also craves for it.
Please give it to me!
Give me your cum!
Pump all that monster cum into me.
Release it all, pour it all!
I'm so full.
So full that it feels like it's about to burst.
No... no more...
I'm at my limit... I already came too much...
Both my ass and my pussy...
Just kept cumming, and I can't ever go back anymore.
Rinko.
I forgot one more thing.
I didn't mention that you'll be
living inside that flesh vessel for a while.
Two weeks.
You'll never have time to sleep as it takes care of you.
You devil!
This can't be!
I can't survive here for two weeks!
Save me!
Release me from here!
Let me out of here!
Two weeks later
Rinko.
I guess she went crazy after all.
Rinko!
Do you know who I am?
I'm your master, Ryal.
Master... Ryal...
Listen.
I'll throw you in there again if you try to defy me.
I don't want this flesh vessel.
I'll go, so please don't.
Please don't put me in here!
If you don't want to, then you'll have to follow my orders.
Understood, you swine bitch?
Yes, Master Ryal.
I'll do anything.
I'll listen to anything that you say.
So please forgive me.
The Taima-mn, Rinko,
has completely fallen.
Tetsurou...
It's alright.
I still remember.
I'm Yukikaze, a slave prostitute.
Thank you very much for appointing me.
I shall perfectly satisfy your dick with my pussy, sir.
Yukikaze.
It's hitting me, your raw dick is hitting me.
Raw dick feels great.
It's big too.
How's my pussy?
It's small and wraps around nicely, right?
Now, please fuck me hard!
You're about to cum, right?
It's alright, just cum inside.
Just cum deep inside me,
pump it all into this cum dumpster!
So hot.
It's twitching as it pumps cum.
Lost of it is flowing inside me.
It's cumming lots.