An entity of darkness.
A Japan of the near-future,
tainted with violence and corruption.
Under its belly,
we were tasked with infiltrating the
place, and rescuing my mother, Shiranui.
However,
we were betrayed by Zokuto, the slave dealer.
Our minds were forcibly altered to make
our bodies very sensitive to sexual stimuli.
Our virginity was stripped from us,
we were subjected to humiliation, as well as forced alterations.
We spent our days constantly
being violated as slave prostitutes.
Tatsurou.
This is the proof of our love.
Yeah.
I'll protect you, Yukikaze.
I'll protect you with my life.
I'm yours, no matter what.
So please, don't forget.
I believe in you, Yukikaze.
It's alright. I still remember.
I miss you so much, Tatsurou.
Yukikaze.
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
To dyeing the night without color.
tada mu kijun naru yoru o someru
I simply painted the ever-changing moon,
sore wa kagen no tsuki ga terashita
and it shone at the moon's last quarter.
menimieru omote no kao no iro
The color of these shown faces which I can see,
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
is painting the colorless night,
menimienu ura no kao o someru
and also smears the hidden faces which I can't see.
saihate no sora mo umete nidoto
It even filled the ends of the skies and sealed,
kesenai sadame
the fate which would never be erased.
sukui no nai kono mi wa
My own self, which cannot reach salvation,
dareka no ishiki no naka de yurameku
wavers within someone else's consciousness.
aka ni somari sazameku sekai
This world, which will be covered completely in red,
kasanariau futatsu no kioku
with these two overlapping memories,
ketsui o himeta yoru no kage ne setsuna no yurameki
and my momentary hesitation that hides my determination in the night.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I've prepared myself for this already.
Is that so?
This is something I've heard from Ryal.
Many of the bigwigs are about
to gather in this night's orgy party.
I heard that some of the best slave prostitutes,
have already become exclusive
prostitutes to the most prominent of these big fishes.
Then, my mother could be one of them?
There is no conclusive proof.
It's time.
It's as if they're animals in the heat of the mating season.
Mother, where are you?
Looks like the rumored Taima-nin are late.
Yukikaze, and Rinko, I presume?
Yes.
We're pleased to be assigned to you today.
I'm Yukikaze, Taima-nin and slave prostitute.
I'm Rinko, Taima-nin and slave prostitute as well.
Thank you for waiting.
– What service would you like to partake of, sir?
– This flirting expression is starting to become second nature.
– Just requests you wish.
Looks like your dick is already very stiff, sir.
Would you allow me to fellate it with my mouth pussy.
Suck on it, bitch.
Alright, I'm taking it in.
What a stinky dick this is.
It's covered with smegma.
I'm about to vomit.
But, I actually don't hate it.
So good, this smegma's actually good.
His copwer fluids are also starting to overflow.
It tastes so salty and bitter.
I love this taste.
I feel like licking it more.
Show me your pussy.
Okay.
Please, take a good look at it.
This is my pussy.
How is it? Can you see it clearly?
It's already wet.
That's because your dick tasted so good.
I can't help but feel horny as I suck it.
Sorry for having such a perverted lewd pussy.
Oh, please just use it as you see fit.
I've been raped countless times already,
but everyone always praised me for being a really great sex toy.
My clit's being rubbed.
Oh yes, my clit feels good.
I want it already.
Hey, you can fuck me anytime now.
Do you want it, bitch?
Yes, I want your dick.
I can't wait for it anymore.
Please, put your very sturdy dick into my slutty pussy.
Your dick's so hard.
So big!
My pussy's small and narrow, so it's a snug fit, right?
I'll grip it even more.
I want to feel your dick more.
It's hitting my very depths.
It's penetrating my womb,
and it's twisting around while doing it!
Oh yes, my pussy feels great!
More, do it more.
Fuck me more.
Violate it more, penetrate it more!
No need to hold back, because I'm a slave prostitute.
I'm trained to feel pleasure even if I completely lose it.
So please do it more!
Dicks are amazing, dicks are amazing, dicks are amazing!
My pussy feels great, my pussy feels great, my pussy feels great,
my pussy feels great, my pussy feels great!
My pussy's totally horny, my pussy's
totally horny, my pussy's totally horny,
my pussy's totally horny, my pussy's totally horny!
More dicks, more dicks, more dicks, more dicks, more dicks!
My pussy's about to cum, my pussy's
about to cum, my pussy's about to cum,
my pussy's about to cum, my pussy's about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
Give it to me. Give your cum to me.
Pump your cum inside and impregnate me.
Pour all of your cum into this
slutty pussy and make me pregnant!
Cum!
Cum already!
Please cum!
It's coming out... so hot.
So warm.
It's still coming out.
My womb is now full of cum.
My womb's about to overflow.
Getting cummed inside is the best.
Your fellatio feels very good, it made my pussy really wet, sir.
Do my love juices taste good?
There, that's the spot, my clit feels so good.
Bite it, try to use your teeth more.
Pull it with your teeth, please.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum.
Please, let me suck your dick.
It looks so big.
I wonder if it'll fit in my mouth.
Excuse me, sir.
About to cum, sir?
It's alright, just cum in my mouth.
Let me drink your cum.
I'm going to cum in your pussy.
So you're going to put it in my pussy, sir?
I'm honored, sir.
I'm going in gently.
It's still quite big, though.
So... big!
What's this? It's so big that my
opening feels like it's going to rip.
It's as if my pussy's about to be torn apart.
So big, just so big.
So huge... it's actually too huge.
Your huge dick is completely filling my pussy.
I can strongly feel it, like it's about to crush my womb.
Amazing. This just feels too good.
My pussy feels great.
I never thought the Slashing
Taima-nin would be such a dick loving pervert.
Yes, that's right.
I'm a sex toy that loves and craves for dicks.
Violate me more.
Fuck me more and more and more with your huge dick!
Does that include your ass?
Here comes the anal!
Now I'm being fucked in my ass too.
This is the best... the absolute best!
Both my ass and my pussy are being violated at the same time.
Fuck me more.
Make a complete mess of my pussy and ass with your dicks, sirs!
Penetrate and ruin me completely!
Are you trying to squeeze my dick
off with that disgusting ass of yours?
Your pussy wraps around me really nicely.
You're the worst slut ever.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming with my slutty holes.
Both Taima-nin's and this failure of a human,
is about to cum both in her ass and pussy!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
It's pumping in,
both are cumming and pumping cum in me at the same time.
I'm still quite impressed, Ryal-san.
You actually broke these two virgin Taima-nin's this far.
So good.
Tastes so good.
My pussy feels good, my mouth pussy feels good too.
Does it really taste that good, Ms. Taima-nin?
Taima-nin.
Go away, go away, go away!
I'm everyone's slave now.
I'm a prostitute!
I'm a slutty sex toy, a failure of a human
whose only purpose is to fulfill other's sexual desires!
I'm about to cum now.
Face here.
I'm cumming.
It's coming, it's coming out!
You have my praise, Yukikaze.
As expected of my number one, my
most popularly requested slave prostitute.
This boy is also quite happy about it, see?
Tatsurou.
Why?
I see.
So this Tatsurou-kun never knew.
She already quit being a Taima-nin,
and instead chose to be a slave prostitute.
Just look.
She's a slut who bares her pussy to just about any dick she sees.
Tatsurou, don't look.
Don't look.
Looks like her pussy is empty again.
Your beloved lost her virginity with my very own dick.
Why don't I reenact the very moment the mighty
Taima-nin Yukikaze lost her virginity for you, boy?
It's the least I can do for you as an apology, since
you're supposed to be the one to do this anyway.
Stop.
No, stop it, Yazaki.
I don't want Tatsurou to see me get fucked by this stinky, dirty...
and beloved dick.
I'm going to cum immediately
just like when you first fucked me!
You slut!
Tatsurou, please... don't look!
Don't look at how lewd I am.
Please, I want you to look.
Watch carefully how I get violated.
Watch how I get fucked.
Watch how my pussy overflows with love juices,
as I drown in ecstasy with this dick in me.
I want you to watch, Tatsurou.
I want to show it to you.
Yasaki's dick is just the best.
His dick and my pussy are the perfect match.
My pussy loves it.
Even praising it is not enough, for this dick is just godly!
His dick is the best, my pussy feels so good.
His dick is the best, my pussy feels so good
his dick is the best, my pussy feels so good!
Don't look, Tatsurou!
My pussy is about to cum, so please watch.
Stare at it, keep your eyes completely peeled.
Etch it in your memory.
Carve it into your lifetime trauma!
I'm about to cum in her!
Cum, cum, gimme your cum!
Pump it all inside my womb!
Impregnate this slutty sex toy of a pussy!
Let me be pregnant with your child, Yazaki!
Here comes the cum!
It's pumping inside me!
Yazaki's cum.
I was cummed inside... yet again.
It can feel it flowing inside my womb.
It's total chaos inside.
I feel so happy.
Yazaki's my very first man,
and I'm happy with that.
Looks like you're quite the deviant as well.
Well? Do you want to have your
long-awaited first time with her anyway?
Your dick tastes weird with my juices and your cum covering it.
Oh, it's gotten big.
Come on, you can't get a boner yet,
or else I'm going to want to be fucked again.
Tatsurou? I knew you'd come here.
Doing well?
Hey, why did you go back halfway through?
You shouldn't have done that.
You should have watched till the end!
You see, after that,
while Yazaki was fucking me,
everyone started fucking me anally one by one.
Every one of them came inside.
Your dick actually does look kind of good.
I wonder if it would feel as good as Yazaki's when it fucks.
Hey, do you want to fuck my pussy?
Do you want to? Want to? Wanna?
Come on, give me an answer!
Y-Slut-chan's Pregnancy Video No. 4
Notice from the Landlord
Y-slut-chan's Training Video TBA
Y-Slut-chan's Training Video No. 13
NEW
HIstory Refresh
What's with that weird expression?
Oh, you reek of squid.
You've been fapping to my videos again, I see.
I know all about you, you know.
Hey, can you guess who the father of this baby is?
Y-Slut-Chan Training Video No. 13
This is my special Thanksgiving event for
being a slave prostitute for over half a year.
Please, just cum inside to your heart's content.
With this slutty and extremely perverse,
public sex toy.
None other than my, the former Taima-nin's, own pussy.
Have at it, everyone.
I'll most likely get pregnant today.
I think... no, I'll definitely get pregnant!
I'm totally excited!
Please look.
I really can't wait anymore, and it's so wet.
Would you please forgive this sloppy and perverted pussy?
I can't hold back anymore.
I don't care who cums first, just please fuck me already!
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
To dyeing the night without color.
tada mu kijun naru yoru o someru
I simply painted the ever-changing moon,
sore wa kagen no tsuki ga terashita
and it shone at the moon's last quarter.
menimieru omote no kao no iro
The color of these shown faces which I can see,
sore wa iro no nai yoru o someru
is painting the colorless night,
menimienu ura no kao o someru
and also smears the hidden faces which I can't see.
saihate no sora mo umete nidoto
It even filled the ends of the skies and sealed,
kesenai sadame
the fate which would never be erased.
sukui no nai kono mi wa
My own self, which cannot reach salvation,
dareka no ishiki no naka de yurameku
wavers within someone else's consciousness.
aka ni somari sazameku sekai
This world, which will be covered completely in red,
kasanariau futatsu no kioku
with these two overlapping memories,
ketsui o himeta yoru no kage ne setsuna no yurameki
and my momentary hesitation that hides my determination in the night.