After going to the point of no return with
Kou, who I had always seen as my son.
We fell in love with one another.
But that happiness crumbled as if it were a sand castle.
By the hand of our sworn enemy Edwin Black.
As well as the Japanese government who sold us out.
Gosha Academy was destroyed.
And Murasaki and Sakura were captured.
I love sock
Public Urinal
And worst of it all, they transformed Kou-kun into a ball of flesh.
And now, I...
With no choice left with Kou-kun being held
hostage, I let myself be captured by Oboro.
Welcome to the Six night Seven day tour of
the demon world's medical experiments.
I'll make you into an obedient slave,
a pet who'll do anything I say.
Near future kunoichi adventure
Anti Demon Shinobi Asagi
Stop it! It won't fit!
It feels so slimy! Stop!
It's rubbing me so deep inside!
I'm gonna cum! No!!
Three at once isn't possible!
All three of them are hitting my womb at the same time?!
It's spreading me so wide!
My clit... It feels so good!
What is this? It's so good!
Oboro!
I...
I'll never...
Bend to your will!
Stop!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum! I'm really gonna cum!
It's coming! It's coming!!
It's going through me!
I can't! This sex is gonna make me go crazy!
You look pathetic.
I can't give up.
Sakura... Murasaki...
Kou-kun!
I'll save you all!
How's it hanging, Asagi?
Sakura? Murasaki?!
Hey, Master? Who's this bitch?
She's acting like she knows us. How impudent.
Oboro, what did you do to them?!
Don't speak to Master like that without respect, you fucking pig!
These two have been augmented by Master Black.
They've been wiped of their previous memories.
They've been reborn as demons.
What did you say?!
Could we kill her right now, Master?
Absolutely not! If she dies anywhere,
it'll be in the Demon's Arena.
Demon's Arena?!
You remember this place, don't you, Asagi?
The Chaos Arena is where your beloved was killed.
I've rebuilt this arena on top of it.
And now, you'll be fighting Murasaki and Sakura in it tomorrow.
Kousuke's life will be riding on the outcome.
If you kill both Sakura and Murasaki,
I'll return Sawaki Kousuke back to his original form.
What?!
Win or lose, one of my wishes won't be granted.
If that's the case, then...
I'll have to take a chance!
Ninpo: Koujinka!
Prepare yourself, Black!
What?!
Did you just try to attack Master Black?
I guess that means this has no further use.
Stop!
Do as you wish with her.
You look pathetic, Asagi.
Kou-kun!
Something wrong with our clit-dicks?
Clit-dick?
Looks like this little slut has an interest in our dit-dicks.
Yeah, she's been staring at them this entire time.
Your mouth has a vacancy. Why don't you
hurry up and suck this, little piggy.
Why the hell would I do that?!
If you don't, I'll grind that lump of meat into the ground.
Wait! I'll suck it, so don't hurt Kou-kun!
Do it better. Make me feel good, little piggy!
I know you have it in you.
You've already sucked thousands of dicks by now, I'm sure.
She's definitely just as dirty as I thought!
She's reacting really well down here too!
You must be so happy right now.
Know your place, livestock!
I'll suck it myself! So stop moving me like this!
You came!
That was befitting of a pig like you.
Hey, Mu-chan, I can my turn fucking the pig now, right?
What, is her mouth-pussy not good enough for you?
Yeah, I wanna fuck this cheeky little bitch
up until she can't even stand anymore.
Look at how wet you are from Mu-chan's clit-dick.
Don't worry, I'm putting mine in shortly.
It went in!
My clit-dick is filling up your piggy pussy!
Thank her for putting her clit-dick in you.
A pig like you should know that already.
You fucking impudent pig!
She got even tighter. Looks like this little
piggy has a little masochist in her.
I'll spray the cum you like so much all
over you and give you a kid, okay?
Sakura! Please don't make your big sister pregnant! Don't!
Who's my big sister?! You're nothing
but a cum dumpster of a pig!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
The cum from my clit-dick is coming out!
It's coming out!
Cum is really coming out!
Aren't you missing some politeness
in your speech, you fucking pig?!
– My womb is being spread!
– Right here feels good, doesn't it? Cum
from my clit-dick piercing your womb!
I'm cumming!!
I'm not as nice as Sakura.
Brace yourself!
Murasaki, please stop!
You mean Mistress Murasaki!
I'm gonna keep piercing your womb until you call me that!
Mistress Murasaki!
Please stop thrusting your clit-dick inside me!
Mu-chan, I think she wants your cum really bad.
Then beg for it, you pig!
Please, I beg you.
Please pour your cum into my pig pussy!
Well said.
I'll let your womb drink my cum as you wish!
My insides are being spread!
I'm gonna cum from your cum, Murasaki-sama!
Half a year later...
Looking good, Asagi.
I heard that you're willing to surrender?
Come on, answer her!
Y-Yes!!
Th-That's right, Oboro-sama.
I have a child inside me.
I love sex and I'm Murasaki-sama's and Sakura-sama's slave.
Они что, специально издеваются?!
Good work, Murasaki, Sakura.
It wasn't easy.
But after she got this pregnant, she just gave up.
Don't hit me!
Oh, right. Today, I brought the person most important to Asagi.
This is Asagi's husband.
My husband!
Yes! This! I wanted this dick!
I've wanted it this entire time!
It feels so good!
It's so great, my love!
Look at her soft expression.
Is this what having sex with love involved looks like?
It's kind of pissing me off.
Keep having sex, you orc's wife.
Wife? Oh, that makes me so happy.
I'm an orc's wife.
I'm gonna cum, Asagi.
Of course he's gonna cum inside you.
Make sure you don't spill a drop.
I won't! Cum, sweetie!
Shoot your cum inside me!
I'm cumming, sweetie!
I'm cumming! Asagi is cumming!
Here's a reward.
Take my cum as a reward for you two.
Take mine too.
I'm cumming!
Hey, at least try and taste it.
So, are you done with Sawaki Kousuke?
Who?
The guy you raised as your son.
Son?
The only son I have is the one that I'm having with this orc here.
You really are one happy pig, Asagi.
It's my turn now. Move, orc!
Wait, I'm first.
Fucking Asagi-san.
I'll save Kousuke.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч