That day, I was able to possess Yui's body!
Or rather, my spirit possessed her body.
With this app, I can transfer my
consciousness to another person's body!
I just got a text.
See you.
Hmm? Like this?
What's going on?
Is this...
me?
Did I become Yui?
By taking over her body, I was able to
experience a pleasure I've never felt before.
My insides are being messed up!
Hot stuff is coming out!
Who should I try this out on next?
God, I freaking hate that damn baldy.
You shouldn't say stuff like that.
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing...
I see.
Takahashi?
Quit leering at Arisa's tits, you sicko!
What? I wasn't looking at them!
And the pope ain't Catholic.
What you gonna say you can't see
through those creepy bangs now?
Miki, you're going too far!
Whatever.
You really think we can't feel your sick male gaze?
Look, I speak for all the girls when I say this...
Do this shit again,
and you're fucking dead.
Think you can just say whatever you want?
I'll just have to make you apologize to me.
And this app will make that possible.
All I have to do is choose my target, and then
I'll possess their body at the designated time.
Which is just about now!
All right, here it comes!
Takahashi's gross
So this is Miki's body, huh?
Her tits are so small.
Huh? She wrote something.
Fuck this bitch.
Excuse me.
What's the matter, Shintani?
Um...
I...
If it's nothing, then sit down.
I'm really horny right now. Would
you mind if I started schlicking off?
What are you saying?
Stop messing around.
Sorry, my tongue slipped.
Can I go to the bathroom?
Just go already.
Okay.
We're just getting started.
So cold!
So this is the girls' bathroom, huh?
It's pretty clean.
Am I supposed to lift my skirt or pull it down?
This is my first time peeing as a girl...
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
It's coming out!
All the piss in Shintani's bladder is coming out!
Is that it?
I'm surprised the relief of taking a
leak is the same between genders.
All right, time to make you apologize to me.
I'm sorry for calling you gross.
Even if you don't forgive me, please accept
this masturbation video as an apology.
Please watch my pussy.
Okay, apology accepted.
Her boobs are pretty small compared to Yui.
But they're good in their own way, though.
Her nipples are so sensitive!
I guess even a stuck-up bitch like
Shintani can feel such intense pleasure.
Her pussy's starting to get excited.
I'm so deep inside her...
I can feel it throbbing.
This is so good! I'm gonna cum!
I hate her so much, but...
I'm playing with the place she just peed from!
I'm cumming!
Oh, I forgot to hit record.
Guess I'll need to do it all over again.
I'm beat.
I wonder if Shintani's tired too?
But the day isn't over yet.
Ichimiya Arisa...
She's prim, proper, and super fucking hot.
What should I do to her body?
Oh, looks like it's possession time.
Huh? Who's that?
Wait, stop!
This is so gross!
What's going on?
I don't think this is Arisa's room.
Why is she dressed like this?
Can I put it in now, Arisa?
Put it in? Put what in?
You know what it is, bitch.
W-Wait!
I'm not Arisa!
That's no good. I'm paying a lot for this, y'know?
P-Paying?
No! Stop!
This place doesn't have a time limit,
so I can cum as much as I want, right?
Th-That's... I don't know!
You're being too rough!
I can't believe Arisa's doing this kind of work...
You were better than usual.
So you're desperate for money?
You're doing this to pay for you
and your brother's tuition, right?
So that's why she's doing this?
Guess you'll need to work your
ass off, in more than one way.
Wait, not yet!
I just came!
Is he going to put it inside me again?
Why does it feel so good?
Is this a body that's been shaped to pleasure a man?
Ow! W-Wait!
Stop!
You've got this all wrong!
I can't move!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum!
So hot...
Do you mind cleaning my dick for me?
Why am I sucking some dude's dick?
I should hate this, but...
My entire body is shaking.
Arisa's body is craving this.
He came again.
That was so gross.
I never would have guessed Arisa
was doing something like that.
Being fucked as a woman isn't too bad, but...
It's really fucking with my head as a guy.
Who the hell are you?!
You are quite rambunctious.
Wait, you're the girl from the app, right?
Indeed.
I'm a former god who gave you the power to possess others.
Former god?
I was curious to see what a human
would do if they had my power.
In other words, I gave you this app as a way to kill time.
Seems like you used it exclusively
for satisfying your sexual desires.
What?
Watching you lose all sense of morals while
possessing someone was rather entertaining.
Of course, a former god like myself has no sexual desires.
I do not understand how one can
drown in such things so easily.
Anyway, I've grown bored of you.
I'll be taking my power back.
Wait, no, you can't!
Take it back?
So I won't be able to possess people anymore?
You're kidding, right?
I don't want that!
I understand.
I'll give it back.
Could you give me my phone?
I have some important stuff backed up on there.
Understood.
Just wait a little.
Sure.
Like hell I'd give it back!
I have no clue if this'll work,
but it's worth a shot!
Wait, what are you doing?!
Isn't it obvious? I'm taking over your body!
Wait, what happened?
Huh? Why am I...
What's going on here?!
Finally awake?
Wait!
What are you doing while possessing a god's body?!
I'm teaching you the greatness of sexual pleasure.
Your lower half is on fire, right?
You're getting turned on from these huge knockers.
C'mon, put all of your focus into your dick.
Why would I...
Your cock is restless, isn't it?
It hurts if you hold it back.
Just shoot it all out.
Who would succumb to such a worldly desire?
I know it feels good. Don't resist.
How about this?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Just be honest with your body.
Your dick's starting to twitch.
It wants to cum.
So cum and put yourself at ease!
Look! You're cumming!
How was your first orgasm?
It felt amazing, didn't it?
This is... pleasure?
Does this mean my sexual desires have been sated?
We're actually just getting started.
I'll teach you more, Goddess.
I will make you experience the highest
form of pleasure a human can experience.
Looks like my dick can't wait another minute!
Is the though of having sex with yourself turning you on?
I'll make you feel good.
For someone who claims to have no sexual desire,
your body is really sensitive.
Even if you are a god, you're still a woman.
I'm going to start moving.
This feels too good!
I love women's bodies!
So how is it?
How does it feel to experience human pleasure?
It feels good, right?
This is what sex is.
Your erotic body is feeling so much pleasure!
After experiencing this slutty body...
I don't think I'll ever be able to go back to mine!
You want to drown in sexual desire too, don't you?
Drown in sexual desire?
Looks like you understand now.
A human's...
sex drive...
Make me...
Make me feel more pleasure!
Don't stop!
It feels amazing!
I'm gonna cum soon!
You're about to cum too, right?
It's okay. Cum inside me!
That's good!
Give in to your desires!
Cum!
The pleasure of transcending genders...
It's something you never want to let go of.
I remained in the body of the app mascot.
And her soul stayed within my body.
When will you return my body to me?
Who knows.
Aren't you having fun drowning in the pleasures of humans?
Such blasphemy! You will surely be cursed.
I can't be cursed if I'm a god.
No, I'm the god!
Shut your mouth,
you lowly human.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч