I know my girlfriend best
Soul ninst
Navi Fox
Welcome to the app
that will help you get
to know that girl you like!
How about a test run first.
Begin Tutorial
"Get to know that girl you like?" This just reeks fishy.
Yui-chan, welcome back!
I'm back, oni... Naoto-san.
You don't have to be so nervous around me.
I'm not. That's not what...
When my dad remarried, Yui-chan became my little sister.
We've lived together for about half a year now.
Yui-chan is very quiet, loves games,
and doesn't talk to me much.
I wonder what she thinks of me.
If this app is the real deal, then...
Um, I'll be going now.
Oh, wait a second.
Mom called earlier to say she'd be back late.
Yeah, she texted me earlier.
Goodbye.
Touch the button
Uh, like this?
Huh?!
Is this...
I think it's...
Wasn't I just in the hallway though?
What's going on?
– Is this...
– Is this me?!
Did I become Yui-chan?
I can feel her lips.
So does that mean this is Yui-chan's room?
I never thought that this would be how
I'd come into my sister's room.
What's going on?
Soul Insert
Part 1
First encounter in the female body
It's kinda weird looking into the mirror
and not seeing my usual self.
But, right now, I'm Yui-chan.
Basically that means I can do whatever
I want with this body.
I can touch my sister's body... I mean, I'm Yui-chan now.
There... shouldn't be a problem with that, right?
Yui-chari's boobs really are big.
And just look at the dirty look on her face.
Yui-chan, I'm sorry!
The big boobs that seem out of place for
a girl like her are right in front of me!
So this is what real boobs look like?
How am I supposed to resist?!
Yui-chan's boobs are sinking into my hands!
So this is what it feels like when
girls get their boobs rubbed?
What if I touch the nipples?
Oh my god, her nipples are so sensitive!
It feels like electricity's running through
her body every time I touch them!
Now it's starting to get hot down there.
What is this feeling?!
Yui-chan's wet?
This is... vaginal fluid, right?
This is what she tastes like?
Sorry, Yui-chan.
Yui-chan's pussy's a perfect pink. It's so beautiful.
Do girls usually get like this with their panties on?
I wonder what the inside's like.
This is the labia minora and this is the labia majora, right?
And the clitoris is...
What is this?!
It feels kinda similar to rubbing the tip of my dick, but...
Man, masturbation for girls is soo intense!
It's completely different from a guy's!
I need to do it harder.
The clitoris feels so good!
My arousal from her body is seeping into her body!
Playing with her clitoris makes me feel like I'm gonna faint!
Right now with my hands, Yui-chan is...
She's getting off!
She's usually so quiet and reserved, but right now
she's making a dirty face and masturbating!
Her pussy and her expression right now are so loose!
She's moving her hands so hard trying to masturbate!
But this isn't enough to satisfy me.
I want something more!
My finger slipped in!
It went inside?
My finger's being sucked in!
Wow, it's wrapping around me.
This is what Yui-chan's insides feel like... It feels so good!
I can feel the pleasure spreading over me from down there.
If I keep doing this, I'll never be able
to masturbate with my dick again!
What's happening? Something's coming!
This sensation is...
Am I cumming?
Am I really gonna make my sister cum?!
I'm cumming!
I actually kept going until she came.
Yui-chan... I'm sorry.
Wait, what about my body?!
Hey!
Are you okay?!
Yui-chan, what's the matter?
It's me.
Are you really okay?
What do you mean?
What's going on?
Wai... Did I do something to make you mad?!
It's really me.
But the person inside Yui-chan right now is me too.
Um, do you mind getting off of me?
I can see your boobs.
Did I really just get hard?
You're nothing but a virgin, but you're rubbing against me?
But my body's still hot from what I just did.
My body's just reacting on its own.
And my hips are moving on their own too!
If it's my real dick, then...
Wha... Yui-chan?!
I wonder what it feels like.
Wh-What are you doing?!
What does it look like? I'm making your dick feel good.
We can't do this!
Why not?
Tell me...
Onii-chan...
You're not using my name?
Doesn't it make you happy when I call you onii-chan?
How about when I do this?
These are your little sister's boobs that you love so much.
I don't love them or anything.
What are you even saying?!
What a liar.
You've had dirty fantasies of me, haven't you?
I've been wanting to have sex with
you for a long time, onii-chan.
My nipples feel like they're on fire.
Yui-chan's body wants this.
Her body wants them to be touched.
Onii-chan, rub my boobs.
We can't go any further than this!
It's your fault that my nipples are this excited.
It feels so much better than when I do it myself!
Yui-chan's womb is throbbing! It wants a dick!
I'm at my limit!
I'm gonna have sex with Yui-chan's body!
Ow!!
I went too fast and now it kinda hurts.
But right now my dick is inside Yui-chan!
I just stole Yui-chan's virginity and the experience
that girls can only have once in their life.
I just stole her entire first time!
This is terrible, but I... I'm so turned on right now!
Yui-chan's entire being is mine.
Onii-chan, I'm going to make you feel
good now, so wait a little, okay?
It hurt a lot before, but now my
body's slowly getting used to it.
It... It feels good when it thrusts against my womb!
This feels so much better than masturbating!
As long as I hit the right spots, it's
like the pain never even happened.
The pleasure from the dick rubbing against
me is sending shocks throughout my body!
The pleasure from my pussy is spreading through my body!
The timing of my body thrusting and me moving
my hips in this body is in perfect sync!
Yui-chan!
Yui-chan! Yui-chan!
Looks like I'm finally in the mood.
My pussy's getting tighter!
Yui-chan never even had a say in this.
I know I'm doing something bad, but...
Her womb's getting so hot!
Onii-chan, do it harder!
This position... Holy crap!
I can't think straight!
I'm going to lose my mind!
It's going even deeper. Deeper!
It's going even harder!
Don't mess my insides up so much! Stop!
I'll never be able to go back to my
body if you keep doing this!
Please! Stop! Stop!!
It's swelling up inside me!
Are you about to cum?
Are you about to cum inside me?!
I don't care anymore, I'll stay a girl forever,
so just cum... cum inside me!
Etch the pleasure of cumming into
Yui-chan, your little sister!
I'm...
Cumming!!
The hot stuff is coming out!!
Huh? Wasn't I just...
I'm back to normal!
What about Yui-chan?
She's just sleeping?
Thank goodness.
Do you know everything about your girlfriend now?
This is impossible.
Did this app make me go inside Yui-chan's body?
I can't wait until tomorrow.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: oblivionshadow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч