I know
the most
about her!
Find out everything about the girl on your mind!
Welcome to the app!
Navi
Fox
Start
app
Find out everything about the girl on your mind, huh?
There's no way.
Yui-chan, welcome home.
I'm home, Onii-
Naoto-san.
There's no need to be nervous!
No, it's not that...
When my dad remarried, Yui-chan became my little sister.
It's been over six months since living together.
Yui-chan is quiet and loves her video games.
However, she doesn't talk to me much.
I wonder what she thinks of me?
Navi
Fox
Start
App
I know
the most
about her!
everything about the girl on your mind!
Welcome to the app!
If this app turns out to be real, then...
Um, please excuse me.
Hey, wait a sec.
Mom called saying she'll be late tonight.
I received a message from her just before.
Thank you.
Touch the icon
Hm, like this?
Touch
Touch the icon
t
h
the
Isn't this...
I thought...
I was in the hallway...
What's going on?
It's-?!
It's me?!
Have I become Yui-chan?
I can feel her lips...
Does that mean I'm in Yui-chan's room?
I never would have dreamed that I'd end up in her room like this...
What's going on?
Shikkaku
Tamashii Insert
Fansubs
Presents:
SRF - Editing, QC
Tax_Peace - Everything else
Credits:
Episode 01
The First Contact into the Female Body
It sure is strange looking in the mirror and not seeing your own reflection.
But...
Right now, I am Yui-chan.
Which means...
I can do anything I want to this body.
My little sister's body...
I can touch her body, since I'm Yui-chan...?
There's no problem, right?
Yui-chan's boobs sure are big...
On top of that, she's got such a lewd expression...
Yui-chan, I'm sorry!
Yui-chan's big boobs are right here...!
So these are what real boobs are like...
There's no way I can hold back!
It feels like Yui-chan's boobs are sticking to my hands!
So this is what it feels like to have your boobs fondled...
How about the nipples?
Amazing, the nipples are so sensitive!
Rubbing my nipples sends chills down my spine!
My nether regions feel kind of funny.
What's this feeling?
Yui-chan's wet...
This is precum, right?
Yui-chan's taste...
I'm sorry, Yui-chan...
Yui-chan's pussy is pink and pretty!
So this is what's beneath a girl's panties?
I wonder what it's like inside?
Is this the labia minora and labia majora?
Where's the clitoris?
W-Whats this?!
It's similar to touching the tip of a penis, but...
Masturbating as a girl feels too good!
It's totally different than doing it as a guy!
Harder...!
The clitoris feels too good!
Yui-chan's body is getting turned on from me getting aroused by her body!
My mind goes blank when I rub the clitoris beneath the folds!
Yui-chan's body is reacting to my hand...!
Her body is getting aroused!
The usually quiet and non-talkative Yui-chan is feeling good with such a lewd expression!
Her pussy and her expression feels like it's melting...!
She's vigorously rubbing herself with these her small hands!
But, but...
I won't be satisfied with this, I want stronger stimulation!
My finger slipped!
It went in...
My finger's getting sucked in...
Amazing, it's clinging around it...
This is what it's like inside Yui-chan.
This rough, textured spot... It feels so good!
This amazing feeling... It's spreading throughout my body!
Compared to this, male masturbation is nothing...!
What's this? Something's coming! This feeling-
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum to my sister's body!
I ended up going all the way...
Yui-chan... I'm sorry...
Rather, what's going on with my body?!
Hey, isn't there anything strange with you?
Yui-chan, did something happen?
It's the usual me.
Is there really nothing wrong?
Nothing wrong?
What's going on?
Wait-
Did I do something wrong?
It's me, but I'm also inside Yui-chan too...
Um, would you mind getting off me?
I can pretty much see your boobs...
Has my body gotten hard?
This guy...
He's nuzzling it against me, even though he's a virgin.
I'm still aroused from before, my body is hot...
It's reacting on its own.
I can't help but move my hips...
If it's a real cock, then...
Wait, Yui-chan?!
I wonder what it feels like?
W-What are you doing?!
What do you mean?
I'm just making your cock feel good.
We shouldn't be doing this!
Why not?
C'mon...
O-nii-cha-n!
You're even calling me "Onii-chan"!
Are you happy I'm calling you Onii-chan?
Then, how about this?
Look! These are your sister's beloved boobs!
It's not like I like them!
What are you talking about?!
You liar, you were fantasizing about me, weren't you?
I've always wanted to become one with you, Onii-chan!
The tips of my nipples are getting hot...
Yui-chan's body wants these nipples rubbed!
Onii-chan, please fondle my boobs!
We definitely shouldn't be doing this!
Its your fault my nipples have become so hard!
It feels much better than doing it myself!
Yui-chan's womb is throbbing... She wants the cock!
I can't hold back!
I'm going to have sex with Yui-chan's body!
It hurts!
It's a bit tight because it's her first...
My cock is inside Yui-chan's pussy!
I've taken my sister's virginity, a girl's one and only first-time experience!
I've stolen Yui-chan's first...
Even though it's a horrible thing to do,
I'm super aroused!
Yui-chan's everything has become mine.
Onii-chan... I'll make you feel good so bear with me...
Although it was painful before, it's faded away...
T-This...!
It feels so good when it hits against the womb!
This feels much more amazing than masturbating...!
If you know where to rub, the pain of losing your virginity vanishes in an instant!
It feels tingly every time the tip rubs against my insides!
This feeling, it's spreading out throughout my body!
The timing of when I push down and it thrusts up into me, it's perfect!
Yui-chan!
Yui-chan, Yui-chan!
Looks like I've stopped holding back.
My pussy is tightening by itself!
To think I'm doing such things without Yui-chan's consent...
I know it's an awful thing to do, but...!
Her womb is throbbing hot!
Onii-chan! Pound me harder!
This position feels too good!
My mind is going blank!
I'm going to lose my mind!
Deeper... Harder...!
Stop pounding the spot under my bellybutton!
If you don't stop, I can't stay in control!
Please stop! Stop it!
Your cock is swelling up inside me!
Are you gonna cum inside me?
Going to spurt out your semen?
I don't care anymore, just cum inside-!
Cum inside me!
Let me feel it!
Ingrain your little sister's body with the the bliss of being creampied!
I'm cumming...!
I'm gonna cum!
The hot stuff is filling me up!
Huh?
Wasn't I...
Oh, I'm back to normal!
What about Yui-chan?
Looks like she's just asleep. Thank goodness.
Did you find out
everything?
It can't be...
Was it because of this app that I was inside Yui-chan?
Things are going to be fun from now on.
Please use body possession apps cautiously! - Shikkaku Fansubs