I'm the One Who Knows Her the Best
Navi the Fox
This app lets you understand everything
about your girl of shoice! Give it a try!
Start tutorial.
"Understand everything about your girl of choice?"
Sounds like a gimmick.
Yui-chan, welcome home.
I'm home.
Onii...
Naoto-san.
You really don't need to be so formal.
That's not it! It's...
My dad got remarried, and Yui-chan
became my younger sister.
It's been half a year since we
started living together.
Yui-chan is a quiet girl who loves games.
She doesn't speak to me very often.
I wonder what she thinks of me.
If this app is the real thing...
Um, excuse me.
Wait a sec.
Mom called to say she'd be
coming home late today.
Yes, I got the message.
Excuse me.
Click the icon
Like this I guess...
This place.
It's...
I could swear I was just in the hallway...
What's going on?
Is this me?!
Did I just become Yui-chan?
My lips feel soft now.
That means... this is Yui-chan's room?
It's so strange that I'm inside my
sister's room, looking like this.
What's happening?
Soul Insert
A Woman Body: First Contact
It feels weird to have someone
else's reflection in the mirror.
But...
Now I'm Yui-chan.
Which means...
I can do whatever I want with this body!
If I touch my sister's body.
Since I'm Yui-chan.
There's no problem, right?
Yui-chan's breasts are large, just as I thought!
And to think she makes such a lewd face!
Yui-chan, I'm sorry!
Breasts bigger than you'd expect from
a girl her age... and they're right here!
So this is what breasts feel like...
I just can't resist!
My hands are naturally rubbing her breasts!
So this is how a girl feels when
her breasts are touched...
I wonder how the hippies feel?
Wow! Her nipples are so sensitive!
It's like electricity is running
inside me from my nipples!
It feels itchy between my legs. What is this feeling?
I'm all wet.
This is... love juice, right?
So this is how Yui-chan tastes...
Sorry, Yui-chan.
Yui-chan's pussy is so pink and beautiful.
So this is what it looks like under a girl's panties...
I wonder how it feels inside.
This is the labia minora, and
here's the labia majora.
And the clitoris.
What is this feeling? It's like playing
with the tip of my dick, but...
Female masturbation is so intense! It's
nothing like masturbating as a male!
I want to rub it harder!
My clitoris feels so good!
The arousal I'm feeling with Yui-chan's
body keeps bursting forth!
When I peel back the hood while I play with it,
it feels so good that it's making me crazy!
My hands are making Yui-chan feel like this!
Yui-chan is usually quiet and reserved,
but now she's making such a lewd expression!
Her pussy and her expression
are both in sheer pleasure!
I'm using her small hands to masturbate!
But this won't be enough to satisfy
me. I need something more!
I just slid my finger inside!
It's going in so easily!
Wow, my insides are wrapping around my finger.
This is what Yui-chan feels like inside.
This rough spot feels so good!
The pleasure is spreading all over
my body from deep inside me!
After this, masturbating as a guy is just.
What's this? It's...
This feeling means I'm going to cum! I'm
going to cum with my sister's body!
I ended up doing it until I came...
Yui-chan...
I'm sorry.
Wait! What's my usual body doing?
Hey! Are you feeling OK?
Yui-chan.
What happened?
It's the normal me.
Are you sure you're feeling OK?
What do you mean?
What's going on?
Did I do something wrong?
That's me all right.
But I'm also the one inside Yui-chan.
Um, would you please get off?
I can see your breasts.
He's got an erection.
This guy... blaming his arousal on
me even though he's a virgin.
I'm still horny from earlier. My body feels hot!
My body's reacting on its own!
My hips are moving!
If I used a dick to pleasure myself.
Yui-chan?!
I wonder how it would feel.
What are you doing?
"What?" you ask. I'm making your dick feel good.
We shouldn't be doing this!
Why shouldn't we? Tell me.
O-ni-i-cha-n.
She called me onii-chan!
Do you like it when I call you "onii-chan"?
Then how about this?
These are your sister's breasts.
I know that you love them.
I don't like them or anything...
What are you saying?
What a liar. You fantasize about me, don't you?
I've also always wanted to be with you like this.
My nipples feel hot.
Yui-chan's body wants it. My nipples
want to be played with!
Onii-chan, rub my breasts.
We really shouldn't be doing this!
It's your fault that my nipples are perking up, so...
This feels different from masturbation,
and it feels so good!
Yui-chan's womb is throbbing!
It wants a dick inside!
I can't hold back any more!
I'm going to have sex with Yui-chan's body!
It hurts!
This is her first time, so it's really tight!
My dick is going inside Yui-chan's pussy!
I've taken not only her virginity but
also her experience of losing it!
I've completely stolen Yui-chan's first time!
Even though I know this is wrong, It feels so good!
Yui-chan's completely mine.
Onii-chan, I'm going to make myself feel
good now, so hang in there for me, OK?
It used to hurt a moment ago, but now
I'm getting used to this feeling.
It feels so good to have something
thrusting into my womb!
This is so much better than masturbation!
Now that I know which spots to focus on,
the pain from before is completely gone!
The movement of his dick inside me
makes me feel jolts of pleasure!
The ecstasy I'm feeling from my pussy
is spreading throughout my body!
My hips are falling at just the
right time when he thrusts!
Yui-chan!
Yui-chan, Yui-chan!
Finally, my own body is getting into it...
My pussy's contracting on it's own!
Doing something like this without
Yui-chan's consent...
I know it's so wrong...
But my womb feels so hot! It wants this!
Onii-chan, do me harden!
This position feels so good!
I can't think straight! All I want is him inside me!
Deeper! Harder!
You're stirring up my insides! Not so hard!
Any further and there's no going
back. Please stop! Stop it!
Your dick is throbbing!
Are you going to cum inside me?!
Are you going to cum?
Oh, forget it! Give it to me just
like that! Cum inside me!
Teach this body the pleasure of being creampied!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Something hot came out!
What's this?
I was just.
We switched back!
Yui-chan?
She's just sleeping, whew...
Did you learn all that
you wanted to?
You can't be serious.
So this app put me inside of Yui-chan...
I'm going to make things interesting tomorrow.
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч