This is Tokiwa Reiji-kun,
and he will be studying with you all.
Everyone, get along with him, okay?
Wow, so few.
These are all the students in the entire school?
Shiho, who's one year younger, is even
in the same classroom as Midori.
Also, they are all girls.
It's your first time here, right?
Just ask if there's anything that you need to know.
It's okay!
I'll guide him around.
No one comes around here.
So don't worry.
Hey, Midori...
But, we'll be noticed if you talk so loudly.
Woah...
I can tell that it's throbbing hard.
Well?
Does it feel good?
Why?
What?
Well, umm...
That's too intense!
I'm cumming!
It tastes weird,
but I was able to drink it all this time.
"This time", huh?
Oh yeah, she did give me a blowjob last night.
Who was better, Shiho or me?
I just walked away without answering because I got flustered.
And yet...
She just greeted me normally when we met this morning.
And now we're even doing this.
She's acting like nothing happened.
Hey, Midori...
Rei-chan, are you free this evening?
I'm going to prepare dinner.
The vegetables that we grew are going to be delicious!
And just so you know, I'm quite good at cooking.
You should be happy to know that you're
about to have a taste of my dishes.
Rei-chan!
Oh, Reiji-kun, so you're here.
Drop by the faculty office before going home, okay?
There are still a few transfer papers for you to finish.
Rei-chan, Rei-chan, let me borrow
the keys... the one for your house.
I'm going to go ahead and prepare everything.
See you later!
My, my, you two are really close.
Tayu Tayu 2
It's gotten quite late.
Shiho.
Oh, are you keeping beetles?
Wanna have some?
She's not saying anything about what happened.
I wonder what she thinks of me.
If I say that I had mistaken her for Midori,
she might get hurt.
Maybe she'll get angry?
Then, I might get a slapped.
Wait, what's wrong with that?
It's just a slap.
I really need to apologize.
Shiho, you see...
You're having sex?
Sex?!
Oh, you're asking the beetles.
Can the beetles feel pleasure from sex, just like humans do?
Hey...
Wanna do it again?
Alright, I'm gonna do this!
Maybe I was a bit too pushy.
We're going!
Shiho,
what do you think of Rei-chan?
Nothing really.
I had sex with him too afterwards.
Hmm...
You're just nodding like you don't care!
Aren't you surprised?
Just do what you want to do.
I can't really see through that straight face of hers.
No, there's nothing wrong with what I did.
Yup.
Okay, I'm going to do this all the way.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Rei-chan.
You want dinner first?
A bath first?
Or maybe...
You want me?
Oh no, I don't think I'll be able to handle that!
He'll probably take me viciously from behind.
No...
Good...
It feels good...
Huh? What am I doing?
Wow...
This is amazing.
No...
It's deep.
Why did it turn out like this?
Wasn't I supposed to be apologizing?
I'm cumming!
Maybe, insects don't really feel that kind of pleasure after all.
If it does feel good for them,
then they would be doing it a lot.
Hey... Shiho?
Let's do it once more.
I just came, so I really...
Don't take it out.
You can do it slowly.
So, just keep thrusting in and out.
Yes...
H-How is it?
Does it feel good?
It's really sucking me in.
Oh no.
It's sucking it all up and doesn't want to let go.
Do it more.
Make me feel it more!
Yeah, that's what I intend to do.
I'm going thrust it all the way.
Rei-chan sure is late.
Everything's set already.
Yes...
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum.
Okay, just cum.
I'm about to as well.
I'm cumming!
Oh crap, it's night already.
In the end, we did it three more times.
Midori will definitely get mad if she finds out this time,
and I won't be able to say that I misidentified her again either.
The lights are on!
Which means, she's still waiting!
Welcome home!
You're late, the food's gotten cold already.
Mi-Midori...
What's with the outfit?
Oh, so you're with Shiho.
Perfect timing.
You two just eat the dinner there, okay?
I was about to go home.
Hey Midori, are you going home wearing that?!
Huh? Is Midori sick?
How is she?
It's the first time I saw her like that.
She never said a word last night,
and I think something was deeply troubling her.
She might have been really shocked.
I'll go visit her later.
Oh, she's not really sick.
She was already gone when I woke up.
She didn't bring her purse, so I guess she didn't go far.
Perhaps she might...
What are you going to do?
I'll come help if you want...
Well, that was fast.
I'm an idiot.
Why didn't I stop her and apologize?
No, even before that,
why did I do it with Shiho?
Because of me, Midori is...
Where are you Midori?
I will definitely find you.
Try to remember.
Is there... someplace where she would go to?
Could it be...?
There she is!
Midori, don't do it!
Huh?
Rei-chan.
I was deeply troubled and I was about to do what?
It wasn't anything like that silly.
Just wear some clothes.
About yesterday...
I'm sorry.
I don't mind.
I was the one who just jumped to conclusions.
Jumped to conclusions?
Hey!
Wanna take a dip?
It's okay.
No one comes around here.
Oh yeah, when we were kids,
we used to play here a lot.
Although, I still occasionally come here to swim.
I was bare naked, just like this.
I noticed that my mind just feels a lot lighter after doing this.
It allows me to forget bad things.
Oh, we were in that part of the forest,
when we made that wedding promise as kids.
Was it?
Well, enough about that.
I'll just forget about those things.
But in exchange...
Will you become my sex friend?
Wh-What are you saying, Midori?
Actually, I really like masturbating.
I do it a lot while thinking about you.
It was really great.
In my mind, you were really amazing,
and you did it a lot of times, without ever getting tired.
Also,
you're very horny and perverted in it.
But,
even though you're very perverted.
You still looked straight into my eyes.
Sorry for misunderstanding.
Being pushy like that after just doing it once with you.
The you today, the you eight years before, and my imagined you.
All of them kind of got mixed up inside my head
that I could not make out the real you.
Hey, why don't we do it here?
In my dreams, you raped me here lots of times.
I was being forced to do it even though I said I didn't want to.
It's entering me.
Yes.
Your big thing is piercing me.
Thrust it in more.
Push it more intensely.
Midori...
Today...
Just today,
I want you to keep doing it from behind.
No, I beg of you.
We're just sex friends,
so this kind of kiss is...
Then, how about this?
Does my imaginary version push harder than this?
Rei-chan, it's hitting very deep inside.
It's intense.
It's very intense...
I guess you're the one who is the real
pervert who loves doing it outside.
Look, the part where I'm penetrating is clearly exposed.
No...
It's starting to wrap me even tighter.
No, don't say that.
Oh no, this is amazing.
Just too amazing...
I can't take it anymore.
Rei-chan, can I cum now?
I can't stop it.
Okay, just cum all you want, Midori.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Rei-chan,
I think being sex friends is better after all.
Maybe... s-sex lovers.
Sex lovers?
I mean, not as friends, but as lovers.
What's that?
You weren't making much sense there.
A sex lover, huh?
A sex lover...