Tokiwa Reiji
This is Tokiwa Reiji who will be
studying with us from now on.
Let's all get along!
Wow there's hardly anyone... this is the whole school?
Not only Midori who's in the same year, even Shiho who's
a year younger than me is in the same classroom...
And all girls, too...
Reiji is new here, right? If there's anything
you troubled with, feel free to ask.
It's fine! I'll show him around!
People rarely come here, so you don't have to worry.
Hey... Midori...
But even so if you shout someone will find out.
Wow! I can feel it throbbing.
How is it? Does it feel good?
Wh-why?
Why what?
I mean... um...
Wait... not so rough...
Cumming!
Such a strange taste... but I managed
to drink it all this time!
"This time" huh... well she did do it with
her mouth once yesterday as well...
Which one is better comparing me and Shiho?
I panicked and ran away without answering.
Yet...
We said Hi normally this morning,
and we're doing stuff like this...
And she's not mentioning anything about yesterday.
Um, um, Midori...
Rei-chan, are you free tonight?
Eh...
I'll make you dinner. The vegetables picked
from our gardens will taste great!
It may not seem so but I'm actually good at cooking!
You're lucky to be able to eat
a meal cook by me, Rei-chan!
Oh, Reiji-kun, so you were here.
Please drop by the teacher's office on your way back.
There are a few things like procedures
for transferring into school and stuff.
Then let me borrow the keys to your house.
I'll head back to make some preparations!
Catch you later!
My, my, aren't you close.
Translation: Snake | Timing: Nicolai | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Ugh, that took quite a while.
Shiho...
Huh? You're keeping beetles?
You want any?
Shiho's not mentioning anything
about yesterday, either...
What does she think of me?
I wonder if she'll be sad if I tell
her I mistook her for Midori...
Or maybe she'll get angry? I might get hit...
No, that's not the point. Being hit is
nothing, I should apologize properly.
Shiho, um...
They're having sex.
Sex!?
Oh, you meant the beetles...
I wonder, do the beetles feel good like humans do?
Hey...
Wanna do it again?
Alright! Here we go!
I wonder if I was a little pushy...
We're off!
Shiho... so what do you of Rei-chan?
Hmm? Nothing really.
After what happened that day,
I had sex with Rei-chan, too...
Hmm...
What do you mean "hmm"!? How can you keep
a straight face? Aren't you surprised?
You can do what you want.
There are times when I don't get what she's thinking of...
I guess there isn't anything that's "too much".
Yeah! Let's go crazy today!
I'm back!
Welcome home Rei-chan? What would you
like to have, dinner? A shower? Or me?
Oh dear don't hug me so tightly!
Not so rough from behind!
No... it's good... it feels good!
Huh... what am I doing!?
Amazing... yes... amazing!
No... so deep...
How did it end up like this? Wasn't I going to apologize!?
Cumming!
As expected, insects don't feel good...
If it felt good, they'd want to do it over and over again.
Uh, wait, Shiho...
One more time...
I just came so... it tickles...
No... don't pull out.
You can go slowly so... keep going...
Yes... it's getting harder... yes...
It feels good...
Amazing... It's wrapping around tightly...
No, don't!
It won't let go of my dick...
Do me more! Make it feel better!
Sure I will. I thrust harder and harder!
Rei-chan's late...
I'm all done already...
Yes... cumming...
I'm cumming!
Go ahead and cum. Me too...
Cumming!
Shoot, it's completely dark already.
We ended up doing it four times...
Midori's definitely gonna be mad if she finds out.
I can't get away with anything like mistaking
her for Midori anymore, either...
Eh, the lights are on.
So that means Midori is still waiting...
Welcome back!
Geez you're late! The food had gone...
Um...
Mi-Midori! What's with that outfit...
Oh so you were with Shiho! Perfect,
have dinner together!
I kinda have to leave.
Hey, wait, Midori! Dressed like that? Um! Um...
Huh? Midori-chan... is sick?
Um... how is Midori doing?
It's probably the first time I saw Midori like that.
She hasn't been talking since last night,
and she looks really depressed.
I guess it was really shocking for her.
I'll go visit her later.
By the way, she's not actually sick.
When I woke up she had already left the house. She didn't take
her purse with her, so I guess she's not going anywhere far.
It could be that...
What are you going to do?
If you want to I could...
Oh. Fast.
I'm such an idiot! Why didn't I stop her
and apologize right away last night'?
No, before that, why did I do it with Shiho!
It's my fault that Midori is... Where are
you, Midori!? I'll definitely find you!
C'mon, remember something... something...
Somewhere she might go...
Oh, could it be...
There she is!
Midori!! Don't do anything stupid!! Huh?
Rei-chan...
You thought I'd be so depressed I'd try to drown myself?
Why would I do something so stupid!
W-wear something already...
About yesterday... um, I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it. It's my fault for misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? Hey...
Wanna try it out?
Don't worry, people don't come here often.
Speaking about that, we used to play here
a lot when we were kids, didn't we?
I still come here to swim once in a while, naked like this.
And then I feel really comfortable and relaxed,
and I'll forget about all the bad things.
Oh it's also those woods where we made the promised
to marry each other when we were kids.
Oh, really...
Well, it's fine.
I'll forget about stuff in the past, too.
In exchange...
Wanna be sex friends?
Wh-wha-what are you saying!
Hey!
To be honest, I really like masturbating...
I do it over and over again every
night, thinking about Rei-chan...
It's amazing... in my imagination, Rei-chan is super energetic
and stays hard even after we've done it so many times...
In addition, you're a pervert and a maniac
and you enjoy fucking outdoors.
But even though you're a real pervert,
you love me straightforwardly.
Sorry for misunderstanding... doing stuff like a
pushy wife just because we had sex once...
I mixed up the real Rei-chan with the Rei-chan
who's been in my head for 8 years...
Hey, wanna do it up here?
I get violated by Rei-chan a lot on this rock.
You'd force it on me.
It's going in!
Yes... Rei-chan's big thing is penetrating...
Thrust more... do it rougher...
Midori...
Today... Just today... only do it from behind...
No... please, Rei-chan...
We're just sex friends... don't kiss me like that...
Then, how about this?
No...
Am I rougher in your imagination?
No... Rei-chan... all the way inside...
Rough... Rei-chan you're too rough!
Turns out the pervert who loves
public sex is not me but Midori!
Hey, the place where we're connected
is completely exposed to the sun!
No!
Woah, you're squeezing real tight!
Don't say stuff like that...
No... amazing... Rei-chan is too amazing!
I can't anymore... Rei-chan, can I
cum? I can't hold back anymore!
It's fine. Go ahead and cum!
Cumming, cumming... Cumming!
Rei-chan... let's be friends with benefits, okay?
Yeah... well, um, then, lovers with benefits?
Lovers with benefits?
Um so... instead of friends... lovers.
What's with that? You wouldn't need
to add benefits at the end then.
Lovers with benefits, huh... Lovers with benefits!