Oh, this is good!
A bath in the backyard. This could
never happen if I didn't live alone.
The view is good, too.
This is so refreshing!
You sure look like it feels good.
I want to take a bath later, too!
Who are you guys!?
Ah, could you be...
What's with that? Did you forget the
faces of your childhood friends?
I see, you couldn't tell because we've
grown into such beauties, right?
Tayu Tayu
Translation: Snake | Timing: Nicolai | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
If you want to live alone, go live
in the countryside back home.
Leaving words like "No one's there
at the moment so it's perfect!"
and "If you don't want to you can just come with us!",
my parents left to work abroad.
Geez, I wanted to live in the city and have fun!
Call a bunch of friends to hang out or party until it's late.
I could invite my girlfriend over...
though I don't have one.
Geez, how is this place so messy!?
What's with this mountain of dust!?
This is the house where my family
had been living until 8 years ago.
After been abandoned for so
long while we lived in Tokyo,
I guess there's no help that it's this dusty.
Geez, standing here feelings upset won't get me anymore.
I'm just gonna do whatever I want!
Oh, I know!
There we go.
There! Open-air bath!
So, you're taking a bath although you
haven't done any unpacking at all!
That stupid part of you hasn't changed has it, Rei-chan.
But this does look really good. Wanna go in later, Shiho?
If we do that it's going to get late.
Geez, you're so cold.
Tokiwa Reiji
Amane Midori
Amane Shiho
Midori and Shiho are sisters living next door to me.
Midori is the same age as me,
and Shiho is a year younger.
They heard that I'll move in today and came to help but...
But this is quite amazing... I guess
dust can pile into mountains, huh?
We should have come and cleaned up first.
Ah! Don't look!
You don't have to touch the smaller boxes, so...
Hey, look, look, how's this?
Don't I look nice as well, Rei-chan?
What are you going?
Why are you still embarrassed about this?
Aren't we best friends?
What?
Don't you dare say you forgot...
C'mon, just show me!
No, why do I have to do something like that?
C'mon, please, I'll never ask for anything else again!
That's...
Then, in the future, can you make Midori your bride?
Okay, of course!
If that's the case I guess it's fine.
Amazing, so it looks like this...
No, don't stare at it too much...
It's your turn now, Rei-chan.
Not doing that!
Rei-chan, you meanie!
Did that happen?
Dude, you're horrible! Even though you saw all of me...
I know, let's continue from back then.
It's your turn now, Rei-chan.
What!? What are you thinking!?
Well then do you want to see Midori's again?
Or we could go beyond just looking and...
Wait...
Oh, it got big.
Don't look!
Where does this go?
Ah, the room over there...
Look, Shiho's working that hard. What's with you?
Sorry, sorry.
That scared me. Come to think of it that did happen.
I remember now. Eight years ago...
She cried so much when I left.
Rei-chan you liar! You said you'd marry Midori!
I wonder if that means she's happy
to meet me after 8 years.
Although it's kinda crazy...
Hey, Rei-chan?
Ye-Yes?
When all the cleaning is done, can I use the bath?
Go ahead.
Wanna go in together?
Dude!
Yeah, I don't mind.
Thanks for everything today. It really helped.
Well then, see you later.
Later, we'll go in the bath together...
Touch each other naked...
Hey what do you think you're doing!?
We're just taking a bath! Don't touch me!
That should happen, right?
It should be like...
Rei-chan, come...
Ouch.
I fell asleep!
So dark! What time is it?
My clock is still in the boxes...
Geez, what am I doing?
Did Midori come? Did she decide not to?
She's there!
What do I do, should I just go like this?
Or she only planning to take a
bath and anything else is...
Stop it, you pervert!
What am I talking about? I can't
chicken out, I'm already here.
She's definitely waiting for me.
There, sneak in quietly without a sound...
Is this okay? If she screams from
suddenly being hugged...
Well I guess I could just shut her up with force no
that's not it! I'm not some kind of monster!
It's fine, it'll go well!
Good, she's not resisting. She
was waiting for me, after all.
Well then... Wow, so soft...
And they're this big, too. Great
growth during the 8 years...
Shiho?
Um, err... Ah!
Are you alright?
Err, um, where's Midori?
She got out of the bath and left just a while ago.
I see...
So it becomes like this.
Shiho, what are you...
Amazing... it's twitching and pulsing...
So guys become this hot.
Does it feel good?
It feels good but... Shiho...
That's good. I felt good as well.
This time down here...
touch me.
Ah... wait...
What is this? She's so wet...
The juices won't stop flowing...
It's like she's peeing herself...
Well, I'm putting it in.
Shiho...
It's in... I'm wrapped by the wetness
all the way to the bottom.
What is this? This feels amazingly good!
No... N-no...
Shiho, this was... your first?
It's fine... It doesn't hurt that much, so
you can move more if you want to.
I probably won't be able to stop even if you told me to...
So rough... Rei-chan!
Sh-Shiho!
Deep... Rei-chan's is going all the way inside...
Amazing!
Damn, I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, Shiho!
It's fine, cum, let it out like this!
Cumming!
Well then, I'm off. Don't catch a cold.
It felt like I could've died from feeling too good...
Ah, I don't want to move.
Rei-chan, are you awake?
Midori...
Wait, wait a moment!
I said wait... let me grab underwear...
Oh, so you were taking a bath.
What do you want at this time of the day?
Didn't I say that I was going to borrow the bath earlier?
Huh? Didn't you already use it?
How did you know? Weren't you asleep?
No... err...
You weren't actually awake and peeking, were you!?
I wouldn't do something like that, you idiot!
Oh really? You said you'd come
in together earlier today, too.
But you didn't have the guts to come at me, did you?
The guts... I did have the guts, but...
It was Shiho instead of Midori there...
And we even did it all the way...
Well, I guess it's fine.
Huh?
It's nothing.
Hey, Rei-chan, wanna go for like a walk?
It's so cool and refreshing!
Come to think of it, what was Shiho trying to do there?
I attached her by mistake, but instead of
refusing she even approached me...
She ended up leaving as if nothing happened, but...
Rei-chan...
Rei-chan!
What does she... think about me?
Hey! Rei-chan!
Hey, Rei-chan! Where are you dozing off to!
Listen to people talk properly!
Sorry.
Geez, fine. C'mon, we're here.
We're where?
School...
Wow, this is so nostalgic! This place didn't change at all.
Yeah, there was a pool on this side.
I still remember. Everyone loved playing here.
This classroom doesn't have any tables...
Yeah, because there aren't any elementary
school students here.
Huh, why?
I guess you could just call it depopulation.
More and more people are leaving the village.
We might be moving elsewhere around next year, too.
Huh, really?
Yeah, really.
Well, good things did happen in the end.
Good things?
Rei-chan came back!
This is a sign from the gods saying
"Make lots and lots of memories"!
Midori...
Well then, what kind of memories shall I make?
As expected it should be like those kinds
of things, or these kinds of things?
Come to think of it it's about time
the pool opens. I'd love to swim.
Well then why don't you swim?
What are you doing!?
Let's make this one of the memories.
H-Hey, Midori...
It's showing, it's showing...
Rei-chan, how long are you planning
to make me wait for?
It's about time you looked at me properly.
Of course I want to look!
But just now I was... with Shiho...
I'm not that indecent...
Rei-chan!
Wait, Midori!
Even if you do this to me, I...
Rei-chan...
This is bad. She's really cute...
You idiot!
Don't suck that much!
Midori's boobs are really soft. They're huge, too.
You sisters both have quite erotic bodies.
Shit, what am I saying?
Hey, how do you know about Shiho's boobs!?
Don't say that... I'm actually bothered by it...
Let me do it next.
Eh?
Can I lick Rei-chan's?
Amazing...
Lick it...
Yes...
Midori's mouth is... so warm!
Does it feel good?
Her tongue is wrapping around... great!
How's this?
Midori...
Feels great, doesn't it? I finally got to do this.
Finally?
I've been waiting to do it for Rei-chan...
So you were actually a perverted girl...
You finally realized.
Shit, if you do that... I'll cum!
Hot!
I'm all covered in Rekhan's...
Well then, it's your turn again, Rei-chan.
Do me?
No, it tickles...
Your panties are kinda cute...
I picked them out just for today...
Well I'll put it in with the panties still on.
No... there's so much...
I'm going to move, Midori.
No, you can't, Rei-chan...
So deep... it's going all the way inside... amazing!
A real one is amazing!
A real one?
This is too rough... Rei-chan, Rei-chan!
That's... that's cheating... it's because you
were thrusting so hard while kissing...
I came just now...
It's fine... I'm at my limit, too.
It's fine, cum inside of me!
You can let out all you want!
Rei-chan, Rei-chan, Rei-chan!
Cumming!
It's flowing... so much of Rei-chan's hot stuff is inside...
Amazing, Rei-chan. You let out so much
and yet you're still hard inside...
It's because Midori's feels good.
I'm so happy to hear that!
Who was better, me or Shiho?
Let's see...
What!?
Ah, it shrank.