Thank you for all of your fan letters!
Reina-chan, are you alright?
O-Oh, sorry. Yes, I'm fine.
Th-This is my first fan meet, so I'm just a little nervous.
I went all out because this is your
first fan meet, Reina-chan!
Thank you!
I'll keep doing my best, so please continue supporting me.
Please do something! I haven't had any
work since last week! Not even a little!
Calm down, Reina.
You just need the right timing and some luck.
I joined this agency to actually have a career as an idol.
If I can't even do that, then what's
the point of me being here?
Do you have the guts to do what it takes?
Guts?
The guts to do whatever it takes to get big.
Of course I do.
If it's for the sake of promoting myself.
Angel Covered in Filth
Alright, who's next?
Okay, see you again.
Out of time already?
I'll come to see you again!
Thank you! I'll be waiting!
Yes, when I speak with my fans, I get
so happy and filled with energy.
I'll keep doing my best, so please continue to support me.
Ms. Reina Changing Room
Whew, Reiha-chan, good work out there.
I bet all the fans out here would be so surprised if they
found out you had this in you while shaking their hands.
If you didn't help me out, I don't think I would've even
gotten this many fans to come today, Matsunaga-san.
U-Um, if possible, I'd like to thank you.
Oh, no, it's fine, you don't have to thank me.
I still want to thank you though. Are you sure
that there's nothing I can do for you?
If you're this insistent, it'd be rude
for me to refuse any further.
Well then, please allow me to take care of you.
That's good.
It's my first time doing something like this here.
Matsunaga-san, your dick is so hard and
hot... I've never had anything like this!
How about it? Sucking my dick like this must
make you very aroused too, doesn't it?
Yes, my heart is pounding like crazy!
All these dirty feelings are coming
out and my pussy is so wet!
Yeah, that's it. Give me more of that!
Please leave it to me.
Please enjoy my mouth to its fullest!
Oh yeah, that's the stuff!
Your technique is so good, I think I'm gonna cum already!
I'm so glad that this pleases you!
There's a lot of slimy stuff coming out from the tip!
This is it!
Go ahead. Please cum.
I'll take it all in with my mouth pussy!
Here I go!
I've always wanted to cum on an idol's
face at least once in my life.
There's so much.
Matsunaga-san, your cum is so hot and
drippy... there's so much of it too!
So, Reina-chan?
You're not done showing your gratitude to me yet, right?
Yes, of course not.
I'm willing to do anything if it's to
make you happy, Matsunaga-san.
It'd be bad if my skirt got dirty before the next fan
meet session, so I'm going to take it off, okay?
Having sex with you makes me feel like I'd never go limp.
In that case, I should try my best.
It's inside!
First, please thoroughly taste my pussy.
Being inside you feels so amazing!
Really?
If that's so, then I'll try being a little rougher.
Reina-chan, you're soaking wet.
What a dirty girl.
Don't say that, it just feels so good!
Oh no, I can't stop my hips from moving!
Your dick's so hard, it's making me more and more horny!
I think I'm already about to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Reina-chan, I'm gonna turn you around.
Look, Reina-chan, everyone can see your private parts.
This is so embarrassing.
Everyone can see your dick inside me.
Look at this. Your nipples are incredibly hard too.
You're such a dirty girl, Reina-chan.
I am.
I'm sorry for my nipples being so hard!
I'm sorry for being such a dirty idol!
My pussy's so wet right now!
If you keep moving that wildly, I'm gonna cum!
Me too. I think I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum! I'm going to cum!
Cum! Please plaster my pussy with your cum!
You and I are perfect sex partners!
That makes me so happy!
Reina-chan, here I go!
Yes! Yes!
Together! Let's do it together!
Amazing! It's squeezing the cum out of me!
Your dick is twitching and your
hot stuff is flowing inside me!
That was so good, Reina-chan.
I'll be sure to take care of your next job too.
Yes, thank you very much.
I appreciate all of your help, Matsunaga-san.
Oh yeah, that's great!
You're great at this, Reina-chan!
U-Um, is this swimsuit really the best choice?
Well, this is for a feature in a magazine about young idols.
Gotta leave a lasting impact, right?
Reina-chan, try spreading your legs apart more.
This position is embarrassing.
Please don't stare so much.
That's a good expression! Very sexy!
Alright, now try to sell yourself a little more.
My heart's beating so hard and my body feels so hot.
I'm starting to feel strange.
Reina-chan, we're already in this deep,
how about you lose the top?
Huh? B-But...
Just cover them with your hands. That's what all
the idols do in their gravure shoots nowadays.
I think doing that will really bring out your beauty more.
O-Okay, I'll do it.
Okay, I'm taking it off then.
Yeah! This is perfect!
It's very mature... I like the way this is turning out.
Oh, thank you very much.
It's very embarrassing, but if you
can get good pictures out of it...
But hey, Reina-chan, if we're aiming for you to be on the
front page, we might need a little more effort from you.
Effort?
I think you know what I mean.
Y-Yes, um...
Is it alright if I start to try harder right now?
Of course.
Reina-chan, you've gotten so much better at this.
Come on, tighten your pussy more.
Make it real tight.
I'll do it. I'll squeeze it real tight.
I'll do my best to make sure that you enjoy yourself!
That's it! Deeper!
That's good. You're making me go crazy!
Do you have any experience back here?
That's not... That's not the right place at all!
That's my butt hole!
That's a great reaction!
Don't worry, you'll get used to it in no time.
I can feel something in my butt! It feels so weird!
This is a good chance. Might as well get
used to doing it in the ass, Reina-chan.
You want a good spread for your photo shoot, don't you?
I don't think it's bad to be a friend to me.
O-Okay.
I'll let you have my anal virginity.
Please be gentle.
I know. I know. Just leave everything to me.
Damn, you're so tight!
Your ass is so amazing, Reina-chan! Just what I thought!
That's great!
Please enjoy yourself with my butt
and asshole as much as you want!
I can't believe you're already feeling so
much pleasure from your ass already.
You really are a dirty girl, Reina-chan.
No! Please don't say that!
There's something wrong with me!
This is so embarrassing, but my body's
just so turned on and it feels so good!
If it really feels that good, how
about I join in on the fun too?
Matsunaga-san, what are you doing?
Reina-chan, your pussy looks lonely.
Let's make this a group activity.
N-No, you can't!
Two at the same time, that won't...
Wow, you're so wet!
I think I can go all the way in!
It's inside! See, you can do anything you put your mind to!
Wow, your dicks are rubbing against each other inside me!
This is perfect! Your ass hole is twitching
so hard! I love this feeling!
I've never felt anything like this before!
The dicks are stirring me up so hard!
I feel like I'm going to lose my mind!
Your moans are getting me so turned on.
More! Let out more of those dirty moans!
Please play with them! Play with my dirty
pussy and ass hole all you want!
More! Play with them more!
I'm so sensitive right now!
Can you tell?
Crap, I'm about to cum!
I'm going to cum!
Both my butt and my pussy feet like they're about to cum!
We'll make you cum a lot, so take
in all our cum, Reina-chan!
Okay, please cum!
Please mess up my body with your dicks!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
A few weeks after that...
The magazine that they were taking pictures for came out.
And the one on the cover wasn't me.
Kuramoto Mirei?
A one-in-a-million beauty.
She's gonna get big.
And with every passing day, her popularity rose,
gaining even more attention than before.
Shows on TV, commercials, drama series, concerts, movies...
everything I wanted to obtain, she got in barely any time at all.
Requests for work became so scarce and both
Matsunaga-san and Kondou-san began to dodge my calls.
KONDOU
Now we might be out of cards to play.
That can't be!
You can already tell, can't you?
Kuramoto Mirei, she's the real deal.
Real deal?
It's not a problem of your talent at
singing or acting or even looks.
She has an aura that can brighten
anything just by standing there.
That's what a real idol is.
But I'm just getting started!
I have a photo shoot next month
and I even have a fan meet!
Yeah, you're right.
Just follow my way of doing things.
Thank you for waiting!
Now then, I'd like to begin the fan meet for Kisaragi Reina!
Hi everyone...
I'm Kisaragi Reina.
Thank you for coming today.
Well, we're about out of time, so please
give a hand for Kisaragi Reina-san!
Reina-chan, I'm sorry.
I thought we'd get a little more traffic here, but maybe
I just didn't spread the word around enough.
No, that's not true.
No, if I tried harder...
No, thank you. Really.
I need to try harder.
If you have another opportunity, our shop would
be more than happy to help you out.
U-Um, do you need help with that?
Huh?
I'll help you out.
What do you think?
A-Am I dreaming right now?
Didn't you want to see this?
My pussy that is.
W-Wow.
I get to see an idol's soaking wet pussy!
It's not just wet.
It's also really slippery and tight.
Would you like to try?
R-Really?
Having sex with an idol? You're
such a naughty shop employee.
Reina-chan's hands are stroking my dick!
You're so hard!
I'll melt it down with my pussy.
I'm going inside Reina-chan!
It's inside me!
It's so big and hard!
Please shove your dick into my pussy as much as you want!
How is it? Is the inside of my pussy really wet?
It's amazing! This is like a dream!
This is real. You're having sex with a real
idol that appears on TV right now.
Right now, I'm really... With Reina-chan!
Your dick's rubbing against me... it feels so good!
Your dick is thrusting into my pussy
so hard! I can feel it so clearly!
No! I'm gonna cum!
Me too!
I'm gonna cum too, Reina-chan!
Please cum inside me.
N-No, I can't!
Please! I want to feel your cum pouring into me!
I-It's coming! I'm cumming!
Wow!
There's so much hot stuff pumping into me!
Please. I want you to do me one more time.
Next, I'd like you to thrust at me from
behind with everything you have.
Please give me more semen!
I want you to cum in this idol pussy!
I-It's inside!
So deep! It's coming in me so deep!
This is so good!
I think I'm gonna cum again!
This idol pussy's about to cum!
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Okay well, since you let me cum inside you twice,
I'll set up two events for you, Reina-chan.
That was pretty great. I can't wait until next time.
Th-Thank you very much.
How'd it go?
Not bad at all.
Hope to work with you again.
Please take good care of Kisarigi Reina in the future as well.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч