Hey, Hiro! Hiro, c'mon!
I think it was, the Intellectual Culture Studies' Association?
Shall I join your club?
Just so you know the club's activities
don't make any sense...
That’s fine; it seems to be fun with Hiro around.
Let's get along, Hiro.
To Hiro love, Club Application
Intellectual Culture Studies' Association
*Sniff Sniff* | Squid
Nanace-cenpai
Hiro-pon...
I'll give you, something very important to me.
Woah, peeping photos?
Even so... that's such a nice ass...
Hiro, what are you doing?
Sorry about that.
That's, that's um...
Hiro, is that...
This is, err...
Photos of me?
I was planning to jerk off!
Masturbating... to me?
Yeah...
That was supposed to be a joke... this is bad, this is bad!
This is bad!
Hey, um...
Y-Yes?
Wanna... have sex with me?
TENIOHA!
~Girls Are Actually Naughty it Well?~
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Hiro's tongue is so perverted!
Let's take a quick break...
I think I'm drunk... from the kiss...
Hey, Hiro...
This is kind of embarrassing...
Your body is great.
The boobs?
Including the boobs.
That's a perverted way to touch it!
No!
Not there...
You'll leave a mark on my boobs...
Hiro's finger is... inside...
It's making... lewd noises...
Hiro's is... twitching...
Hiro... it feels lonely down there...
I’m giving you my virginity... so...
Yeah... I'll be as gentle as I can.
Aren't you a little too wet?
That's because Hiro kisses too lewdly!
If I think about it, I can make out Hiro's shape inside...
Well, here I go.
All yours.
It hurts!
Ami!
Don't stop... let me feel the pain of my first sex...
It's rubbing inside!
It's making squishing noises... going in and out...
So this is sex!
Hiro’s is getting bigger!
It's because it feels good inside Ami.
Even though I'm in so much pain... no fair...
I can't hold back.
It's fine, let it out inside!
Deep inside!
Wow... sex is amazing...
Hiro's is still large, isn't it?
Your sperm is overflowing... is so strange!
This might feel good...
Even though it's my first time...
even though I was a virgin...
Thrust harder and faster inside me!
It feels good!
It feels good... I'm getting messed up even in my head...
No...
No... Hiro!
It's quivering inside...
Is he ejaculating again? Is he going to cum?
Give me semen! My womb is yearning for sperm!
No... semen is overflowing inside...
Geez... you let it too much!
I guess it's because we're really
compatible with each other.
I guess.
Hiro...
Let's do it again sometime.
After that, Ami and I got really into having sex.
Let me... take a shower first.
Why?
I'm sweating...
This is amazing.
Don't sniff at something so embarrassing!
It's got a really lewd smell.
He's smelling the lewd smell of my armpit!
His tongue is twirling around!
It's extremely sour, such an embarrassing smell.
He's tasting every nook and corner!
Hurry! Hurry and stir me up!
Hmm, what should I do...
C'mon, here! Put it in here already!
I guess that can't be helped.
A large penis going in so suddenly!
Your penis is rubbing inside!
It's wrapping around me... the tightness is amazing!
Your penis is going all the way deep inside!
My boobs feel good...
Hiro...
More...
Amazing...
Ami's pussy is really the best!
I love Hiro's dick, too!
It feels good! Sex is so good!
Your penis is rubbing inside me happily!
My womb is going to break!
You're squeezing really hard!
It feels really good when you rub!
Yes! Yes... thrust deep inside me!
Inside!
Give me the thick stuff!
I came while you spurted sperm inside me...
It was meant for couples or friends
to take a memorable photo...
But what happens when it comes to us...
Okay, we're shooting!
Yeah, let’s take one full of memories.