Good morning, Izumi-kun.
Good morning.
You seem sleepy.
What could you have been doing late at night?
I'm interested in your name.
Can you write it here?
Okay...
Great.
Intellectual Cultural Studies Association, eh?
Club Application Form
Club name: Intellectual Cultural Studies Association
Club President:
Hey, wait Hibiki-senpai!
What's your nick name?
Most call me Hiro.
Hiro, eh?
You can call me Nanase then.
Well then, Hiro.
Go get some members for the club, okay?
And with that,
signaled the start of my "no-longer-peaceful" school life.
Intellectual Cultural Studies Association
It was a club that I was tricked into making,
but I spend most of my after school time here.
The club's objective seems to be intellectual cultural research,
but this is actually what it is.
Thanks for waiting, my kittens.
For this kind of club to have been accepted as an official club,
something must be going on behind the scenes.
Tenioha!
part 01: Power, Sexual Harassment, and a first time experience?
~ Even girls are quite perverted you know ~
It's your favorite "falling panties" trick!
Getting it all hard in this situation...
You really like getting a raw footjob, huh?
Yeah, it's the sensation of the feet wrapping around it.
I'm going to take good care of this perverted dick then.
Here, cum already.
Show me how you sloppily squirt it out.
It reeks of squid.
This is bad.
It has gotten hard.
So you want to violate me from within, huh?
Something seems to be dripping from the tip.
I don't hate it though.
These body fluids should be properly cleaned, right?
Does my mouth pussy feel good?
It's warm, wet... It's the best.
Dirty senpai.
You sure are perverted, aren't you?
This is really bad.
Just a dream, huh?
I don't think I have the time to be having this
kind of dream with all these to clean up.
Still, it's these times that I need to...
Hey there.
I came to celebrate your moving in here.
What is it? You suddenly coming here.
I just thought that you might be lonely.
I'm happy that you reacted the way I had hoped for.
Senpai, what are you...?
Celebrating your arrival here, by making you lose your virginity.
I want to take away your sweet virginity.
It's still hidden inside.
Such a shy boy.
I'm going to undress it gently.
Your dick looks really happy.
This is exactly the position needed to take away one's virginity.
You're really a slut.
Just let the lady here take you in.
Your pussy is touching it.
Do you want me to eat your virgin dick?
I want to put it in.
Here, take a look.
It's entering your pussy.
You look really happy there.
Here I go.
Is it your first time too?
That's right.
I thought that you were already experienced with this.
There aren't that many good men out there.
Could it be that I'm...
Enjoy my first kiss.
That was delicious.
I'm going to move now.
Senpai...
How does your first sex feel?
It feels warm and very nice.
Me too, it feels very good.
And I think I might just be getting the hang of it.
The sensation of your dick widening my pussy feels really great.
This feels good.
Sex is the best!
Getting cummed inside feels great!
It's gotten full.
Seems you can still go on.
Your dick is still stiff.
Then I'm the one who's going to enjoy your pussy next.
This kind of sex that turns me into
the one who's being played with...
It feels the best!
It's totally rubbing me inside.
It feels great.
I want the thing stored here inside me.
Release your cum deep into my womb!
Sex is amazing...
Why did you cum outside?
I just instinctively...
Semen is supposed to be released inside.
Was it made to make women dirty?
I'm sorry.
Then let's redo it from the start.
Huh?
Shall we do it once more?
The way you fondle it is very horny.
My sloppy breasts are being kneaded.
You're deeply knowledgeable despite being a virgin.
I've done a lot of image training.
Then let me see the results of your training.
Your meat here...
Looks just amazing.
I'm going to feel embarrassed if you start looking at it that way.
My ass is being played with obscenely while
my pussy is completely exposed.
Hurry, hurry!
Stir up my pussy already!
My pussy is being widened...
Stir my pussy more!
Your stiff thing is hitting deep inside.
Oh wow!
This is really good.
My pussy is being violated, in a position
that looks like I'm being raped.
This is really embarrassing.
Yes...
Rub it inside more.
More, more...!
It feels like it's going to be molded differently.
No sucking there...
Move more...
Stir me up and rub it in more!
Yes!
Rub it in more...
I'm at my limit!
It feels so good!
Oh no...!
I can't hold it in anymore!
Nothing will come out of it anymore...
That's not true.
It's gotten lively again.
But if you've cum inside me this much,
I might just get pregnant.
Huh?!
Just kidding.
I know a lot about it.
So don't worry.
I, want to go... go out with...
Starting tomorrow,
a relationship between the played junior,
and the gorgeous senior begins.