How is it, Takumi?
Does my titjob feel good?
Y-Yes, it feels good.
That same Ayane-senpai is squeezing my cock right now...
Do these slovenly bulging and
indecent tits really feel good?
Th-They really do...
Your tits feel so amazing!
Gosh, Takumi... So, you really love tits.
You've been also stealing glances at them
at the committee meeting, right?
Senpai, I'm already...
You can come onto these tits
that you love so much, Takumi.
Show me how your dick eagerly ejaculates.
S-Senpai!
Takumi, your semen has a very lewd taste.
A-Ayane-senpai!
Let's go, everyone!
Okay!
Uhh, I'll stay a little longer.
Thanks to the troublemaker honor student
Ayane-senpai becoming our head,
the school gave up and allowed the Public
Morals Committee where I belong
to continue despite not having enough members.
Takumi, lock the room afterwards.
Oh, okay.
I was so allured by Ayane-senpai's charms
that I carelessly browsed a porn site in the committee room.
Whoa!
Those are such nice boobies!
I wonder if senpai's are just like those?
That was Ayane-senpai herself.
Tenioha! 2
Hey, shall we do lots of lewder stuff?
Takumi, your virgin cock went inside!
Your dick is running wild in my pussy!
It's delighted from experiencing sex for the first time!
This is it! This is what I've been craving for!
This feels so good! This is what sex is...
So this is how it feels inside a pussy!
Pussies exist to give men pleasure,
but dicks exist to please women as well!
S-Senpai...
If you'll keep on moving like that,
I'll end up feeling too good...
You don't have to hold it in.
You can squirt it out anytime you feel like coming.
To celebrate your loss of virginity, I'll let you
give me as many creampies as you want!
Senpai!
You sure love tits, huh?
Senpai... Senpai!
Takumi... Takumi!
Senpai!
You're ejaculating!
Your dick is having its first ever
intravaginal ejaculation!
You came a lot.
Your insides felt so good...
Your dick is wonderful as well.
Takumi, we're not done yet, right?
Senpai...
Senpai, I really think that this isn't a good time.
If someone comes here...
Come on, be sure to make me feel good as well!
Oh... That's it!
I'm coming in!
Oh? Aren't you early today, Manami-chan?
You both are even earlier,
Ayane-san and Nakahara-kun.
Hmm?
Ayane-san, something's stuck beside your mouth.
Huh?
Oh...
Thanks, Manami-chan.
So, this is how a love hotel looks like inside.
S-Senpai!
I'll rub it using this musty armpit.
Huh?
If you'll manage to ejaculate from my armpit,
I'll caress you with my pussy next.
Your cock is stuffy and it stinks too.
How is it?
How does it feel to rub it against
my sweaty, musty, and stinky armpit?
I-It feels great...
Between your usual masturbation and this self-service armpit job,
which one feels better?
Your armpit feels better, senpai!
You're pressing your cock against my stinky armpit
and soiling it. You look like a monkey.
We can stop if you hate this.
It's useless...
I can't take my cock away from senpai!
I don't want to!
You feel good whether it's with
my genitals or any part of my body.
You truly are a pervert, Takumi.
S-Senpai...
Alright, Takumi...
I want you to show me how you ejaculate
from my sweaty, musty, and stinky armpit!
It feels hot!
My sweaty armpit got even
stinkier from your semen.
Takumi, what should we do?
Should we take a shower?
Or would you prefer going on like this instead?
I want to go on like this.
Gosh, Takumi...
You truly are a pervert.
I never ran into someone, how boring!
That's a good thing...
But while on my way here...
...I've couldn't help myself throbbing down here.
Alright, then...
Shall we have sex worthy of my effort?
I want you to put your stinky dick
in my asshole.
I-In your ass?
My anus, I'm talking about my anus.
Let's have anal sex.
My cock in senpai's ass...
I'm still a virgin at this hole.
I'll give my anal virginity to you, Takumi.
S-Senpai!
Do it, Takumi.
It feels so tight!
Senpai, are you alright?
I'm okay, it only hurts a little.
This sensation is new to me,
so I want to savor it even more!
Then... I'll start moving, senpai.
Ugh... Wow...
Your ass feels way different inside than your pussy!
It's the same for me, your dick feels
way different than when it's in my pussy!
It's an incredibly new experience!
Senpai... Senpai!
You're squeezing me so hard and it feels good!
It's going inside!
Your dick is penetrating me
even deeper than usual!
It feels great! Anal sex is fantastic!
If I only knew that it feels this good, I should've done anal sex sooner!
I should've played with my asshole before!
No way!
Your anal virginity belongs to me!
It's only mine!
I'm giving it to you! I'm giving
everything to you, Takumi!
You're the only one allowed
to masturbate my asshole!
Keep on thrusting it in!
No! My asshole is getting stretched wide!
That thick organ of yours
is penetrating my asshole!
Takumi, your dick is amazing!
It's hitting me just at the right places inside!
I've never had anything as thick as this!
Senpai, I'm gonna come.
I can shoot it in your as just like this, right?
It's okay! Yes... Yes!
Pour your semen in my ass!
Give my ass-pussy a creampie!
Senpai!
You're ejaculating into my bowel!
I can feel you spurting inside me!
I'm coming, here comes my first anal climax!
This is how senpai's pee smells like...
That was incredible, I might get hooked on it.
No... Maybe I already am.
So am I, senpai...
Haven't I told you already? I'm done with you.
The plan was until graduation, but I didn't
expect getting tired of you this soon.
No way...
I already left the committee tasks
to Manami-chan and the others,
so I won't be coming back here.
Bye, then...
Senpai...
Senpai—!
It'll be bad if we go further than this...
Both you and I can't get serious in this relationship.
I felt dejected after things between
senpai and me turned that way.
I attended the Comic Believers
convention to clear my mind,
but something unexpected happened.
S-Serizawa...
N-Nakahara-kun?
I'm alone with a girl in my room,
and she's even reading porn fanzines.
What kind of situation is this?
You really have a bunch of these, huh?
Yeah...
I never expected that you'd
be interested in lewd fanzines.
Yeah... I've been buying them online,
but that was my first time attending an event.
Going face to face and buying them
from the stands takes some courage.
Even I was nervous too until I got used to it.
I'll bet that it's even more so for women.
You're right, that's why having you
there was a huge help for me.
Come over and read them anytime.
Oh... You won't want to read
them with others around.
Moreover, it sounds bad
since this is a man's room...
I don't mind it.
B-But...
Hey, Nakahara-kun...
Let's have sex.
Serizawa...
Whenever I read lewd fanzines,
I get immensely curious about
indecent stuff such as sex.
That's why I want to try it if I'll get a chance.
Haven't you ever wanted to do
something that was in a fanzine?
That's...
Even so, that's...
What you're worried about
was that you might end up attacking
me if we're alone here, am I right?
Then, won't it be fine if we'll be in that
kind of relationship in the first place?
Let's become sexfriends!
Se...
Thinking that you're looking
at me made my nipples erect.
A-Are you sure?
Yes, I'm a very lewd girl, after all!
Serizawa!
Don't suddenly squeeze my tits that hard...
N-Nakahara-kun... So, you love tits...
Y-You're licking my nipple...
Th-That feels good!
You're sucking it!
W-Wow!
N-No way!
You're already so wet.
That's because it's you who am I doing this with.
Huh?
It's nothing...
I'm taking them off.
Okay...
It keeps on dripping out...
This is embarrassing, so don't stare too much...
No...
If you keep licking me there...
N-No...
I'm already...
Put it in already!
I'll be putting it in, then.
Yes, do it...
Ouch...
C-Could this be your first time?
Yeah... It hurts a little, but I'm okay.
Are you fine with me being your first?
Yeah... Start moving...
It feels tingly deep inside me!
I feel like something's coming!
It feels good! Your dick feels good!
It feels so good that it's driving me crazy!
Serizawa...
It feels good inside you as well!
Please say my name! Call me Manami!
M-Manami... Manami!
Come inside my pussy, Nakahara-kun!
Your dick is making me come as well!
Manami—!
Nakahara-kun—!
It's coming out! You're coming inside me!
So, this is an intravaginal ejaculation...
This is how getting creampied feels like...
Sex is such an amazing thing...
We, who were just ordinary friends
have become sexfriends with this, Nakahara-kun.
Call me by my name too.
Then... Takumi-kun.
You can drop the honorifics.
That'll be more comfortable for me.
Okay...
Do this seriously, Manami.
Am I not doing this seriously?
I'm properly looking at the textbook, am I not?
Calling a thin fanzine as a textbook...
A classmate I was having a lesson with earlier
is now giving me a blowjob while we're in school.
This is just like in fanzines!
How was it? Did it feel good?
Yeah, it feels good.
It didn't seem like your first time.
Really? Then, I'll make you
feel good even a lot more.
Seriously, you're good.
Y-You're even licking that spot...
You're too good that I can't hold it in!
Manami, I'm about to...
Shoot lots of it into my mouth!
So, this is semen...
It's hot and it has a very lewd scent...
You look good in it! I'm glad
that I brought it here!
Really?
But this swimsuit is a bit baggy around my chest.
Y-Yeah...
Well, that's Ayane-senpai's size...
This was supposed to be for Ayane-san...
Just kidding!
Takumi, let's have sex!
Manami, your pussy feels better and
better each time we're having sex!
Takumi, are you happy?
Are you happy that my pussy
is starting to feel better?
Of course! I'm glad that we became sexfriends!
Me too, I'm glad that we became sexfriends!
I'm happy that we're able
to have sex just like in fanzines!
Manami... M-Manami!
Takumi... Takumi!
I-I'm coming!
It's coming out...
Your sperm is pouring into me...
Takumi...
What do you want to tell me?
Don't tell me that we're doing it here.
Takumi, can we stop being sexfriends?
Huh? Wh-Why?
This isn't gonna work out anymore.
A-Are you saying that you got tired of me?
If this goes on, things will end up the wrong way.
I don't want to be your sexfriend,
but your lover instead!
I love you, Takumi!
I loved you all this time.
I want to be your girlfriend!
Manami...
Takumi...
I love you too, Manami.
The void that senpai left in me
has been filled up by Manami.
I'm gonna ask you as well.
Please be my girlfriend.
T-Takumi...
Are you really fine with me?
You are kind and adorable...
You're lewd and you understand my preferences.
So much so that I feel undeserving.
Takumi...
Manami...
And with this, we went beyond
an exclusively physical relationship.
Both our bodies and hearts are now bound as one.
Takumi, your cock feels great!
Aren't you intense today, Manami?
That's because this is our first sex as lovers!
Your cock only belongs to me now.
I won't let anyone else have it!
Your pussy only belongs to me as well!
And so are your tits!
You're squeezing my tits!
You're hollowing my pussy out!
My boyfriend's cock feels great!
Your pussy is also fantastic!
My pussy is for your exclusive use!
I'm the one who can pleasure you the best!
It feels good...
Manami... Manami!
Takumi, let's come at the same time!
Takumi!
Yeah, I'm gonna come...
I'm gonna come inside you, Manami!
Yes, come! I'm coming as well!
Ejaculate in my pussy! Give me a creampie!
I'm coming—!
Your semen is spilling out...
My boyfriend's semen is spilling out!
He's pouring it inside me!
Senpai's batch is graduating soon...
S-Senpai!
It's been a while, Takumi...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji