Good morning, Izumi-kun!
Good morning to you.
You look sleepy. What were you
doing while staying up late?
I'm interested in-your name. Can
I get you to write it here?
I guess...
Izumi Hiroto
Good job!
Intellectual Culture Studies' Association?
Application Form for Club Activities
Club Name: Intellectual Culture Studies' Association
Club president:
Hey, Hibiki-Senpai!
So do you have a nickname?
People call me Hiro...
Hiro, huh...
It's fine if you call me Nanase...
Well then Hiro, good luck on looking for club members!
And so, a-non-peaceful school life began.
Intellectual Culture Studies' Association
Although I was tricked into creating this club, I end
up spending most of my time after school here.
The goal of our activities is supposed
to be to study intellectual culture...
But in fact... well, as you can see.
Sorry for the wait..
little kitties.
This person must have done something,
for this to be allowed as a club.
Tenioha!
~ Girls Are Actually Naughty as Well?~
Part 1: Power Harassment Sexual Harassment First Experience!?
Translation: Snake | Timing: Nicolai | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by erobeat | httpV/www eraeeit.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
Here are you favorite panties!
Getting erect from a position like this...
you like being rubbed by my bare feet?
Yes, I like it when your feet and
the sticky stuff cling on...
I'll take good care of you.
Hey, cum! Show us how pathetic
you are as you ejaculate!
You reek like a squid.
Disgusting.
You're hard, aren't you.
Do you want to violate my insides?
It's flowing out already.
I don't hate this taste.
It won't stop flowing out...
I'll have to make sure to squeeze
it dean, or it won't do..
Does my mouth-pussy feel good?
It's warm and slippery, it's the best.
Senpai is such a pervert.
Disgusting.
Ouch!
...So it was a dream.
I guess I was too tired from moving
for anything like that...
At times like this...
Yaho!
I came to celebrate moving with you.
What's with coming so suddenly?
I thought you might be lonely by yourself.
I'm happy you reacted like I expected.
Senpai, what are you...
A celebration to congratulate you
on moving to a new place.
I thought I'd happily take your virginity.
It's hiding under the skin... what a shy guy.
I'll take good and gentle care of you.
Hiro's penis is really happy about this.
I'll eat up your virginity in this position, Okay?
You're really a pervert aren't you?
Just enjoy being eaten up by me.
Senpai's pussy is hitting...
You want me to take your virgin penis?
I want to put it in...
Hey, look carefully...
It's going into Senpai's pussy...
You're making a great face.
Here we go.
This is also Senpai's first time?
That's right.
I was sure that you were really experienced with this...
There weren't any good men so...
Could it be that you...
Go ahead and enjoy my first kiss...
Thanks for the meal.
Well, I'll start moving.
Senpai...
Any thoughts on your first time haying sex?
It's warm inside and it feels wonderful.
I feel great, too!
I could get addicted to this.
The feeling of your dick spreading my vagina is amazing!
This is so good!
Sex is the best!
Being creampied... feels good!
I'm so full...
You can still keep going, right?
You're still rock hard...
Well then, I'll be exploring Senpai's insides some more!
Sex in the riding position is the best!
It's grinding deep inside!
It's so good!
Stuff stored in here...
Give it to me inside!
Let it out all the way deep into my womb!
Sex is amazing!
Why did you cum outside?
I couldn't help but do it by reflex...
Sperm should be let out inside. It's
not for staining the girl's body.
I'm sorry.
Then, let's redo that.
Wanna do it again?
That's a lewd way of touching them..
My naughty tits are changing shape as they are rubbed...
Even though you were a virgin, you're quite a maniac!
I've done training through imagination.
Then show me the results of your training.
Amazing, such a lewd body.
It's embarrassing when you look so much...
I'm having my lewd, large butt rubbed while
my pussy being raped by your eyes...
Hurry, hurry! Stir up my pussy!
My pussy is being spread open!
Stir in my pussy more!
A hard one is hitting deep inside!
Amazing! This is amazing!
My pussy is being violated in a
position like I'm being raped!
This position... so embarrassing!
Yes! Rub inside more!
Yes! More, more!
They shape is going to change...
Not only there... No!
Move morel Mess up my inside morel
Yes!
Rub my insides... more...
I'm at my limit! This is too good!
No...
I can't hold back anymore!
I can't cum anymore...
No way...
It's hard again. Although, if you cum
this much I just might get pregnant
Huh?
Just kidding. I'm quite knowledgeable
in those areas. So be at ease.
I want to... with Senpai...
From tomorrow, we'll be the teased
junior with the beautiful senpai.