Aoi-chan...
I must've put the body of the robot around here somewhere.
Not here.
How about this box?
What's up, Gengoromaru?
Did you find something interesting?
Huh?
Oh. This is...
We used to play with that toy water gun together, huh?
Yeah, right.
Huh?
Are you looking for something, Shin-chan?
What?
Yeah, but nothing important.
I'll help you.
That's okay. I can do this by myself.
Come on.
I'm better at finding stuff than you.
Um...
In addition, I know your legs haven't fully recovered yet.
I'll go check the upstairs.
Don't get hurt, though.
I'll be fine.
But...
Wow, it's so dusty here.
So?
What are you looking for, Shin-chan?
Well, um...
My glove...
Yeah, my baseball glove.
I wonder if this is it.
Let's see. Hm...
No, this isn't it.
Maybe it's somewhere else.
I'll look a bit more.
Ah, the box!
You mean this one? Hold on.
What are these?!
Dirty magazines!
No, they're my dad's!
You're lying!
It's true! Really!
Ow...
Hey, are you okay?
Hey.
Shin-chan.
Huh?
Oops!
This is...
Um...
You pervert!
It was just an accident.
Ah, they're in the springtime of their youth.
Transfer Student
Orphan Fansubs presents
Sexy Private Lesson
Sweet Potato
Give me some.
No way.
Just one of them, please?
Hot!
I liked their summer outfits,
but autumn outfits are nice too!
Wow! She looks even better now!
She does too!
I have to take notes!
Boy, they keep me so busy!
Where did I store it?
I'm sure I put it away with her hat.
Are your legs okay now?
Yup. See?
I'm spinning it more than usual.
How about that?
That's good to hear.
I was worried about you.
Mami-chan!
I'm so glad to see you fully recovered.
Thank you.
What's that?
Oh, this?
I wanted to change myself,
so I joined the Lacrosse Club.
What?
Are you quitting the Flower Arrangement Club?
No. It might be tough,
but I'll be in both clubs.
Good luck, Mami-chan.
Yes!
It's all thanks to you.
Well, I'm going to the Lacrosse Club now.
Okay.
Hey, Shinichi, don't you think she's changed?
Yeah, I guess so.
Her boobs have got bigger too.
I like her in the school uniform, but she must look cute in the lacrosse uniform too.
I'm taking a note!
Mami Fujino, joined the Lacrosse Club and got bigger boobs.
Her rank on my list went up!
I'm sure you're going to live a long life.
You hold here and do like this.
See?
That's how you make the flowers stand.
Wow!
That's wonderful, Reika-senpai.
Now, you girls can try.
So use this hand and go like this.
Okay.
That's better,
but you need to relax
your shoulders more.
Okay.
You're doing well.
Go ahead and try.
Yes, good...
Kenzaki-kun!
R-Right!
Well, keep what I said in mind, okay?
I will.
Thank you very much.
You need to relax your shoulders too.
That was so cool!
She's beautiful and humble and looks great in her kimono.
She's so mature and attractive.
If she ever hit on me,
I'd totally lose control!
Kenzaki looked like such a dork today, huh?
He got away from Aoi-chan right after Reika-san called his name.
“Well, keep what I said in mind, okay?”
That was hilarious!
You sound exactly like him.
I'm in a good mood today.
Why don't we eat something on the way back home?
Cool, I'm in.
All right! Let's go!
Oh?
That bastard. Again!
What should we have?
Hamburger, curry, ramen, spaghetti, or beef bowl?
What do you think, Shinichi?
Hey, Shinichi?
Hello, Shinichi?
Hello?!
Oh, nice pic.
So what did you want to tell me, Kenzaki-san?
Sorry to make you come all the way here,
but I just couldn't say this in the club room.
Are you free tomorrow, Aoi-kun?
Huh?
Tomorrow?
I got these by chance,
so I thought I'd ask you to join me.
YNO
Concert
Oh, tickets to the YNO concert!
I'm a big fan of theirs!
Oh? Then that's perfect.
Hm, I'll consider it.
Damn it!
I was worried about her getting harassed by him again.
But she looks so happy just about a ticket.
She is so...
She is...
to me...
She's my old friend...
who lives next door...
and has transferred into my class...
and...
Shinichi?
Yay!
No, I lost!
No! I lost!
You're so strong
You're so strong.
One more thing and she'll be naked.
Lizzy and I win!
You lose!
Wow, you're good!
You got a point again.
Cool. I've never seen that attack.
Way to go!
You're amazing!
You're completely invincible.
So cool, miss!
Yay!
Please play again.
Hey, Tsukui-kun.
Huh?
It's me.
Ah ha! Reika-senpai!
Sorry, but I only have some tea right now.
That's fine.
This place is really too spacious, isn't it?
Living here by myself
can be quite a bother.
By yourself?
What about your parents?
They left me and are working in New York now.
I haven't seen them for a year.
I feel like I'm on a transfer away from my family.
I've been distracting myself from loneliness by playing video games.
I still get lonely once in a while,
and that's when I go to the arcade.
I was really surprised to see you there earlier today.
I thought that even at home,
you arranged flowers in a kimono.
Oh, stop talking like I'm a grandmother.
No, I mean you're so mature!
That still sounds like an old lady to me.
N-No! That's not what I mean.
How should I put this?
You're mature and attractive... um...
and well, sexy.
You've finally started to sound like you.
Y-You think so?
Beauty
Your flowers are always beautiful, Reika-senpai.
No, they're not really any good. They're just gathered nicely.
They're not heartfelt.
Heartfelt?
They're trying hard to look nice so people will like them.
They remind me of myself
when I was little.
My parents came home late every day.
But I thought they would come home early if I was good.
Mama and Papa
Papa, Mama,
I promise I'll be good,
so please come home early.
We're home.
Welcome home!
Now, they're on their long-term business trip in New York.
I've been left alone again.
Flower arranging is interesting.
The flowers you arrange reflect your heart at the moment.
My heart...
What should I do?
I want to go, but...
Hm. I wonder...
He's back!
Hey, Shin-chan?
Do you have a minute?
Huh?
What do you want?
I need your advice on something.
What is it?
Well, I got a ticket from Kenzaki-san.
What do you think?
What do I think?
If you want to go, then go.
I'd like you to come with me.
Why should I have to go with you?
Well, I don't know.
Tell me.
Why?
Because we live next door?
Because we're in the same class?
We're nothing but childhood friends!
So we're just classmates?
We're nothing but childhood friends, huh?
I'm...
What is she saying?
You idiot!
Huh?
I'm doing well, Mom.
Don't worry.
Really.
What, a boyfriend?
I don't have one yet.
Yes.
Yeah.
Huh? Good news?
Tell me. What is it?
Yeah.
Huh... me?
All right, I will.
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Yes.
Sorry to be late, Kenzaki-san.
No problem, Aoi-kun.
I just got here.
Let's go, all right?
Yes.
Hold me tight so we don't lose each other in the crowd.
Okay. Like this?
Let go of me!
I'm sorry, but my grandmother really wanted to come with me.
Your grandmother?
I'm Aoi's grandmother.
Please call me Sayuri-chan.
N-Nice to meet you.
I-I'm K-Kenzaki K-Kotoro.
What am I doing here?
Flower arranging is interesting.
The flowers you arrange reflect your heart at the moment.
My heart...
Really?
Is this my heart at the moment?
Reika-senpai!
They truly reflect your heart at the moment.
Huh?
Hm...
They look like they're just placed randomly, but they have lots of life.
They don't care what other people think of them.
They're free-spirited.
And those are your flowers.
Is that right?
Yes.
That's something I'm missing.
Tsukui-kun?
Yes?
I want you to share your freedom with me.
R-Reika-senpai...
I have to move to New York next week.
My parents want me to study abroad there.
I'm glad that I can live with them,
but then I will remain just as I am now.
I need to change myself.
Can you share your freedom with me?
I need your help.
Reika-san...
Snow...
It was snowing on that day.
This is so like you.
A nice bed of flowers.
Reika-san.
Tsukui-kun...
Shin-chan...
Thank you, Tsukui-kun.
Reika-san...
All right!
Do you want to go for a walk, Gengoromaru?
Now, let's go.
He's doing that again.
And he won't tell me about it.
Where is it?
Please come out, robot body!
Damn!
Where is it?!
I don't need just the head, I also need the body!
He's remembered about the past.
Oh, I saw this the other day as well.
Shin-chan!
Huh?
Aoi-chan.
Are you looking for something again?
I'll help you.
Ah, don't worry.
I want to.
So what are you looking for today?
Well, um, it's...
It's, um...
I'd love to give you my heart right now
ima sugu anata ni hohoemi soete
Along with a smile
kokoro todoketai
You always have those kind, youthful eyes
itsu demo yasashii shounen no me no
And I love you for them
anata ga daisuki
Seeing the setting sun shine upon your back
ima yuuhi wo abiru anata no senaka
I mutter to myself quietly
tada chiisaku sotto tsubuyaite miru
Rather than walking home alone
hitori kaeru michi wo
I want to walk home together
futari arukitai no
Yes, I'd love to smile at you right now
sou ima sugu anata ni hohoemi kakete
And give you my love
ai wo todoketai
I'll become a wonderful girl
tobikkiri suteki na watashi ni natte
For I love you
anata ga daisuki
I'd love to give you my heart right now
ima sugu anata ni hohoemi soete
Along with a smile
kokoro todoketai
You always have those kind, youthful eyes
itsu demo yasashii shounen no me no
And I love you for them
anata ga daisuki
Translation
Song Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Raws
anonymous
convexity
Yogicat
.
Collectr
Calyrica
pornolab
Next Time
Hey, Satoshi, why are you so excited?
Isn't that obvious?
Because the next story is about Christmas!
I'm expecting to get a lot of presents from girls!
You never change, do you?
That bastard Kenzaki!
He asked Aoi-chan out again!
What are you going to do about it, Shinichi?
Do something!
Transfer Student, final episode:
Christmas Memory.
It's the climax!
Aoi-chan is going to be in danger!
Please watch again!
By the way, what about my love story?