Transfer Student
Orphan Fansubs presents
Do you think
Santa will come?
I'm sure he will
because we prayed for it!
Really?!
If not, I'll bring him to you!
Shin-chan... I love you.
It's cold!
What's wrong, Gengoromaru?
How beautiful.
So you wanted to show this to me?
Thank you, Gengoromaru.
Dinner
Breakfast
Hi, Shinichi.
Dinner
Breakfast
Mom and Dad are going to a hidden hot spring in the mountains near Tohoku.
Dinner
Breakfast
Warm Up
Dinner
We're going to spend Christmas and New Year's Eve there.
Warm Up
Dinner
We'll be back by New Year's Day. Look forward to your souvenir!
Warm Up
Dinner
I'm starting to wonder
if they really love me!
There you go.
Let me see.
That's so cute.
Shin-chan!
We don't have any club activities today, right?
Yeah. So?
Why don't we go home early and make a snowman together?
A snowman?
Yup.
Let's make one together,
like we used to.
Okay?
Yeah.
Shin-chan...
Ow! Who did that!
Hey, Shinichi.
There!
Don't underestimate me, Satoshi-kun!
Here I go!
Oops.
Take this!
Hey, you're really bad at this!
Use your brain, Satoshi-kun.
All right, you asked for it!
There!
Shin-chan, go for it!
What about me?
Got you!
I win!
That serves you right.
Aoi-kun.
Huh?
Oh, Kenzaki-senpai.
Do you have a minute?
Yes.
What does he want?
I don't know.
What is it, Kenzaki-san?
It's about today, Christmas Eve.
Whose bag is that?
This is Shin-chan's.
I mean, Tsukui-kun's bag.
I don't think you should be hanging out with kids who still play in the snow.
You should be with people
who are more mature instead.
I don't like the way he talks.
Hey, Shinichi?
No, I wanted to hold this for him.
Yeah, yeah, we're just kids, all right.
Can't you even say thank you?
That's why I say you're a kid.
Where were we?
I made a reservation for two at the restaurant in the Hotel Grand Blue.
Aoi-kun, will you join me?
Well, today, I'm...
Do you already have plans for tonight?
I really want to spend
Christmas Eve with you.
You know what this means, right?
Aoi-chan isn't here yet.
I wonder if she's still talking with that Kenzaki guy.
What if she agreed to go with him tonight, and they're busy making plans right now?
I thought I'd finally be able to eat some Christmas cake with a girl this year.
But it looks like I'm spending
Christmas Eve with Shinichi again.
No, I won't give up!
Do you want me to introduce you to a girl?
I'm sure you want to spend
Christmas Eve with a girl too.
So who do you want?
When it comes to girls, I don't need your help.
All right, I'll introduce you to the prettiest girl!
Like I said, I don't need your help for that.
What are you guys doing?
Mami-chan.
What are you doing, Mami-chan?
I'm going to the club room to get some stuff that I left.
Are you going to knit something?
Oh, this?
Because it's Christmas tomorrow, I thought I'd knit a scarf.
So you have a boyfriend now?
Well, no.
But If I can knit a scarf by Christmas, Santa will bring me a boyfriend.
That's what I believe.
Don't worry. You'll get one soon.
Mami Fujino, looking for a boyfriend, knitting a scarf.
How do you even do that?
Well, I'm a pro at this.
Shin-chan!
Hi, Mami-chan.
Hi, Ayase-san.
Aoi-chan, did Kenzaki do anything to you?
We were worried about you!
Don't worry. Everything is fine.
Are you sure?
Yes.
That's enough!
Hey, Shin-chan, can I talk
with you for a bit?
Sure. What's up?
Well, um...
Can we talk alone?
I mean...
Hey, Shinichi, go ahead
and talk to her,
you handsome boy!
O-Okay.
It's beautiful.
Snow makes me happy.
So what did you want to tell me?
I don't like the cold.
I'm sorry, but I really wanted to tell you...
Well... um...
They're in...
...a romantic mood.
Go on.
Well, it's Christmas Eve today, so I was wondering if you...
Christmas Eve?
Unlike you, I'll just be by myself.
Hold on. I'm...
You're going on a date
with Kenzaki, right?
You went to a concert with him, and next is dinner on Christmas Eve, right?
I'm jealous.
I'm saying...
What do you want to say?
You want to tell me I'm a kid too?
A kid who can't make plans for dinner at a restaurant and stuff.
Good for you.
Have fun with the mature guy on Christmas Eve.
So you don't care if I go to dinner with Kenzaki-senpai?
It's not my business anyway.
You won't stop me?
No.
Aoi-chan!
That idiot!
Shinichi!
What are you doing?
Go get her!
What's wrong with you?
It's not like you.
Stop sulking!
Will you be okay if Kenzaki gets Aoi-chan?!
Sure... if that's her choice!
You damn fool!
What the hell?!
Aoi-chan wanted you
to tell her not to go!
Why is that?!
If you want to stop her,
then you should do it!
Aren't you the president of her fan club?
I want to, but it has to be you!
What do you mean?!
You still don't get it?
Stop!
Stop, you two!
Please!
Nurse's Office
Oh, sorry. Does that hurt?
N-No, I'm fine.
What happened, Shinichi?
It's rare for you to have
a fight this intense.
Nothing.
Leave that foolish guy alone, Mika-chan.
Oh, why don't we go to karaoke and have a Christmas party together?
What do you think, Mami-chan?
Well, I'm...
All right, I'll go.
Yay! Let's go!
How about you, Mika-chan?
I can't join you. Sorry.
I plan to have a Christmas party at the hospital.
There are people who can't go home on Christmas Eve.
So I talked with the nurses, and we decided to have a party for them.
We all should have fun on Christmas Eve, right?
Why don't you join our Christmas party at the hospital, Shinichi?
Sorry, but I'm not in the mood.
Oh, no!
What should I do?!
What happened?
My!
That's cute.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault!
Do you want to be hospitalized at our hospital?
I'll take care of you.
Anyway, I'm sorry, Satoshi.
Shinichi-san...
Shinichi...
Shinichi.
What are you going to do, Aoi?
Are you really going on a date with Kenzaki-san?
This isn't a date.
We're just going to have dinner.
Shin-chan is...
Shin-chan doesn't care about me.
He doesn't want a childhood friend like me around him.
That's not true!
Shin-chan is...
He's...
Then why doesn't he stop me?
Why doesn't he say, "Don't go, Aoi"?
Th-That's...
Um...
Christmas
Sale
Can we get the whole cake?
Thank you for the presents.
Satoshi's right.
Why can't I be honest with myself when I'm with her?
This Christmas tree is really big.
It's beautiful.
I want this in my house.
Yeah.
Anyway...
My father knows the chef of this restaurant,
so he made some special dishes for us.
I hope you liked them.
They were quite beautiful... right?
He's a first-class chef,
so he values presentation as well.
The food at this restaurant looks very nice.
Dad said it tasted terrible.
Terrible!
Well, ordinary people wouldn't be able to appreciate the delicate taste.
Excuse me for a second.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Dad?
About the restaurant you were talking about...
What? Their food looks perfect but tastes terrible?
Why didn't you say that before?
What?
You bring girls to this restaurant
when you want to break up with them?
No!
I was talking about taking someone special!
Please do something!
I don't want to ruin the date!
No! I want to put it higher than that.
This is high enough.
No.
Put it higher.
It doesn't make any difference.
But Santa flies up
in the sky, you know.
We have to put the sock up high so he can see it.
You may be right.
Let's do that!
A sock...
Shin-chan, be careful...
I'll be fine. We have
to put the sock up high
for Santa to notice it.
I feel like I've done something with Aoi on Christmas in the past.
Hey, young man.
Merry Christmas!
Can I help you?!
You look bored on Christmas Eve, huh?
Do you want to come to the neighborhood karaoke party with me?
Th-Thank you, but no, I'm okay.
Huh?
What?
A sock...
I'm glad you're okay.
I'm going to be your wife.
Yeah, at the time, she told me...
At the time, he was... he was...
What's wrong, young man?
Yeah, that's right!
Thank you, Sayuri-chan!
I'm going!
I have no idea what he's up to...
but go for it, young man!
Let me do it.
Here.
Is this good?
Yeah!
Now I'm sure Santa will come.
Thank you, miss.
Thank you too.
Come on.
Aoi-kun!
Kenzaki-san...
I...
I'm sorry!
Aoi-kun!
Wait!
I just booked another restaurant!
So... Aoi-kun!
Please come back, Aoi-kun!
Please, Aoi-kun!
Aoi...
Oops!
S-Somebody...
call an ambulance!
Unabara Shrine
Oops!
I... love you.
ima sugu anata ni hohoemi soete
I'd love to give you my heart right now
kokoro todoketai
Along with a smile
itsu demo yasashii shounen no me no
You always have those kind, youthful eyes
anata ga daisuki
And I love you for them
ima yuuhi wo abiru anata no senaka
Seeing the setting sun shine upon your back
tada chiisaku sotto tsubuyaite miru
I mutter to myself quietly
hitori kaeru michi wo
Rather than walking home alone
futari arukitai no
I want to walk home together
sou ima sugu anata ni hohoemi kakete
Yes, I'd love to smile at you right now
ai wo todoketai
And give you my love
tobikkiri suteki na watashi ni natte
I'll become a wonderful girl
anata ga daisuki
For I love you
ima sugu anata ni hohoemi soete
I'd love to give you my heart right now
kokoro todoketai
Along with a smile
itsu demo yasashii shounen no me no
You always have those kind, youthful eyes
anata ga daisuki
And I love you for them
I'm going to be your wife.
Translation
Song Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Raws
anonymous
convexity
Yogicat
.
Collectr
Calyrica
pornolab