Ha ha ha ha...
Hey, stop that, Shin-chan!
Shin-chan!
Just a dream.
I don't want to see a dog in my dreams.
Good morning, Gengoromaru.
Shin-chan!
Help me!
Gengoromaru, stop! Come back here.
Don't do that, Gengoromaru.
Are you okay, Shin-chan?
Yeah, I'm all right.
What happened to you?
You used to like dogs a lot.
Huh? I did?
Yeah.
No, I've been scared of them since when I was little.
No! Don't you remember?
In the past...
Remember what?
Your... thing is...
What do you mean by my thing?
Don't make me say that, you pervert!
What's with her?
Hello, young man.
You look like you're full
of energy, as usual.
So does your thing.
What?
P-Please excuse me!
You sure are a healthy young man.
Transfer Student
Orphan Fansubs presents
Seduction of a Nurse
So you really don't like dogs, huh?
Maybe you have a bad memory of them.
No idea.
As far as I can remember, I've never liked dogs.
Hey, girls in class A,
getting some exercise after lunch?
Do you want to join us, Yamashita-kun?
Yes, sure!
Let me join you guys!
Have fun.
Ready?
Huh? I don't know her.
Is she a transfer student?
Yeah, she transferred in yesterday. Her name is Ebina Mika.
All right. She's cute.
Hey, is that you, Shinichi?!
Long time no see!
Do I know you?
We were in the same class
all through elementary school.
I'm Mika.
Mika, huh?
You really don't remember me?
We used to play doctor together a lot when we were little.
We did?
Now take off your clothes and lie down.
What seems to be the problem?
You're Mika-rin!
Yeah, finally.
Did you guys have enough time to enjoy your fateful reunion?
I didn't recognize you immediately because of your Osaka accent.
Would you really have recognized me right away without that?
My dad had to move to Osaka to work at one of the hospitals there, remember?
Right...
But what about that?
That's how I got the little bit of accent.
Oh, yeah?
The store sells a lot of cute stuff.
And they're cheap too.
Let's go there together.
Hey, Aoi!
Wait for me, Aoi-chan!
Hello!
Huh? Hey!
Oops.
Hey! Wait up! Please!
What do you want?
Well, nothing really.
Then why did you call out to me?
What are you angry about?
Nothing.
I'm sorry about this morning.
I don't care about that.
It just showed me how perverted you are.
What?!
It's not like I wanted to show...
Gengoromaru, why are you here?
Is that you, Aoi?!
I was walking Gengoromaru,
but he suddenly started running.
Don't do that, Gengoromaru.
We don't want you to be missing.
Yeah, seriously.
Unabara High School
Exit
Oh, they are both struggling!
Shinichi is getting attacked.
And Makino is still attacking!
Now Shinichi avoided Makino's attack, and he's on the offensive!
How are we supposed to clean the room?
They might get hurt.
Ah!
Makino is holding up Shinichi!
Shinichi can't escape.
He's in trouble!
And Makino throws Shinichi!
Ow...
It hurts.
Oh, sorry.
Shinichi!
Stay still!
Mika-rin.
What?
Show me your palm.
Do you always carry that stuff around with you?
It's my dad's influence.
I have to help someone who's injured.
Isn't that funny?
All right, there you go.
How's that?
You're good.
I know, right?
So, Shinichi, whenever you get hurt,
you can come to me.
I can cure you anytime.
Don't push me!
Hey, Mika-chan, I injured my hand.
Would you look at it?
Where?
Is this it?
It hurts.
Oh, there, there.
I can take care of that.
Shake it, Satoshi.
You're not in our class in the first place.
Do you see the long line?
Hurry up, or I'll die.
Don't worry. I'll take care of you all, okay?
Yay!
Oh boy, these guys are so simple.
Yes, and very annoying.
I feel like the same thing has happened before.
Right. One time I injured my hand like this,
and there was a girl...
But was it Mika-rin?
No, that was before I met her.
Shin-chan.
What are you doing, Shin-chan?
Oh, I just couldn't sleep.
Ouch!
Are you okay, Shin-chan?
I'm fine.
That's good, then.
I remember you were a scatterbrain even when you were little.
Yeah.
I know... but are you making fun of me?
That reminds me.
What?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
What is it?
When you say, "When you were little," how long ago was that, exactly?
What?!
Does that mean you don't remember me?
Um, I mean, I just can't remember when that was.
I was wondering...was it the summer of two years ago?
I see. You've been dating so many girls that you forgot about me.
What? No, don't get me wrong.
Yeah, right. Maybe that was the spring of two years ago!
Oh yeah, now I remember...
That was a lie.
You've always been irresponsible.
You peeked into my room while I was changing.
You joined the club just to get close to girls.
You showed me something dirty in the morning.
You're such a pervert!
What did you just say?!
Stop saying tha-
You don't understand.
I was really happy to see you again.
However,
you're...
an idiot, Shin-chan!
Unabara Hospital
Now, let me give
you an injection.
Give up, Shin-chan.
You lost at
rock-paper-scissors!
Shin-chan.
Shinichi.
Mika-rin and Aoi.
Does it hurt anywhere?
Me? Hurt?
I don't feel any pain.
What the hell?!
I'm sorry Shin-chan. It's my fault.
You don't need to worry so much.
He's a tough guy, and that's his only redeeming trait.
Right?
Y-Yeah.
And my dad works here,
so you can totally rely on this hospital.
By the way, are your parents away now?
I can't get in touch with them.
They're on a trip now.
At their age, they like traveling by themselves.
Oh, yeah?
I wanted them to see me all grown up like a beautiful lady, though.
Huh? Beautiful lady? Where?
Oh, even your eyes have gone bad, huh?
Do you need medicine for that?
All right, all right, cut it out.
I'll go get your clothes.
Oh, thank you.
No problem.
Bye now.
What?! Shinichi-san has been hospitalized?!
Yeah, really. He's such a careless guy.
Mika-chan's dad runs the hospital, right?
I wonder if she takes care of him all the time.
I want to be hospitalized too!
But why did he fall from the second floor?
Maybe a dog barked at him or something.
Um, excuse me, nurse, I need to use the bathroom.
Okay.
Mika-rin?!
Why are you dressed up like that?
What do you think?
I borrowed these from a real nurse.
The outfit looks good on you!
But you need to stay away from me!
You don't need to be embarrassed.
Stop it!
I-I'll call someone else!
No one's coming to help you.
I'll take care of
the patient in 305.
I've arranged everything for this.
I'll take care of
the patient in 305.
N-No, please stop. Stop!
Tsukui
Shinichi
Aoi-kun!
Huh?
Hey.
Kenzaki-san.
So, my kitten, will you tell me what's bothering you?
Come on.
Nothing. I'm fine.
You looked like you had something in your mind.
I'm on your side as your colleague in the Flower Arrangement Club.
Aoi-chan and Kenzaki?
What's going on?
Kenzaki-san?
What are you afraid of, Aoi-kun?
P-Please let go of my hand.
This is not good. This is really not good.
So you're popular, huh?
Huh?
Look. See these flowers and a card?
"I hope you get better soon. A.A."
"A.A."?
What's wrong?
Your tea is getting cold.
After this, we'll go on another bike ride.
Kenzaki-sama!
It's so nice to see you!
H-How did you guys know I was here?
Oh, because we got a message on our beepers telling us to meet up.
That was you, right?
Well... um...
I wasn't expecting you to be the first one, Aoi-san.
Um, not exactly.
It serves you right, Kenzaki!
Unabara Hospital
Tsukui
Shinichi
Oh, yeah?
Tsukui
Shinichi
Watch out!
Tsukui
Shinichi
That SOB Kenzaki was trying to manipulate Aoi-chan!
Then Satoshi, a hero of justice, came up with an idea.
I told Kenazaki's fangirls where he was through their pagers, and...
Hey, are you listening?
It gets better from here.
Go home.
I don't care if she goes to a café or goes on a bike ride with Kenzaki.
Wh-What?
I was just trying to...
All right, as you wish!
I'll never come back here!
I wonder why I'm so frustrated.
Come in.
Who is it?
Shin-chan, I'm sorry that
you got hurt because of me.
I never expected all this.
I'm really sorry.
No, it's just that I'm clumsy.
It's not your fault.
Shin-chan...
More importantly, you shouldn't be here.
I mean, isn't Kenzaki waiting for you at the café?
What?
What are you talking about, Shin-chan?
Satoshi saw you...
at the café with Kenzaki.
That was because he forced me to...
Shinichi, do you want some apples?
Oh, I didn't know you had a guest.
That's fine.
She's leaving now.
Shin-chan...
Take care.
It's not all that bright now.
I'm not doing this because of the sun.
You look like you're all wrapped up in bandages. It's cute.
Tsukui
Shinichi
I used to play in a hospital when I was little.
So almost all the men I knew were swathed in bandages.
Doctors were too busy to play with me.
So the patients there played with me and gave me snacks.
Now men in bandages and the smell of antiseptic solution...
turn me on.
Please, Shinichi.
With your hand wrapped in bandages...
That feels good, Shinichi.
I like that spot.
Shinichi...
Shinichi!
I love you!
Unabara Hospital
It looks like he's gone to sleep.
Discharge Day
Unabara Hospital
Thank you for taking care of him.
It's good that you recovered sooner than we expected.
As if you care.
Where were you guys anyway?
We were at the hidden hot spring in the Tohoku forest area.
It's very popular with
hot spring aficionados.
It was very romantic.
Just how old do you think you guys are?
You're always welcome here whenever you get hurt, you know?
I'll take care of you again.
I hope that's not going to happen, though. I hate pain.
How cool!
Hey, Mika!
Sorry, but he's got more bandages than you.
No kidding!
Are you serious?
Oh, I almost forgot.
You were holding this tight in your hand when you were brought in by ambulance.
Huh?
Shin-chan. Shin-chan. Shin-chan...
Shin-chan.
Aoi...
Shin-chan
you idiot
Shin-chan, you idiot!
Shin-chan
you idiot
I'd love to give you my heart right now
ima sugu anata ni hohoemi soete
Along with a smile
kokoro todoketai
You always have those kind, youthful eyes
itsu demo yasashii shounen no me no
And I love you for them
anata ga daisuki
Seeing the setting sun shine upon your back
ima yuuhi wo abiru anata no senaka
I mutter to myself quietly
tada chiisaku sotto tsubuyaite miru
Rather than walking home alone
hitori kaeru michi wo
I want to walk home together
futari arukitai no
Yes, I'd love to smile at you right now
sou ima sugu anata ni hohoemi kakete
And give you my love
ai wo todoketai
I'll become a wonderful girl
tobikkiri suteki na watashi ni natte
For I love you
anata ga daisuki
Translation
Song Translation
Timing
Editing &
Typesetting
QC
Raws
anonymous
convexity
Yogicat
.
Collectr
Calyrica
pornolab
Next Time
Do you have a minute, Aoi-kun?
Yes. What is it, Kenzaki-san?
Why don't we move on to
a more adult relationship?
If it comes to that,
I think the club president, Reika Hayama, is more suitable for you.
She's pretty and modest.
And imagine what's under her kimono...
U-Under her kimono?
Next time, Transfer Student, episode 3:
Sexy Private Lesson.
What's under her kimono?!