Natural  Color Love Alcohol
Hello!
Oh, come in.
She's here.
She's here!
Oh, Yuu-kun.
Mayu-neechan, welcome back!
Ow~.
That surprised me.
You're as lively as ever, Yuu-kun.
Hey, hey, can I show you something?
Oh, what could that be?
Is it something funny?
Or something cute?
Yuu-kun, you must really be eager to meet
her dashing out of your room like that.
He's been fidgety the entire time.
He usually hates being left in the house, but today...
Were going Mom.
I'm coming in!
Okay then...
Now I feel sad.
Look! I really worked hard during the last exams!
I'm the only one who got this in class!
That's really amazing!
You sure did your best, Yuu-kun.
My tutoring efforts were really worth it.
I'm really happy.
I can't breathe.
Maybe I should go and tell this to everyone.
Okay, time to give you your reward then.
Reward?
You can request anything from me.
So just say what's on your mind.
O-Okay...
Well... Well...
Mayu-neechan...
Oh, what is it?
Umm...
I want to touch your boobs!
Jeez, so you want this kind of grown-up reward, eh?
Can you keep it our little secret in this room?
Yes.
Okay then, here's your reward.
Do whatever you want with my breasts, Yuu-kun.
How is it, Yuu-kun?
It's really soft, so white and soft, like a marshmallow.
Yuu-kun, that hurts a bit.
I-I'm sorry, Mayu-neechan.
You see, breasts need to be held very gently.
G-Gently, like this?
T-That's right, you're good.
Down then up, and touch the nipples occasionally.
Nipples...
Like this, Onee-chan?
The tip is starting to feel hard, right?
That, you see, is a sign that it feels good.
Would you like to lick it?
It tastes really good.
Yuu-kun...!
Mayu-neechan... Onee-chan!
Yuu-kun...
Onee-chan...
Yuu-kun!
Onee-chan!
Onee-chan, it feels like I want to take a leak.
My peepee feels really tingly.
It's okay, Yuu-kun.
Just leave it to me.
I'm going to make that tingly sensation feel better.
It'd hurt since it's still sheathed, so I have to lubricate it.
Onee-chan!
I remember, when you rub it with your palm like this...
No, don't, my peepee's going to lose it!
Oh no, he's just so cute!
Onee-chan, my peepee feels like it's going to burst.
I see, then let's prepare something grown-up for it.
Looks like I hit it.
Onee-chan, don't lick it while putting it in your mouth...!
Onee-chan... toilet...
I need to go to the toilet...
It's coming out!
I just peed.
It's okay.
Yuu-kun, this is not pee.
This is something that all men squirt out when doing this.
Really?
Dad also has it?
Of course.
That's one sign of being a grown-up.
But, to become more grown-up,
We need to do a very erotic kiss, using my pussy and your peepee.
Rubbing and sliding together.
Over and over.
I want to do a grown-up kiss.
Yuu-kun, don't.
Now I'm getting even more aroused to do it.
I want to do it.
Okay, let's do it lots.
Don’t move, okay?
I'm going to insert it carefully like this.
What is this?
My peepee is being held very tightly.
This you see, is a sign that I really love you.
Don't you like it?
No, I...
I mean, I love you too very much.
Yuu-kun.
Yuu-kun!
Onee-chan, it feels really tingly.
My... My peepee feels hot and hard!
Oh my, Yuu-kun...
Should I pull it out after all?
N-No, don't.
You mustn't!
Why?
Because it feels very good.
Your honest self is really cute.
Oh no, it's coming out!
It's okay, Yuu-kun.
Just let it out.
Onee-chan, it won't stop.
It just keeps coming out.
You're cumming.
You're cumming lots inside me.
Your fluids are filling me up.
Mayu-neechan.
Umm... Well...
What's wrong, Yuu-kun?
My peepee is still hard and stiff.
It won't go back to normal.
Then I'll help you until it shrinks to normal.
Really?
Yup, in exchange,
I want you to do it well, then I'll give you your reward.
The door was opened.
The door to the secret flower garden.
Secret Flower Garden
Snow...?
It's not that time yet, maybe I'm just seeing things.
But the way I see it...
Huh?
That's...
Welcome home!
Eh?!
Yu-Yu-Yuki-senpai!
Yes! Do you remember me?
Of course I do.
I'll never forget.
Because your first time is mine now, right?
Here.
We're at this point already, so just go ahead.
No matter what you said, you still seem to love breasts very much.
I'm sorry, I love them.
An honest answer, good.
Anyway, is this your direct way of telling me what you want?
Umm, well...
What do you want to do then?
If possible, I'd like to use your boobs to...
Jeez, you're so easy to read, Eiji-kun.
Your dick is twitching between my breasts.
S-Senpai, I'm cumming!
My breasts feel hot.
Senpai...
Then, shall I take your first time already?
But, if you do it raw the first time,
you might not want to use a condom anymore.
Eiji-kun, push your dick harder!
Stir me more intensely!
Just mess it up wildly.
Senpai, it's really tight, and it feels really good.
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!
It's okay.
Anyway, you sure came a lot.
Senpai, that position is really killing me.
Youngsters sure are amazing.
Guess I have no choice.
Eiji-kun?
I-I'm sorry, I was just surprised...
I mean... three years!
It's been three years!
I-I can't believe this.
Where were you and what were you doing all this time?
Hey senpai...!
The way you react sure hasn't changed.
It feels like I've really come home.
Those things really pack a punch as usual.
It's not good to just stand here like this.
So open the door already.
Uh yes...
But...
This apartment is a single male's room.
Hurry up.
Um... but...
I'll start screaming if you don't.
Were you just playing with me on that passionate night?
Okay, I'm opening, I'm opening it already!
Hey, I've opened it already!
I'm barging in!
What the hel is she thinking?
Hey senpai, take offt your shoes.
Oh sorry about that.
I got too used to life overseas.
It feels really nostalgic.
Doesn't really seem that different from before.
Well, about that...
And it looks cleaner than I thought.
Oh, and boys usually have...
Hey, what are you...?
If there's one thing I remember from three years ago,
it's this forceful way of being dragged into her pace.
Huh?
Wait, this exposed butt...
Oh, there it is!
P-o-r-n.
Hey, those are...!
Oh, doesn't this girl look like how I used to?
But, I think she won't match up to my meaty body.
Eiji-kun?
Pervert.
Hey, senpai...
I still need to ask you...
It's okay, just fire away.
I'm listening.
But please don't suck on it like that.
Huh? Why?
The sensation is...!
Oh well then.
But, that method is also...
Nope.
I'm not stopping.
H-Hey now...
Umm...
I tried to find you.
But I never found you.
Eiji-kun, am I getting bad at this?
You're still completely composed.
I'm gonna have to get serious now.
Why does she always have to...
Beer always taste good, but your cum is also...
Right?
Looks like tears.
Oh, I kind of feel hungry after that.
Is that even a related comment?
Shall we go out for a few drinks then?
Like before?
Well...
The end was the same for both of us, right?
Her breasts really are beautiful.
Umm, I'm not going to touch those senpai.
Oh? Your answer doesn't really sound honest.
I want to touch your breasts.
How honest.
What about sex?
But, if you do it raw the first time,
you might not want to use a condom anymore.
Don't you want to cum inside me like that night?
I have never forgotten,
that first night.
From what I remember happened, I did it again and again.
I want to do it, Yukino-senpai.
Okay.
Do it gently, okay?
Yukino-senpai, does it hurt?
No, it feels too good actually.
That's good then.
Eiji-kun don't pinch my nipples like that, you're doing it too lewdly!
Your hole down there just keeps sucking on my dick senpai.
No way, no way...
Why didn't you even try to contact me?
All this time I...
No special reason really.
I just did the things I did, and worked, as always.
Soon I'd forgotten to check up on you.
I never actually planned on showing up like this, but...
I'm sorry.
Just forget about it.
Yukino-senpai, you don't understand a thing.
We can't escape each other anymore.
That's why please, just let yourself like me.
Idiot...
How cute...
What? Are you really Eiji-kun now?
It should be first done with a kiss, right?
I'm going in.
Yukino-senpai, say that you love me.
Please say it.
Say it.
I love...
I love you! I love you!
I love you.
I'm cumming...
It's very deep inside me...
I'm cumming!
Amazing, it's overflowing.
It's been built up for three years.
Stop kidding me.
Then I'll prove it to you.
Eiji-kun, Eiji-kun!
Senpai, senpai...
Oh wow...
I'm cumming!
I can't believe you'd just dump that big-busted babe.
So much for your pride as a boobs lover, eh?
Well, you see...
My love for boobs and my preferences
in women are completely different.
Do you get me?
You understand what I'm saying, right?
Just like how clothing preferences
and male preferences differ, right?
Yes, yes, it totally is.
What I meant is that I'm not gonna hump
any girl just because they have big boobs.
Besides, I've already thought about you long ago.
See you then.
Senpai...
I gotcha.
I'm caught.