Natural Color Love Alcohol
I love you, Naoto-kun!
Let me give you a massage next.
You don't have to do this much, Akira.
Don't worry about me.
I'll make you feel good.
This is great, Akira.
Feels so good.
Do the balls too.
Just like this.
Akira, I'm...!
It's...It's coming!
Naoto's dick is still hard...
...Isn't it?
Of...Of course!
Here's your reward.
Lift your butt a bit more.
Ok.
So big!
Naoto-kun!
It's so hot I could melt!
Akira!
Naoto! Naoto!
Cumming!
I'm cumming!
Akira, to thank you for the blowjob, I'll wash your body.
Just do the washing and nothing more.
B-But we were only supposed to wash ourselves.
At this rate we'll catch a cold.
No!
Not like that!
I'll put it all the way in, Akira!
Feels so good!
So stiff and so deep inside me.
It's hard...Naoto-kun's...
You've become so tight!
Naoto, no!
Akira!
It's overflowing so much...
Did you feel good, Naoto?
It was great!
"Akira & Naoto"
See?
I leave you alone for just a moment and this is what happens.
Sorry for the mess but it's almost over.
Can't you be more considerate of yourself?
But look, my fever's already gone down.
Naoto...
Stop, don't move.
W-What are you...?
Akira?
You're right, it doesn't feel that hot.
But your face is red.
You know, that's because...
Anyway, I'm okay!
down-hearted
Sorry I made you worry.
You're here so I feel better now.
Oh, that's...
I'll make dinner today!
What do you want to eat?
Tits...
Hm?
What did you say?
Tits!
What?! I didn't mean...
I would like to consume your breasts!
Em, why are you being so formal...?
I wanna eat it! Wanna eat it! Wanna eat it!!!
Will you get better if you eat them?
I will!
Tits!
Tits!!!
Oh you, Naoto...
Then feed me, Akira!
Make me say "aaah"!
Hurry up!
Say "aaah".
Aaah!
Your nipples have gotten bigger.
No, don't say something like this!
Stop that, Akira. If you move away I can't eat them.
O-Okay.
Don't take your hands off.
No...
Don't suck on the tip!
If you keep on licking like that...
Are my breasts tasty, Naoto?
Have you gotten better?
Thanks to this I feel a lot better.
See?
A lot better.
You idiot...
Can I also eat something?
What exactly?
Naoto's...penis...
Akira! Well, that's great and all but I haven't taken a bath so...!
Just shut up already and take it off!
It's so hot I could burn myself.
Well, It's because my fever...
What about that fever?
Sorry, I got excited.
So cute.
And Naoto's smell...
It's so slippery.
Somehow it feels like my head is full of Naoto.
I'm digging in then.
O-Okay.
Feels good, Naoto?
Is it nice?
Not good, Akira.
Thank you for the meal.
Um, Akira-san?
Is it the full menu already?
If the client's condition allows for it I can bring in the main dish.
So my next order is...!
Sigh...
You're an idiot.
Yeah...
You're not considerate...
I was worried.
Yeah...
You're perverted...
But I like you.
Yeah...
My Akira is so sweet!
She loves me so much!
Stop it, you idiot!
I wonder if it will be ok like this.
Just lie there and I will do the moving.
I'm putting it in then.
Don't move by yourself!
Your penis has gotten even bigger.
If I don't do it slowly I...
Akira, show me your face.
Let's kiss.
No!
But I can't wait.
No, don't!
Don't look!
Akira...
I said no!
Come on.
But I told you not to look...
It's going deep, teasing my weak spots and filling me up!
It feels too good.
My balls are so full that it feels like they're going to burst.
I want to release my semen inside you, Akira.
What's that?
I want to cum straight into your uterus.
No way...
I want to make you pregnant!
I'm starting to lose it.
Your pussy feels so good.
Don't be so rough!
I want to melt inside you.
Stop it or I will cum!
You'll make me cum!
Then go on and cum!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Naoto!
Akira!
Oh, my fever's gone.
I forgot about your dessert, Naoto.
So sour!
Until you recover completely I'll feed it to you everyday.
Natural Color
Love Alcohol
Akira-chan.
Time to close.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry to make you work on such
a special day for your boyfriend.
No problem at all. I'm expecting double a payment.
Haha, you'll get your compensation.
Since it's Naoto's birthday I've been hesitating about what to do.
Thanks to the money from my part time we can do lots of things!
First I'll buy a present.
Then we'll go to that restaurant that I've been looking at lately.
Thank you for your work today.
And after that...
Have something to drink.
You're so considerate, manager!
But that's an alcoholic drink from a mistaken order!
What is...
Akira-chan! Akira-chan!
Oh!
Are you okay, Akira?
Wha...
Naoto.
It's Naoto!
Oh, looks like you've had a bit to much.
Naoto!
Your manager was worried so he contacted me.
He told me you were drunk and dizzy and asked me to come.
Thank you, Naoto!
I love you!
The time!
What about the store?
Ah, it's alright.
Your manager has entrusted me with
the key, so rest until you get better.
The present...
The restaurant...
I'm sorry.
Your birthday is already over.
It's ok, don't worry!
I've bought a lot of things as I thought
we'd be celebrating... home...
But I wanted to prepare properly...make you happy...and yet...
Hey, don't worry about it so much, Akira!
I've got your favorite cake!
I've even brought a bottle of Bordeaux wine!
But we don't have any wine glasses.
How is it?
That's better than drinking it from a wine glass.
Isn't it?
Give me some more!
Here's Naoto's favourite glass.
Drink it in one gulp!
Cheers!
Hey, not so...
Such a perverted way of drinking.
I want some too, Naoto.
Some of it spilt so I must clean it lip.
You're lying, you idiot.
Hey, don't suck on it!
There's also lots of wine here, Akira.
No, that's not...
See? So much of it.
If you keep teasing me like this...
It's comming!
It wasn't wine, more like champagne.
What are you doing, Naoto?
Let me try a different glass this time, ok?
No!
Don't look down there!
It looks like it's about to overflow.
Guess I should take a sip.
But it's dirty!
I haven't taken a shower after work so I'm not clean!
It's even tastier when mixed with sweat.
That's enough!
Don't move your tongue that much!
You'll make me cum again!
Your champagne is so tasty, Akira.
Let me drink some more.
No, stop!
I'll cum again!
Akira, could you...?
Wait, Naoto!
Not fair if it's only you!
Y-Your eyes are dim.
Is it ok if I eat my favourite penis?
Don't leave any leftovers, ok?
You idiot.
In that case...
I've eaten Naoto's thing in one bite.
Your insides are wiggling so much, Akira!
They're swallowing my dick!
Taste mine too.
Taste my pussy with your dick, Naoto.
Yummy! It's so tasty!
Akira!
Your pussy is also exquisite!
Oh god, it's coming!
Damn, I'm close!
It's coming!
Give it to me!
Let me drink lots of your white stuff!
My dick is melting inside you!
I'm melting too!
It's coming out.
So much of Naoto's white stuff inside me...
I'm sorry, Naoto.
Although it's your birthday I even made you clean.
It's nothing, I'm having a very happy birthday.
But...
In that case, let's start with getting the present.
Right! Leave it to me!
Tell me if you want something, I'll go
and get it right away and then...
Then I'll give you this, Akira.
X Getting a present';
"0 Giving a present"
A ring?
Well...in other words...
If you put it on your ring finger then...
Yes!
I'll give you everything!