Now it's time to see whether Duranta of
the wind can defeat the lone Rigucio.
It's gone well up until now, but can I really keep this up?
No, he'll help me keep it up. As tong as I fly right here!
I'm flying, sensei!
I'm really flying!
I want to be part of your family.
Why did you win? You ruined all our plans!
The entire script's messed up now.
I'm really sorry. I fell short.
I know that it's not in your nature to hold back.
But that's exactly why we asked you to work for us.
Give it a rest boss. It'll get old real fast if
the champion keeps getting replaced.
Everyone comes hoping to fight him.
Kill that bastard! No mercy!
He's supposed to play the villain, get people excited, and
then I'm supposed to come in for the revenge match.
That'll create the best experience for the viewers.
Just make sure not to lose in an unseemly way.
And so I worked for the boss too.
For the Thunder Gang's sake.
Good work out there. You fought well.
Thanks, but that guy's really strong.
Let's keep this going and get the crowd hyped.
I'll do my best... So in return, could you...
Keep going. Move slowly and precisely.
Sorry, I'm so inexperienced.
I think that swing went really well...
Slowly and precisely.
You're aiming for the wrists.
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
I have more things I need to teach you, you know?
O-Okay, I got it. I'll do my best!
My body can move!
I won't lose!
I heard that the Berk Tribe was filled
with people as hungry as bears.
Yeah a big part of them is like that.
I'm kinda like the black sheep.
I get it. I'm constantly looked down
on because I'm a woman and an elf.
Yeah, and there are tons of people coming
in and out of the city to trade too.
Elves are a rare sight, that's about it.
But just from looking down on someone,
the seeds of segregation begin to sprout.
Humans sure are annoying.
Sorry, I talked too much.
You really are different than the
others in your tribe, Rigucio.
Duranta of the Wind is closing in on One Eyed Gaft!
I can do this!
There is no one more talented than me!
This is all so I can repay my debt of gratitude to sensei!
Is that your way of saying "you're next", Elf woman?
The wind speaks through me! It says
that the next to fall will be you!
Good work out there. Really shook things up.
Good work... What's the matter?
It's a secret medicine from the forest.
It works as a healing agent.
I'm sorry, sensei.
It was a good fight, Duranta.
Let's make the next matches just as exciting.
Yes, sensei.
You're not gonna just do that by yourselves, are you?
Yeah, we're gonna help you guys out!
All's peaceful down here, huh?
Duranta? Rig? The crown princess
has invited you two to dinner.
And so? How do you plan to liven up the next match?
I'm gonna pound my opponent into the dust.
I'm going to do my best to match that.
Duranta, they say that a strong sense of revenge comes
from a strong sense of humiliation, you know?
You act kind while you should be craving the enemy's
blood. So let's try getting you into the right mindset.
We added some aphrodisiacs into Rigucio's meal.
Being made into some man's plaything
is a woman's greatest shame.
Now then, Rigucio, rape Duranta.
She wants me to do that to the
kind but clumsy elf, Duranta?
Rape? Is sensei going to rape me?
Wh-What should I do?
That makes me too happy!
He has wit and insight that can easily overwhelm anyone...
Not to mention his surprising diligence and kindness.
And he has wisdom like a sage.
And above all else he accepted me for who I was.
And today... every time I thought of him,
my womb was hit with pangs of joy.
You like him don't you?
He's a big virgin and dense as a brick, so this might
be a good opportunity. You should go for it!
If it's for your sake, your highness, the Lightning
Gang will listen to any order you give.
My boobs? But...
Nipples are special to a woman. Playing
with those is my privilege now!
This is kinda too boring.
Come on, really get in there!
Damn it boss, I'll rape you next!
Sorry, but I promise I won't go all the way.
He won't go all the way? You're kidding.
Are all gentlemen in possession
of something that impressive?
No, that's a rare kind... a real, sturdy dick.
Both the size and shape are incomparable.
You must be so frustrated, Duranta!
I'm so... frustrated.
I'm so frustrated that he's not putting that into my womb.
This embarrassment is too much.
Sensei's dick keeps peeking through
my boobs at my face. It's so cute.
Here, eat this!
Curse you!
And look how much came out. So amazing!
I've subjugated this elf's beauty.
How was that, Crown Princess?
People from the Berk tribe really are tremendous.
And now the show really starts, right?
Your wish is my command, Crown Princess.
You're finally coming inside me?
Thank you princess!
Oh wow, you're wet.
Sensei's slowly coming inside me.
Mess her up!
He's inside! Sensei's inside me!
I don't want to let go of him!
What's with this? Oh, shit...
Sensei's cum is flowing into my pussy that's
been cumming over and over again already!
I'm so sorry. Seriously.
I-I'm fine, so keep going, sensei.
Everything about this, whether it's the pain
or something else, they make me so happy!
I'm so happy, but I can't let it show.
I'm gonna give it to you good!
I'm so frustrated.
Stop pushing inside me!
Sensei, I'm so happy!
Give me more!
Sensei's gonna cum again! Cum inside me!
I'm so happy, I'm gonna cum again!
I might get pregnant while I'm being forced
to pretend to be disgraced by this!
Is it just me or are Duranta's feet wrapped around him?
That's her finishing move.
The boss is helping to fool them.
Sensei, pour your seed into me!
I'm gonna get you pregnant, Duranta!
No! I don't want to get pregnant!
Get me pregnant, sensei! Come on, womb!
Take in as much sperm as you can!
Sensei! Sensei!!
How is there still so much?
Is it because my body felt good for him?
That makes me so happy.
That was magnificent, Rirucio.
That was shame of the highest caliber.
I'm sure that Duranta is...
It's nice to be young, isn't it?
Keep working hard, you two.
Boss, thank you! Sensei, thank you!
I'll give you the best baby ever.
Duranta, what are you doing?
Healing treatment.
Yeah, I get that, but... why with your mouth?
Do you... not like it?
No, it makes me really happy, but it's still light out.
Is somebody here?
What's the matter, Zelzelno?
You're with Duranta way too much.
I wanna be with her too. So I challenge you!
She's so focused that she can't
even hear what we're saying.
Fine, after I'm done with work.
Great. I'll be waitin'.
Sensei, who was that?
Are they gone now?
Y-Yeah, we're good.
Sensei, I want it.
Let me drink lots of it.
There's so much of you in my mouth!
Sensei... wanna do it?
Sensei, your dick is digging inside me and it's
churning up both my pussy and womb!
Sensei! Sensei!!
Make me pregnant!
I want all of your seeds inside me!
Oh my god, this is so intense!
You're messing me up so hard inside!
Sensei, cum!
Give me lots of your seed inside me!
It's coming so deep inside me!
It's definitely going to get me pregnant!
It's okay sensei, you can cum.
Plant lots of your seeds inside me!
Get me pregnant!
It's coming inside me.
So many of your seeds are coming inside me!
Sensei's seeds...
I love you, sensei!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч