Here we go! Can "Hurricane" Duranta defeat Liguceun The Barbarian?
It's gone well so far, but can I properly coordinate the ending?
He'll adjust to me, as long as I jump at him now!
Sensei, I'm flying!
I could fly!
I wanted to become... a family...
What's the point in YOU winning!? Our plans
and the performance are all messed up now.
I apologize, it was due to my shortcomings.
I already know it's hard to make it look flashy since Duranta is so
weak. That's what you were supposed to cover for as the heel!
That's a bit naive, Leader. The crowd'll quickly get bored
if we just keep pushing the winners to the forefront.
Everyone is doing their best for the troupe.
Don't just kill off the brave angel!
Using the heel to rile up the crowd, setting up for my
revenge match... The crowd seems to be at its climax.
Make sure you don't have an unsightly performance this time.
Me too... For our leader... For the Thunder Troupe!
Good work, you were amazing out there.
Yeah, because he's skilled. Let's keep hyping it up like this.
I'll give it my best effort. So...
Keep moving slowly and precisely like that.
I apologize for being so unskilled.
That one felt like it clicked!
Like I keep telling you, slowly and accurately aim for the armguard.
I just kind of went with the flow...
C'mon, I still have a lot more I have to teach you after this too.
O-okay, I'll do my best.
My body feels great. I can't fail anymore...
I had heard the Velk Tribe were all like hungry bears.
Most of them are, I was just a bit eccentric.
True, you do not look down on me for being an elf or woman either.
Well, the people here change a lot due to the
slave trade, so elves are a bit rare, but that's it.
Once you start looking down on people, it's easy to
develop prejudice. Humans are a troublesome bunch.
Sorry, I got a bit carried away.
You really are quite the eccentric one, Ligu-sensei.
"Hurricane" Duranta is pushing One-Eyed Gaft to the corner!
I can do this! I have to do this for Sensei and everyone who's helped me!
You dare pick a fight with me, Elf?
The Winds command me to take my revenge upon you!
Good work out there Duranta!
Good work! Er, what're you doing?
This is a secret medicine from the Forest,
to stop your bleeding. I'm so sorry, Sensei.
That was a great fight, Duranta. Let's put on a great performance next time too.
Yes, Sensei.
Performances aren't a two-man show, are they?
I'll do my best to support you guys too!
I see you're all in good spirits.
Duranta, Ligu, Her Royal Highness has invited you two to dine with her.
So? What are your mindsets going into your next battle?
I'll beat her into the depths of hell.
I will respond to the best of my abilities.
Duranta, to exact revenge is to wash away
your previous embarrassment with blood.
Let's give our gentle little Duranta some motivation to be more bloodthirsty.
I put an aphrodisiac in Liguceun's food.
To be despoiled by the man you despise should
be the ultimate humiliation for a woman.
Do you understand, Liguceun? Rape Duranta.
I have to do this to Duranta, who's so shy, clumsy, and caring...
Sensei? Fuck me? What am I going to do, I'm so happy!
He easily brushed aside my hardest strike,
surprised me with unexpected dexterity,
Overwhelmed me with his intelligence, and most of all.
He acknowledged me even though all I do is deceive everyone by fixing fights.
And today... Everything I learn about him makes my womb flutter.
You like Ligu, right? That virgin is thick-headed
about these things, so make the most of this chance!
The Thunder Troupe's supreme swordswoman says
she will endure any hardship for Her Royal Highness.
My boobs... But...
The breasts are an important place for a
woman, the Velk style of rape is to grope them!
Hmm, this is just boring.
C'mon, put it in already!
Damn it, I'm going to fuck the Leader later.
I'm sorry I have to do this, but I'll make sure to protect your purity at least.
No way, he doesn't plan to go all the way?
Oh my! Are all males so imposing?
No, that one is quite a find, your Highness. The size and shape are perfect!
Do you feel frustrated, Duranta?
I'm so frustrated.
That Sensei isn't ravishing my womb.
You're embarrassing me too much.
Sensei's dick poking out is so cute.
Take this!
How dare you!
Wow, he came so much!
With this, I've conquered the elf's beauty! Was that to your liking, your Highness?
The Velk Tribe is amazing... He must only be getting started!
Your wish is my command, Your Highness.
He's finally fucking me! Thank you, princess!
Hmm, you're wet.
He's coming in so slowly.
Fuck her!
It's in! Sensei's inside me! I don't want to let go!
Argh, what is this? I can't hold it in!
Sensei's cumming inside me while I cum over and over!
I'm so sorry.
It's okay, please continue, Sensei.
Even the pain is making me happy.
I'm so happy but I'm not allowed to show it...
I'll thoroughly ravage you!
N-no, how could I be taken like this.
Sensei, I'm so happy, please give it to me more!
Sensei is about to cum again... Give it to me inside!
I'm so happy I'm cumming! I can't believe this!
I'm about to be forcefully impregnated while being raped!
Aren't Duranta's legs pulling him closer in?
That's definitely just Duranta's secret grappling technique!
Leader somehow played it off for me... Sensei, give me lots of your baby batter!
I'm going to knock you up, Duranta!
No! Don't impregnate me!
Come, Sensei! Impregnate me! Implant your semen into my womb!
Sensei! He let out so much... Was it because my body felt good? I'm so happy.
That was amazing, Liguceun!
Such a vile ravishing, I'm sure Duranta is...
It must be nice to be young. Keep doing your best from now on.
Thank you, Leader. Thank you, Sensei. I'll conceive a wonderful baby!
Ms. Duranta, what are you doing?
I'm healing you.
I get that, but why with your mouth?
Do you... not like it?
I'm thrilled but... it's still daytime.
Someone's here?
What's up, Zeruzeruno?
You're with Duranta all the time. I want to be with her too! Fight me!
She's so focused she can't even hear him.
Alright, when I'm done with my tasks.
Sure, I'll be waiting.
Sensei, who was it? Did he leave already?
Y-yeah, the coast is clear now.
Sensei, I want it. Let me drink your cum.
I'm full of sensei's stuff...
Sensei, do you want to do it?
Sensei's penis is ravaging my pussy and turning my womb into a mess!
Sensei... Impregnate me! I want all your semen.
You're so rough! You're stirring up my insides!
Let it out, Sensei! Give me all your cum straight into my womb!
It's hitting so deep, I'm going to get pregnant for sure!
Sensei, let it out. Implant... your seed...
It's coming Sensei's seed is flowing into me...
I love you Sensei.
Translator: Shameless Persimmon
Timer: Shameless Persimmon
QA: Dorans, Fogil
softsub: торрент иваниваныч