Coliseum
The ruling empire dispayed its might through magic. Those who were captured as prisoners of war became slaves, destined to be sold off by slave traders. In such a world, these slaves were pitted against each other. In this coliseum, killing is naught but a sport, theatrics employed by none other than Her Majesty, Lunahasol III.
Her Majesty, Lunahasol III
The cute, unrefined, Princess Lunahasol with a penchant for sadism. A deviant princess who gets off on watching strong men plead for their lives before being mercilessly slain. Even though she harbors a thorny side, she is pure, and quite gullible. She never once doubted the Flash Brigade's doings, simply admiring their swordplays.
The Flash Brigade
The Flash Brigade is a perfomance troupe whose sole purpose is to entertain the refined princess, Lunahasol Laitius. The troupe's leader and business representative handles all sponsorships for their perfomances. A petite beastkin that is also flat-chested, she secured her freedom from the coliseum with a hundred battles, and is now regardes as a legendary warrior.
Her Flash Brigade is backed by not just Princess Luna, but all the other spectators. Thus, she excels in raking in profits. However, in reality, though their fighters appear to kill each other, they have learned to deliver non-lethal blows, continuing the show without a casualty.
The Erotic, Big Busted Elf Warrior Duranta
The busty, dual-wielding, bikini-armored elf. She is Duranta, the idol dual-wielder of the Flash Brigade. Her bombastic body is encased in her glamorous bikini armor. Moreover, the very sight of her turning the tables and felling a powerful male opponent, coupled with her real combat skills as an idol dual-wielder, makes her a formidable force in the coliseum. However...
In reality, Laitius' foolproof plan is at play. She's a cleverly placed piece purely for spectacle. The true Duranta never liked battles, and is a warm, compassionate woman. An busty elf that is more akin to an elder sister.
Survivor of the Hot-Blooded Warrior Race Velk,
Rigshon Etvelka
A survivor of the extinct berserker race Velk. He is the Flash Brigade's slave swordsman. Though, he's actually a man who died in the 21st century. A former washed-up, post-graduate freeloader who reincarnated in this realm. He's supposed to be some sort of "harbinger of knowledge", but so far he's just been nothing but a rash idiot, spending his days merrily fighting for the Flash Brigade.
Soon, the scripted bottles Laitius orchestrated for entertainment concluded. The main attraction was at hand. Duranta, in tears, shoken, and her spirits crushed. She forces herself to strike a pose in order to bolster her facade. As coordinated earlier, she is to assault her opponent Righson. Then...
Harem Colosseo
Will Duranta the Gale be able to defeat Rigshon?
We've done it perfectly up to this point,
but can I perform till the end?
I'm sure he's going to do it accordingly.
If I lunge straight at him now.
I'm flying.
Sensei, I can finally fly.
I wanted it to be a family.
What were you thinking by lunging like that?
The plan's all ruined!
The show's also in tatters.
I'm sorry. I wasn't able to do well.
I know that holding back isn't your specialty.
Which is why you were supposed to counter at that moment.
You're making it sound so easy, Boss.
People would get tired of watching
if someone wins immediately.
Everyone takes the troupe very seriously.
Don't give our brave swordsman a pathetic death just yet!
He's to be the opposition, the one
to rouse the crowd's excitement.
Afterwards, she shall be humiliated by my hand,
for the audience's climax.
Don't mess up next time.
I also did it for Boss.
For the Flash Brigade.
Good work.
You did well.
Yeah. But he was pretty good.
Let's rouse them up even more.
I'll... do what I can.
That's why.
There. Just keep your movement precise and clear.
I'm sorry for not being skilled enough.
I think I got the hang of it!
Slowly, and precisely.
Aim for the forearm.
I kind of just swung out.
There's still lots I can teach you.
I get it. I'll work hard.
I'll move my body according to my will.
I won't mess up.
I heard that the Velk are usually voracious eaters.
Pretty much.
I'm quite different, though.
I see.
I wouldn't be surprised if you underestimated
me because I'm an elf and a woman.
Foreign relations are also quite tight in this place.
Though, I was only dwelling on how elves were a rarity.
When you underestimate someone,
you tend to discriminate against them.
Sorry, I spoke too much.
You really aren't a normal person, Rig-sensei.
Duranta the Gale is pushing back Gaft the one-eyed fighter!
I can do this.
There's no use worrying about their unbridled prowess.
It's all to repay back my gratitude to my teacher!
An official challenge, eh, elf woman.
The wind shall reveal it all,
and it's showing me your eventual defeat!
Good work.
You did great there, Duranta.
Thanks for your hard work.
Hey, what's up?
This secret medicine from the forest
should staunch the bleeding.
I'm sorry, sensei.
That was a good match, Duranta.
Let's make it more exciting next time.
Yes, sensei.
You two aren't the only ones running the show, you know?
I'll do my best to assist as well.
It seems so merry in here.
Duranta, Rig.
You ware asked to attend her Majesty's meal.
So...
I wonder how the match between you two will turn out.
I shall drive her down to the depths of hell.
I, too, shall give it my all.
Duranta,
you should strive to retrieve your honor
with a good amount of humiliation.
Why don't we make the match even more exciting,
by having our courteous Duranta spill
some much needed blood, shall we?
I've laced Rigshon's meal with an energizer.
A woman's greatest humiliation,
is to be molded into a tool of "comfort" by the man she hates.
Well then, Rigshon,
rape Duranta.
An elf who actually dislikes wielding weapons.
Duranta's.
Rape?
Sensei is about to rape me?
Wh-What should I do?
It's making me happy.
Instantly deflecting away my precise sword attacks,
has a weird habit of being too particular with things,
and is also as wise as a sage.
And most importantly,
he accepted me, a person who was
already used to deceiving others.
And today.
The more I learn about him, the more my womb tingles.
You like him, right?
It's that blockhead virgin we're talking about.
This is a good chance to agree.
If it is for our Majesty,
warriors of the Flash Brigade shall not defy her commands.
My breasts.
But.
These "boundaries" are always so precious to women.
To make folly of it, such is the humiliation we the Velk can give.
This feels kinda lame.
Come on, make sure you fuck her silly.
Boss, you.
Damn.
Sorry. But I'll hold back the "last line".
He'll hold it back?
Oh, come on.
Do all men have such huge things?
No, that's actually quite rare.
It's not just the size, the shape is also perfect.
Humiliating, isn't it, Duranta?
M-Mortifying.
It's mortifying that he didn't aim for my womb.
This is such an embarrassment.
His dick is going in and out. So cute.
Here, take this!
Why you!
So much cum.
Amazing.
I've conquired this elf woman's beauty.
What do you think, Your Majesty?
The Velk race sure overwhelming.
So, you're about to do the real thing next, right?
Everything that I could ever hope for, Your Majesty.
He's finally fucking me!
Thank you very much, Your Highness!
It's wet.
Sensei's thing is inching its way inside me.
Rape her!
It's in!
Sensei's finally in!
I absolutely don't want to let him go.
What is this? I can't hold back anymore!
Sensei's pumping it into me... into my womb
that already came so much earlier.
I'm really sorry about this.
I'm okay. Just keep going, sensei.
This pain, and everything else, just makes me happy.
I may be happy, but I can't show it.
I'm going to eat you alive.
So humiliating.
Such a disgrace.
Sensei, I'm utterly in bliss!
Just fuck me more!
Sensei is about to cum again.
Cum inside me!
I'm so happy I'm about to cum.
So amazing.
I'm being raped and forcibly impregnated!
Wait, aren't her legs wrapping around him in an embrace?
It's one of her grappling techniques.
She's trying to explain it away for us.
Here, sensei, pump all of your seed into me.
I'm going to impregnate you, Duranta!
No, I don't want to be impregnated!
Cum, sensei! Impregnate me!
Get ready my womb, release your load inside me!
Sensei, sensei!
It's still flowing in.
It felt amazing,
so I'm happy.
That was wonderful, Rigshon.
Humiliation of this level.
I'm sure Duranta is also.
Being young sure is nice.
I need you to work hard from now on.
Thank you, Boss!
Thank you, sensei!
I'll be pregnant with a wonderful child.
Duranta-san, what are you doing?
I'm treating you.
I get that,
but why are you using your mouth?
You don't like it?
I'm extremely happy about it,
but it's still daytime.
Someone's coming.
What's up, Zelzelno?
You spend too much time with Duranta.
I want to be with her, too.
So I want you to fight me!
She's so focused down there that she didn't hear.
Alright then. After I finish my rounds.
Yeah. I'll be waiting.
Sensei, who was it?
Is he gone now?
Y-Yeah. It's fine now.
I want it now, sensei.
Let me drink lots.
There's lots of your cum.
Wanna... do it, sensei?
Your dick is drilling through me, sensei,
and it's stirring up my womb!
Sensei... sensei...!
Impregnate me.
I want lots of your seed in me!
This is so intense.
It's stirring me up inside.
Cum, sensei.
Please pump all your cum into my womb.
Penetrate my very depths.
I'll definitely get pregnant with this.
Oh yes.
Sensei, cum.
Impregnate me... give me your baby.
It's flowing in.
There's so much cum...
so much of sensei's cum.
I love you, sensei!