The Colosseum
It is an age of swords and magic. It these lands, might prevails over right, and to the victor goes the spoils. To be weak means to be captured. To be captured means to be sold into slavery. While slaves provide decent work, they were found to have a much more entertaining role – combat. Matches to the death thrilled the masses – especially Lunahasole, the Crown Princess of the lands. She enjoyed these gladiatorial matches so much that she ordered a colosseum be constructed to house the battles.
The Lightning Gang
The Lightning Gang is a group of slaves whose endeavors on the battlefield won them the favor of Crown Princess Lunahasole. She became their benefactor and provides them with all of their needs. They are led by Litius,, a demi-human with a childlike body and impeccable sword. By winning one hundred matches, Litius earned rights for all slaves.
The Crimson Blade
Marshtal
Crown Princess Lunahasole's older sister. She is very beautiful, but that beauty belies something much more dangerous – a ferocious warrior. Her fierceness has earned her the moniker of "The Crimson Blade". She had the potential to rule the land as the Warrior-Queen but was deemed unworthy due to her lack of magical skills. Despite this, no one views any less of her, as her blade speaks louder than any words. She works tirelessly to uphold the empire's prestige.
She is not very open-minded and has many doubts about the Lightning Gang her sister favors so much. Despite the Lightning Gang's popularity, she harbors prejudice against them and believes they are hiding something.
The Inept, Sadistic Crown Princess
Lunahasole
As Crown Princess, Lunahasole is an extraordinarily inept ruler. None dare speak openly against her, however, as she is renowned for her extreme sadism and cruelty. She had the Colosseum constructed as the gory slave battles aroused her like nothing else. She is a deviant who gets turned on by watching burly men get beheaded as if it were nothing. She enjoys nothing more than watching people begging for their lives and being mindlessly killed.
Despite all that, she is a woman of her word and very trusting. She favors the Lightning Gang for their endeavors on the battlefield. She spectates their matches without a care in the world, unbeknownst of their secrets.
The Last of the Berk Tribe
Rigucio Etvelka
A slave who fights for the Lightning Gang. He is thought to be the sole survivor of the bloodthirsty Berk tribe, but in reality, he's actually a part-timer who graduated from a third-rate college in the 21st century. He had died in his world and was reborn into this one. His intelligence surprises others, as they believe him to be nothing more than a barbarian.
After finding out the Lightning Gang was rigging their matches, Marshtal challenged Rigucio to a duel in hopes of exposing the group as frauds. Knowing he had no way of defeating the Crimson Blade in combat, Rigucio infiltrated the villa of Marshtal's sister, Luna. There, he slept with Luna's wet nurse and mentor, Nero, and learned the truth behind Marshtal's power.
With this new knowledge in hand, Rigucio accepts Marshtal's challenge, as defeating her would greatly increase the Lightning Guild's notoriety. Their fight was over as soon as it begun as Rigucio knew the secret to Marshtal's power – a secret she didn't even know herself. Before her lied defeat... and a throbbing rod, greater than any other sword she had ever faced.
Harem Colosseo
Reborn Gladiator of the Baby-Making Colosseum
I couldn't do much in that situation.
You held it in as best as you could.
I know it's sorta messed up, but she has her reasons.
In any case, I think you have her
favor since she always calls for you.
You may be from the Berk tribe...
but you're pretty smart, aren't you?
Boss, what are you doing?
Finally awake?
Well, I guess you did have a long night.
Wait, don't tell me we...
Do you always wear so little underneath?
The less clothing you wear,
the easier it is to move around.
But more importantly...
More!
Women from the Badger tribe are really deep.
A perfect match for your huge thing!
That was pathetic. Say it with real passion.
C'mon, you're a man!
Fuck me like the barbarian you are!
You fucking slutty kid!
I'm gonna shove my dick into your womb and knock you up!
Oh? Just try it!
Do your best, little boy!
How can someone so small be so slutty?
I'm gonna keep fucking you until your womb breaks!
That's right! Deeper!
Keep thrusting!
You're messing me up so much!
Your dick is the best!
I want to feel every last inch of you! Give me more!
Anyway, I'll help you out with your "sword" training.
Are you sure no one will find out?
Everyone's eating right now.
In fact, that's what I originally came here for.
But after seeing that serious look on your face...
Wow, that didn't take long!
Duranta should have left already.
So good! Your huge thing's digging into me!
I'm being violated!
You're not drunk, are you?
I'm drunk on your dick.
It feels so good having my pussy rammed by your...
Sensei?
What are you doing?
Oh, you're still here?
I wanted to see you before I left,
but it looks like you're busy.
Oh, sorry. I'm just doing some training.
The thought of us getting caught...
It turned me on more than I imagined.
I'm drowning in your dick milk!
Where's Litius, the boss of the Lighting Gang?
Atone for the sin of sullying the Empire's prestige!
Marshtal, the Good-For-Nothing Princess with Huge Titties
Pisses Her Armor While Being Humiliated
My name is Marshtal. Remember it!
I am the empire's Crimson Blade!
She's strong.
"Strong" doesn't do her justice.
In any case, there's no doubting her power.
If Rigucio were to be sliced in half like butter by Marshy...
That'd be the best!
How do I explain it?
It just makes my lower half so tingly.
You understand, night?
Nero?
Where'd she go off to?
Not that it matters.
I want to see him butchered so badly!
She's very deranged.
As her mentor, I really worry about her.
It's probably because Lady Marsh spoils her too much.
The two of them are very close, but the
rest of their family hates Lady Marsh.
They believe she taints their
lineage since she cannot use magic.
Perhaps that's the source of Lunahasole's spitefulness.
But even without magic, Marsh is beyond powerful.
It's because of the armor Lord Edmatora bestowed her.
I charge it with magic, and it gives her great strength.
If you're trying to get to Luna,
you should probably start with Lady Marsh.
I'm cumming!
How dare you put on rigged matches before my
sister and tarnish the prestige of the empire!
If I may, Your Highness.
We may have been rigging matches,
but we are not weak.
Not weak, you say?
A fraud like you dares to spout even more lies?
Why don't you test me then?
I'll prove myself on the battlefield.
I accept your challenge. May our duel reveal the truth!
Winner takes all!
You did your best, Princess Marsh.
The princess was so close to defeating the barbarian
and exposing his crimes against the empire.
But despite her valiant efforts, she was
met with defeat rather than triumph.
Um, Your Highness?
I didn't know this magic armor was the source of my power!
So, um...
Please?
Oh, I recognize your strength! You're the real deal!
I was wrong to criticize you!
On behalf of the Royal Family, I apologize.
So will you please forgive me?
I believe your words were "winner takes all".
But I didn't know about this armor!
Besides, what would you possibly want from a loser like me?
Marsh!
Let's join forces and look for a new way of living.
That sounds scary...
It'll be fine. This is the start of a new age.
We'll pretend to be enemies in order
to usher in a new era of peace.
You'll spare me?
But do you truly expect me to become
friends with slaves and commoners?
All right, time for you to fulfill your end of the bargain.
We're gonna fuck.
I knew this would happen!
What madness is this? It's even bigger
and more daunting than before!
It won't hurt if you're a good girl. Just leave it to me.
I have had good practice with Nero and the others.
Um, please be gentle.
I don't want it to hurt.
H-Hurry up already!
So you want me to just shove it in?
Sorry, I was out of line!
I don't want it to hurt!
No! I'm being groped by a barbarian!
He's having his way with me, a princess!
But you're a woman before anything else, right?
Give in to the pleasure.
Watch your tongue, barbarian!
This is so vulgar!
This feels so gross! Please hurry up and finish!
I hate filthy mongrels like you!
Did you cum while saying you hate me?
P-Perish the thought!
There's no way a barbarian could make me...
No, don't! I'll die if you put it in again!
I don't want it to hurt anymore.
You should know when to give up.
It's going in! It's really going inside me again!
No way! How could you?
Stop! I don't want this at all!
It doesn't fit, so please stop!
It hurts! It hurts so much!
How is it so painful?!
I can't take any more of this!
I just said I couldn't handle any more, so why?!
I hate this pain!
A princess' body is truly something else.
It doesn't feel good at all!
It hurts way too much!
Stop it! I beg of you!
You need to loosen up. You're too tense.
Come on, deep breaths.
Focus on the pleasure.
Impossible...
This is my first time, but...
I can't cum from this! It's too embarrassing!
No!
You make the best face when you give into the pleasure.
Lies! Such a thing could never bring me joy!
This body was not meant to pleasure barbarians!
No! If you move like that, I'll...
What are you planning?!
Oh no... I feel it coming!
You're really sensitive.
Let's cum together, Your Highness!
No! Stop! I don't want to!
I don't want to, but I can't hold it back!
What's this?
It's flooding... It's flooding inside me!
I'm a princess!
But I just got raped by a troglodyte.
Marshy?
Luna!
No! Why are you here?!
Nero said I would find you here...
Sister, why are you...
She's very deranged.
What are you doing?! No! Stop!
Don't show this to her!
Welcome to the Barbarian Skewers
His Dick into the Princess Show!
It's inside me again!
It's going even deeper than before!
Please don't! You can rape me all you want...
Just not in front of Luna!
Can you not hear me, you stupid barbarian?
No!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming even though I hate this and Luna is watching!
Don't worry, Marshy.
I will always love you, no matter what.
No! Stop, Luna!
Don't look at it! You mustn't!
The barbarian's thing is going inside you...
It's firmly rooted inside you,
tearing apart your chastity.
No! Stop that, Luna!
Don't touch there!
If you touch me there, I'll...
Watching my sister's pussy get ransacked by
a barbarian can't possibly be this arousing!
It's almost as good as watching you
piss yourself in fear for your life.
You were watching? You saw all that?
Watching you be defiled fills my
loins with a sensation most divine!
How lovely!
Stop! That hurts!
Let go!
It hurts so much...
No! Stop!
I can't hold back any longer!
Please stop, Luna!
No!
I hate this!
Please stop!
You're pissing yourself while being filled
with the barbarian's seed? Incredible!
That was truly wonderful, sister.
Wh-What are you doing, Luna?
I want to see even more!
I want to see you endlessly ravaged
until your face is drenched in despair!
A high-and-mighty princess being
subdued by the lowliest of dicks!
Her face covered in tears and despair as she
becomes something even lower than a slave!
– The deeper she falls into despair, the
closer she begins to resemble an animas!
– Marshtal was supposed to be her anchor,
but now she's losing it even more than usual.
C'mon, Rigucio, get to it, already!
Oh, I just love that face.
You're so pitiful, Marshy!
L-Luna?
What's happening?
Okay, you're up, Rigucio.
Just treat her like a toilet.
What are you doing?!
Bad girl!
What did you just call your big sister?
You think a lowly barbarian like yourself can
get away with assaulting my hindquarters?!
If that didn't make you learn your
lesson, then perhaps this will.
What are you...
No way! No way!
What is this? Don't tell me...
I don't think I need to tell you.
It's the same dick that violated your sister.
So I really am being raped right now...
I'm being...
Yep. By a lowly barbarian on top of that.
A filthy barbarian's dick is pillaging my insides!
No! Pull it out at once!
It's thrusting inside me relentlessly!
I can feel it plundering me!
Stop... Luna's still a child.
She's old enough to get married under law.
I'm going to pound the pleasures of a woman into her!
I will never forgive you for this humiliation!
Never!
translation: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
You're making me take it like an
animal and pounding me even harder!
I can't believe you're subjecting me to the
same humiliation you put my sister through!
Please stop... Stop doing this to my poor sister.
She needs to learn her lesson.
This is all your large bosom is good for, wouldn't you say?
Luna, stop! That hurts!
Spank me more, Daddy!
No... It's getting even bigger.
It tastes so good...
Pour more inside me!
It feels so amazing!
You're slamming my pussy so hard!
My body's starting to feel strange!
You're going so deep inside me all at once!
My pussy feels like it's being torn to shreds!
How divine!
Daddy...
How cold.
You're looking at me like I'm some
sort of depraved, disgusting pig.