Not weak, you say?
How dare a cheater like yourself spout even more lies.
How about I prove it by facing off against
you in the next bout and winning?
No! I'm being groped by a barbarian!
He's playing with me!
I'm the crown princess!
But you're a woman before anything, right?
Just let yourself feel the pleasure.
Watch your mouth, you lowly barbarian!
This is so vulgar!
No! Don't put it in, I'm gonna die!
It's gonna hurt too much! No!!
You should know when to give up.
This is bad!
It's too embarrassing!
No!
You're very beautiful when you're
feeling pleasure, your highness.
No! That doesn't make me happy!
I wasn't born with this body to pleasure barbarians!
No! The way you're moving...
What are you planning on doing?!
Something's coming!
You're really sensitive.
Let's cum together, your highness!
No, please! You can rape me all
you want, just don't show Luna!
No! I'm cumming!
I don't want to and Luna's watching, but...
I'm gonna cum so hard!
Onee-sama? Don't worry.
No matter what you do, I'll always love you.
No!
Luna, stop!
You can't look at it!
The barbarian's thing is going inside onee-sama...
It's so firmly seated inside, it's tearing apart your chastity.
I love that face.
You're so pitiful, onee-sama!
What are you doing?!
You dumb little sister!
What do you think your big sister is?
You really think a lowly barbarian like yourself
can get away with touching my butt?!
Fine. If you don't get the point after being hit, then...
What are you trying to...
The filthy dick of this barbarian is moving inside me!
No! Please take it out!
It's moving!
It's rubbing against me inside!
Stop... Luna's still a child.
She's old enough to get married under this kingdom's laws.
I'm going to pound the pleasures of a woman into her!
I will never forgive you for what you've done to me!
I won't!
Harem Colosseo
Reborn Gladiator of the Baby-Making Colosseum
The incompetent, complete sadist imperial princess: Lunahasole ~Sadistically punishing her little by little~
How dare you rub that filth around inside me!
You will pay for this treachery with your life!
You need to relax more.
I'm the imperial princess and yet I'm being
raped... violated by a lowly barbarian!
Now you're putting me in this position like I'm
some kind of dog and you just keep pounding me?!
How dare you make me experience the same
embarrassment that you put her through!
Hey, stop it!
Stop being mean to Luna!
This princess needs more.
Onee-sama, please don't stop this
wonderful thing from happening!
This man has made me cum so many times already!
This is so amazing!
I'm glad to see that you've taken
a liking to this barbarian's dick.
I didn't say I liked it.
But I think I might've been born for this thing's sake!
Luna?!
Please do it harder!
Please make a mess out of me!
It hurts!
But I'm so happy!
I want you to rape me like this every day!
You're happy to be reduced to a lowly
barbarian's cum dumpster, aren't you?
I'm happy to be a barbarian's cum dumpster!
I'm so glad to be teased like this, onii-sama!
Inside me...
It's inside... I'm so happy!
My insides are being defiled just like yours were.
H-Hey Luna, that hurts!
Don't grab onto my boobs!
Why do I have to...
Your overly big boobs are only useful in times like this.
Ow... Luna, stop!
That hurts!
Onii-sama, please punish me more!
Please punish me a lot with your brutish dick!
Do it to me and onee-sama at the same time!
I don't want to do anything more embarrassing than this!
Please cover us with your warm and sticky stuff, onii-sama!
No... I-It's starting to swell up.
That's good.
Onii-sama's cum...
It has such a vulgar taste. It's so wonderful!
Really? Do we really have to do it?
Dicks scare me.
It's fine. Nothing to be scared of.
See? It feels really good.
It's not scary.
Onii-chan, are you going to be nice to me?
Yeah, both me and my dick will be nice.
We'll make you feel good, Marsh.
Yeah, make me feel good!
It's making my insides so full!
This is so amazing!
My pussy's being pounded against!
My body's starting to feel weird!
My boobs...
This is too much!
Onii-chan!
You're gonna become a great dick slave.
I will!
I will! I'll become your dick's slave!
So please give it to me deep!
All the pleasure... I can feel it inside me!
It's so hot and amazing!
It feels so good!
I feel weird!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm... gonna cum!
Geez, onee-sama.
It's my turn now!
Stop spacing out and get out of the way!
You're treating your older sister like that again?!
Onii-sama, please mess up this dirty
pig in front of you with your dick!
Hurry up! Please punish Luna's pussy with your dick!
I'll give it to you all you want.
You're already this deep inside me?!
It's like my pussy's about to break!
This is wonderful!
Why didn't you rape me sooner?
I'm mad!
I can't believe you've been holding this
wonderful thing from me all this time!
I want more!
I'll drill it into your body so you'll never forget.
I'm being verbally and physically abused by you!
This is all a dirty pig like me deserves!
Your huge dick is stirring up my insides!
It's so good, onii-sama!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My pussy and head feel so hot from your dick!
You had me on the ropes there.
You can save the flattery.
You were kinda like Sansara.
I thought you were kind of similar to
him when I saw you in the slave market.
Like my old friend that is.
So you know about the man who
gave wisdom to the Berk tribe?
But your timeline's a little off.
So what came before then?
Oh, I see.
Princess Luna is calling for you.
I'm sorry I was such a bad little sister, onii-sama.
Sansara, right?
Memories from a past life.
Parting ways with women because
of death has happened too much.
What are you doing, Luna?
Your cold eyes... It's like you're looking at
a pig... like you're looking down on me!
Onii-sama, I'm a bad girl who couldn't
wait any longer and got this wet!
Do you want to punish me?
What's the matter? Can you not listen to my orders?
How pathetic, onii-sama.
Well then, let me give you the most possible
amount of embarrassment, as you wish.
You're so rough onii-sama!
What's going to happen to me?
It's coming deeper than it's ever come before!
It's rubbing against me so hard!
My dirty pig pussy is so happy!
Now savor this ultimate embarrassment, princess.
I'm going to plant my barbarian's seed inside you!
I won't forgive you if you do that!
Know your place, you lowly animal!!
A brutish pervert like you who has no trouble
exposing me to this much embarrassment,
is so filthy.
You're nothing but a filthy sewer rat!
I don't care. I'm definitely going to get you pregnant!
Plant your seed in me!
Are you really going to make the
empire... the world, your enemy for this?
Y-You're a fool.
You're going to be a criminal.
You're going to be burned alive!
Please give it to me!
Your barbarian cum... it's going to impregnate me!
Rigshion!
Righsion!!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч