Previous on Reborn Gladiator of the Babe-Making Colosseum
Now it's time to see whether Duranta
of the Wind can defeat the lone Rigucio.
It's gone well up until now, but can I really keep this up?
No, he'll help me keep it up. As long as I fly right here!
Sorry I'm so inexperienced.
I think I nailed that swing right now!
Do it slower. Be more precise.
Aim for the wrists.
Good work out there. Really shook things up.
It's a secret medicine from the forest.
It works as a healing agent.
I'm sorry, sensei.
My boobs? But...
Nipples are special to a woman.
Playing with those is my privilege now!
I'm so frustrated...
I'm so frustrated that he's not putting that into my womb.
This embarrassment is too much!
Sensei's dick keeps peeking through
my boobs at my face. It's so cute.
Your wish is my command, Crown Princess.
I'm so happy, but I can't let it show.
I'm gonna give it to you good!
I'm so frustrated.
Stop pushing inside me!
Sensei, I'm so happy!
Give me more!
Sensei, who was that?
Are they gone now?
Y-Yeah, we're good.
Sensei, I want it.
Let me drink lots of it.
Sensei, your dick is digging inside me and
it's churning up both my pussy and womb!
Sensei! Sensei!
Make me pregnant!
I want all of your seeds inside me!
It's okay, sensei, you can cum.
Give me lots...
Harem Colosseo
Reborn Gladiator of the Baby-Making Colosseum
Litius, the Girl with Animal Ears and a Child's Body, Approaches
There's so much of you inside me, sensei!
Keep it down! Don't give people the
wrong idea of the Thunder Gang!
Anyway, you've been summoned by the princess.
So good!
I think I'm gonna call it in early.
C'mon, we don't get much one-on-one time together.
I've always wanted to have a cold one with you.
We've both been messed with by the princess.
I figured we could bond over that.
I couldn't do much in that situation.
You held it in as best as you could.
I know it's sorta messed up, but she has her reasons.
In any case, I think you have her
favor since she always calls for you.
You may be from the Berk tribe...
but you're pretty smart, aren't you?
The gears in my head don't move too quickly.
After all, I'm a third-class Japanese.
Or at least, I was.
Even if you say that, your quick thinking
has saved a lot of your comrades.
You even fix matches to put on a show for the audience.
Mindless killing should be saved for wars.
Besides, that was your idea.
I just feel like we in the Thunder Gang
should feel proud for cheating others.
All right, let me reward you for being so modest.
Bon appetite!
Didn't expect someone from the Berk
tribe to know how to use chopsticks.
I try to learn everything I can.
So that's how it is...
You're so hopeless.
Your hair's covered in blood.
They were after me, so why did you save me?
Don't close your eyes!
Thanks for making last night so fun.
I wonder what you're dreaming about.
I'm kinda offended this isn't waking you up.
How about this?
Boss, what are you doing?
Finally awake?
Well, I guess you did have a long night.
Wait, don't tell me we...
Yeah, there's no way...
How could you forget? You were so rude to me!
You called me a slutty little kid and
called me by my name instead of "Boss".
I really don't remember doing any of that...
Maybe this will help you remember.
I want your dick so badly...
Perhaps it's karma for what I made you do with the princess.
You're so big and hard, Rigna.
You act prim and proper, but you're
really just a dick-hungry slut, aren't you?
That's right.
You make fun of me for looking like a kid,
but I'm a full-grown woman, you know?
You really do have a child's body.
Yeah, I do.
My body's just like a child's.
Do you always wear so little underneath?
The less clothing you wear, the easier it is to move around.
But more importantly...
Look, I'm all good to go!
Do me as hard as you want!
I wish. There's no way it'll fit.
Don't underestimate an older woman's pussy.
I'll take it in all at once.
It's going in!
Shove it all the way inside! Go balls deep!
I was wrong... It really did fit.
Yeah, you were. So make up for
your wrong by doing me right.
Since you're our glorious leader,
I will give it my all to fuck your brains out.
Good! Do it rough!
Like how you do Duranta!
Women from the Badger tribe are really deep.
A perfect match for your huge thing!
More! Deeper! Deeper!
Go all the way in!
You're pushing so far in! Everything inside me is all yours!
Fuck, you feel so good, Boss!
Really? You're not gonna call me
by my name in this situation?
L-Liti?
That was pathetic. Say it with real passion.
C'mon, you're a man! Fuck me like the barbarian you are!
You fucking slutty kid!
I'm gonna shove my dick into your womb and knock you up!
Oh? Just try it!
Do your best, little boy!
How can someone so small be so slutty?
I'm gonna keep fucking you until your womb breaks!
That's right! Deeper!
Keep thrusting!
Get pregnant, Liti!
Cum! Give me lots in my womb!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I can feel it pouring inside me.
It's filling my tummy up.
I can't take it!
Don't let a single drop out.
Boss... No, Liti, you're now my personal cum dump...
and I'm not done with you yet!
What? You're not even going to take it out?
This...
This is so good!
My insides are so mushy! I can't stop!
Shit, how much semen do you plan on wringing from me?
You're messing me up so much!
Your dick is the best!
I want to feel every last inch of you! Give me more!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You truly are a barbarian.
But you're not done yet, right?
Yes!
More! Deeper! Cum even harder inside me!
You really are special.
My head won't stop spinning.
Don't tell anyone about this, okay?
Or about what I'm about to do.
I can see all the way inside you right now, Boss.
Being loved to the last drop is every man's dream, right?
Huh? Oh, yeah... I guess.
Don't be grossed out!
You're hurting this old woman's feelings!
I know we just a fucked a lot, but...
You're an endless tank of lust, aren't you?
I'll get you off when Duranta isn't around.
Be grateful!
Seems like you're doing this more for yourself.
Guilty as charged!
I'll give you the best wake-up call ever.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good night, Rig.
Your rematch with Duranta's coming up soon.
Let me know when you have time to have sex, okay?
Where are you, sensei?
Did he not come back yesterday?
I wanted to see him before I left.
Is he out training?
You scared me!
You've still got a lot to learn.
Your head would be flying off
right now if this were a match.
Duranta's been summoned by the princess.
Does an absent Duranta make an absent-minded Rig?
It's not that I let my guard down.
I think I just got a taste of your true strength, Boss.
I told you, didn't I?
It's easier to move around with less clothing.
Anyway, I'll help you out with your "sword" training.
Are you sure no one will find out?
Everyone's eating right now.
In fact, that's what I originally came here for.
But after seeing that serious look on your face...
Wow, that didn't take long!
Duranta should have left already.
I'll fuck her when she gets back.
For now, your tiny mouth-pussy will have to do.
That's the spirit!
Were you looking for the least romantic place to fuck?
Shut up. I don't want to hear it.
Both of us can't afford to be found out.
Good! This angle's good!
It's going straight inside!
I can feel your weight!
So good! Your huge thing's digging into me!
I'm being violated!
You're not drunk, are you?
I'm drunk on your dick.
It feels so good having my pussy rammed by your...
Sensei?
What are you doing?
Oh, you're still here?
I wanted to see you before I left,
but it looks like you're busy.
Oh, sorry. I'm just doing some training.
You're doing a good job of fooling her, but it's
all for nothing if you keep making me moan.
I'm just about done. I'll see you off in a minute.
Okay, I'll be waiting.
You're so mean.
It's hard to hold back when you're being so rough.
You say that, but you just kept getting tighter and tighter.
It turned you on, didn't it?
The thought of us getting caught...
It turned me on more than I imagined.
That's good! Just like that!
Give it to me deep!
I guess I'll just give him a hug and go.
That should be fine, right, sensei?
You're thrusting so much!
I feel like I'm flying!
Your dick's making me go crazy!
Boss?
Rig! Cum!
Pour it deep into my womb!
So much cum!
I'm drowning in your dick milk!
Where's Litius, the boss of the Lighting Gang?
Atone for the sin of sullying the Empire's prestige!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч