In the 22nd century, depleted energy
reserves and rapid population growth...
...have forced humans to look for
a home in the vast reaches of space.
Each planet in the solar system, along
with countless space colonies, are...
...connected via
the Planet Network System...
...and humans have
advanced even to Pluto.
100 years have passed.
Humans have overcome
harsh living conditions...
...and people have adjusted to
life in new environments.
Eventually, people's bodies
have even begun to change.
However, no one could
have imagined that...
...the day would come when they might
lose everything they had achieved.
State your name and
identification number.
Jonathan Tyberius.
ID number
3150-103-S.H.P.
Jonathan Tyberius, you are
different from other people.
You possess a very special power,
one I assume you're already aware of.
We are about to give you
the final test to see...
...whether you have what it
takes to pilot the powered suits...
...that our military has been developing.
I know you requested to
participate in this project...
...however, I have to tell you this...
We've had six people with the same
ability you have take this test before.
And all have either died or gone mad.
If you want to stop
this test, tell me now.
Okay then. We will now begin the test.
Pluto became the first
victim 2 years ago.
There were no survivors.
They appeared without warning before
humanity, just as they were...
...about to advance beyond the solar
system they had conquered.
We didn't know where they came
from, but we knew why they came.
They would capture humans and
assimilate them into their bodies...
...obtaining information about the
human race from their brains.
Those who were ingested became
components for their weapons.
Out of fear and contempt,
we called them the Apocalypse.
Five minutes until shuttle descend.
My name is Jonathan Tyberius.
I'm a space fleet mobile
infantry unit ensign.
Right now, on my own request...
...I'm heading to Ganymede,
the outermost moon of Jupiter.
Perhaps I was trying to
keep my promise to him.
My promise to Leonard Schteinberg...
The Legend of the Blue Wolves
Vol.1 The Seventh Man
How does that feel?
Do you pledge your loyalty to me?
Y-Yes, I do, so please...
So?
P-Please...
Please what?
You have to tell me what you want.
Please let me come!
How many times do I have to tell you?
When you talk to your superior,
you must address him as "Sir"!
I beg you, sir!
Fine.
But before that, you must entertain me.
Yes, sir.
Good, now turn around.
Lieutenant, I can't hold it any longer.
Good, are you going to climax with me?
Sir, yes, sir!
Jonathan Tyberius...
It should be around here...
We are trespassing on naval
manoeuvres.
Please remove yourself from
the vicinity immediately.
An enforced evacuation warning?
That means...
Thank you,
you saved my life...
What the hell?
If this was a real battlefield,
no one would save your ass.
Unfortunately, our forces have yet
to achieve a successful combat test yet.
However, the new improved Powered
Suit is nearing completion.
And you are the elite, top graduates
from the military academy...
...qualified to pilot the Powered Suits.
From now on, I want you
to train hard as ensigns of the...
...81st mobile infantry
unit, 25th graduating class.
Those commanders who were
promoted in the field...
...are already at their posts,
so try not to cause any trouble.
You are...
You are the guy from manoeuvres...
Brother!
So you are my roommate,
Ensign Leonard Schteinberg.
I am Jonathan Tyberius, I have been
appointed here as an Ensign.
So you're the rookie lieutenant...
You threw a good punch back there.
Oh, stop it.
I heard you were the youngest
martial art champion at the academy.
That's right.
So I punched someone way
out of my league, didn't I?
Well, that was my fault, I'll never
make a mistake like that again.
I sure hope so.
The Apocalypse don't take hostages.
Once captured, anyone
will become your enemy.
Even if it is someone you love...
...The Apocalypse will turn them into
your enemy and you'll have to kill them.
This training is hard.
But if you want to survive, don't stop.
Three minutes to shuttle descent.
Maybe it was my mother who made
me choose the life of a soldier.
My father died when I was little,
and my mother raised me by herself.
She never showed me any
motherly tenderness...
...and was very strict
about my education.
Not only in academics, but she also
made sure that I trained in martial arts.
Men have to be strong.
So they can
protect the ones they love.
That's what my mom used to tell me.
I still hear her voice inside me.
What's the matter?
Why don't you shoot the Manhead?
I know.
But when I see human faces, it's just...
What do you think people who were
turned into one of them feel?
What?
They don't feel anything.
Because they aren't humans anymore.
That's why we should at
least put them to rest...
...while they look human.
Shoot them out of their armed shell
and reveal their humanity.
They deserve to die
with respect and dignity.
So aim well.
And make sure you kill them on the
spot.
Shoot them as your
enemy and one of your own...
...who have already lost their
human lives in battle.
Ensign Tyberius.
Lieutenant Continental is calling you.
Please report to his office.
Ensign Tyberius reporting, sir.
I heard that you're having
trouble at the target range.
Sir!
I will earnestly try my best to
improve my shooting skill, sir!
I like your attitude.
But you don't understand the most
basic thing about being a soldier.
You're supposed to respond to
your superiors with "Yes" or "No".
Y-Yes, sir!
One more thing.
It's "Sir, yes, sir."
Sir, yes, sir!
Good. You're a fast learner, aren't you?
Take your clothes off.
Take them off!
Sir, yes, sir!
So, do you pledge your loyalty to me?
Say you do!
Sir, no, sir!
What's that?
You object your superior's order?
I'm not saying it as a soldier,
I'm saying it as a human being.
Please give me orders
on the battlefield.
It's not only the Apocalypse that
can take dignity away from humans.
Rather, it's humans who take away the
dignity of others for their own desires.
How pitiful...
Attention!
Today, I'd like to
demonstrate Muay Thai.
Ensign Tyberius, step up!
I heard that you hold
the record as the...
...youngest martial arts
champion in the academy.
Sir, yes, sir.
Very good then.
I'll be your opponent.
Show me what you've got.
Sir, yes, sir.
We've just started...
I will teach you a lesson.
That's all you got?
If you pledged your loyalty
to me, I could stop this.
I'll never say it even if he kills me!
Sir, no, sir!
Who told you that you could pass out?
Come on! Stand up!
Who the
hell...
He's already down, sir.
If you'd still like to fight, I'll take his
place as his roommate and fight you.
Damn you!
I forgot to tell you, but
my speciality is karate.
Don't move.
Continental, that bastard...
He did a real number on you.
Leonard, are you...
That's right...
But don't worry...
...I'll never force anyone to
do what they don't want to do.
When I realized, I had an erection...
I would imagine myself having a
beautiful body and I'd get aroused.
That beautiful body
I dreamt of having...
The perfect body looks
just like Leonard's...
I was getting aroused, but
not because I was narcissistic.
It was because I was...
Emergency roll call!
Wake up! Emergency roll call!
We have information that a spy
might have slipped into our base.
Therefore, we'll perform a body cavity
search.
Got that?
Sir, yes, sir!
Lieutenant!
That is indeed the emblem of the
Apocalypse!
So you are the spy, aren't you?
I'm asking you, are you the spy?
Sir, no, sir!
I see, I guess I have to investigate
this case a little more.
Take him away!
Since you're his roommate,
you're also responsible for this.
You will be confined to the guardhouse!
Stop it!
Brother! Brother!
Brother! Help me!
Brother!
Brother! Brother!
Stop it!
You bastard!
Are you going to draw your
weapon on your superior?
Continental, I will not
forgive a thug like you.
This incident was taken
care of secretly...
...and Headquarters
will never find out.
And a couple of days later...
...Leonard was transferred
to fight at the front lines.
I have so many memories from
this knife, good and bad...
...but I want you to have it.
Take care of yourself.
Please wait!
Leonard was sent to the 2nd Titan
recovery project, never to return.
Five...
...four, three...
...two, one...
...take off.
Bail out of the mother ship immediately.
We will rendezvous at the
coordinates 2-7, Mark 135.
Enemy ahead! Destroy them!
Alpha 1, Beta 3, go around the left.
Roger! Alpha 1,
turning left...
Leonard!
What?
You said you'd never force anyone to
do what they don't want to do, right?
Yeah.
I know when you look at me, you're
thinking of your brother, but...
You are you.
My last wish in this world
is to spend a night with you.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am.
Promise me,
...if you see me in the battlefield, and if I
become one of them...
...I want you to kill me.
Leonard! It's me!
Leonard...
Shit!
Leonard, it's a promise...
Leonard!
2199 AD, March 15, on the surface
of Jupiter's satellite, Ganymede...
...The Earth Defence Force won against
the Apocalypse for the first time.
But I can't believe we would
find such a thing on Mars.
It seems like it has something
to do with their power.
That mysterious transmission we
received from planet Barnard...
...mentioned something about them.
So we brought the tenth S.H. P here.
Then surprisingly, the main computer
of Battleship Iron Man was activated.
Battleship Iron Man?
Oh, excuse me.
It looks so strange
that's the nickname we gave it.
We are reaching the bottom floor.
Please remain seated.
To be continued...