Onee-chan...
Keep your voice down!
I... can't do that.
Because I'm now making love to my dearest brother.
O-Onee-chan...
It's okay.
Oh yes...
But, if anyone finds out that we siblings are doing something like this...
Onee-chan... this isn't good!
This feels,
this feels really amazing.
Oh yes.
We're having forbidden sex as siblings.
But I don't care a bit about that.
Your raw dick...
I just want more of your raw dick.
Here, look.
Your dick has already opened up my pussy this much.
What's wrong with you today, Onee-chan?
You seem to be really horny today.
Well, you see,
it's not safe for me today.
I might be ovulating now.
That's why, my body... no, my womb,
wants to receive your cum very badly.
Th-Then...
Yes, that's right.
And at this moment,
you're really having sex with your actual sister.
Doing it... with my actual sister...
Yuu-kun,
this is really amazing.
You're reaching the very depths,
and, and it feels good!
It feels great!
It feels really good.
The way you fuck me is really amazing.
Onee-chan, I'm about to cum.
I'm about to...!
It's alright.
Just cum lots.
Onee-chan, it's going to burst.
Yuu-kun, this is amazing.
Yuu-kun, Yuu-kun!
Onee-chan... Onee-chan...!
I'm cumming.
I'm really about to cum inside!
Give it to me already.
It's in my womb right now,
I'm now impregnated with your cum, Yuu-kun.
Your thing is still lively it seems.
We can't just go to sleep with you like that, you know...
Onee-chan...
I have to, hold it in.
2:30 am...
I wonder if she's already asleep.
Onee-chan,
I can't endure this any longer.
What is it?
O-Onee-chan!
If you continue yelling out like that,
they might wake up.
Umm... yeah.
What are you doing at this hour?
What about you?
What are you doing going around like that?
Even trying to sneak in.
You couldn't be...
I-I had to go to the toilet!
To the toilet.
Oh, I see then.
Toilet, huh.
Aren't you going in?
'To the toilet' I mean.
Hey, Yuu-kun,
did I do something wrong?
Why are you avoiding me?
Wh-What's with that...
But you won't even look at me anymore after that day!
I guess the fact that we did it,
the fact that we had immoral sex,
was something that you regretted, am I correct?
I didn't!
I was really happy back then,
and it also felt good.
Umm, it's not really that...
It's because whenever I look at you...
It becomes completely like this.
Oh wow...
Wait, you didn't have to avoid me because of that!
You also seemed like you weren't in a good mood...
It's because you tried to avoid me the very day after we had sex.
Of course I wouldn't be in a good mood.
Besides,
I was so focused on keeping it a secret.
Jeez, Yuu-kun, you're such a...
I felt really uneasy the entire time, you know.
I'm sorry.
My my... but are you really sorry about it?
Yeah.
You say that,
but your thing down there is still reacting like this.
But, I haven't done it in one week so...
You endured it this entire time?
Yeah.
I see.
So you did keep our promise.
Yup!
Alrighty then.
Then let's settle this together, right now.
It's quite thick.
Huh?
Something already came out?
That comes out... whenever it gets aroused...
I think, it's about this hard, right?
Oh no, Onee-chan, please don't...!
What? Sorry, did that hurt?
N-No
That was close.
L-Like that.
Alright, I got it then.
It feels good, Onee-chan.
Do you understand the situation we're in?
We're doing indecent things right in the hallway.
That's right.
How are we going to explain ourselves if someone finds us here?
Oh no...
Now I'm starting to feel really anxious.
Jeez, Yuu-kun...
Umm,Onee-chan...
I'm...
Okay then.
Mouth, mouth!
Mouth?
Yeah.
I want you to use your mouth.
Alright, I'll use my mouth then,
and this time, I'm using it till the end, okay?
This... this feeling...
What we did together,
was something I just couldn't forget.
It makes me excited.
I guess this is how it feels when it's really good.
I already decided that if we did it again,
I'd be sure to cum in your mouth.
O-Onee-chan...
Onee-chan...
Oh no, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum lots inside your mouth, Onee-chan!
Umm...
I drank it.
How did it taste?
Well...
Just like that.
I'm sorry!
I just...
It's my turn.
Yuu-kun, that's...!
Don't, Yuu-kun!
It's dirty down there.
Oh no...
I'm starting to moan.
What should I do?
This just feels too good.
Oh yes...
That part is...
I'm really about to cum while you lick my pussy.
Oh no!
I can't hold back anymore.
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming...!
Did you just cum?
I did it.
Just wait, Yuu-kun.
I don't want to do it here!
Eh? … O-Okey.
I understand.
Well...
So, why did you choose this place?
I know that you don't want the bed sheets to be soiled, but...
Onee-chan, your legs...
Move forward a bit.
Like this?
Yup.
It's all the way inside.
Oh, did it hurt?
You also haven't done it since we had sex that time, right?
Are you alright?
It doesn't hurt.
I feel even better than before.
I'm glad.
Yeah, thanks, Yuu-kun.
What was that just now?
Something just squeezed me inside!
It just twitched, because you were so gentle with it earlier.
Also,
you're not exactly the only one who’s been holding it in for the past week.
Onee-chan,
we're having sex right now.
Onee-chan...
I can't stop...
Onee-chan, you're the best.
I really, really wanted to do this for a long time.
So, I'm really aroused.
 Му insides feel amazing.
No, this position,
makes me really feel you inside me.
But I'm happy.
I always thought that you hated me for this.
So it's just...
Do you really think I'd hate you, Onee-chan?
Of course not.
Even before we did this, and even after doing it, I've always...
I've alwas loved you.
Yuu-kun, I'm happy.
Me too, also love you.
Yuu-kun,am I heavy?
Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm perfectly okay.
Yuu-kun, you're quite strong.
Quite cool actually.
Onee-chan, it's not safe for you today, right?
How do you know that?
Because you said something like that in my dreams.
What's that?
Then, if I say that it's true,
are you going to cum outside?
No, no...
I want to cum inside.
I want to pump it inside you.
Y-Yuu-kun!
I'm going to bear a child if that happens!
A child...
of your own...
This is amazing.
Yuu-kun, you really planning to impregnate me?
Amazing, sex like this feels awesome!
A-Amazing...
It's going wild inside.
Huh?
What's this? I can't stop...
Oh wow...
You came lots and lots inside me.
Will you get pregnant now?
I'm not really sure.
I'm actually safe today, but...
With this much cum...
Onee-chan...
It's okay, Yuu-kun.
What's wrong?
Somehow, well, it's already too late,
but I just realized that scenes from porn manga really do happen in real life.
I never thought,
my smart and diligent Onee-chan,
would actually do something this indecent with her own brother.
Nobody would probably believe me even if I told them.
Jeez, don't just say those things.
This is, after all, a secret between you and I, Onee-chan.
Well?
Does my dick feel good?
Yeah, it does.
It feels great.
For me, your pussy is the best, Onee-chan.
Both our wet parts are getting even wetter.
It's really amazing!
That's because...
The dick of my beloved Yuu-kun,
is hitting my deep soft spots over again.
Yes, that's great.
I'm really happy that I'm your brother.
I can do these kinds of indecent things anytime.
Let's do lots of pleasurable things from now on, okay?
Let's do it regularly from now on.
What is this?
What did you do, Yuu-kun?
I'm sorry..
I just came.
No way.
And you're still fucking me while cumming
Amazing.
That's amazing, Yuu-kun.
All those sloppy sounds are making my insides even sloppier.
How are you even doing it?
But, but I just can't stop this pleasurable sensation.
Your cum is making...
Is making its way all through my pussy's insides.
I'm definitely going to get pregnant.
Onee-chan, Onee-chan...!
My insides feel all tingly.
Your hot thing is...
Yuu-kun, that's good.
Just keep on fucking me.
This is amazing, really amazing!
Deeper, deeper inside...
Directly... deep inside your very womb!
Yuu-kun, that's not possible.
This is too strong!
I'm going to get torn apart.
But, thinking that you're really making love to me...
I just start to crave for it helplessly.
Crave for your hot and thick seed,
inside where I'm supposed to bear a child!
I'm cumming, it's coming out.
Onee-chan, Onee-chan!
It's okay... me too, I'm also about to...
No, no...
Yuu-kun, feeling sleepy already?
No, I'm still fine.
Figures.
Because your thing down here is still so lively.
I guess you still can't sleep with this.
Oh yes...
Yes...
Oh yes, oh yes...!
To be continued... probably...
Thank you for watching.