Your dick...
It's hitting me deeply.
My thing is all the way inside you, Onee-chan.
You came so many times inside me already,
that my body became this slutty.
Me too, after all the times I've cum inside you,
my body still hasn't had enough!
Your pussy is the best, Onee-chan!
The way your dick pushes inside feels so good.
Oh yes... oh yes.
Fuck me, fuck me more.
Onee-chan.
Sorry about this.
I'm supposed to be the older sister,
but I'm doing it in such a slutty fashion...
I never thought that I'd love sex this much.
When I was masturbating to your panties before,
I was imagining you exactly like this.
That's why I'm very happy.
Really?
I'm glad, then.
I love the you that loves sex!
Onee-chan, let's do this together.
Wait... Yuu-kun...
Stop...
The door, the door is...!
The door?
Oh, it really is open.
But, I'm already about to...!
I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum already!
Oh wow, I can just feel it.
My pussy feels like it's about to burst!
So hot, it feels so hot.
Oh wow.
I'm going to cum inside, Onee-chan!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's pumping inside me again.
My womb is completely filled with my own brother's cum
Jeez, that really startled me.
You didn't lock it?
Huh? I didn't?
Oh come on, Yuu-kun...
Jeez.
You're just like a baby, Yuu-kun.
Shall we hit the sack now?
What?
I don't wanna.
I want to do it more.
See?
Hey, look at this, Yuu-kun.
You came this much.
#unrecognized text#
Oh, hey!
Till tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Whoopsie.
We're done here.
Okay.
Oh, Onee-chan,
the floor is wet over here.
Oh my.
Try wiping it with your sock.
What? ...Jeez...
Alright. Goodnight, then.
Yeah.
Oh, Yuu-kun, good morning.
So you were able to wake up on your own.
Good boy?
Huh?
Where's Mom?
She's not around.
Work?
Not sure.
I haven't heard about it from her.
More than that,
it's bulging really hard.
We did it so much last night.
Still not enough?
W-Wait, this isn't what you think.
This isn't it.
It'll go back to normal right away, so...
Huh?
Alright then.
Come over here.
O-Okay.
and just release it when you have to.
Okay.
Alright, here we go, then.
Oh, I fame already.
Such a waste.
Hey, Onee-chan,
Umm... once more, please?
Please, Onee-chan?
Onee-chan...
Go on, your friend already came for you.
Why? It's still so early.
Oh wait, I'm assigned on duty today!
I have to change panties.
I'm home!
Oh, wait...!
You surprised me.
That's dangerous, you know.
I'm sorry 0nee-chan.
I was fixated on you the entire day.
I just wasn't able to restrain myself.
Hey, you still need to study properly, you know.
Alright.
Onee-chan...
Good grief...
Onee-chan, I want to kiss.
It tasted sweet.
Strawberries?
I was eating some candies a while ago.
Onee-chan, I'm already...
Let's have sex.
But why don't we change before that?
Okay.
Wait, those words mean...
Wow, just wow!
You look too cute, Yuu-kun!
I knew I was going to wear something like this again.
I already told you that this is embarrassing for me.
You even prepared this wig...
Come on, try speaking just like earlier.
I can take these off already, right?
Onee-chan?
You really don't want to wear it?
Even though you're actually so aroused right now.
Th-That's...
That's absolutely not true!
S-See!
Oh my, how small.
Huh? That's strange.
Hmph!
Oh?
So it gradually grows like that.
That was interesting.
So you're aroused now.
Jeez, just forget about that!
Let's... let's do it already.
What exactly?
Oh come on!
You said we were gonna have sex earlier, right?
Onee-chan's such an...
...idiot.
I'm sorry.
I may have teased you a bit to much.
Then, let's have lots of sex, okay?
Alright, here.
Onee-chan, now we're finally...
...doing it!
It's so,
so big.
You're pushing it so deep into me...
Slow down a bit.
It's... it's your pussy!
Yuu-kun...
Take it easy.
My dick is pushing into you...
...into your most erotic parts.
I feel so aroused.
Oh no, it's too deep...
It's just too deep.
Amazing,
dick in and out of your pussy.
to cling onto my foreskin.
Your pussy just feels so good, Onee-chan.
This position is embarrassing.
Can I cum inside today?
It's alright.
Cum a lot.
Oh yeah!
I'm going to cum a lot then, okay?
Here I go, Onee-chan.
My insides feel amazing.
There's an overwhelming sensation inside me.
I'm about to cum.
It's going to come out.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
It's twitching really hard inside.
You just... came inside me.
Lots of it is pumping into me.
My insides feel hot.
That felt so good.
But then this...
This guy won't call it quits yet.
Onee-chan...
No way.
Oh no... it feels amazing.
My insides are being stirred.
Like it's being turned to slurry.
Onee-chan, your expression is becoming lewd.
What is this?
No, I can't keep this up.
Stop grinding me like that.
Th-This is...
I think I can go even deeper, Onee-chan.
It feels really good.
Onee-chan, you really are the best.
Oh no, seeing you like that makes it really hard to restrain myself.
I'm going to cum, okay?
No, oh no... you're going too fast.
I'm cumming, it's going to come out!
Onee-chan!
Yuu-kuh... let's rest for a bit.
I'll probably go crazy if we don't.
Yuu-kun....
Are you listening to me?
Come on, keep it up.
Here.
Onee-chan...?
Come on, do it as vigorously as earlier.
You were going to keep fucking me until you came inside, right?
Onee-chan...
Yes, that's right, more,
fuck me deeper!
Onee-chan!
It's gripping me really tight!
It feels so good!
Yuu-kun.
I love you.
I love your dick.
My insides feel all tingly.
Yuu-kun.
It's so hot.
It's going to melt.
My pussy feels as if it's going to melt.
Onee-chan.
Onee-chan!
Your dick feels amazing.
It's really stirring me hard,
and it's hot... it feels so hot.
Yuu-kun...!
Yuu-kun.
Oh no, Yuu-kun, big sis here is about to lose her mind.
Oh yes...
I-I'm going to cum too!
Let's cum together, Onee-chan!
Here I go!
Let's cum together!
I'm cumming!
Yuu-kun.
My insides are...
Yuu-kun,
Yuu-kun...
Yuu-kun.
That was amazing.
You just finished cumming.
I'm going to pull out.
Okay.
So white.
It was so big earlier.
Now it looks all petite and cute.
I guess it finally calmed down thanks to you, Onee-chan,
Onee-chan.
That's...
Oh no...
Look, it's all fine now.
But,
I can't move anymore.
It's okay.
Just stay right there.
Leave this all to big sis.
Well, how is it?
This is the pussy that you really love.
Feels good, right?
Onee-chan, your insides feel good.
My dick is being sucked inside.
Even my hips are being pulled up.
Yuu-chan's such a cutie.
Show me that face some more.
Yuu-chan,
Sex... really feels good, doesn't it?
Somehow, I feel...
I feel like I'm raping a girl.
So this is how it feels for guys.
I might just learn to love this.
But, I'm a guy.
This shouldn't be, and yet...
Jeez, you really aren't honest with yourself.
This is unfair.
But you like it, right?
It's alright, just say it.
So good...
Oh yes...
It feels good being raped by Onee-chan.
It feels pleasurable for me too.
You're about to cum, right?
I can feel it.
I'm going to cum, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Give it to me.
Don't waste a single drop.
Pump it all into my womb.
Alright.
This should be okay.
We're doing it once again.
We're not done yet?
Onee-chan, I'm already...
Already... forget it...