BB Store
Geez, Mie! You call this clean?
Well... yeah, sort of...
lt hasn't been cleaned at all!
You need to do your job! Sheesh!
Here goes Fujisawa with her lectures again...
A-Anyway, let's just finish up.
She's always so sweet to me. Otonashi, thank you!
Man, you're too easy on him, Otonashi!
And then there's this bitch...
What's that look for?
Oh, no, it's...
...nothing...
That fucking bitch.
She embarrassed me in front of Otonashi again!
''You call this clean?'' Whatever! Who does she think she is?
l know that haughty bitch writhes in pleasure with a cock up her at night.
Well, not that l've seen it, but...
Huh?
Ow...!
l'm so sorry! l was in a rush.
lf l don't hurry, the dimension tremor will end.
Disappearing Tablets
Disappearing tablets?
''When on tour, please use these to avoid getting involved.''
''lt will bend and disperse space, and make you disappear.''
So you become invisible? What the hell?
Well then, l must be going now.
Hey, you dropped this-
Here it comes.
What's with that guy?
Shh! He'll hear you!
They're still mooching off their parents. How dare they laugh at me!
Normally l wouldn't be dumb enough to do something this dangerous, but...
...your laughter seems to have given me the courage!
Let's go... you moochers!
Ow!
What's wrong?
l just bumped into something.
Eek!
What was that? lt didn't feel like the wind...
l wonder what l bumped into?
lt's for real!
Bath House
Then this is the first place to go!
l thought it'd be all old women. l wonder if there's a girl's dorm around here?
Captain! l've spotted the target!
Huh?
Oh no, did scratch myself somewhere?
l shouldn't get my period for a while.
Well then. Pardon the intrusion!
Right, left, right, left, right, left, right, left!
lt's like l can hear her voice...
Here. Drink as much as you like.
Well? ls it good?
Yes! lt's so yummy!
This feels kind of good...
Stop, don't stare at me like that.
What? You're getting aroused? You're so dirty...
l'd better clean here too.
lt's soft and warm.
What? You want to see this too?
Here, this is my butt.
ls she going to...?
l'm gonna cum!
l might as well wash off too.
Come to think of it, the instructions said the pills only last for an hour.
l'd better be careful.
Hello, Miss. What is it?
Did you want to join me? You should have said so!
Sit wherever you like.
Whoa!
You want to sit there?
Th... This is bad. Her scent, and her softness...
Nooo!
Please don't notice!
lt's okay. Calm down. l'm not here. l'm the bath water.
That's right. l'm the bath water. l'm the bath water!
This is the bath water. lt's just the bath water moving!
Does it feel good?
lt feels great. More... Fondle me more...
So, what about this?
No... That's my weak spot...
All right, l'm not gonna lose!
There... there...!
lt's inside. lt's inside!
lt's okay. Thrust it in deeper!
l can't hold myself back anymore!
lt's okay, you don't have to hold back!
l... can't hold it anymore...
lt's okay. l want you to cum!
Mie! lt's filthy again!
C'mon! You should say something too, Otonashi!
The truth is... Mie looks like my dog, Rick.
That's why l have a hard time getting mad.
Hanazono All-Female Academy
Damn that Fujisawa! l ended up here in rage.
Now this is soothing!
l see. Good, good.
We'd better get changed quick! We're going to be late.
Ah, they just finished phys-ed!
You never get to smell their sweat by watching a DVD...
What an aggressive girl!
Damn, that was nasty!
Target sighted! Captain! Please give us your orders!
Very well then, attack!
Huh? Where's my milk?
Right here!
Tell me God, am l an idiot?
Geez...
Oh, don't mind if l do.
Huh? Does anyone know where my juice went? lt was right here.
Damn it! How dare you torture me so...
Suzu, hurry up! You're the only one who hasn't changed!
Yeah, l had to clean up the equipment.
Well, we're gonna go then!
Huh? Wait for me!
Oh, by the way, there's a ghost at this school that attacks women when they're alone.
Be careful!
Hey! Don't say things like that!
Th... They don't exist...
l'm right here.
Terrible things will happen if you don't stay quiet.
B... But...
Well? Do you feel it?
No...
What... What will make you rest in peace?
Hmm... let's see. First, get on the desk.
Well then, let's start with your gym clothes...
Then of course...
No!
Okay, you're ready. Get on all fours, make a fist with your right hand...
..bring it next to your face with the palm facing down, and say ''Meow''.
M... Meow...
C-Can you rest in peace now?
How am l supposed to stop after seeing that?!
But... Nooo!
lt kinda tastes like sweat...
Nooo!
S-stop...
Okay, let's get started.
No... No, l'm going to pee...
Thank you very much!
Wh-What's wrong Otonashi? You seem a bit down today.
Wh... What?!
Stop making her cry!
l... l'm sorry. He didn't make me cry.
My dog Rick died yesterday. That's why...
Oh... well don't startle me like that! But, l'm sorry for your loss.
Hey!
Wh-What? lt's your fault for putting yourself in that position!
Why you...! l'm gonna smack her one day!
But...
l want to cheer her up, but...
Whoa! Otonashi lives in an expensive condo like this?
Rick... Why did you die?
So this is Rick. There is sort of a resemblance...
Hey Rick... Were you happy with me as your owner?
l was happy.
l was happy to be owned by you.
Rick? ls that you Rick?
Yes, so please don't be sad. l'll be watching over you from Heaven-
Oh Rick, if you're here, cheer me up like you always did.
What?!
So... does that mean...?
Does that mean...?!
Come on, lick me all over.
Rick, does it taste good? Does my pussy taste good?
That should do it.
Come on. lt's okay, Rick. Fuck me...
Fuck me?
What? You want me to face this way?
Here. Does that make you happy?
What?! They were fucking too?
l'm starting to get jealous, Rick!
Yes...
Rick, yes...
Huh? You always came quick, but...
Rick...
No... No, no...
l can't last that long!
No... l'm going to cum... l'm going to cum!
Mie...?
She... She saw me...!