The man who got an invisibility potion through bizarre circumstances, Mie Naito.
He used it for many pranks, but...
...Mie got a little careless, and was seen by a drunk Otonashi.
Huh, l wonder what's going to happen to him now?
She... She saw me... What am l gonna do?
Hey, you.
Y... Yes?
We just got a report from a woman. There's been a...
That's him!
He was in my room!
O... Otonashi!
Why don't you come with me down to the station.
lt was a dream...
That's right. l was too scared to go home to my apartment, so l slept here...
But, that wasn't a dream...
Please let it be a dream!
l know that's impossible, but...
Huh? lsn't that the weird guy from the other day?
l don't even feel like getting mad today.
But having problems and being horny are two different things.
Hanazono All-Female Academy
l've come, my dear alma mater!
l swear there was a ghost!
Sure, sure. You want me to come to the bathroom with you, right?
l'm telling you, there was!
Yeah, yeah.
You don't believe me!
l'm really, really, really positive there was!
The bathroom, eh?
Welcome!
Huh? You're that lady from the bathhouse!
So you're a teacher here?
Oh! Honey, what are you doing here?
What? You want to see me pee?
Geez, you're such a pervert.
Fine, l'll show you.
What? You want to see it closer?
Here, this easier to see, right?
l was fantasizing again.
Seems like l go into fantasy mode whenever l see her.
So, who's next?
Hurry, hurry! l'm going to pee my pants!
Oh! That voice!
That's...!
l guess it's that time of the month.
Blood... blood is...!
From a girl like her? A girl like her?
Calm down. Calm down.
lt's a path all girls must walk!
See? Look how pretty everyone is.
Nature plays such beautiful melodies.
Figures, l have to go too. l'll meet you there.
But study break is almost over, and if you're alone...
l'll be fine!
But l'm telling the truth...
What's going on?
This can't be happening!
No... l have to go...
lt's okay, go ahead! You're not peeing, but your pussy juice is coming out.
All right, here l go!
The... the day's finally come... But Otonashi hasn't said anything to me yet.
l'm positive l saw Mie, but that can't be. l was really drunk too...
Am l in love with Mie? He looks like Rick, so he seems approachable, but...
Maybe she didn't notice? l'm sure she saw me, but...
Uh, um...
Mie, you go first.
No, please, you first.
U-Um... This might sound strange, but two nights ago... Um...
Tw... Two nights ago?
Heat that up, will ya'?
l couldn't ask her. Why am l like this?
lt's Fujisawa.
She ignored me.
Fine then, bitch!
l'm positive she went into this park, but...
There she is!
This is my chance to get revenge!
Man! Just because you're cute, you think you can look down on me.
l'll look down on you! Take this!
Was that a bug? How gross!
On top of that, l saw him earlier... Today kind of sucks.
Who are you talking about?
Who do you think? That Mie guy l work with...
You've got some balls to say it out loud!
What... what the...!
All right! Here l go into fantasy mode!
Prepare yourself, Fujisawa!
Mie, is that you? l'm so sorry for everything. Please forgive me!
What? Say my name with some respect!
Mr... Mie...
That's a good girl.
Here's your reward. Doesn't it feel good?
l knew you had huge breasts. You're always showing them off!
Th... That's not true...
Oh? You're getting wet, huh?
P... Please... Forgive me, Mie.
''Mie''?
Mr... Mie...
lt's too late for apologies!
Here l go!
Oh? You're starting to relax.
No... l can't...
Oh, what? Are you starting to feel it?
Mie, your fingers... feel so good...
Ah, right there!
More! Finger fuck me more!
Yes... Yes... Fuck me harder!
l'm going to cum! l'm going to cum!
All right, now it's my turn.
Please, no more...
That's right, have everyone look at you.
N... no...
D-don't look at me!
Sure, l was drunk, but... l shouldn't have done that!
Please stop!
Otonashi is in trouble!
Hey baby, l love girls with glasses.
What do l do? l have to save her! But there are two guys.
Leave me alone!
l'd lose even if there was only one, but...
Someone, help...!
C'mon, lady, it'll be fine.
Rick!
Oh yeah, l'm invisible right now!
lf they can't see me...
Ding!
Master!
What the...?
Huh? ls tha you, Rick?
D... Dammit! Where is he?
M... Mie?
H-huh?
You bastard!
Oh noooo!
U-Um... Does that mean the Rick from two nights ago was you, too?
But, it's not weird that you do that with your dog!
Pervert
l heard ninety percent of women who own a dog do it! Well, maybe... probably not...
Uh... that is...
Yeah, that's right! Compared to me you're fine!
lf you're weird, what does that make me?
l'm ugly. My personality sucks too.
Yeah, it's really unfair. Just look how small my dick is!
Yep.
l'm the worst of all...
l took advantage of my invisibility and did all that to you...
Not just you, Otonashi... Other women as well.
l can't help it. Look at you.
''We are those who give compassion. That is what guides us all.''
''And we shall practice compassion as well.''
Fine. l'll forgive you.
So this time, let's...
l know we can't see each other, but it's still a bit embarrassing.
Yeah, l know. We can't see each other at all.
Flash.
Eek!
Wh... What?
Did... did you see?
Eh? See what?
Then, can you see this?
Can you not see this, either?
l'll die if you see me doing this!
ls this the naughty boy that teased me?
Otonashi, l didn't know you were so bold.
''O night. Hide me in your cape of darkness.''
''Cover my bold love inside my shy heart,
until bashfulness disappears.''
Does it feel good?
lt's okay. You can cum in my mouth.
Otonashi... l'm going to...
lt's okay. Cum in my mouth.
lt's lost its spunk.
l can't get it up that fast.
Get hard. Get hard.
lt's not getting hard.
l wonder if this will work.
Wh... what's going on?
Here. Open wide.
You're right. This tastes good, Otonashi.
Don't suck so hard...
That's enough up there...
By the way, Mie...
Yeah?
You said you did things to other people as well, but what exactly did you do?
You little trickster.
Um... l'll tell you because you forgave me, but...
This.
That.
That too.
Even that.
Huh?
l'm terrified to go to work today.
Good morning, Mie.
O-Otonashi... What's this?
l invited everyone here.
Everyone, you say?
Does that mean...?!
Mie!
Otonashi! Whatever happened to compassion?!
''The roots of sin should have an axe wielded against them!''
Come on, everyone! Take the medicine and get him!
Yeah!
Not there! Stop! Don't touch! But keep touching me there...