I'm home!
The Girl who is a Hindrance
First Part
Sorry, Aya-chan! My cleaning duty took longer...
Oh, Sumika...
Hmm?
Ah, you're together again!
N-No... We just happened to pass by each other!
Gosh, get away from onii-chan!
Hey... what's with you, Sumika?
You've been acting weird lately!
You two have been sneaking around lately
and it's suspicious!
Onii-chan loves me,
so don't go clinging all over him, okay?
Sumika, listen...
No matter how much you
love him, you're blood-related.
Isn't that kind of weird after all...
What I'm trying to say is...
Sorry, I'm going home alone after all.
Sumika...
Aya-chan, you dummy...
She was rooting up for me when we're little,
but now she's getting in my way!
Hachimori? I knew it was you!
Why are you here alone
making that unusual face?
Susaki-san...
Who's this girl?
It's a cute junior of mine.
Oh, don't act like that.
It's not like I'm here to tease you.
We're about to go somewhere,
so you should tag along.
Aren't you free for today?
Welcome! Please follow me.
Spread your legs wide and show us!
That's great!
Whoa... they look crazy...
They're almost naked!
M-Maybe I shouldn't have tagged along...
H-Hey, I think that I really shouldn't...
It's alright!
You can just sit back here
for a chat and drink some juice.
Ehh, so that's how it is.
Isn't that such a tough love?
I thought that they'll laugh at me,
but they're earnestly lending me an ear.
I think that I'm now feeling a little better somehow...
Even so, despite what Susaki said...
The girls here are like, wild...
They don't show any resistance!
They're getting on with it...
Uh-uh, you're not listening.
Hey, Hachimori. Come with me.
Huh? W-Wait...
If you love someone so much, then
you should just make him yours.
I thought that you could use a rehearsal with this man.
W-Wait, Yumi-chan. You're being mean.
And if you keep being inattentive like that,
that Aya will end up swiping him away from you.
L-Like this?
Gosh... This really is crazy...
It feels so hot and it's stiff!
Whoa... I peeled the skin off!
It's coming out already!
That was so quick, mister!
I'll clean this up for you.
Here... Won't it be a waste of the
semen that you worked hard for?
So, how's the taste of semen?
Oh?
She got aroused!
No! What are you doing? Stop!
What, did kissing me make you horny?
Hey, let's end this with that one,
that specialty of yours!
Ahh...
E-Enough already! Stop...
Don't... This is bad... bad... this is bad!
Don't touch me there!
I'm coming!
Whoa... I came...
I'm fully exposed in this disgraceful state...
Alright, we'll be on our way.
This girl will be taking care of you now.
Huh? What is she talking about?
I'm sorry, Hachimori! Doing 'that' gets the biggest pay.
No, I never heard anything about this!
You're too good for your own good as always.
You trust just whatever people like us say, after all.
I like that part of you, though.
See ya! Let them teach you lots of stuff.
I don't want to... Onii-chan... Help...
Oh, I came a lot!
I hope that your brother will be glad for you.
Do your best, Sumika-chan.
Why do I have to go through this?
Onii-chan might have been worried about me...
Aya-chan?
Hey, just one more time.
Wait, what if Sumika comes home?
What, it's not like we have to keep about us a secret.
susaki_yyy (8:22 PM)
Don't tell anyone about what happened today,
or else an embarrassing URL will spread around.
There's nothing for me to be depressed about.
This is something bound to happen,
and that day just happened to be today.
I already had an inkling about it...
About the fact that onii-chan doesn't look at me...
And about the fact that I have
no way to get in their way.
And that I am but a hindrance for them.
You're doing great!
Sumika-chan, your pussy is a perfect fit for my cock!
I can come no matter how many times we do it!
My womb is throbbing, it feels
like it's gonna melt down!
But if I didn't do that, my best friend and onii-chan...
I felt that I will lose those two
dear to me at the same time.
That's what scared me all along.
And now that time already came.
I ask myself about where I should go now...
Hey, it won't be fun if you're crying.
We geezers here will help to make you forget
all about it. This is a place where fun resides.
We like your crying face as well though.
That's unfair... Doing these things to me...
And telling me those words...
No matter how close a friend might be,
they'll cast each other aside
when the going gets tough.
Your tongue is coiling around!
Your mouth-pussy feels heavenly!
Coming! I'm about to come!
Is it really okay even if we don't wear a rubber?
Y-Yes...
I knew it, doing it raw feels way different!
It's going inside! It feels so warm!
It's slipping inside! This feels great!
More!
Does this feel good, mister?
You got good at this now, Sumika-chan!
It feels good when you rub
against my mucous membrane!
More... Keep plunging it inside me!
We're gonna pour a lot of semen
in your asshole too, okay?
And strangely enough, doing this
makes me forget about those things.
If that's the case, then I might
as well drown myself in this.
You're gobbling it so eagerly.
Do you like it that much?
You're such a lewd girl, Sumika-chan.
Yes, I love cock!
I'm gonna come just like this!
Come! I'll gulp it all down using my whole body!
Coming, coming!
I'm coming!
Alright, let's start with an introduction.
Newcomer
Pussy
My name is Uchimori Sumire!
I'm a newcomer meat toilet.
I had a lot of men bang me for today as well,
but I'm a pervert who couldn't get herself satisfied!
My pussy is still far from being an adult's,
but it is capable of satisfying my beloved cocks!
I'm going to serve you a lot, okay?
That's a good take.
Goodbye, Aya-chan... Onii-chan...
I finally found a place where I belong!
Hey, hey! Have you heard
about Hachimori from class 2?
Ahh, you mean that video?
Isn't that a different woman?
I'm sure that's her!
Ugh! That's nasty!
Wait... Let me watch it after you!
What is this...
And also, doesn't she look so mature?
That's all a lie! Right, Sumika?
Sumika! Umm, you see... There's this strange rumor...
Aya-chan...
You shouldn't get yourself
involved with me anymore.
The Girl who is a Hindrance
Final Part
It's that same dream again.
Sumika...
She never went to school since that time.
It's all my fault for saying those things...
I never meant to push her away...
Sumika...
Hachimori?
There's no way that she's here.
I was told that she's here...
U-huh...
Are you perhaps... Aya?
Y-Yes, I am...
Alright, then...
Try to look for her in this place.
Just tell them that you're my acquaintance.
So you are Aya-chan, huh? I've been
contacted and told about you.
Well, sit down and let me offer you some juice...
No, thanks! More importantly, where's Sumika?
Don't get too antsy, we're in front
of a magic mirror right now.
You can see what's behind it, right?
Though, I'm not sure if she's the same
Sumika-chan that you knew.
Come on, mister! Move your face closer!
Feast your eyes on my pussy!
Are you shocked?
She's been going here day after
day to be banged like crazy.
It looked like she got fed up
with something in life.
I'll clean it up using my mouth!
You're sucking my filthy cock with
no trace of disgust on your face...
I'm so happy!
Take care of this one as well.
Look at her face in ecstasy.
What she wishes for is to be in this place.
This is a place that Sumika finally found,
where she can belong after you drove her away.
Are you going to take this away from her again?
Well, if you still say that you want to stop her,
then there is a way to do so.
You know what I mean, right?
There's someone who can replace her here...
We once had a conversation about that.
"How about you sell Aya to us,
just like how you got sold here", I said.
Oh, that's the only time when I saw
her make a very serious face.
That's one thing I never want to do!
She said that if those two dear to her
are happy together, then she
doesn't want to break them apart.
I got so moved from what she said that
I ended up coming inside her five times!
If you want that admirable
Sumika-chan to stop this,
then I'm not the one who can make her do so.
That felt amazing, Sumika-chan!
It's warm and it feels good.
The smell of semen is gushing into my stomach,
and it's making me feel like coming again!
You're close to getting tired of
doing it with us geezers.
What are you talking about?
Doing this is the happiest thing for me...
Huh, Mr. chairman... Have you gotten a new one?
That's such a cute girl as well...
See, she's Sumika-chan's friend.
She wants to join as well.
Sumika...
Aya-chan...
Why... Why did you come here?
Even though you finally got to be with my brother...
I accepted a deal earlier.
If I'll take care of everyone here,
then they'll let both of us go.
Just stop...
I'm staying here on my own will.
You've always been that way, Sumika.
You always give up on yourself and sulk behind.
However...
No matter how close you are with people,
you always cared about them more than you should.
And being aware of that, I...
I'm sorry!
I'm not worthy of being your friend anymore, right?
Why...
You should be fine even without me around...
As long as you two are happy,
everything should be fine...
Even so, I don't want to be left out in the end.
I'm scared of being alone!
I want to be together with the two of them!
Aya-chan...
Gosh, doing something like this...
My sacrifice means nothing now!
I thought that it would be fine even
if I just vanish from existence...
I would have been fine no
matter what happens next.
After all of this, I should be able
to have sex with onii-chan.
You should make him agree on it, Aya-chan!
And then...
The three of us will go on a trip,
then we'll eat delicious food...
Let's make lots of memories and be happy!
I'll forgive you only after all of that happens.
What a wonderful feminine companionship!
With this, you can put your minds
at ease and enjoy being fucked.
Will that be fine? Letting them go just like that...
It's alright, that's my intention.
Whatever will happen next depends
on Sumika-chan's older brother.
Well, but if by any chance that brother
of hers is unable to restrain her...
She'll be coming back here for us.
I'm sure of it.
Jeez, you two are so lewd together!
You're both making all of these indecent sounds!
Your keep drooling like faucets.
How is it?
Does being raped with your childhood
friend make you feel horny?
That's...
You get to share this enjoyment together!
Hey, hey! The sun will set before
you get to satisfy all the men here
with only this level of work!
Make sure to spread it wide!
I'm being treated like a toilet again!
No! I can't help myself from coming!
Come!
Shoot a lot of it inside my pussy!
Aya-chan...
Sumika...
I won't leave you alone, Sumika...
And so...
And so, you're not allowed to go anywhere else anymore.
At the times when I'm being raped...
I thought that I should just throw everything
away and vanish from existence.
But things are different now.
—New Message—
hachimori_wtf (5:45 PM)
I am no longer a hindrance.
That's because I got the words I wanted to hear the most from people dear to me!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization