Art modeling?
I kind of carelessly made a promise about it!
Please, Amana!
This will be the first and last time.
I'm glad... She easily agreed to it.
Looking For Students:
Sketch Room
Second Studio
I'm Kurisaka Amana.
I'll be under your care.
Hey, hey, sensei...
Where did you find such a young girl?
Even though this is a favor a relative of mine asked...
First Part
I never heard about this being a nude modeling!
Wow... They're huge!
I'm glad that I'm not absent today!
Uhh... What should I do?
But activities like this are highly renowned, right?
Alright, sit down here.
Put your hands right around here.
Okay...
No! I shouldn't think about weird stuff!
I'm doing a serious task here.
Just a little...
Touching myself a little should be fine...
The truth is, this isn't my first time
to be naked with people around me.
It was several years ago at
my school's summer camp...
Be sure to stand guard right there, okay?
Yeah, yeah! I gotcha!
All of the restrooms are occupied at that time.
I ran out of options...
I'm peeing with everyone nearby...
It was a bizarre sensation.
I'm sure that it's like an ember for me at that time.
I'm certain that something like a little flame
lit up inside me in that moment.
This is incredible!
It really feels way different this way!
It should be fine if I touch myself a little more, right?
Does it feel good?
What's the matter? Carry on.
Let us see you do it one more time.
Uhh, I'm not...
What, what's up?
What's this about about?
No... D-Don't tell them about it!
Well, see... This girl was rubbing herself just now...
You're wrong! That was...
Oh... So that's it.
If that's so, don't hold back
and let us see more of that...
"Masturbation".
Please excuse me!
Oh my, my...
...and that's what happened.
It's not my fault. Right, Enrique?
I wonder if they thought of me as a pervert...
Why am I wet...
Was it because everyone found me out?
No way... It's as if I'm a...
What's the deal, jeez! It was just masturbation.
I'll bet that papa, mama, sensei
and everyone else do this too!
I'm not a pervert!
Don't hold back and let us see more of that...
Oh... No... Stop staring like that on me!
What I'm doing is something normal!
If I went on with them at that time, I'll be...
I'm sure that I'll be...
Lecture Room
Well, you specifically came
here just to give that back?
Payment for the month
of September
Miss Kurisaka Amana
You should have just kept it.
I went home midway so I'd feel bad keeping it...
Your name's Amana-chan?
Are you someone who desires
to expose yourself in front of
others in a ridiculous manner?
You don't have to hide it.
I met a girl just like you before.
And you never really came here
just to give this thing back, right?
I can set up just the right place for you if you want.
No... How tactless of me to ask that...
At any rate, you're a pervert who voluntarily
came here without any underwear.
Welcome, little bitch.
Oh, sorry for the wait.
I wonder where we are right now...
The girl from yesterday?
The eagle pose! That's the eagle position!
Five... Six... Are there even more of them?
Wow...
They're not touching them, but my nipples...
And my clit too, I know that they're already stiff.
And this smell is from a dick, right?
We're smothering you with
our cocks at the moment,
but bear with it a little longer until
the students are done sketching, okay?
I wonder how I am being watched...
Not having my pussy touched puts me on the edge!
I want to play with my pussy already!
Well then, I'll remove your blindfold.
Finally, so this is what surrounds me...
Huh?
Am I outdoors?
I can put it in already, right?
Huh? No way...
Wait, if you do that now...
I'm coming!
Aren't you glad to have your
wish granted, Amana-chan?
I'm now outdoors
and I'm being raped while stark naked...
There, have a look.
Students ranging from the elderly
to someone about your age
are all closely watching your shameful looks.
Didn't you want to be seen?
Here, let's have them sketch
the creases of your asshole as well!
This is embarrassing!
This is far more amazing than
anything else I ever imagined!
If people I know, like my classmates, see this...
I wonder how good it'll make me feel?
If they find out that I'm just a pervert,
far from how they thought I am...
Wait, my pussy is coming!
So what if you came?
We're far from being satisfied here!
Hey everyone, please keep on sketching
my indecent appearance!
Looking For Students:
Sketch Room
Second Studio
I want to learn more...
I don't care if I end up burning myself!
I want more of this pleasure that
feels like it's burning my chest!
I need to douse it with more fuel,
so the flame that ignited on that day won't go out.
We're here, Amana-chan.
Alright then, go at once and take
a photo of yourself as a proof.
Umm... Am I really doing that here?
Well, it's not like you're being forced
to do this. Should we stop and go back?
Final Part
I'll do it...
Is that clear? Until we give you the permission,
you shouldn't play with your pussy.
Alright, I-I made it!
Oh, I didn't expect that I won't be caught!
This is amazing!
I already got this wet just from walking naked outside!
I was told to not touch myself,
but I can't hold myself back...
I disobeyed my instruction! Ah, it feels good!
Huh? The car keys...
I turned crazy ever since that day.
I know that I'm doing something wrong.
Having that in mind, I have to stop doing these...
I knew that I'd regret doing this someday!
I'm done for!
Here it is, right here!
Sorry for the disruption!
Huh?
He won't call anyone out?
U-Umm...
You won't tell anyone else about
what you saw here for me?
It feels good!
Keep on shoving it more inside!
Hey missy, you sure play such
a precocious game here.
Do you always do stuff like this?
You came here to take some photos, right?
Come on, take a commemorative photo with me!
If papa and mama find out this side of me,
will they be heartbroken?
Me who drowns myself in pleasure...
Me who behaves well...
I don't want to abandon either of them.
What a pretty convenient reasoning that is.
I'm about to come!
Shoot it out just like this!
I want it inside...
Please shoot it into me!
Come on, clean my cock up.
O-Okay!
Huh, you're naked?
Why aren't you wearing any clothing?
You'll catch a cold if you're naked!
P-Please lower your voice!
Just wait there, I'm gonna bring you some clothes!
I'm fine!
Grandpa—!
Whoa!
No way, an exhibitionist?
Wow, she's bare naked!
I got carried away!
No way, I need to go back in the car immediately!
Amana-chan, it seems that you
wandered around too much.
You shouldn't be fooling around like that.
Sensei, thank good—
This is a nice opportunity.
Give yourself some pleasure
right here just like that.
And say to everyone that you're a slut
who loves masturbating while doing it.
What are you saying... This isn't the time for...
It can't be helped, then.
It's time for us to go our separate ways.
Huh?
How disappointing. And here I thought
to myself that I found a great model.
Th-This can't be!
No, wait!
Don't cast me aside just like that!
Please take a look, everyone...
I am an exhibitionist pervert!
My pussy is making wet squishy sounds!
There's no going back for me now...
And neither I have the intention to do so...
I have to play with my pussy around-the-clock
or I won't settle down!
Forgive me for being a masturbation
loving and lecherous woman!
I get thrilled when I masturbate in front of a crowd!
Look at the totally perverted
face of a sow like me as I climax!
From that point onwards,
our acts have only escalated further.
Having a sense of security from
not getting sued at that time,
we've been having fun at other prefectures,
but soon dared closer up to next town.
And at last, I'm now flashing
myself bare in my hometown.
Your cocks are delicious!
I'm sure that I can't let go of all these anymore.
Whenever I'm tainted white and
I meet those gazes full of contempt,
it feels like I lose something in me as a human being.
Letting go of such depravity would be...
Please, this one as well...
Please play a lot with my ass too!
Your cock feels good!
Hey, shake that ass even more!
O-Outdoor sex incredibly arouses me!
We're putting another one inside!
She's really taking them all inside her!
Her anal muscle might get torn apart though.
Seems like a very cute girl is doing
it with men! Let's have a look!
Huh, are you serious?
It's spreading around!
Come on, say it!
Which hole is making those
particularly indecent sounds?
I-It's my ass!
It's my ass-pussy!
Wow, she's taking several cocks inside her.
Whoa, for real?
Rumors about my ridiculous self
are spreading through the whole town.
She has enormous tits!
Ah, I saw it!
Watch me more as I get humiliated!
Watch me more!
This is something I wanted myself.
But I still...
...haven't had enough.
You know what, I saw it yesterday
while I'm on my running routine!
For real?
Could that just be someone who looks like her?
But still...
Ah, Kurisaka-san, you dropped something.
Huh, are these...
I'm giving you those so use them as you please.
Starting today, I'll become a
sex doll for all of you boys.
I'm saying that I want it too, you see?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization