I'm doing it again and again.
There really isn't any other way...
Oh, welcome.
Episode 2: Young Succubus Miyu
An Embrace That Connects To The Underworld
Tiny Evil.
Second episode: Young succubus Miyu.
An embrace that connects to the underworld.
She's been appearing night after night lately.
She always squeezes me dry until I faint,
but I'm yet to die.
I think that I've wrung you quite a lot,
but you just won't die, mister...
Could you actually have a powerful sexual urge?
It can't be...
Maybe my power isn't enough...
Hey, these candles are useless. Turn the lights on.
O-Okay.
I'm sorry.
Hey mister, I'm parched.
Get me something.
Uhh... O-Okay.
This room doesn't have a TV, right?
Gosh, bring me something else then.
And sweets too.
U-Umm...
I want to... do it today as well...
I'm busy right now, ask me later.
I-I'm begging you, please.
Gosh... I can do you if you really want to
but don't distract me, okay?
Okay! Please do so.
She's doing it so roughly,
but it feels insanely good!
Jeez, I lost again.
This one's pretty strong.
That... feels good!
Oh, tell me if you're about to come.
It'll be a problem if you get the smartphone dirty.
Huh? Right there! Looks like
I'm gonna win, just a bit more!
Go! Go!
Alright, I won!
Yay—!
I-I'm coming!
Gosh!
Your semen flew all over, mister!
You're gonna stain the smartphone!
S-Sorry.
Huh? You're still lively. Want to do it more?
Y-Yeah... Please.
Yeah, yeah.
Keep it coming.
Well, umm...
Will you use your feet?
Ehh... Isn't using my feet too kinky?
You sound just like a pervert, mister.
Is that a no?
Oh well, okay.
Here, show me your dick.
It feels good!
Huh...
So, this makes you feel good...
Maybe you really are a pervert...
Umm, the texture of the soles
of your feet feel good.
What does that even mean? Then, how about you rub yourself on my knee socks?
Should I lend it to you?
That's not it...
This feels crazy!
Coming! It's coming out!
Okay!
Do your best, do your best!
Whoa! I did it! I got a rare item!
Huh? Oh—!
Huh? You're still good to go.
My feet will be fine, right?
Here you go.
Huh?
You should have told me sooner
if you like it this way, mister.
This is easier for me.
You also get to feel great, so it's all good.
Well...
N-No...
I won't be... satisfied with only this.
Huh?
Gosh, you're being selfish!
Isn't your dick throbbing in pleasure?
How about you?
Won't it feel good for you too
if I put it inside you?
You're so naive! If we do that,
won't you end up on the verge
of dying if I use my pussy?
What I'm saying... is that's what I...
Listen, before you talk cocky like that,
squirt it out first.
Look, you came!
I'm feeling good even when she's doing a half-assed job.
But with only this much, I'm...
Hey, listen...
Hmm, what?
Well...
How long will it be before you decide to kill me?
Huh?
Tiny Evil!
How long will it be before you decide to kill me?
I kind of figured it out already,
but you really are 'that' kind of man.
I squeezed you dry lots of times
until you faint already,
but you just went along with it, right?
Mister, besides being socially awkward,
you are a submissive masochist.
Aren't you a failure as a human being?
You even feel good from
having your nipples teased?
How pathetic!
Just a little more!
You're gonna die soon!
Cover my insides with your semen!
I'll rub you inside me for as long
as I want. I'll make you ejaculate!
You'll die a miserable death while
being ridden by a little girl.
You'll definitely die from
excessive ejaculation, though.
I'm sure that even you have friends,
a mother and a father, right?
What are they gonna think about that?
It would be embarrassing, right?
I don't have anyone who I can call as a 'friend'.
And even my parents...
They won't be bothering to ask about how I died.
Ever since I started living alone by myself,
they didn't even once contact me.
I am alone.
But, even so...
I wanted to at least
be able to love myself.
Over and over, I looked forward to tomorrow.
I worked myself hard to death for that.
However...
I couldn't change both myself and the reality.
I'm tired already!
Even after I tried to face reality
and my despicable self...
Oh my, you're crying...
You see, you are my sustenance, mister.
I'll suck your dick,
I'll rub you with my pussy, I'll wring you dry
then I'll take your soul, that's the end.
Your tearjerking life story won't sway me.
No, that's not... sorry.
That wasn't my intention.
Please continue.
In all 25 years of my life,
this moment is the happiest I ever had.
I'm able to have sex to a girl as adorable as you.
Dying this way is a fulfillment.
Thank you.
Wha... What the hell!
Just drop dead for real!
Here, here you go! Isn't it even deeper than before?
Can you see it? Your whole dick is inside me!
Mister, your perverted masochistic dick
is trying hard to shoot semen inside me!
Squirt lots and lots more of it!
Come on, it's alright. You can still go on!
There, right there!
See, you're doing great! You can do it if you try.
Keep doing it even more!
Your dick rotated inside my pussy!
Doesn't it feel good, mister?
It's reverberating deep inside my pussy!
Mister, your perverted dick
is jamming up my tight pussy full!
Thank you...
What?
What's that, mister perverted scum?
Thank you... Thank you...
Thank you...
I'm still alive.
Is she already gone?
Maybe it was all for naught.
Was it my fault for being persistent?
I'm back!
Huh? You're up already.
Huh? You...
H-Huh?!
I'm not a succubus anymore, as you can see.
Huh?
You see, succubi are beings that charm humans.
Falling in love with a human being
will turn us into humans instead.
Fall in love... Huh, with me?
Yeah! I love you, mister.
I love you so much!
That's why...
No more saying that dying is a fulfillment anymore.
From now on, I'll squeeze you dry a lot until you die!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization