Shit! Shit!
Damn it...
Sh-Shit!
I did it.
I really am hopeless to be trying to do such a thing.
Yes?
Good evening! My name is Miyu.
I came here to squeeze your dick dry!
Episode 1: Young Succubus Miyu - Hip Shaking
That Lures Men Towards The Purgatory
Tiny Evil.
First episode: Young succubus Miyu.
Hip shaking that lures men towards the purgatory.
Huh? What? Who are you?
How mean! Aren't you the one who called for me?
Ahh... Ehh...
Are you by any chance a succubus?
Pardon my intrusion!
Uhh... Umm...
Are you really a succubus?
You were the one who summoned me.
I never would have thought that
you'll enter through the front door.
So, did you expect like I'll go out
of that doodle or something?
Well, yeah...
That usually can't be done.
Well, taking that aside...
Let me milk you dry already...
...mister~!
I'll do this on your dick...
You're making such lewd moans!
Here you go, here you go!
Mister, did having your dick
stroked make you aroused?
You're disgusting!
Huh, could it be that you're feeling it?
I'm only giving you a handjob.
Aren't you too sensitive, mister?
I'm still okay...
I wonder about that...
It will be boring if you're a quick shot.
Come on, come on!
Do your best, mister!
Hey, hey... Stick your tongue out.
That's a good boy.
That was fast!
Was our tongue licking too stimulating for you?
Boys who wet themselves so
easily end up getting teased!
Here you go, here you go! Just like this!
See?
You're all too worn out for
the third round as expected.
Then, I'll make you hard by force.
Yapanose arakuto untokebu!
Ta-da! I did it!
I can do it if I try!
What did you just do?
I made your dick lively!
You should now be fine even if we do this, right?
We still have a long time to enjoy
ourselves! Don't we, mister?
Tiny Evil!
Okay, I'll make you ejaculate again!
3... 2... 1...
Okay, squirt!
Hey, do you understand it?
The one in control of that dick of yours
is neither your sleazy mind nor your indecent body...
...but me instead~!
Regardless of your stamina or sex drive,
your dick will stay hard and
you'll keep producing semen.
You'll keep squirting as I milk them out.
And what do you think will
happen after that, mister?
You will die.
Compared to semen, the soul tastes
more delicious and is rich in nutrients!
Like for example...
In a ramen, the noodles alone
can fill someone's belly.
Even so, there's no way that one won't
even take a sip of the broth. Am I right?
I'm someone who drinks all of the broth.
Here you go, here you go! How is it?
How does having your dick smothered
with a succubus's love juice feel?
I'll let you die this way,
so come a lot that you'll die without any regrets.
You came again.
Alright, one more time.
W-Wait a second!
I want to put it inside already...
Ehh... You don't deserve that so you can't!
I'm begging you...
I'll lose my mind if we keep going
on with just intercrural sex...
Lose your mind.
Won't it also be better for you if I'll
shoot my semen directly inside?
Won't it be a satisfying meal for you?
So it really does work that way, huh?
Huh?
Don't tell me that this is your first time as well?
Ehh... You're a succubus, yet you're still a virg—
Th-Th-That's right, I'm a virgin!
Of course, even succubi have to start somewhere!
I'm still a succubus in training!
I just started the practicum,
so I have to ring the doorbell to enter your room!
Is that so...
I'm sorry, you don't have to brood over it.
Making fun of you wasn't my intention.
I'm not brooding over it!
It can't be helped,
so I'll put the dick of a miserable
virgin like you inside me!
Wait—
What's this!
What's the matter?
Did you think for a bit that you'd be able
to take the lead because I'm a virgin?
Of course, even if I'm a virgin
there's no way that you'd hold yourself together
after thrusting your dick
inside a succubus's pussy!
Take this, take this, take this!
For such a monkey like you
who doesn't know his place,
Here's a harsh punishment!
Wow, your semen leaks out
with each thrust of my hips!
Did you know about it?
You'll die if you ejaculate beyond your limit!
I don't care, just go on!
Okay.
Alright then, I'll kill you just as you wish.
I wonder if you're close... Are you about to die?
Hey, hey! How does having a girl kill you
by riding you in a cowgirl position feels?
Tell me, I'm asking you!
I wonder if you still are conscious.
I wonder if you're gonna die soon.
Is it scary? Hey, are you scared?
I wonder what will happen after you die, huh?
Come on, more...
Keep coming more, mister!
I'm alive... Am I not?
She's gone.
But what happened last night wasn't a dream, right?
I never came that much before...
So an actual girl feels that good.
That felt incredibly good.
It really felt so good that I thought I'll die.
I'm not sure why but I managed to survive.
Having sex until I lose my consciousness is incredible.
If it's that way... If it's with that girl...
That would be an ideal way to die.
I'll try summoning her again.
Next time for sure, I'll definitely...
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization