Dolls...
Human-shaped objects...
I thought of them as scary at first.
One is already in my room even before I realized it.
She's looking down towards me
at the top of my drawer.
It was like she's observing me.
"You're a bad girl, so I'll throw you away",
I thought to myself.
But some sort of curse might befall
me from doing something like that.
And so, I properly left it to someone else's care.
But in the end...
It might have been too late for me.
She's still staring intently on me.
"There's no escaping her anymore."
...I thought to myself.
I thought that I should just take a good
care of it instead if that's the case.
I decided to clean, dress up
and enshrine her up there.
Episode 4: Female Doll Nina
Bottling Up of Pure Affection
Tiny Evil.
Fourth episode: Female doll Nina.
Bottling-up of pure affection.
After that happened,
good things kept coming to him, one after another.
He is in good shape.
He is doing well in schoolwork
and is having fun every day.
And most of all, he got himself
a girlfriend despite being like me.
And he goes out for dinner
every day just like this.
Huh?
And he lived happily ever after.
No, that's not a happy ending at all.
Huh? Was that story about you, Shuu-kun?
That's right, it was based
from my own experience.
Even though it started off as a scary story,
didn't it mellow down at the ending?
No, the ending is actually the most creepy part.
Huh? Do you mean that the doll
really is at your place?
Yeah.
Up until now?!
Huh... So it is still enshrined in your room.
Huh...
Oh, don't get creeped out of me.
Even cursed dolls can be quite cute
if you'll take good care of them.
It's alright, there's nothing to be afraid of!
No, you're the one I'm afraid of.
Huh?
Enough talking about that.
Then, maybe I should stay at
your place for tonight.
Huh? Are you sure?!
Let's just say that I want to see that doll.
What's up with this situation?
She really went straight to sleep right
after taking a look at the doll's face.
Huh?
When she said that she's coming
over to see the doll earlier,
she was actually implying that
she's fine with "it" tonight, right?
Or could it be that she wants me
to go after her from her back?
But she's sound asleep right now...
What the hell...
I thought that we'd finally be doing it tonight...
No, isn't it normal for couples to
do it in this kind of situation?
Gosh, mister!
You shouldn't let strangers inside this room!
Oh...
N-Nina? Why are you...
Haven't I told you before that this room is mine,
and that I only gave you a special
permission to stay here?
I-I'm petrified again!
I wanted to see you happy
so I chased all of the evil entities away from you.
But you took advantage of the good luck
you got to find yourself a girlfriend...
What a blunder...
Huh? She looks adorable for some reason.
I have to thank this woman, though.
It was so frustrating for me,
and those thoughts gave me the power
to turn myself in human form.
That is why...
While the girlfriend you
finally got is right next to us,
I am going to rape you.
Her tongue... Damn, it feels fantastic!
But I can't open my mouth!
Are you, perhaps, petrified?
Then that means that you are my doll right now.
Doesn't it feel good to have a girl licking your lips?
Look, your dick is in a pinch!
You wanted to have your tongue
inside this mouth of mine,
but I will instead have your dick inside it first.
This is bad...
Did the petrification get undone?
W-Wait, Nina! W-We can't do this!
Look, I gulped down a lot!
Ah! Oh, I see...
You've been at the receiving end up until now.
Alright, here you go.
Give my tongue some love.
So, you do like small breasts...
How cute—!
You must love my small cunt as well, then.
Come on, down here! You can put it inside!
B-Before that, here...
Huh?
You want to use a condom at a time like this!
What do you mean "at a time like this"?
It is supposed to be used at such times!
Gosh, you don't get the situation!
I am in the midst of raping you right now!
While your girlfriend is sleeping next to you,
a little girl is going to rape you!
But alright...
Since you are such a cutie,
I'll heed your words and use this
on your dick as I rub it inside me.
Here, take this!
Hey...
Your girlfriend might wake up
if you keep moaning that loud.
Gosh!
It can't be helped, then...
Here, you can have this.
Here, I'm gonna keep moving a lot down here!
Hold your voice down, okay?
Hold
Hold-it
Hold-it-down!
Good boy!
Come while groaning just like that!
Both you and this room belong to me, mister.
I'll never allow anyone to have their hands
on either of the two ever again.
Tiny Evil!
What's happening here?
Huh, is that child the doll?
What?
You're awake!
I'll let you have that if you want to.
Don't you want this man's semen, miss?
It's freshly squeezed and piping hot!
The cops...
No!
Don't move.
My body is...
Your body feels so soft!
Your breasts are huge and
your pussy is squishy as well!
How nice...
I envy you since my body isn't as soft as yours!
But I wonder which one of us does he prefer...
Come on, mister!
Choose which one of us do you like!
We already ran out of condoms,
so choose whose pussy would you rather
be wrung out by and fill
with your gushing semen!
You ended up choosing the pussy
which you mustn't have!
I'll be taking care of you in his place instead, miss.
This is the worst...
Or it should have been...
As this girl goes on violating my body...
I wonder why...
I don't care anymore...
Here comes the creampie!
Sorry!
It wasn't your fault at all.
But please...
Get out of this house.
You'll then forget everything about him
and what happened today.
And lastly,
you'll never show yourself
anywhere near us ever again.
Your girlfriend has left.
You are so mean.
Well, I am just as cruel for choosing
someone like you over her.
It's not like that.
It was your body who chose me.
Isn't your dick now a slave to me?
No, that's not it!
I mean, that's also true...
But it's because I never put a limit for myself.
I tried to but never managed to do it.
Just as you said, I might have thought
of having a girlfriend as my own happiness.
But, you...
For me, you are...
It can only be you, or else...
What I'm saying is,
I'd still end up choosing you anyway, Nina!
Of course, I love you so much!
Huh?!
Hiroko acted like we never met before.
I stopped going to university.
I only go shopping for the bare
minimum I need for living.
And so, about what I have been doing lately...
Hey, come on! Shoot it out already!
You'll feel relieved!
I want to come after holding it in as long as I can!
If you'll say something like that, then...
Three...
Three... Two...
Three... Two... One...
See? You came!
Nina, if you keep squeezing me that hard...
...I'll come in no time!
Looks like your car is about to go off-course, mister!
You need to focus.
E-Even if you tell me that...
Alright, you lost.
One more round, okay?
Each day passed by.
I indulged in my daily life where Nina
keeps squeezing me dry of semen.
By the way, where have you been staying
before coming over here to me?
You said it was the room beneath, but we're on the ground floor.
Hmm? Wanna go there?
Will you lift that flooring up?
O-Okay...
Oh... So, even a rundown apartment like this
has a basement beneath this floor.
I think there was a different building here long ago.
Oh...
What is this room?
Huh, is that an urn?
Then, is that the portrait of
the owner of the remains?
Huh?
A letter?
Dear Nina,
First of all, it's been a while. As you already know,
I had to suddenly leave our home. My illness took a turn
for the worse and I had been brought to the hospital.
I've been here in a room up until now, and I want to
at least leave something for you in the end,
so I had my mother write this letter for me.
I've been sick ever since I was little. I barely had been able
to go to school, thus I never made any friends. That is why
my parents gave you to me as a gift. Others might see
my life as a short one, a life which amounted to nothing.
Even so, I can say that this life is a happy one, for I was able
to meet you.
Thank you for giving me the honor of taking care of you.
Thank you for staying by my side.
And lastly...
My parents granted this selfish wish of mine, so it seems that
I'll be able to stay together with you again afterwards.
I might not be able to talk to you anymore like I always used to,
but we'll be together forever.
-----------------------------------------------------------------— Kiyo
This is...
Nina, didn't you tell me that your
previous owner abandoned you?
Yeah.
Have you never read this letter before?
I couldn't care less about some letter.
I was only able to move around freely
ever since I managed to take a human form.
Then this girl had no idea
about how much her previous
owner might have loved her,
and how she passed away from an illness
and won't be able to meet her.
Nina, you weren't abandoned.
This letter is proof of that.
No! That human abandoned me!
Hey...
She left me behind and have
long forgotten about me!
Nina!
And even now...
She's somewhere out there, being carefree...
and living her own life!
The reason she never came back for me
is because she abandoned me.
That is why...
This girl didn't just easily decide by
herself that she was abandoned.
She truly believed on her owner
only to have that faith betrayed!
You never loved me, so you abandoned me.
I'd rather be a miserable doll like this.
So please, if anything else...
I wish for you to live your life
somewhere out there.
Nina!
I'll take you with me!
When the time for me
to leave this world comes,
never again will I ever leave you alone!
We will be going together!
And then, the two of us...
...will meet your previous owner over there.
That's a promise!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization