Dolls...
Human-shaped objects...
I thought of them as scary at first.
One is already in my room even before I realized it.
She's looking down towards me
at the top of my drawer.
It was like she's observing me.
"You're a bad girl, so I'll throw you away",
I thought to myself.
But some sort of curse might befall
me from doing something like that.
And so, I properly left it to someone else's care.
But in the end...
It might have been too late for me.
She's still staring intently on me.
"There's no escaping her anymore."
...I thought to myself.
I thought that I should just take a good
care of it instead if that's the case.
I decided to clean, dress up
and enshrine her up there.
Episode 3: Female Doll Nina
An Innocent Sexy Leisure
Tiny Evil.
Third episode: Female doll Nina.
An innocent sexy leisure.
Hiroko
Thank you for today.
I'm so happy to know
how you feel for me,
Shuu-kun. I'll be under
your care from now on.
Thank you for today.
I'm so happy to know how you feel for me, Shuu-kun.
I'll be under your care from now on.
Finally...
Even I got myself a girlfriend now...
I've been having good luck lately.
I got good grades on college exams.
I got a wage hike in my part-time
job at a convenience store.
I end up finding money on the road as I walk.
Good things mysteriously keep
happening, one after another.
I wonder if this is all because of you...
Oops... I don't have time for this.
I should abstain in preparation for the day
when I'll graduate from virginity!
Just kidding...
Whoa... That's amazing!
Hey, what are you doing?
Huh?
Eh... Eh... Who are you?
I am Nina.
Aren't you the one who put me up there, mister?
Don't tell me... that you are that doll?
That's right, you named me Nina!
Thank you for not giving me a weird name.
Why are you in human form?
That's because I want to talk to you, mister!
You see, my previous owner abandoned me.
I've been staying in this room ever since.
And so, this room is my home.
But people have tried staying here.
I gave all of them bad luck!
But in your case...
I fell in love with you at first sight.
That's why I tried hard to come
out of the room beneath,
but you tried to throw me away instead.
How mean!
However, you came back for me in the end.
You took good care of me.
You cherished me.
That made me happy.
Huh? What's happening?
I can't move my body!
By the way, mister... Were you masturbating?
Should I lend you a hand?
Like this? Maybe like this...
Why are you twitching? You're weird!
What's happening here?
A girl started giving me a handjob out of nowhere.
This doesn't make any sense!
But...
It feels good!
Is that so? Oh...
So, this feels good for you...
If this feels good, then I'll keep
doing this even more for you.
I'm... already...
It feels good!
Wow, that's amazing! There's a lot that came out!
Delicious!
So she's using her mouth next.
I'll do that for you as well!
Shoot that thing from here earlier.
That delicious treat earlier...
Its smell kind of makes me feel weird.
How is it? Does this feel good?
It feels good—!
She's bad at this,
But it feels quite good as her tiny mouth
and tongue make the slightest movement!
How does it feel when I gobble it up like this?
Just from the fact that I'm being
pleased by such a cute girl as her...
Hey, will it take longer? Hurry up and shoot it out!
Is it a sweet treat? I wonder if your
sweet treat is coming out...
Doesn't this taste so good?
Hey, give me more!
Tiny Evil!
Hey, hey mister! Give me more!
Ow... O-Ouch...
Huh? I can move...
Hey...
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Hey—!
D-Do you wear anything beneath?
Beneath?
Do you mean beneath my clothing?
This is the only thing that I'm wearing.
Look!
Whoa! Idiot, why don't you have any panties?
Huh? But I don't have anything else apart from this!
More importantly...
Shoot more of your sperm out, mister!
Hey...
Hey, I want more! Shoot more of it!
This girl... Why is she craving for semen?
But to be honest, a handjob won't
be enough for me anymore...
H-Hey, listen.
If you want more, I think I'll shoot even
more if you insert it down there.
Down there? Where?
Ah... Umm...
I'm talking about your pussy.
You see, that place on your groin.
Oh, this thing.
Okay, I got it!
Whoa! Wait, wait!
Let's use a rubber! Here!
Eh... Why?
We just have to!
Umm, that's right.
You can't drink it when I shoot it
in there without one, right?
What a bother...
Hi-ya!
Did I startle you?
You... I almost came from that...
That's what I've been saying, shoot it out!
Come on, come on!
Shoot it out, shoot it out!
Hey...
It's finally here!
Hey, hey... Do you have more of this rubber?
Umm...
There's a lot more in that drawer...
Hey, let's use all of them.
Huh, right now?!
That's right! Hey, come on! One more time!
Alright, here's the next one!
Come on, shoot it out! Shoot it out!
Here you go! Come on, come on!
More... More!
We're far from done!
You can shoot more out, can't you?
Come on, right here!
More, more, more!
You came, right here... Huh?
Isn't this amount less than usual?
Hey, I'm already at my limit...
If you won't come anymore,
then you don't need these anymore, right?
Here you go, bust your nuts!
Hey, look at that!
So, you can still come after all.
Okay then, let's continue!
More, more, more!
That was delicious!
Hey there, mister!
We're far from done.
I want even more.
More, more, more!
Not yet, not yet, not yet!
Wow...
Did I come that much?
You're best, Nina.
Huh?
Maybe I should buy her some
undies and clothes tomorrow.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization