Good morning.
What's wrong? Your eyes are so red!
l was so excited last
night, l had hard time sleeping.
lt was really something to
look at from such a close distance.
Quite a scene.
By any chance, do you mean yesterday?
So good!
lt's always like that every day after training.
l wonder if they ever get tired of it.
What are we going to do?
We can't finish our report like this.
Okay then. l'll kill time with the mecha guys.
Well, l sure was a little excited too, but...
Yeah, the close up angle is really something.
What?
lt's so different from what you watch in videos.
The real stuff is so great!
Oh really?
Hey, Noriko, l can't hold it any longer.
What!
l don't get satisfied by just watching anymore!
What is it with that look?
Hey, Noriko.
Don't get any closer!
What?
l have no intention of doing it!
lntention of what?
Hey! You are so wimpy, Yasuo.
Huh?
Stop freaking out!
Just grab a woman, hold her
tight, and kiss her passionately.
That should work just fine, right?
Oyama!
Don't give him any encouragement!
What?
lt's all right. Yasuo and
Noriko make a nice couple.
Why don't you attack her.
What are you talking about!
All of you talk about me like
l'm some kind of sex maniac.
You just said that you
couldn't hold it any longer.
l was talking about the Crab Cop!
This is what happened.
l was helping the mechanic guys to
adjust Crab Cop's equipment last night.
l just want to ride on it as soon as possible.
And that made me too excited to fall asleep.
l see.
l could kind of figure that out.
You are a mecha otaku, aren't you?
What are you saying?
You all misunderstand me!
Besides, how could l get
excited about this kind of woman.
Well excuse me for being this kind of woman!
Bastard!
Not fair at all!
l don't get it!
What's that? What are you mumbling about?
This, this!
Noriko told me not to get any
closer, and then punched me...
...even though it was her fault.
She just doesn't make any sense!
You moron.
You are too crazy about
machines to understand women.
According to Captain Yamagami's report...
...your skills have improved
greatly over the last few days.
l see your training has been very effective.
Therefore, we will begin the combat training.
Yes, Sir!
You mean, we can ride on the Crab Cop?
Sure. l want you to handle that mobile
mecha like it's your own arms and legs.
Count on me!
Good for you, Yasuo.
Okay then, this is the new
formation for the mobile force.
The navigator for Number
2 mobile is lsamu Oyama.
Understood!
The pilot for Number 2 mobile is Yasuo Kawasaki.
Yes Sir, l will do my best!
The navigator for Number
1 mobile is Kayoko Kuraishi.
Yes, with pleasure.
And the pilot for Number 1 mobile is Noriko lbuki.
Yes! l will accept with honor!
Okay!
Well done. Switch with Number 2.
You jerk! What are you aiming at?
Hey, don't hit it so hard!
What are you going to do
if you damage the machine?
You idiot!
The bonnet is not that fragile!
Besides, what's wrong with your shooting!
l did it exactly as it says in the manual!
Stop it, you two!
l am so worried. What if they ever
make it to an actual fighting zone?
l am counting on you, Captain Yamagami.
Oh, no.
Do you still have a thing for the manager?
No, stop it Kayoko!
lf you like him so much, why
don't you steal him from the captain?
How could l do such a thing!
l am telling you, it's so hard to
shoot and move at the same time!
Of course! You think our
enemy will stop for you? Asshole!
That was a hard training
session today. My body is really sore.
You have very good instincts.
What?
Handling and shooting, you did
both a lot better than Yasuo.
Good job! l am counting on you!
But if the training gets
any harder, l won't survive.
That's why l am telling you.
Active sex keeps you beautiful and healthy.
l hear you!
l am envious of you, Kayoko.
You have such a good body, you'd have
no problem getting any man you want.
You are not like me.
Did you take the stuff he
told this morning seriously?
That crap is just something
Yasuo let slipped to hide his emotions.
Hide his emotion?
Yasuo really likes you.
He just doesn't realize it yet himself,
but it's obvious to the rest of us.
That mecha maniac? Have a thing for me?
No kidding!
You don't feel anything?
Well, you really need an education about men.
Training about men?
What are we going to do in here?
A kind of massage. Take off your towel.
Why do l have to be naked?
Don't be embarrassed!
Take it off and come sit here.
Loosen up.
Take a deep breath.
Try to relax.
Feels good?
lt feels strange, it kind of tickles.
Because you know it's my
fingers. Pretend it's someone you like.
Somebody l like is touching me.
Relax, let the bad memories go.
Drop your negative feelings about sex.
Just relax as your body feels my touch.
How is it now?
Feels good, doesn't it?
You can moan, if you want.
No way!
Don't be so uptight!
See, it's getting hard.
No, stop.
That's good, just like that.
Even here, you see.
Oh, no!
lt is really wet.
Please stop, now.
That's good, keep moaning!
Let it go and release yourself.
l knew it.
You have a very sensitive body.
You don't like sex because
you had a bad first experience.
l'm scared. l may go insane.
Don't worry. You will be able to
enjoy sex just like everybody else.
Really?
Sure, trust me.
Be gentle.
You are so cute.
How's it now? ls it getting better?
Yeah, it's so good.
Not yet. lt's getting even better.
lt's amazing Noriko.
Can you hear it? You are soaking wet.
No, l am so embarrassed.
lt's amazing, Noriko.
lt's dripping more and more.
lt's beautiful, shiny pink.
ln this case, the suspect could escape
because you were not aware of his intention.
From this case study, we should analyze...oh?
Ms. lbuki, Ms. lbuki?
Yes, Sir!
l know my lecture is boring, but for your
own safety please pay more attention.
l am sorry.
Well then, to compare with the case
one, let's move to the next case study.
Under this circumstance...
That was pretty intense
shooting practice, wasn't it?
Yeah.
l bet your body must have felt intense, too?
Good, good. Your body is awakening.
Since then, it's so weird. With a little
stimulus, my body turns hot so easily.
When you feel aroused, it's
best to be pampered by a man.
A man, huh?
Say Yasuo, don't you
think lbuki has changed a little?
You think so, too?
Hey, even a brute like you could notice, eh?
She looks a lot sexier, and more womanly.
l guess the manager
has already come on to her?
Just kidding.
But seriously, you better hurry.
Or maybe l'll try her, too!
l'm gonna take lunch now.
Manager Shibata, Manager Shibata?
Excuse me, is Manager Shibata here?
Here l am!
Manager! What are you doing?
One of the mechanics is sick. This greedy
company knows how to use employees.
So, did you want to see me?
Well, l came to your office to submit
the report about the fighting practice.
l heard that you would be here.
l will take a look later,
please leave it on my desk.
Yes.
Can you come over and
help me with something?
Sure!
Please sit down.
Okay.
Hold it here.
Yes.
Like that, yes.
Amazing! You can do everything.
My background is more in
the actual mechanical stuff.
l'm not much of a manager, l feel much
more comfortable working with machines.
That sounds like Yasuo!
No, why did l mention his name!
Good, well done.
Thanks, you saved me a lot of time.
lt's nothing. l'd love to help you anytime.
Ms. lbuki?
Yes?
Do you remember my promise?
Your promise?
l said l would like to take you out for
dinner sometime. Are you free tonight?
You want to take me out?
lf it's not too much trouble.
No! Of course it's no trouble.
l've been having a problem lately.
Problem?
l can't get the image of you
running naked out of my mind.
M-Manager Shibata.
Please, forget that memory.
l can't!
l always had this feeling
about you ever since l met you.
Manager.
Don't be so formal.
l am just a man before you.
Sorry to bother you. l'd like
to speak with you for a moment.
Sure, l'll be done in a
minute. Wait for me in my office.
Thank you, Sir.
Well, l have to go back to
being a boring manager now.
l should get off work on time. Why
don't we meet at some coffee shop and...
Manager...
Well, l don't think l can
make it. l have things to do.
Really?
l am sorry!
Hey Noriko!
Manager, be happy with Captain Yamagami.
Good bye, Sir!
Wow, you are so intense
today, did you have a rough day?
You are right. To be honest,
l was dumped by a pretty girl.
What? Oh no!
What's so funny about that?
Don't try to make me jealous!
Yes. You are the only woman for me.
Good!
This is armored car number 26!
We are being attacked by an armed tank!
We need back up ASAP!
Repeat, this is armored car number 26...
We received an emergency rescue request!
Finally, we get to go into the
field and see some real fighting!
Considering the worst case scenario,
we'll send just the number 1 mobile force.
Number 2 mobile force
will stay at headquarters.
Yes! Number 1 mobile
force will move right away!
We are standing by!
This is Shinjuku headquarters. The
criminals are getting away with the cash.
Security police force is
guiding them to the old city hall area.
This area is all in ruins and there
are no civilians, so feel free to fight.
Did you hear that? This is the time
to show the results of your training.
Yes!
Noriko, aren't you scared?
l am not okay! l may wet my pants.
They are just cheap thieves. With
your skill, we'll get them. Be confident!
Yeah!
Distance to fighting point, 800 meters.
Number 1 mobile force, ready to land.
Lines connected. Landing burners ready to fire.
Auto balancer is acting normal.
Let's go Noriko!
Launch!
What is the hell is that?
To the suspects, throw down
your weapons and surrender!
Shit!
Shit! They blocked our back, too!
We'll have to blow it up to get out of here!
Got it!
l repeat! To the suspects, to the suspects.
lf you don't surrender now, we will attack.
Here you go! There's our answer!
So you want to do it the hard
way. Noriko, let them have it!
Roger!
We're finished! Let's grab
the money and get out of here!
Yeah!
There's nowhere to hide!
This is Self Defense force, we have the criminals.
Roger! Our duty is finished.
Good job, Noriko!
We're back!
Welcome back! l am glad
you are not hurt or anything!
Oh, lsamu!
l feel so hot inside!
Yeah, l know what you mean!
lt's such a different feeling when
you go to the real fighting field, isn't it?
Well then Noriko, we are
going to head out for a quickie.
What? So, do l have to
write the report all by myself?
Why don't you ask him?
What?
Yasuo... what's wrong with him?
He's grumpy because we
didn't get to see any action.
He is such a baby.
Noriko, why don't you pamper him?
What? Why me?
He can help cool you down!
What are you talking about?
Good luck!
Rats!
Hey, Yasuo, can you help me?
No!
Why not?
How could l write a report
without actually being there?
But, you're more familiar with the mecha stuff.
That's not the same as being here.
Please, please!
No!
Please!
Yasuo!
Shut up! No means no!
Let's see, such and
such, therefore, as a result...
Great! How could you
write such a good report?
This should be it.
Well, it's all done! You have to
do the print-out yourself, all right?
Sure, thanks!
Oh, my shoulders are killing me.
Good work!
A little thanks from me!
l knew you'd be the best
person for the Crab Cop.
You should have gone
to the field instead of me.
That's not true.
You are much better than
l am. You deserved the shift.
l am just a mecha maniac
with lousy combat skills.
Sorry. Did l hurt your feelings?
No, it's okay. l knew l should grow up.
l found something
more important than mecha.
What a coincidence.
l was thinking the same thing.
lf l am trapped with the past too long,
important things before me may be lost...
Noriko, then you mean?
Yes!
Are you sure, you mean me?
Yes, l like Yasuo.
Are you okay?
My breasts are small, aren't they?
No, they aren't.
You are lying.
lt's soft and feels real good.
Are they better than mecha?
ls this your first?
No, it's not, but my first was a real
disaster. l don't want to remember it.
So, you've never done it with anyone since?
l'm sorry, if l can't satisfy you.
Don't be! l've never done it properly before.
Yasuo!
Am l hurting you?
No, not at all!
Really?
Really, you can move a lot more.
Okay...
Yes! More!
lt's good!
lt's really good, Yasuo!
lt feels good!
lt's great! Feels so great, Yasuo!
Really?
Can l move, too? l want to move, too.
Sure.
Look, it's so great.
lt's really going inside of me.
Can you see? Can you see?
Yes, l can see it.
lsn't it incredible? lt's so great!
Are you feeling good? l am
feeling so good. Are you feeling good?
lt's good.
lt's getting hot! Yasuo!
l like you, l like you Yasuo!
Do you like me, too?
l, l like you, too Noriko.
Emergency call! Emergency call! There
is a riot in progress in the Ginza slums!
Mobile Police Force, get ready!
Crab Cop number one, ready!
Crab Cop number two, ready!