Master Setsuya?
Yeah, don't you think
Setsuya's cool?
You shouldn't address
your master that way.
That's not nice.
That's okay.
l can call him Setsuya.
We're dating you know.
You're being delusional again.
l'm not being delusional!
lt's true!
Setsuya said he likes me.
He even smiled at me.
Smiled?
Really?
He did!
He smiled!
Oh, so he smiled only at me.
l want him to open his heart more.
Entering password
Access granted
l have to help Mistress Aoi
with her bath.
l'm jealous. You have
big boobs, Miki.
Stop it.
Let him squeeze yours to make
them bigger...
Your beloved master, that is.
You're vulgar! Rough Sayaka...
Are you jealous? Small Boobs...
Small...
Oh no.
There it goes.
What are you going to do?
l didn't know you were
sniffing around.
You're the best, brother.
Do you think they'll
suspect me after we switch?
Who cares? They won't be
able to tell the difference.
ln our faces, that is.
You're going to do it?
Yeah.
l'm releasing the junk.
Waterworks normal.
Air conditioning normal.
Lights and sound, both normal.
The bells...
Why?
lt's moving.
The Mansion Without Time has
begun moving on the rails of time.
Now wake up.
Wake up and start this thing.
Let's live like humans.
A Time to Screw Vol. 1
l feel hot.
Yes?
Excuse me.
Mistress Aoi.
The grandfather clock out in the
hall...
l know.
l heard the bells.
lt's midnight.
Thirteen?
Why?
You are...
Yes?
Miki, right?
Of course.
Fine. You may go.
Yes.
But your bath?
l'll take it later.
Then l'll call you again.
What?
You can go now.
l'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Sorry l'm late, it's Mutsuki.
l was waiting for you, but
Miki was the one who came.
l was disappointed.
Things feel weird today.
l couldn't get out easily.
Let's hurry up and go.
He's waiting for us.
So l won't get lost?
lf you have this, then l'll
know where you are, Kasumi.
You're teasing me right?
You know Setsuya...
Setsuya is...
Setsuya.
lnstant effect.
ltsuya...
Hurry...
The usual... Give me the usual...
Give me the usual...
Please, please, please, please,
please.
Please!
Don't confuse me with ltsuya.
Right now, he's...
Let Mutsuki do it for you.
That's too bad.
l don't care who it is...
Hurry...
l feel hot...
l'm about to melt...
l'm ordering you...
Do it!
You're annoying, old maid.
Yell at me more!
Kick me more!
Spirited away...
lt's a story from ages past...
When this grandfather
clock sounds thirteen times...
...one person will disappear for
sure.
lt's just a superstition.
But because of that, you can't
bring clocks inside the mansion.
That's why...
So inconvenient, right?
No, l don't mind.
l want time to stop forever.
One person will disappear...
Master Setsuya...
Master, are you asleep?
What is it?
l brought you some tea.
Tea?
l'm sorry, l knew it was early...
l'll come back at the usual time.
No, don't.
l'm sorry?
You don't have to bring any tea.
l don't need it from now on.
l understand.
Good night.
lt went in...
lt went in again...
lt keeps going in...
l'm going to run out of balls soon...
l'm coming, l'm coming...
l'll climax, l'll climax, l'll climax...
l'm going to come...
Master, l'm happy.
Opening break.
Mistress Aoi?
Where am l?
lt hurts...
No...
No!
l'll untie you...
So you'll have to give it to me...
Give some to me too.
One that's thick and hard...
Lots of it...
No!
l don't want that...
Tie me up...
Much tighter and harder...
Push them deeper until my stomach
bursts!
Hurry...
Come on, hurry!
What did you say?
What are you complaining about?
Who do you think l am?
What am l to you?
Give up and submit to me.
Just spread your
legs and suck it in.
You slutty slave.
So there's nothing wrong with her
legs...
She just thinks something's
wrong, but she has already healed.
Did you know that, brother?
You bastard...
l'm ltsuya.
l want you to remember my name.
l see, so you don't care...
...about your worthless
brother who was...
...abandoned in this
basement after he was born.
What did you do to this mansion?
l restored time.
Take a look, they're making
progress.
They're moving slowly
towards destruction.
What do you want?
Everything you have...
What's wrong?
ls it painful?
You can come if you want.
But you can't use your hands.
Can you climax using your
imagination?
lt's a wet dream while you're awake.
Stop...
Stop it...
Oh no, l threw up...
Oh no.
Great, it's not going in.
lt's no use.
Anyway, l...
Feels good...
What's wrong, Rika?
Setsuya...
My tampon wouldn't fit.
No, it's embarrassing.
Setsuya...
lsn't it boring playing
with my small boobs?
lndeed.
What?
l can't tell whether l'm grabbing
your clothes or your boobs.
You're mean.
Sayaka's mean too.
She told me to make them bigger
by having you squeeze them.
l can't let you do such
embarrassing things.
Who are you calling Setsuya?
You keep calling me that.
lt's ''Master Setsuya''!
l'm your master!
Setsu...
Besides, why do l have
to make your boobs bigger?
Squeeze them yourself to make
them bigger.
What's wrong? Master Setsuya...
You don't have to do it, then.
Starting tomorrow...
Let's see...
l'll put you in charge
of the back storage area.
You'll sleep in storage too.
l never want to see you around.
l'm sorry.
No, l don't want that.
l want to see you.
l'll squeeze them
myself, please forgive me!
Ouch!
Do it naked.
lf you do it with your clothes
on nothing will get bigger.
Oh no.
We have no more.
Well?
Are they getting bigger?
No, not yet.
Umm...
Can l play with my thing down
there?
Down there? You mean your feet?
No, down there.
What? l can't hear you!
My cunt.
No.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You're exposing your flat
chest in front of everyone.
Ouch!
She's terrible.
She's just trying to pleasure herself.
Just come already.
l'm not excited at all.
Umm...
l was wondering if
you can lend me a tool.
Tool?
This is all l have.
This isn't bad...
You're getting pretty dirty.
lt's sucking them in...
Everything inside my stomach...
Clean up after your mess.
lt doesn't look like
it's sucking at all.
Maybe it's full.
l'm coming, l'm coming!
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm
coming...
Master...
Please...
l want your huge thing...
My huge thing... You mean this?
There.
Well?
How does it feel?
Your master's thing...
Master Setsuya?
No.
You're not Master Setsuya.
What about me?