ls your commute safe?
Do you fear for your life?
Hire the TPP, the Tokio Private Police now!
Ten thousand private security
officers guarantee your total safety.
Sign up now, and you will
receive this special sports bag...
That sucks! Who came up
with such a stupid TV commercial?
Yes, this is lbuki.
Noriko, how long are you gonna stay
there, come down to the station, damn it!
Chief?
Hold it, l am assigned to the Mobile Police,
and l don't work for the Ginza district anymore.
Don't talk about such
details at a time like this, damn it!
Crazy bastard is making such a mess
with a mobile robot. Turn on the TV.
Not again.
Reporting live from the crime scene.
Suspects who robbed the Matsukoshi
department store reportedly ran off to the slums.
This is the picture from our zoom camera.
They're driving an illegal factory mobile robot.
Oh, a cannon is turning in
this direction! lt's shooting at us!
Oh, this is such a mess.
We don't have enough people, damn it!
Move your ass over there or you're fired!
Hey, what about my paid holiday?
Huh, they just don't know how
to appreciate their employees.
l was going to tone up the
body a little during my vacation.
These days, crime and violence
are getting worse all around the city.
The police have become so inept that
they depend on private security companies...
...to maintain safety in the city.
Since the capital of Japan
was moved to Kyoto in 2030...
...Tokyo has not only been a
center of commerce, but of crime as well.
Ginza, which used to be the most beautiful
shopping center in Japan, now looks like this.
The area has been taken over
by the homeless and illegal aliens.
lt is now called the ''Ginza Slums.''
The streets are filled with unregistered
children as the crime rate gets worse.
Because of tight budgets, the number
of police officers is still severely limited.
As a result, the crime rate
continues to climb at an even faster pace.
This is why among the upper middle
class it has become common to hire...
...private security companies for protection.
Now it may be possible to buy safety
in the big city only with a lot of money.
Tokyo has become such a rotten place.
Nothing changes, everything
just keeps getting worse.
Other than a few rich
people, everybody is so savage.
No, don't come any closer to me!
There, l got you!
No, stop! No!
What the hell, this chick has a TPP transmitter!
No, stop!
l'd like to help the client,
but l'm not on duty now.
Please, let me go.
No fucking way!
What a good view!
Please stop, stop.
No, stop, please.
Check this out, man. This chick
says no, but actually she likes it.
No, please stop it now.
Even before l licked it, it was soaking wet!
No fucking way! Men are such disgusting animals.
lt was just like that.
No, please stop, please.
No, l don't want do it! Stop! You're hurting me!
Hey hey, don't get lazy!
Come on guys, hurry up!
Hey, pretty boy, you can't be watchin' for free.
You! l'm talking to you! We'll let you
do it later, so give us all your money!
l...l'm a woman!
What the fuck?
Oh, what little tits...
What are you gonna do, huh!
l just called TPP! You better behave yourselves!
No shit, you're wasting our time!
This time on weekends there are always
more train delays than pizza deliveries.
You know the system pretty
well, you guys must be regulars.
You got a pretty face and wanna fuck with us?
Bro, a pretty boy's ass ain't bad for a change.
You can have it.
Don't make me repeat it! l am...
A woman!
Shit!
Die!
Don't move! This is TPP.
We are authorized to arrest any criminals.
What the fuck... Ouch!
Jeez, if l knew an undercover guy was on
the train, l wouldn't have had to act like a cop.
l wasted so much energy.
Did you send a rescue order?
Yes, l did.
Sorry for the trouble, but would you
come with me and tell us what happened?
Sir! Noriko lbuki, TPP Ginza department,
will cooperate and respond to all questions!
Oh, you are also a TPP officer.
l see that you were well trained.
l am sorry it took so long.
lt's okay.
But, l'm surprised that an attractive
woman like you belongs to the Ginza unit.
Oh, no l am not that attractive,
l'm always mistaken for a boy.
Yes, you are. You just don't
think you deserve a compliment.
l'd like to ask you out to dinner when we're off duty.
Oh, my! l've never been
asked out by anyone like you.
Well, l have to go back to headquarters. Take care.
Yes, you also take care of yourself, Captain Shibata!
How nice... in the headquarters
office, there are elite suits like him...
TPP is not such a bad place after all!
Yamagami reporting, sir.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Hey, you are working late.
So are you, captain.
lt's too bad, a manager has to
take a patrol duty in the subway.
Not enough people around
during the weekend rush hour.
The final member of the
newly established mobile police...
l guess this is your team, Captain Yamagami.
Yes.
Congratulations.
C-Captain?
This is my tribute to you.
No, l will get in trouble!
No!
You are so pretty, Keiko.
This is my new workplace and accommodation.
Please wait for me.
l don't see any supervisor.
Excuse me...l am assigned to the
first mobile police force as of today.
Oh, so you are finally here.
How do you do! l am...
Noriko lbuki, aren't you? l was waiting for you.
Yes l am.
l am Kayoko Kuraishi.
l have been transferred to the
mobile police force from headquarters.
So, l am superior to you.
Yes, please to meet you.
Your room is next to mine,
building A102. Here's the map.
l'll bring up your luggage, so
why don't you go out for groceries.
lsn't there a store in here?
Yeah, but you can't get anything you
like in there...you can go out for now.
The captain's first lecture will start in two hours.
You better hurry.
Yes!
lf you get it, run!
l am on my way!
Hey, you!
Yes!
lf you are on the way out,
could you get me some underwear?
U-Underwear?
Size XL, l don't care about the pattern.
l was at the national defense base
at Fuji mountain until yesterday...
...so l am a total stranger here.
Excuse me, but...
Bring them to lsamu Oyama's
accommodation in first platoon building A.
The first platoon? You are not saying
that you're also a mobile police member?
Oh? You, too! All right then!
We'll be teammates from now on!
You don't have to have another
teammate get underwear for you!
What's wrong with asking a man
to get underwear for another guy?
l am a woman!
What! A woman! l haven't seen any
women for a while, sorry...but hold it.
What are you looking at?
Are you a she-male, by any chance?
Well, that was an some response for a comrade!
No, it has to be out today! ''Mechanic
Magazine'' is coming out today, isn't it?
l'm not sure.
l always pick it up every month on this day in Mitaka!
l have to be able to get it in Shinjuku, too!
l know what you are saying, but...
Here it comes, that must be it!
You got Mechanic Magazine there?
What a psycho.
How are you.
l found it! This is what l've been waiting for!
Thank you.
l am sorry!
l am not sorry!
l don't know how to apologize.
What? Men's underwear?
Oh, give me that back!
l can't believe it!
Why do l deserve this?
As of today, l am captain of the mobile
police's first platoon, Keiko Yamagami.
Attention!
There's someone late, but l'll begin the
briefing anyway. The aim of our force is...
l'm sorry for being late.
Yasuo Kawasaki, reporting sir!
You are the Mechanic
Magazine freak from that store!
You're the men's underwear woman from the store!
Don't tell me you're another of my team!
Why, do you have a problem with that!
Hey, you! What is it with your
attitude, and being late today too?
Hold you private conversations
later, l haven't finished my speech yet.
Yes Sir.
Our team must deal with city crime by using
our mobile machines to maintain the peace.
Originally, we were four
platoons comprising one mid-sized unit...
...but as of today we are only one platoon
consisting of five members including myself.
What! This is all the members right here?
Core mobile machines will be four
for each platoon, totaling sixteen, but...
...unfortunately, we have only two.
Two machines for five members...
How are we going to make it through a shift?
For now, we will go on a trial drive.
The formal shift will be made
once we have more members.
Uh, Captain?
Yes?
Where are the mobile machines?
l heard that the latest Crab Cop
model will be introduced soon.
Right below here is the garage. We can take a look.
That is a Crab Cop! That's
so great! Cool! lt's so real!
That unusual leg formation
is the reason for the name.
Twenty millimeter Vulcan cannons
with three thousand rounds per minute.
What beautiful form it has.
lt's perfect! lt's more than a perfect
mobile mecha! And l will be riding on it!
With state of the art technology in Crab
Cop, the only weakness is running speed.
The maximum speed is only 40 kilometers per hour.
Forty kilo per hour?
Therefore, it will be
transported to the mission site by that.
A big transportation chopper,
a Pelican! lt's great, huge, cool!
Who is going to drive
that, maybe, by any chance...
Yes, l will be on it and
command the force from within.
Well, well, the headquarters'
man power shortage is that serious...
lt may be tougher to work
than the Ginza section was.
Hi, everybody.
Attention!
l am Shibata, your commanding officer as of today.
l don't have anything additional to add
after you heard the brief explanation...
...of our force from captain Yamagami.
But, l want you all to keep in
mind that you are the fighting tool...
...for our company to show the public.
We're a PR attraction?
What is that look? Did she catch me looking at her?
That's all l want you to remember.
Now, we will break for lunch.
After lunch, change to your
workout clothes and meet at the gym.
What, are we training today?
Yes. You will work on the simulation
practice and basic training for now.
No...l was hoping to go on the Crab Cop today.
Well, we have no choice.
The company can't afford to inexperienced
pilots breaking it every time we go out.
Yes, l know, but...
You boys are very good. Hang in there.
Yes, Captain!
She is so hot! l want to ask her to
do it with me, but she is my superior.
Noriko is not really my type...she's too
green, with that temper...and the other?
Not bad breasts at all...
if l go for it, this is the one.
l won't have to worry about any
strings with that kind of woman.
But if they claim sexual
harassment, l'll have no excuse.
One, two, one, two...
Fight... Physical training is not what l thought.
This is not what you thought?
What are you talking about?
Nothing is organized here!
lt is a joke that the Crab Cop is not
fully inspected so that we can't ride in it!
l hear you, but this is company
policy. You have to understand that.
You always bring up company
policy issues... you have changed.
ls that the reason you have been in a bad mood?
lt's fine. l'll go back to the
gym for some more training.
Wait! lf the captain is in that kind of
mood, it'll affect everyone else, too.
Here, l want to see you smile as usual.
Don't give me a hard time.
Oh, M-Manager...l'll get
in trouble, please let me go!
No, l won't.
Not until you can show me your smile again.
l can't take it.
l always like watching your sweet spot.
No, don't get so close... l'm so embarrassed.
l can't wait any longer... hurry, come inside.
Not yet, we don't have to rush.
But, the others are waiting. l should be there soon.
So, you want to stop now?
You are so mean!
Then, get in your favorite position.
Please, hurry, come inside me now.
Hurry up, you moron!
l... l can't run anymore.
How can you protect the city like that! Stand up!
He's so outdated.
Look, even the female
members are making fun of you!
They're laughing at you.
Hey, you think it's okay? Are you listening to me?
That feels good, so good, good, Manager Shibata.
Say, you seeing anybody right now?
No, not really.
l see... but don't try to come on to Shibata.
Why?
He is involved with Captain Yamagami,
everybody knows about them here.
Oh, really.
What are you two doing here!
What are you guys doing
here, this is the women's shower.
l know, but the men's shower is under
repair, so we were told to come here!
l'm sorry, l'm sorry, we are leaving right now.
Hey, l don't mind. We're teammates.
Hey you! Don't walk around naked!
Why, are you shy? l know you
were watching me during training...
...with your hard on. l know that.
Our job here is gonna be real hard, you
know what works best for stress, right?
Yes, but what...
No! What is she doing?
This woman is really a sex maniac.
lf l could do with this chick everyday, l'd love this job!
lsamu Oyama, charge!
Harder, right there.
This is getting really good.
That feels so good! Come to me, hurry up!
Okay, real slow.
Oh, yes... here, yes, yes, that's great.
l see.
Geez, l can't get dressed in here.
Yes, yes, more, harder.
l'm having a hard time.
l can't count on him.
Well, Kayoko, l'm sorry
but l'll catch up with you later.
Hey Noriko, why don't you join us?
What?
Don't be shy. Let's enjoy having sex together.
l am not shy, l just don't like sex.
Why not? lt's such a great thing to do.
Great? lt's never been great for me.
lt's good, so good, Noriko, it's unbelievable.
Why, why can you do that?
l am, l am...
Feels good!
l'm coming!
Stop, l don't want this, please.
lt's my first time, so please.
No! Stop it! No!
No! Don't be so rough!
That hurts!
No!
l liked you... why couldn't you be more gentle?
Manager Shibata!
No, please don't look!
Ms. lbuki...
What happened to you?
Did somebody hurt you?
No... it happened as
stupid mistake... really, l'm okay.
l see... l hope you really are okay.
Are you cold?
l am fine... l am sorry l made you concerned.
l don't want you to catch a cold.
You'll have to continue your training tomorrow.
Yes, Sir!
Good! l like your answer.
l am your boss and come
to me anytime you need me.
Yes! Well, l need to borrow your jacket for now.
Yeah, sure.
Thank you, Sir.
Wow, that was close. l almost attacked her.
Oh, l'm so embarrassed from just the first day.
But there will be another training session tomorrow.
l won't give up just yet!
l won't be scared away by those
mecha-freaks and sex maniacs!
Let's go!