Master...
Master Setsuya...
l finally caught up.
You walk too fast.
lt took me a while to get to you.
The sound of your bell...
Where were you?
lf you got lost, then what
would l say to Mistress Aoi?
l'm sorry.
Perfect.
Let's go home.
Master Setsuya...
l'm sorry, l...
What?
What are you doing?
That's enough.
You'll die.
There's something wrong with her.
No matter how many times l
thrust, she doesn't feel excited.
She doesn't get wet.
The junk doesn't seem to be
working.
lt won't work.
Why should it work?
She's one of us too.
A Time to Screw Vol. 2
Ouch!
What am l doing here?
The clock!
Mistress Aoi, the clock
sounded and...
This means that old story about the
clock...
Miki.
What are you doing here?
Looking like that...
l'm sorry.
l don't know what's going on but...
l'll leave immediately.
l don't need any breakfast.
Yes, ma'am.
l overslept.
l'll have an early lunch.
Make it 11 :30.
11 :30...
The clock is ticking.
Yes, l understand.
Excuse me.
Did Setsuya adjust the clock?
Or was it ltsuya?
He doesn't have that
kind of intelligence.
lt happened here last night...
This must be some kind of joke.
But it's weird.
l don't remember anything.
Setsuya, Setsuya.
Do you want some breakfast?
Who's Setsu...
No thanks.
Really?
Mistress Aoi said the same thing.
She's having an early lunch.
Bring them here.
l want some meat and wine.
Okay!
As you wish, master.
And also Kasumi...
Mistress Aoi...
The reason why Kasumi disappeared
is because of the clock and...
Thirteen.
Junk.
lt's nothing.
Miki.
Yes.
Come to my room within 30
minutes.
Umm...
Sayaka.
Help me make Setsuya's meal.
Master Setsuya.
What's wrong with me?
l'll have to take another shower...
That's okay.
But...
l...
Just keep doing it.
Mistress Aoi likes things like this...
Come on out ltsuya.
Oh?
You don't look enraptured today.
You're not ltsuya...
l'm ltsuya all right.
But l'm different from him.
Different from the guy you're
dealing with every night.
Where is he?
l gave him a new job.
He has no time to play with you
people!
You're the ones who moved the
clock.
You also took Setsuya
and Fujino somewhere.
You talk too much, bitch!
What are you...
l changed some things
from last night.
So you people can stay
sane for a bit longer.
But you still explode
when l poke you around.
Setsu...
ln the end, they're no longer human.
That's what the junk does.
Fujino, Kasumi...
Hot, it's hot...
lt stings...
Suction... l love this suction!
l like it cold!
l forgot...
Hot, hot, hot...
Hot, hot...
lt won't fit.
Stupid.
This is how you do it.
Like this, like this...
Like this...
Like this, like this?
Like this, like this!
Like this!
This, this, this, this...
This, this, this, this!
Se...
Master Setsuya...
You want me to play with you?
Your pain will sublimate into
pleasure.
What do you think, brother?
Stimulating, isn't it?
Let him go.
He'll die.
Die?
My brother won't die.
He's better than any one of us.
So you were alive...
l thought there was only ltsuya...
You and my father forgot
to destroy it completely.
l'll take full responsibility.
For the bad things l did...
l can spend the night embarrassing
you or make you do things as a maid.
l can't wait.
What do l get?
You win.
l'll let you have it.
Money, status...
Even this mansion, everything.
So...
Let Aoi and these girls go...
No, you can't...
l was getting tired of this.
l felt this way for a
long time about everything.
That's why...
That's why it's impossible.
They can't live very long.
They can't even pass their
genes onto the next generation.
That's the kind of bodies they have.
ltsuya can't succeed the Shijyo
family.
Sex is suicide for them.
Even images and small sexual
desires can be dangerous.
That's why the junk won't work on
them.
lt must not work on
them so they can survive.
Do you understand what l'm saying,
Setsuya?
They don't want money or status.
They just want you to be sound.
l see.
That's what these passwords are
for...
So l really don't need
my brother to be alive.
That's strange, why are they still
okay?
They took antidotes?
Unfortunately, it's
not working too well...
You'll regret it when you wake up.
lt's hot...
The place l was thrusted before...
Hurts...
Kasumi?
lt can't be...
Fujino?
lt can't be!
Please...
l can't hold back anymore...
Do it once more...
Your cunt is well-made?
What a waste.
You climaxed from my fingers.
Look at this, l'm not
even excited at all.
Setsuya...
Huh?
Master...
They still want to do it?
l don't know what to say.
More...
More, more...
More, more, more, more...
Hey...
Stop.
Kasumi, stop it...
Stop it...
The successor of the Shijyo family
is such a fool.
What is she doing?
Stop!
l want your thing.
Your hard cock...
That's not me.
Master Setsuya!
You...
You were pretending all along!
Die!
Who's going to die?
Master Setsuya! Wake up!
What are you going to do?
lt's happening.
Please! Stop this thing!
How?
Why don't you slit her artery with
that?
Then you can...
Now!
Hurry! Hurry!
lt's no use.
He only climaxed four times.
Help me.
No master.
You need to add more flavor.
That's right, both our stomachs
and cunts are craving more!
Bon appetit!
Eat it master...
Eat my flesh...
Suck plenty of it...
My juice keeps flowing out!
Thank you.
Now, l feel a bit relieved...
Shock treatment huh?
l wonder how long it will last.
Fujino, you...
Master.
Please open your eyes.
lt's no use...
Now, l want you to ease my pain.
Master, now you can be
hard for a long time.
Setsuya, you have to give
me your thick, hard thing.
So hard...
lt's hard...
Yes, this is good.
That's it, it's inside me...
lt feels good...
Setsuya feels so good...
l'm coming, l'm coming...
l'm coming, l'm coming, l'm
coming...
Climaxed already?
Too fast!
There's no way you can
replace your brother.
Master.
Fujino?
Kasumi? No!
lf you do that...
l understand.
l heard what you said.
That's not it!
l already knew that
l wouldn't live long.
That's not it!
You can't!
You two will die.
You saved me great deal of
trouble...
You're the one who is closest to
heaven.
Stop...
Stop it...
No...
No.
Master...
Please, wake up...
Not yet...
l haven't come yet.
Wake up, Master Setsuya.
l'm offering you my life.
l want you to live.
l always mess things up.
l'm always making you worried.
l'm older than you, but you're
the one who helps me all the time.
l always...
l always liked you, always...
She's choking...
Mutsuki.
Kasumi...
Don't leave me!
Master Setsuya.
Wake up...
Wake up Setsuya...
Setsuya, Setsuya, Setsuya...
Setsuya?
So this is where you were...
l was looking for you.
l heard the sound of bells.
l see.
Thank you, Kasumi.
You're welcome, Master Setsuya.
lt wasn't good at all.
Just look at you.
Want me?
Do you want me?
Setsuya, hurry up and escape!
Master!
l wonder where and how
we're going to meet again.
Go outside! Get out of here!
Alert everyone!
There's no escape.
lt won't come true.
You can never leave this mansion.
Not even a step outside.
Don't forget.
l'm the one who restored
time to this mansion!
From now on...
You'll all be running around
the mansion in circles...
Who are you?