The Kanto region suffered two tremendous earthquakes.
Because of the catastrophic damage caused by the
disaster, the country's capital was relocated.
The area where Tokyo once stood has now become
a haven for underground activity. An intoxicating
drug called "milk", which acts as an aphrodisiac
putting the user into a state of intense euphoria,
has spread among those who live there.
Amid this turmoil, an evil organization headed by 12
leaders called "The Twelve Angels" has gained immense
power and influence through the sale of milk.
A.D. 2054
Tokyo Shinjuku
No! Stop it!
Please, let me go.
I can't...
Isn't that Hakufu? One of our Twelve Angels.
And they want us to turn her into a cow?
But why?
It's Koryuu-sama's orders.
What's the meaning of this?
What the hell happened?
Well then, let us begin.
No! No, anything but that!
Please!
No!
Anything but a cow!
Oh no...
No... Not so roughly...
Wh-Why are you doing this?
No! Please stop there!
I'm begging you!
Take that cow to the Barn at once!
I've heard that swallowing the semen of tentacles
gives one's entire body an immeasurable thrill.
Rei & Fuko, special duty agent
Vol.01 The Cattle Pen
Milk is extracted from the nipples of women who
have been shot up with the tentacles semen.
When the semen fertilizes their eggs, they
immediately gain the ability to lactate.
The egg reacts to the pleasure flowing
in the woman's body and mutates.
The sex cells of the tentacles remain inside the
female host, granting her eternal pleasure.
Since the pleasure is too intense to tolerate,
the females lay their eggs,
releasing everything with them.
"Cows."
That is what the women who
lay these eggs are called.
And just now, Hakufu has joined the herd.
Why aren't we getting the go-ahead?
I know it's right by this dome.
I know there's a milk factory right here!
Shit. We're cut off.
What did the Chief say?
They're getting reports of gunfire
in some other location right now.
And thanks to that, he can't give
us permission to act on our own.
They don't think very highly of us,
being special duty agents and all.
Yeah. Especially the drug investigation unit.
That's just because you're always
so reckless, Rei-san.
It's their own fault for assigning
a genius kid as my partner.
Don't call me a kid.
I've been working with you for a year now.
When someone hasn't even been so much as
kissed, it's perfectly fitting to call her a kid.
Your boyfriend told me everything.
You want to stay completely
pure until you're married?
What? Did Yamase-kun tell you that?
Sorta. Well, guess we'd better go back.
I'm not in the mood to storm
the place blindly as it is.
We're not entirely blind...
I scanned the place and found several entrances.
As long as you're here, wouldn't you
at least like to investigate them?
I've been called a genius ever
since I was a little girl.
When I was ten, I was accepted into MIT.
But I had no friends or siblings
and I was very lonely.
So when I was assigned to be your
buddy, I was really pleased!
Thanks.
Umm... By the way, may I ask you a question?
Is it true that your little sister was
captured by the Twelve Angels?
Yeah. My little sister Anna was
captured while on a drug bust.
But it can't be helped; danger comes with the job.
Wait a minute.
Help me...
What's wrong?
Please help... My sister is underground...
Shall you hand that woman over to me?
You're Shien!
You're the with Koryuu, the head
of the Twelve Angels, aren't you?
Chief Shien!
So you're ceramic. Just like the rumors say.
Fuko!?
Are you awake now?
You're that girl from earlier...
My name is Koryuu.
Rei-Oneesama, Fuko-Oneechan,
how does it feel to be captured?
You can't move, can you?
So you're Koryuu?
You bitch. I'll kill you!
I'm afraid I can't let you do that.
It's your own fault for falling into our trap.
But in a way, that allowed you to
infiltrate this place easily, right?
Trap? So the intelligence reports about
a milk production factory here were...
Of course they're fake.
The gunfight going down at the other
area was also a ruse laid by us.
What's your objective?
Objective?
Getting rid of pests like you.
By the way, that investigator that
was captured two years ago...
Anna, right?
She's your little sister, right?
How fitting that her sister would have the
same fate and be turned into a cow.
Well, sounds like you planned things through nicely.
But unfortunately, reality is never that simple.
I know what you're implying.
You were injected with GC-3, the drug that makes
you immune to the tentacle's sperm, right?
But all it takes is some climaxing
from sexual pleasure and...
...it seems as though the effects of
this incomplete drug wear off.
Which means that even your painstakingly
procured GC-3 will still let you get pregnant.
Y-You don't mean...
Oh, I do.
First, I think I'd like to give you
a fun time, Rei-Oneesama.
Stop it!
Our dicks have been genetically enhanced.
Give us lots of fun, okay?
If you think monstrous things like these
will please me, you're dead wrong!
Have your fun acting cool while you can.
Take your filthy hands off me!
Rei-Oneesama, stop playing strong
and just have fun, okay?
And remember the fact that you are an animal.
That hurts!
You inserted yourself into me without lubrication?
You don't even know how to
pleasure a woman. You suck!
Stop it!
I like her screaming.
I think we'll have fun with this one.
It's so thick...
I can feel it in my uterus.
I can tolerate this much.
I can't cum... I can't let myself cum!
She's getting wet now.
This is awesome!
Her insides are squeezing me tight.
This isn't funny!
And it doesn't feel good to me in the slightest!
Who the hell would... enjoy this...
I hear what you're saying, but your voice is gasping.
Eh? Miss Special Agent.
Well? Aren't ya starting to like it?
Your smelly dicks... being rough with me...
...doesn't turn me on at all!
You're talking too much.
Let's shut that mouth of yours.
I don't want that dirty, smelly dick in my mouth!
Just like her little sister.
Well then, next up...
How cruel...
You needn't worry too much.
In time, we'll have her squealing for joy.
Please stop doing cruel things like this.
How can you do this to your fellow woman?
Don't do it! Please!
D-Don't!
Please, don't look.
Stop it!
Oh dear. Fuko-Oneechan, you're soaking wet.
You must've gotten turned on by watching
Rei-Oneesama being fucked by those guys.
No! That's not it at all!
Oh my? Could it be that you're a virgin?
You're a bad girl.
Even though you're still a virgin you get so
excited watching your partner being violated.
That's not... That's not true.
Yummy.
What? Stop it!
Fuko-Oneechan, you seem very sensitive.
Stop it!
No... What is this sensation?
My body is tingling.
Is this what being turned on is?
No! I can't let myself be turned on!
The antidote will wear off!
I have to resist it!
Rei-san's up against much worse
and she's resisting it.
I'm getting wetter!
Fuko-Oneechan, it feels good, doesn't it?
It's turning you on, isn't it?
It's not... turning me on.
It doesn't feel good in the slightest.
Then, how about this?
No! No, no, no! Please stop!
Just say it.
Say it feels good. Hurry!
It feels good!
It feels very good!
Do you want to cum?
I want to cum. Let me cum!
Please, let me cum!
I'm cumming!
You look great, Fuko-Oneechan.
Hey, boys.
What? What's going on?
This time, you guys play with Fuko-Oneechan.
However, you mustn't thrust into her.
Got it?
Stop it.
Please.
You needn't worry.
We won't rob your virginity.
Where does the cum keep coming from?
It's so smelly I can't stand it!
She's still resisting it.
I wouldn't expect less from the
elite of the special duty agents.
Hey! What are you doing?
Not there!
Oh? Your first time doing anal?
Stop it!
Not in there!
How about it?
That hurts! Stop it!
Woah, very tight. I can't stand it.
That hurts! Don't move!
I'll tear apart!
I won't stop.
I'll let you cum gradually.
There are two dicks scraping inside of me.
I've never been so humiliated in
my life. But I have to resist it.
If I don't resist it... then I'll get
pregnant with a tentacle's egg!
I'm almost there!
Me too.
No! Not inside of me!
Stop it! Stop moving so much!
Please! I'll break apart!
No!
It's over.
Yeah, with the first group at least.
Now it's our turn.
We had to wait an extra long time.
So give us an extra good time.
I must resist it.
I must.
I'm cumming!
Fuko-Oneechan, you came again?
How many times has that been now?
You sure are a little whore with an innocent face.
No...
What's going on?
I've been violated so many times.
And I've cum so many times.
And yet it still turns me on?
Am I really a whore?
No!
Hey, boys! I thought I told you.
Don't thrust into her.
But if Fuko-Oneechan asks for a dick herself...
Then we won't mind putting one in for you.
But I don't... want that at all.
Really?
No! Not any more!
Not that!
You want it, don't you?
You actually want a dick inside you, right?
Stop it... Please, stop it.
Well?
Doesn't this dick look yummy?
Just say it. Say it with pride.
"Shove that dirty cock into my dirty pussy."
No...
I can't hold out...
Come on, just say it.
Be honest.
I want it.
Say it louder, please.
I want the dick!
Shove that dirty dick into my slippery
pussy and wiggle it around!
Thrust it in and let me cum!
I'm begging you!
Koryuu-sama, preparations are underway.
I see.
In truth, we had something special
prepared for you, Fuko-Oneechan.
I wonder if you'll like it?
It's the perfect partner to lose your virginity to.
Rei-san... I've cum so many times now.
I'm sure the antidote's potency
has diminished significantly.
Even though you're putting up such a strong fight...
I'm so sorry.
This is bad.
It's starting to actually feel good.
I need to focus on something else!
She's been filled up with so much
and she still hasn't cum yet?
How many times have we cum inside her now?
How many times have you cum inside me?
With your filthy dicks in me, I couldn't
cum even if I wanted to.
I'm cumming!
Are we finished now?
Look at that.
Her belly is all swollen from our semen.
That hurts. Stop it.
Woah, awesome!
How funny!
No!
Hey, we stopped fucking you.
You have a problem with that?
Why does this feel good?
Why is it turning me on?
What's happened to my body?
No! No, no!
Don't feel it!
The bitch.
She's pissing herself.
No! Don't look!
What a disobedient pet.
She needs to be punished.
Stop!
She's turned on by it, the bitch!
I'm not turned on. I'm not!
I am turned on. My pussy is so turned on by this.
Don't do it, Rei.
You must resist it!
That just brought my dick back to life.
Mine too.
Hey, bitch, on your hands and knees.
This time for sure we'll make you cum.
It's no use.
I feel it pulsating in me.
Fuko... are you okay?
I don't think I'm going to make it...
I once had dreams, but after my failures, I just gave up.
ano koro no akogare tsumazuite wa akirameru dake
There wasn't a side of me that didn't
have feelings that were too young.
osana sugita kanjou jibun nante nakute
And so time passed, and the more
I cried, the more I understood.
sou shite toki nagarete naite wa wakatta bun dake
And I also learned to protect myself
and those things I loved.
mamoru koto mo oboeta daiji na mono mo dekite
I'm sure I'm ignoring someone else's pain so that I can rise.
kitto dareka no itami o mushi shite nari tatteru
In a world that only knows how to take
pride in oneself by shaming others.
kuraberu koto de shika kagayaku sube o shiranai sekai de
If you look up, you'll see the vast universe
expanding before your eyes.
miagereba hora hiroi uchuu ga me no mae ni hirogaru no ni
But the rainclouds formed by your tears
close up the path that leads to it.
kimi no namida ga tsukuru amagumo
sono saki o tozashite shimau
But when you cry and the shadows look
like they are about to disappear,
kimi ga naite sono kage ga kiesou ni naru toki ni wa
I will become the wind and reflect your heart.
boku wa sou kaze ni natte kimi no kokoro o utsushi dasu yo
I will stir up a storm.
arashi o okoshite