Stop!
Somebody...
Is somebody there?
No!
Stop... don't!
Please.
Anything but that.
Anything but that, please.
I'm still a virgin.
I beg of you!
It feels tight.
It hurts!
Stop moving!
Pull it out.
Pull it out please!
No, no...
I'm going to break!
You devil.
Pervert!
I'm about to cum.
No way.
Is he planning on cumming inside me?
No, I don't want that!
Stop!
Save me, Mom!
I'm about to cum!
No, no, no!
Inside you!
Stop please!
It's coming out!
It's really pouring inside me.
Stop.
Please, don't record this.
Tokubetsu Jugyou 3
I've been teaching for 20 years already.
Starting this spring.
I'm going to teach at my alma mater.
Sensei, what are you recording?
This school, where I will teach,
will once again become a place to remember.
Right now the old school building.
is just a place waiting to be torn down.
I was assigned as the area's caretaker.
Huh?
Saki-chan and... Ishizuka?
What are they doing in the old school building?
For others, taking care of the old school building,
might look like a very troublesome thing to do.
But for me, it's actually a blessing.
Because I can do all sorts of "disciplining",
without anyone in the school knowing.
And the first one to receive my disciplining,
is none other than you, Saki.
He's doing this even though he's a teacher.
I'm going to send you to the cops!
Stop!
Pervert!
Soon this will feel totally ecstatic for you.
No way in hell would it!
My body will never...
N-no...!
What's this?
It feels even stronger.
No, it hurts, it hurts!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
No...
No!
Your insides are starting to twitch.
No, no!
We're just getting started, Saki.
Stop this!
Your nipples are getting this hard already.
Stop!
My breasts are not toys for you to play with!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming with your tit fuck!
No...
I can't keep up with this anymore.
Seems like you still need lots of disciplining.
How about your mouth pussy?!
My mouth isn't a pussy!
It's rubbing hard inside.
Come on, suck it more erotically!
It's going... deep inside my throat!
I came a bit.
Here, there's more!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum inside your mouth!
It's coming out!
I'm going to pour it inside your mouth pussy!
The main course is yet to come.
I'm going to completely rape you today.
I don't want this anymore!
Stop thrusting inside me!
Stop!
Your insides are twitching.
I'm going to squirt it inside your womb!
Stop!
Don't cum inside me please!
No!
I'm going to completely break your current self.
From now on, you're going to be reborn as my sex slave.
Stop this.
Stop messing with my body already!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum again.
I'm going to cum lots.
You've also come a lot of times already, haven't you?
There, there, there!
No, anymore and I'm really going to get pregnant!
No!
Stop I don't want to cum anymore.
I'm going to cum inside!
This is terrible...
Strange.
That expression of hers after I disciplined her,
looked like someone else's.
Something is really strange.
Saki-chan seems very troubled these past few days.
And she's acting very odd.
That teacher's definitely involved in this somehow.
I'm sure of it.
What...?
What are these?
It is forbidden to enter this place without permission, you know.
I knew you were doing something to Saki-chan!
You perverted teacher!
If I spread this video around,
Saki's life would probably be over.
If you want to protect her,
you’ll have to take her place and be disciplined.
Me?
Saki-chan?
That's right, I'm going to take her place.
I'm going to put an end to this guy!
I'm not going to let him do terrible things to Saki any longer!
Suck my dick more!
Don't let your teeth out.
Suck the dick... using my mouth...
Use your tongue properly.
Make me feel it more!
This stinky and dirty thing,
I don't get any of this!
That's good.
So you can do it if you try.
Of course I can,
and I'll go even further!
Go ahead, and open your mouth!
Here I go,
I'm going to squirt it all over your face.
Take this!
Wow, I came lots.
Savor it well, and then swallow it.
What's wrong?
Saki can do it properly, you know?
Okay, good girl.
There's still more left!
Here, here!
I can't breathe.
My throat's completely clogged!
No, stop!
I'm going to cum inside this mouth urinal.
This is it.
Make sure to drink it all.
Looks like you're getting the hang of it.
I'm really going to use it as a urinal now.
Here it comes.
I'm going to pee now!
Don't spill it, drink it.
Huh?
This isn't good at all.
I'm going to completely discipline you now.
If you really care about Saki...
You understand already, right?
Huh?
You look pretty tired lately.
Did something happen at school?
Nothing really.
It's alright.
And you're even taking care of the house regularly.
Should I share a bit of the work load?
It's okay!
You're working all by yourself Mom.
So it's just natural for me to do all of the other chores.
Let's hurry now.
I can't tell her,
that I've been violated like that.
I don't want Mom to worry.
I guess...
...I guess, enduring it is the only choice I have.
I see.
So Saki's mother was that woman.
This will be useful.
My, oh my.
What a mess.
Those who take a leak without warning should be punished!
It's cold.
But it wasn't just pee, was it?
It's getting really wet down here.
No way.
That can't be.
Why?
I absolutely hate this and yet,
being "disciplined" like this is just...
I'm slowly getting used to being violated.
I don't want this.
I shouldn't be accepting it, and yet...
My body's getting horny, it won't listen to me!
I'm starting to desire being enslaved.
I mustn't like this!
I absolutely should not want this!
You really have a horny body, Saki!
I am very happy as a teacher,
to have been able to discipline you into my sex slave like this.
Now, what do you want me to do?
Like this?
Here I go.
I'm going to squirt it all over you.
No!
Save me!
That horny expression of yours,
it looks just like Rie's, your mother's expression.
Why does sensei know Mom's name?
20 years ago, Rie and I,
became involved with each other in this very school.
The master and slave.
Our relationship was that of a master and a slave!
What happens when the slave feels hornier than the master?
Master, your thing is stirring me inside.
No...!
With these two inside of me, I'm going to...!
I'm cumming.
Please tease me more, and cum inside my pussy!
I'm going to give you the same pleasure that your mother had!
No way, Mom really...?
That can't be...
That can't be true!
As I thought, the way you squeeze me tightly really is the best!
It's going deep inside.
It's rubbing my insides.
And the sensation is going through my whole body.
Your ass is now perfectly trained as well.
I guess you already came lots of times
while being fucked in here, right?
That's not true!
No, no!
I won't cum.
I definitely won't cum!
I wonder how long you can last?
I'm going to cum inside your ass!
No, don't!
Don't!
I'm cumming!
Wow, it's squeezing me really tight.
No, stop this already...
This hole too, it's very wet already.
No!
Take this, and this, and this!
No, stop!
No!
It feels really warm and wet inside!
No, no!
Become my slave!
I'm going to make you cum as many times as I want!
I'm cumming!
Stop!
I'm cumming...
Amazing.
I'm being sucked inside.
That’s good.
From now on, you are my slave.