Stop!
Someone! Is anyone around?
No!
Stop! No! You can't!
Please... just that...
Please at least spare me from that!
I... I'm still a virgin! So...
So...
It's tight...
It hurts! It hurts, it hurts!
Don't move!
Pull it out... pull it out!
No, no!
I’ll break! I'm going to break!
You monster! Pervert!
I'm gonna cum soon!
No way...
Is he planning to cum inside?
I don't want that!
No! Mom, save me!
Cumming!
No...
No, no!
Inside!
Stop it, please!
Cumming!
No...
It's coming...
It's really... coming inside!
Stop, stop...
Please, stop filming!
Translation: Snake |Timing, Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Special Lessons
It's been more than 20 years since I've become a teacher.
Since this spring, I've been working
at the high school I graduated from.
What are you filming, Sensei?
This school is also a special place,
where I first stood on the lecture platform.
The old school building at that time,
now awaits its demolition,
and I've been given the job of its management.
Huh?
It's Saki-chan and... Ishizuka?
What are they doing, going to the old school building?
The management of the old building
could seem troublesome to others,
but it is the perfect gift for me.
Because I can have such a great training room
inside the school with no one noticing!
The first to receive training in this room is you, Saki.
Such actions despite being a teacher...
I will sue you for this!
Stop it! You... pervert!
Sooner or later, this will become irresistible pleasure!
There's no way that could happen!
You're doing what you want with my body and...
No, no...
It's getting... stronger and stronger...
No! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Cumming, cumming, cumming!
Here!
No...
You're starting to twitch inside!
No!
No!!
It's only just begun, Saki!
Stop it!
Your nipples are so hard and erect!
Stop! Don't use my boobs like toys...
I'm cumming!
Cumming from your titty fuck!
No...
I can't...
Stop this already...
Looks like your mouth-pussy still needs more training!
No! It's not a mouth-pussy!
It's so wet and slippery inside!
Suck on it harder!
It's going deep... down my throat...
I came just a little.
More... More!
Here... Here I come!
I'll make a creampie inside your mouth!
I'm cumming...
I'm cumming inside your mouth-pussy!
The real thing has just begun
I'll be sure to violate you thoroughly today.
No! No more!
Don't move anymore!
Stop!
You're twitching... deep inside!
You're going too deep inside!
I'll spurt it deep inside your womb!
Please stop!
Don’t cum inside!
No!!
I'll break the you that has lived until today.
rom today you will be born again as my sex slave!
Stop already!
Don't mess my body up!
Cumming, cumming!
Cumming again!
Here I go on your face!
You’ve cumming again and again, too, haven't you!?
Take this, take this!
No!
If you cum any more inside me, I’ll get pregnant!
No, don't!
No...
I don't want to... I don’t want cum anymore!
Gonna cum inside... again!
So cruel...
Something like this...
This is strange...
Her face while receiving training...
Is similar to someone...
There's definitely something wrong!
Saki-chan's been looking like she's in pain recently,
she hasn't been herself at all!
That teacher definitely has something to do with it.
Huh?
What?
What... is this?
It’s against school regulations...
to enter without permission.
As I thought it was you who did that to Saki-chan...
You sick pervert of a teacher!
If this video is spread around,
Saki's life will be completely ruined.
If you want to protect Saki, you should
receive training in her place.
I...
Saki-chan...
That's right, I should take her place.
If it was me, I'd be able to take care of this guy!
I won’t let you do any more cruel things to Saki-chan!
Suck more on the dick with your lips!
Don't you dare bit.
Suck... with my lips...
Use your tongue properly! Entertain me more!
Such a stinky and dirty thing...
I don't get the point of this!
That's right, looks like you can do it if you really try!
You...
It's getting hotter, he’s almost cumming!
I'm cumming, open your mouth!
Here we go, I'm cumming on your face!
Take it all!
Amazing, I came so much!
Taste it thoroughly and then swallow.
What's wrong? Saki had done it properly.
Alright, good job!
I still have lots to cum!
Here, take this, take this!
It's painful...
It's going all the way to my throat...
Stop! Stop it!
I'll let it all out in your mouth-toilet!
Here I go, be sure to drink it all!
Seems like I've gotten the urge to pee.
I'll use your mouth as a toilet like this!
Here we go, I'm peeing!
Drink every drop without spilling!
You're completely no good.
I'll have to train you a lot from now.
For the sake of Saki and yourself...
You know what to do, right?
Huh?
You've been looking really tired recently...
Did something happen at school?
It's nothing, really.
Nothing's wrong.
You're helping in our store, too...
Should I give you less work for now?
I'm fine! Mom is working alone already.
Of course I should help, right?
Let's go!
I can't tell her.
I don't want to worry my mom with stuff like that...
There's no other way... I just have to endure it.
I see...
So Saki’s mother is that woman...
Oh my, what do I see.
Someone who can't hold it in, needs punishment!
Cold... it's cold...
Looks like this isn't just pee here.
You're completely drenched!
No way... that's not...
Wh-Why?
This should be unbearably disgusting...
This kind of training...
I... getting used to these horrible things he does to me...
Even though I don't want to... even though I shouldn't...
My body is hot... and out of control!
I... I'm really becoming a slave.
That can't happen!
What a slutty body you have, Saki!
Sensei is happy that you've grown
into such a great sex slave!
Well then, what do you want me to do?
Like this!?
Here we go, I'll pour tons onto you!
No! Help!
No!
You look just like your mother, like
Rie, when you're excited like that.
H-How does Sensei... know my mom's name?
Over twenty years ago, Rie and I
had a relationship in this school!
What?
Master and slave... a relationship of slavery!
My nipples are going to break!
You can't feel better than your Master, as a slave.
Master's dick is stirring up my insides...
No! Please punish me deeper and deeper inside!
Cumming, cumming!
Please punish me, use my pussy
make a cream pie inside me!
I'll give you the same pleasure I gave your mom!
That's... My mom was...
No way! You’re lying!
Just like I thought, you squeeze
incredibly well in this hole, too!
It’s coming in!
Rubbing my insides...
Echoing up to my stomach!
Your anus is twitching!
Rie came over and over again from anal, too!
That's not it!
No, no!
I won't cum! I definitely won't cum!
How long will you last?
I'll creampie you inside your asshole!
No, don't!
No!!
Cumming!
You’re squeezing... incredibly...
No... I don't want this anymore.
This place is soaked, too!
No!!
Take this, and this, and this!
You can't! No!
No!
No! No!
Amazing!
It's hot and drenched!
No, no!
Become my slave!
I'll make you cum again and again!
Cumming, cumming!
No...
Cumming...
Amazing!
You're sucking me dry!
That's right.
With this, you are my slave!
kono te niwa mada orokasa ga iki wo hisome
In these hands, stupidity still holds its breath hiding.
migurushii jibun e no kakushin e
Towards the confidence, of the hideous self.
hana ni tsuita kaori ga kako wo yonda
The scent that the nose catches, calls for the past.
mouichido koko kara hajimaru sekai e
Towards a world, starting from here once again.
mezame hajimeteru shinario wo tadotte
Following the scenarios, that have begun to awaken.
fiirikazashita kono te ni
On this waving, brandishing hand,
yobubou wo matotte
Wrap lust and desire.
koware hajimeteita kokoro ni wa mou
The heart, that has already started to break.
tomerareru hazu mo naku yukkuri to
Slowly, yet unstoppably,
kuzure yuku
Crumbling down.