After two deadly earthquakes, society plunged into
a state of chaos fueled by a hallucinogenic drug
called "milk", which acts as an aphrodisiac putting
the user into a state of intense euphoria.
Special duty agent Rei, along with her partner Fuko,
went to investigate the suspected location of the
manufacturing plant of an organization behind the
production of milk. However, the two were captured.
Rei attempted to escape the organization with her
sister, Anna, who had been taken captive one
year ago...
But with Fuko brainwashed by the organization,
the escape was not a success.
This is what happens to women who are
no longer useful to our organization.
At least lactate a little. Then you can redeem yourself.
Rei & Fuko, special duty agent
Vol.04 A Resolution!? Aei and Koryuu
Koryuu...
There is something I still want you to do for me.
So I want you to stay here.
That warm water you are submerged in makes pregnancy easy.
I want you to get pregnant with the Shoku-Kichu's baby.
And then give us your milk.
I can't...
Or perhaps... You may have gotten pregnant
with Fuko-Oneechan's baby.
Fuko!
Wake up, Rei-san.
Get away, Fuko!
Fuko, not there...
K-Koryuu. What did you to do Fuko?
Don't worry. I sent her away.
Sent her away?
Yeah. I got bored of her.
And she broke from too much milk.
What do you mean?
I'll show you.
Ya-Yamase-san?
Gimme your cock.
St-Stop...
It's so thick and yummy, your cock.
Let me have it!
What are you doing?
Get away from that woman!
I want a cock.
Izumi Fuko? The agent?
I'm giving birth!
Fuko!
What a disappointment Fuko-Oneechan was.
Koryuu!
Never mind that.
I just want you to hurry and give birth to a Shoku-Kichu baby.
It'll probably be really ugly.
Kokuran, Rosho, keep close watch over her.
Yes.
Lately, Koryuu-sama has seemed a little irritable.
Yes, so much that it's scary.
I didn't think she'd sacrifice Soko and the
others so easily just from minor mistakes.
All of you... will end up the same
way as Hakufu, Soko, and Sekiro!
But we won't mess up like Hakufu, Soko, or Sekiro did.
Is that so?
What are you trying to say?
As far as Koryuu is concerned...
You are just toys!
And she gets bored of toys after a while.
Just like with Fuko.
And just like Soko and Hakufu...
Boring toys get thrown out!
Shut up!
Don't you see it!?
Koryuu is... she's insane.
Yamase-san's baby... I'm giving birth!
Someone... save me!
It's not over yet.
There is something even scarier than what you feel now.
Koryuu-sama, any more and they will die.
That doesn't concern me.
I want to get the data and test it on Rei-Oneesama.
Very well.
And that's why you sacrificed Soko and Sekiro?
And your point is?
I see no problem with it.
Yes, but...
We have no need for useless females.
Or are you trying to tell me you would like
to join the ranks of useless females?
If you understand, then work harder.
Yes.
Rei-Oneesama.
Where are you taking me?
The special operation room.
Looks like you finally got pregnant.
Congratulations.
I'm happy for you.
I'm carrying Shoku-Kichu children?
You'll birth plenty of them in the operating room,
and then we'll get lots of milk out of you.
What's so funny?
The fact that Soko, Sekiro, and Hakufu were expelled
because they made some tiny mistakes.
But the one who is about to make the biggest mistake
to threaten the organization is Koryuu herself.
It seems like she underestimated Fuko.
What do you mean?
That you sent her back home.
She went insane from our brainwashing.
So we sent her away because she is of no threat.
I really wonder about that...
Fuko may not look it, but she graduated from MIT
with top marks. She is an elite among the elite.
She's not an ordinary woman.
She will revive very quickly.
She has been trained to do so.
And when that happens, she will destroy this place at once.
It's only a matter of time.
It looks like Koryuu's arrogant attitude is putting
this organization in the most danger.
How's it going?
According to plan.
She's about to give birth.
I see. That is good news.
Koryuu...
Looks like the extra-strong Shoku-Kichu we bred was a success.
Perhaps this is in part thanks to Rei-Oneesama's
strong will and body.
An exquisite milk we have yet to see the likes of.
I'm impressed, Rei-Oneesama.
If you lay an egg, you'll have plenty of milk, I'm sure.
Oh dear. I wonder if she's miscarrying.
No...
It's coming!
See? Just a bit more.
I'm sorry, Rei-Oneesama.
You just birthed it and I stepped on it.
I don't care about that!
I need to get you pregnant with many more
eggs so we can get milk from you.
I still need to conduct many experiments on your milk.
W-Woah, what a metamorphosis!
Much more powerful than Fuko-Oneechan's milk was.
I guess it takes more than brains to make good milk.
Get away from me!
Since you just birthed an egg, this
size is probably perfect for you.
But you need to test your own milk, too.
It feels great.
More... More... I want more!
This hole, too. Put it in there.
Hurry!
It's melting.
I feel so great, my body is melting.
More...
Her own milk... Must feel wonderful, Rei-Oneesama.
What kind of illusion is she seeing?
After you take the data, we'd better have her birth another egg.
Get me another big Shoku-Kichu like the last one.
Okay.
Rei-senpai...
It's been three hours since they started.
It's endless.
Shien, make them finish so we can start the next experiment.
Yes.
Men, it's over.
Can you hear me?
Yes. What is it.
I can't see the guard.
I am here, Koryuu-sama.
You girls... what are you doing with those useless ones?
Koryuu-sama, we are relieving you
today of your duties as our chief.
What are you babbling about?
We are not your toys!
"Toys"? You talking about me?
Then you girls must also become useful.
We're fighting Shien in Block 6 right now.
We've got things blocked off right now, but...
Kill her.
So the chief of this operation is that woman?
She's not bad looking, eh?
You can make her your toy if you wish.
So this is mutiny, is it?
Shien! Come here at once!
Yes, right awa...
Shien!
Fire!
It seems that the coup is going well.
The fight has started.
Anna! I'm coming!
What's wrong, Shien?
Stop!
Oops.
Shien... protect me... until the very end.
Koryuu-sama, that was always my intention.
But I did not intend to overlook their
invasion. Please forgive me.
Koryuu-sama... I am...
Shien? Shien!
Is this location safe?
Of course. No one's noticed.
Wow, she really does look like a virgin.
Well, we'd better do something about that.
Turn her into a proper woman.
And how about pregnancy? Wouldn't that be nice?
First we'll break your hymen, okay?
Hey, Koryuu-sama. Don't cum just from this.
The men from the organization are waiting for you.
This is nothing.
Of course it's nothing.
We haven't even used this yet.
This is the extra-strength milk that you yourself
extracted from special agent Rei.
Rei-Oneesama's...
You won't refuse, will you?
You tried your utmost to make it.
Don't do it!
Oh, dear.
You just lost your virginity but you're still so sensitive.
You bitches... Don't think you'll get away with this!
Playing so strong. But you just pissed yourself, you know?
Just give up.
Now it's time for you to become useful.
Sh-Shien...
Please, be gentle.
Very nice.
Shien's big penis feels so good!
Shien... Stay with me forever.
More... Give me more.
Shien's hot juice. Give me lots.
More. More.
Is it over already?
More...
Koryuu-sama, you're already pregnant.
Doesn't it feel nice?
You will continue this way forever.
You are the only cow now.
So work hard, okay?
Please...
Stop it...
Anna! We did it! We've escaped.
I once had dreams, but after my failures, I just gave up.
ano koro no akogare tsumazuite wa akirameru dake
There wasn't a side or me that didn't have feelings that were too young.
osana sugita kanjou jibun nante nakute
And so time passed, and the more I cried, the more I understood.
sou shite toki nagarete naite wa wakatta bun dake
And I also learned to protect myself and those things I loved.
mamoru koto mo oboeta daiji na mono mo dekite
I'm sure I'm ignoring someone else's pain so that I can rise.
kitto dareka no itami o mushi shite nari tatteru
In a world that only knows how to take pride in oneself by shaming others.
kuraberu koto de shika kagayaku sube o shiranai sekai de
If you look up, you'll see the vast universe expanding before your eyes.
miagereba hora hiroi uchuu ga me no mae ni hirogaru no ni
But the rainclouds formed by your tears close up the path that leads to it.
kimi no namida ga tsukuru amagumo sono saki o tozashite shimau
But when you cry and the shadows look like they are about to disappear,
kimi ga naite sono kage ga kiesou ni naru toki ni wa
I will become the wind and reflect your heart.
boku wa sou kaze ni natte kimi no kokoro o utsushi dasu yo
I will stir up a storm.
arashi o okoshite
You learned how to smile well, I see.
kiyou ni warau you ni natta yo ne
Is it egotistical of me to want to bring out what's in your heart?
mune no oku o hikidashite agetai to omou no wa ego kana
I'm sure your pride keeps your weak side hidden.
kitto yowai jibun o kakusu no wa kimi no puraido
But when you're around me, please expose your heart.
boku no mae de dake wa dou ka sono kokoro sarake dashite
If you look up, you'll see countless stars, glittering high in the sky.
miagereba hora ikusen no hoshi sora takaku matataku kedo
But the burning light in your eyes is about to cross far beyond them.
kimi no hitomi ni tomoru hikari wa ima haruka sore o koeteku
But when you get lost and your light is about to disappear,
kimi ga mayotte sono hikari ga kiesou ni naru toki ni wa
I will become the wind and stir up your heart.
boku wa sou kaze ni natte kimi no kokoro o utsushi dasu yo
I will stir up a storm.
arashi o okoshite
Surely, some encounters are so necessary they can't be understood.
kitto dare nimo rikai dekinai hitsuzen no deai to
Because the words "we fit together" can only be understood by "us".
au yo ne tte kotoba wakari aeru no wa bokura dakara
If you look up, you'll see the vast universe expanding before your eyes.
miagereba hora hiroi uchuu ga me no mae ni hirogaru no ni
But the rainclouds formed by your tears close up the path that leads to it.
kimi no namida ga tsukuru amagumo sono saki o tozashite shimau
But when you cry any the shadows look like they are about to disappear,
kimi ga naite sono kage ga kiesou ni naru toki ni wa
I will become the wind and reflect your heart.
boku wa sou kaze ni natte kimi no kokoro o utsushi dasu yo
I will stir up a storm.
arashi o okoshite