Your cries sound a lot better now, Arisa.
I just can't take that as a compliment!
And your level of arousal is even better than Saki's!
And look, here's the direct proof!
You want to be like Saki too, right?
– Here's a reward then.
– No!
What?
I'm going to use your asshole.
Stop!
I'll stop if you don't want it then.
I'll just have to do it to Saki instead.
No way...
I get it already!
Just do it!
These are the fruits of my discipline!
– This sensation is quite nice.
– It hurts!
No, no, it hurts!
No need to feel like that.
Your asshole is trying to eat up my dick quite nicely.
No way...
It's just... It's just painful...
It's my asshole pussy!
And you're my slave.
Just try and cum with it.
It's really holding me tight.
Interesting...
How long can you resist?
I'm going to completely turn you into my slave.
Oh no...
I need to endure...
I need to endure this.
If I don't Saki will be the one to endure
all of these terrible things again!
We're just getting started.
Arisa, it's your first time experiencing my electric play, right?
Here, let me snap a photo as remembrance.
No!
– Don't take pictures!
– It's totally exposed.
– Oh no, I'm going to leak...!
– What a foolish girl.
No matter how much she tries to protect Saki, she's already...
I've had enough already...
Wow, my dick is being sucked in!
No!
My body is just...!
Why don't we let your mouth pussy take it easy today, eh?
It's entering deep into your throat.
I can't keep it up anymore.
I can't even breathe!
It'll stay open if you keep pushing hard like that.
But I probably won't be able to hold on before that!
Your insides are getting hot.
It's time to feed your mouth pussy with my cum,
while your asshole pussy gets cummed inside!
I'm cumming!
Amazing, it's squeezing me tightly!
What's wrong? Can't stand straight anymore?
No, please stop this already.
If you don't keep it up, my dick will go inside.
This can't be happening.
It's my first time, I'm still a virgin!
Now, now, if you don't resist more...
No, no...!
– Stop!
– If you insert my dick on your own, that'd
be proof of your submission to me!
– No, no!
– If you insert my dick on your own, that'd
be proof of your submission to me!
– No, no!
Stop, I can't resist any longer.
He's really going to take my first time!
Now you've completely become my slave, Arisa.
It's your first time, and yet it slipped inside easily.
It's going deep inside.
There!
It's hot, no...!
I'm going to cum inside!
I'm cumming!
It's squeezing every bit of it.
Don't pour it all inside me!
I'm giving you a reward for letting me do this.
I'm going to cum inside!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to get pregnant, I'll get pregnant!
It's rubbing it well, inside out.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming while squeezing it!
– No, no!
– It's coming out!
I-It's pouring inside me.
Pumping, flowing inside...
I'm going to discipline you even more from now on.
Look forward to it.
Here you go.
The new teacher.
Majima Mikako.
She's well respected at this school as an elder sister of sorts.
And is also well known by other teachers.
With her almost weird beauty and the
erotic smoothness of her body,
it's almost certain that she's well developed to
the point of becoming a man-craving bitch.
She's even married!
Arisa's recent disciplining wasn't bad at all,
but taking on little girls is getting kind of boring...
Ishizuka-sensei, what is this?
This is Morimiya Saki-san, right?
Why would...?
I do not know.
It was sent to me by an unknown party.
Though, I do remember the place where this was taken.
Eh?
I think it may be the old school building
just beyond the small group of trees.
I'm going to investigate the place myself right now.
Can you take me there as well?
I can't just let this go.
I thought you'd say that.
Circumstances are circumstances anyway.
I was actually thinking of consulting one of the
female teachers here about this matter.
Okay, let's go now then.
Be careful.
Okay.
S-Sensei, what are you doing?
The one that made Saki like that,
was none other than I!
Or at least I was!
I'm going to let you feel exactly what Saki experienced.
You're one gemstone I'd surely like to keep rubbing clean.
I've had my eye on you for quite some time already, you know.
Just so I can make you my slave.
I have a good aphrodisiac here.
And I'm going to test it on your pussy!
No, please anything but that!
Please, don't put it in!
No, darling please save me!
No, I said not to put it in!
Stop lying to me, you're already this wet, see?
No way...
Look, you can feel it on your own too, right?
Darling, save me.
Okay then, let's call your husband.
Mikako?
Why are you...?
This isn't what you think!
– Darling this is not...!
– What isn't what he thinks?
You're the one moving your hips here.
No, that medicine...
That medicine was just used on me.
You're not bound or anything.
And you can simply do as you please.
Stop this, Mikako!
Darling, I'm sorry.
I'm going to cum in front of you...
If you can't stop, then shall I do it more for you then?
Oh no, it feels good.
My pussy feels great.
No, no...!
Mikako...
Cum in front of your beloved husband!
No, anything but that please!
There, there!
Sensei, no, if you keep doing it that intensely...
I'm really going to cum.
– I'm cumming!
– Mikako...!
– That's good.
Next... we do the grand finale on Saki.
Master!
My pussy...
Well, Saki?
This is how your mom, Rie, really is.
No way, mom...
There, there!
No...!
Push it hard, push it hard inside of me, please!
Penetrate me more intensely!
Saki, you should become as obedient as you mother.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...!
Release all of your carnal desires... just as your mother has done.
I'm cumming!
I can't hold myself anymore.
Now everyone's assembled.
It's the beginning...
Of our banquet!
Is this for real?
Can I really do what I want, sensei?
Yeah, do whatever you want.
We have lots of toys here.
Just shame them to your heart's content.
Yes sir!
This will be fun.
This is it, this is it!
Punish me more please!
This is just too erotic!
Punish me!
Violate me!
Violate me while violating me!
She is really erotic!
It's very wet!
It's this wet!
Take this, perverted bitch!
And this too!
Oh crap, I'm about to cum.
Release it!
Cum inside me!
I'm cumming!
Mikaki-sensei it feels great.
I'm happy that it's this stiff.
Push your dick inside my pussy harder.
– Just let it out if you are already about to cum.
– Her true identity is that of a sex-craved swine!
Just cum inside!
It's okay, you can even use it as a toilet if you want to.
I'm going to get pregnant.
Just keep doing it on this side too.
This feels good!
Her throat pussy is great!
I'm cumming!
There it is again.
Please, give all of your cum to me.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum on your face!
Look, Arisa and Mikako look very happy.
Stop...
And the one to perform the grand finale
on you, is none other than her.
This hole is open, right? Let mom plug it for you.
No...!
Now both mother and daughter are slaves to our master.
Your pussy is squeezing it tight!
It makes me feel very aroused!
No, no!
You're actually aroused by your mom fucking you in the rear!
My body feels hot!
I'm cumming inside!
No, I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum if both keeps on pushing me like this!
Not with my ass too!
I'm about to cum!
Arisa, open wide!
Just let all your cum out!
I'm going to cum inside your throat!
I'm cumming on you Arisa!
Oh my, you're going to cum on my face.
Oh wow, this is amazing.
I'm going to impregnate you, Arisa!
Do it, impregnate me!
Pour it all!
Get all your cum inside me!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming...!
I'm going to cum!
Sensei, now I have to take you as well!
No, it's going to leak.
It's going to leak!
Look, it's the proof of our union!
When I get pregnant, it'll be from all of your cum!
Ooh, it's coming out, it's coming out!
Come out, come out now.
It's going to come out!
See? You just gave birth to your beloved teddy bear, sensei.
How nice, right?
I gave birth to my teddy bear...
No, no!
Now this is what I call a blood-related union!
– It feels too good!
– Saki, I was already master's slave when you were born!
You may actually be master and I...
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
Saki, I'm going to cum again!
Take it all into your womb!
No!
I'm sorry master!
I want your dick!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
This is wonderful, now all of you are ours!
From now on, you will all be our sweet, precious slaves.