The red pill makes it easy for a woman's body to conceive.
The blue pill increases a man's genitals.
As part of the responsibilities for my job, I assembled beautiful nurses for the purpose of this experiment.
It was especially appropriate to make these four my junior partners.
Will it be okay?
Do you think I'd make you take a dangerous medication?
No, they're... they're strange, my nipples.
They don't usually get this big.
Usually when they stand up they're smaller!
Sensei's penis is going in...!
If it goes any further, I...
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, cumming, I'm cumming!
Makimura-sensei?
This means...
This is... a clitoris?
What... my clitoris... is this big?
Why?
I'm borrowing this clitoris-penis.
I'm taking your male virginity.
Se-sensei!
Sensei! Sensei!
I'm cumming!
Sensei's semen...
The next experiment starts now.
W
Special Ward
Pleasure's Embarrasing Varieties of Medical Examination
Shinohara-san, you again?
Oh, that was Naruse-san?
Are you okay?
I-I'm okay.
Your face is red, do you have a cold?
No, I spaced out when I was grilling something.
I'll be on my way now, excuse me.
Ah, onee-chan!
Onee-chan...
Even though I came so many times since this morning...
I still can't control it at all.
I can't do my job.
It's a bad habit to rub my clitoris so hard.
Why have I become such an indecent woman?
It feels so good.
But it's embarrassing with a big clitoris like this.
But it's so good I can't stop!
Oh, this is no good, the semen in there is flowing out.
I need to get sensei to use her penis and inject me again...
I'm sorry I came so late.
It's fine. What is it? You wanted to talk?
Yes. Lately I've been noticing mistakes from the nurses in this ward.
Especially Shinohara-san and Naruse-san seem to have their hearts elsewhere.
That won't do.
The two of them need to be punished severely.
If we don't warn them...
This is strange.
I can't help it, my body is getting aroused.
Is this perhaps a side effect of the medicine again?
Was that all?
No, there's one other thing.
What, pray tell, are these.
I had a friend at the university examine these, and he told me they were unlicensed new medication.
Where did you find this?
That doesn't matter.
Don't you think it's strange to have medications like this at a pharmaceutical college?
Don't I think?
What?
What are you...!
You know, in this hospital there are a lot of dangers you don't know about.
Where am...
Bright!
No!
Why am I... like this?
Who on earth would...?
My body feels hot!
And also, down there is... down there...
What does this mean? My body is being strange!
It's not strange.
That's your true form.
The instincts of an oppressed bitch who always relied on ethics and morals have been captured.
Nakimura-sensei.
To awaken the instincts, the body needs to become fertile,
and the desire that is concurrent with reproduction must be enhanced.
That's the purpose of this drug.
That's just like an aphrodisiac...
Don't hypothesize.
Your body should be feeling the effects just about now.
You made me take it, didn't you.
Starting today, you are going to help me with my experiment.
Kaname?
Yes, master.
Sh-Shinohara-san!
What are you doing here?
I'm master's maid.
This girl has lately taken to calling me "master." Isn't it cute?
A maid... th-that machine...
It's all okay.
We're going to raise the voltage.
That's... that's dangerous!
But, if we don't punish people who take other's things without permission...
Y-You're insane.
Those clothes are in the way. Kaname?
Yes.
Stop!
I... I looked up to sensei as a woman in the medical profession!
Oh, that's too bad.
I'm not a woman. Let's start!
Here we go.
S-sensei... ple-please stop...
How is it?
Does it hurt?
But you lead such a strict life, I've been wondering if you were actually a masochist.
What's this?
Oh? It felt so good you became incontinent?
Th-that's not it.
Your nipples are all standing up, too.
Then, next, we'll do your clitoris.
I-It's coming... out...
What a big, thick piece of shit!
You must have been terribly constipated.
Getting it all out will be recuperative for you.
Ah, master, her ass is all like that.
Ah, it's quite opened up.
I wonder if this is a side effect of the medication.
Master, what should we do?
Well, since it's gone to the trouble of being like this, we'll have to clean it up.
It looked like you had a lot piled up in there, so there's probably a good deal left.
Amazing, giving an enema and it goes all the way into the ass like this.
No! This much coming in...
It's fine. If we don't put this much in, you'll stay constipated.
It's enlarging so easily, but it'll come out effortlessly.
No! My butt can't stop it!
It's coming out! I can't stop it!
To make sure that nothing remains in your stomach when it all comes out, I'll help you.
You can't mean that... stop!
It's starting to look good.
Raise your ass up and push it out.
Like that for now.
Now, I'm going...
It's amazing! Thanks to the effects of the electric shock, the anus feels even better than down there.
Master's penis in her ass... I'm jealous...
Stop, please!
My butthole is opening!
It's going to open even further.
Keeping guts that feel this good constipated... what a bad girl.
What are you saying?
I can't stand it, it feels so good!
Sen-sei... Please don't... that hard... in my ass...
Sensei's penis... my insides are... collapsing!
This sensation...
I've never tasted something like this before either.
At this rate, I'm going to be fit to ejaculate in your soft anus.
No! Sensei!
It's going to be strange if you do that!
No, I'm going to cum! I'm going to ejaculate in your anus!
No, don't!
Sensei, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
My anus... and down there... are all open...
The semen is... going in...
My ass... feels so good.
And now, the remaining experimental subject is...
Makimura-sensei, do you really know why my sister has become strange?
Yes, I'm going to tell you now.
And did you take the medicine I gave you earlier?
Y-yes.
But what medication was it?
You'll soon find out.
Makimura-sensei, why are you doing this?
You said you'd tell me why my sister was acting strange, so I came along with you!
Why is my sister...?
Yes, the medication you took earlier will tell you.
Hitomi-san, moisten Chika-san.
Yes, sensei.
W-wait, onee-chan, what are you doing...?
Stop that, onee-chan...
Onee-chan...
Doing such an indecent thing...
Hitomi-san, how is it?
It should be fine, I think.
Well, either way, we have to start.
Sensei, that...
Now we will start the actions which are necessary to get pregnant.
Stop that! Sensei!
We're going to have sex, right?
I'm a virgin, so if you put such a big penis in me, I'll die!
Please stop!
It hurts!
It hurts! It hurts! Help me, onee-chan.
Now that your hymen is broken, give up already.
I'll make you start feeling good soon.
No-no, I don't want this, please don't move!
Even with your sympathy, there's no way it could feel good!
It doesn't hurt, and it's hot down there.
Is this the fault of the medicine I took earlier?
It's so tight. Really, the taste of virgins is exceptional.
Sensei, stop already! You're going to tear me down there!
Not a chance. My sperm have to enter your uterus, so I can't stop.
What's this? The clitoris...
What is that? My clitoris looks like a penis!
You really are sisters, aren't you.
You even smell the same.
That's good! Your insides are coming alive.
Can you feel it, Chika-san?
If I stroke your clitoris like this, I don't know if this counts as masturbation or sex.
Sensei, please don't stroke my clitoris! I feel it too much!
That's good, isn't it?
Your sister loves having her clitoris-penis stroked, too.
Onee-chan...
She can't hold back, seeing her sister enjoying herself like this.
All right, come here.
Thank you... very much.
Stop! Stop! Please!
Hitomi-san, thanks to the medicine, you've become just like a man.
Chika, you're so cute.
No-no, onee-chan, don't fondle my breasts!
Why not? You've always wanted me to fondle your breasts, haven't you?
That's not true! It's not like that!
Chika-san, you've never performed fellatio, right?
Now, first I'll cum in your mouth.
Stop this already! Don't do any more!
All right, Hitomi-san.
Yes.
Hitomi-san, you go there.
Yes, sensei.
Onee-chan!
Chika, the inside of your butt is so warm and feels so good!
A double-sworded samurai in your first experience... that's true sisterly love in the anal version. I'm jealous!
I don't want anything to do with samurai!
This is... so strange... being hit by onee-san and sensei's penis...
And I have a penis, too...
Even though it's my first time, it's starting to feel good...
I feel strange... just like onee-chan, I've become strange!
That's right, Chika.
Let's feel good together.
And then, let's get pregnant by sensei and bear her children.
Pregnant... as in, a baby?
I don't want something like that!
Why not?
If you have a baby, you'll become a fine grown-up adult.
Even so, I don't want to be pregnant!
Chika-chan, let's compete to see who can have sensei's baby first.
I don't want to!
That won't do. You can't go back now.
Onee-chan!
You two, cum.
I'll shortly be letting Chika-san taste the first "internal" in her life.
N-no! If you cum inside, I'll really become pregnant!
That's right, that's the objective here.
Become pregnant with my child!
Onee-chan! Onee-chan!
Chika! Chika!
I'm cumming!
Oh, dear, you couldn't wait until I arrived?
Even though you're all going to become mothers soon,
you can't calm down.
Shibuya's anus and pussy felt so good, her penis nipples won't stop shooting out milk.
Shinohara-san's penis-nipples feel so good!
The breast milk coming out of my opened anus and pussy is overflowing!
Chika's clitoris-penis is going all the way into my pussy, it feels so good!
Doing this with my clitoris is going to make me cum again!
The experiment was a success.
The first subject was Shinohara Kaname.
Naruse Hitomi.
Takayama Kazumi.
My ass... feels so good...
And finally, Naruse Chika.
After all, I was only thinking of conception at that time.
However, the father of these mother's children is me,
but after the experiment is over, our affiliation is not going to end.
We committed this forbidden pleasure.
And then... a new experiment.
This time, I will be...