Tokyo was destroyed by two deadly earthquakes...
An intoxicating drug called "milk", which acts as an
aphrodisiac putting the user into a state of intense
euphoria, has spread among those who live there.
Special duty agent Rei, along with her partner Fuko,
went to investigate the suspected location of a
drug ring...
The two agents fell into a trap, and were violated
by gangs of men involved in an organization which
extracts milk from women who have been turned
into cows...
Rei & Fuko, special duty agent
Vol.02 Clouded Warriors
Well? Are you not going to surrender your body over?
I would never cum because of those mens filthy cocks.
Are you really that scared that your antidote will wear off?
Where is Koryuu?
Koryuu-sama took a personal interest in Fuko's training.
And I was asked to train you.
No, it would be more proper to say that
I asked them to let me train you.
Do you know why?
Why is that?
Your little sister...
Anna!
Yes, and Anna's lover, Hakufu of the
Twelve Angels, is my big sister.
It's been two years, hasn't it?
Hakufu...
I was completely in the dark.
I didn't even know Anna was her lover.
Lover?
You will meet Anna in time.
After you become a cow like her.
Anna... Where is she?
Your outsides and insides are so dirty.
Shut up!
You've been fucked over and over for a whole week.
And you still haven't cum.
One week ago...
Yes, that was when my team was fooled by false intelligence,
which reported that there was a gunfight elsewhere.
But I'm sure that by now they're
concentrating their efforts on rescuing us.
Don't underestimate the Special Investigations Unit.
They might be at the door right now.
You're right. They are.
Fuko's fiancé was also a special duty agent, wasn't he?
Yamase...
And that special duty agent is right at our door.
What are you talking about?
Shien promised to take him to Fuko.
He instructed him to come to a certain location
if he wishes Fuko to be returned alive.
Wh-What are you trying to do!?
You'll see in time.
But before then...
What a pretty clitoris.
What are you going to do?
What is that?
A little something my organization cooked up. Just a little milk.
No... Don't do it!
It'll just increase your sense of pleasure.
My body...
But I can't give in to pleasure.
I suppose it's about time for Fuko to meet up with her fiancé.
Fuko!
Don't scream.
Understood?
If you do, Rei will lose her life.
Yamase-san!
Fuko-san!
If you yell out, I'll kill her.
Yamase-san, what are you doing here?
F-Fuko-san...
D-Don't watch.
Hey. You're filming, right?
Of course, sir.
We'll share this train-molestation
tape with evenyone in the country.
I'll send a special copy to your unit free of charge.
Wh-Why?
Why does this turn me on?
Because I'm in front of Yamase-san?
It's making me even hotter.
I'm such a freak!
Fuko!
She's getting off from her fiancé watching.
Run! Run for it, Fuko!
We told her that if she tries to run or scream, we'd kill you.
Fuko!
She looks like she's having fun.
But don't worry.
Koryuu-sama is really strict about
us not taking away her virginity.
She says that's for her fiancé to do.
Oh dear, what's wrong?
Did Fuko's thrill transmit over to you?
What's going on?
Is it because of the injection?
You think I'm gonna let this get me off!?
Looks like the drug's starting to work.
Stop it...
I'm gonna cum!
No!
The thrill is in your dreams.
But that doesn't change the fact that
you're being violated in reality.
I wonder how much longer you can
tolerate it without facing the truth?
So hot...
But I can't let myself cum.
But... But...
Looks like there aren't enough cows in the Barn.
I want it. I want it.
I want your thing, Yamase-san.
Yamase-san!
The next time you can touch your fiancé
will be when you give him your virginity.
Does that please you?
To make this happen, we've arranged for your
fiancé to join our organization as a master.
You can't!
You get to give up your virginity
to a master at our organization.
Ya-Yamase-san!
Seems like you've cooled off.
Well? How's the milk treating you?
Soko...
Let me shoot you up with something stronger.
This was milk taken from your little sister.
Anna...
That's right.
Your darling sister Anna lives in this organization's
barn, birthing eggs and lactating very strong milk.
Along with my sister.
Stop it!
I hope you dream of your little sister.
Just like my sister Hakufu showed
your little sister thrilling dreams.
Dreams?
Yes.
She was used by Anna when she invaded.
But my gullible sister seriously fell in love with her.
And for her darling Anna, she tried to betray us.
For Anna...
Hakufu was turned into a cow, not even
aware that she had been deceived.
I'll make sure you suffer even more than she did.
N-No...
Suffer more than my sister.
Hot!
What is this... this sensation?
Ya-Yamase? You came to rescue me?
You need to run away.
Fuko... What's happened to Fuko!?
Now...
Time for you to watch.
Let's give him some fun before he becomes a master.
Yamase-san!
Fuko-san!
Consider yourself lucky Koryuu-sama decided to reward you.
Have plenty of fun with us.
Wh-What... Stop it!
Your body doesn't lie.
Ya-Yamase-san...
I want it... please.
Please do me.
He's gotten so big.
Let me put it inside me.
Be sure to lick me well too.
Very nice thing you have.
Hurry, make me cum!
Fuko-san... is watching me.
If you do it so roughly...
If I'm rough with you... Then what?
It's no use!
I'm cumming!
Ya-Yamase-san!
Amazing!
It's so big!
Hitting deep inside!
It's no good.
I can't stop.
Fuko-san...
I'm cumming!
Yamase-san!
Me too!
Yamase...
Why are you...
So big... it's hitting my uterus!
Yamase... Are you going to cum?
Yamase, you can cum inside of me!
So hot. So good...
So you came.
I win.
Bring that thing.
Well then, time to become a cow.
Just like Hakufu and Anna.
I have a last request.
What is it?
I'm a goner.
So at least before I become a cow, let me see Anna.
Very well.
Good idea.
I'd like to see your pained expression
at the sight of your cow-sister.
The special ranking cows are kept here.
Anna...
You will end up here with Anna,
producing especially strong milk.
Anna...
Perhaps I was mistaken, Soko.
I suppose I don't need to inform you that
you will be held responsible for this.
Rei-Oneesama, fighting won't solve anything.
Just accept your fate.
No!
Koryuu-sama!
I once had dreams, but after my failures, I just gave up.
ano koro no akogare tsumazuite wa akirameru dake
There wasn't a side of me that didn't have feelings that were too young.
osana sugita kanjou jibun nante nakute
And so time passed, and the more I cried, the more I understood.
sou shite toki nagarete naite wa wakatta bun dake
And I also learned to protect myself and those things I loved.
mamoru koto mo oboeta daiji na mono mo dekite
I'm sure I'm ignoring someone else's pain so that I can rise.
kitto dareka no itami o mushi shite nari tatteru
In a world that only knows how to take pride in oneself by shaming others.
kuraberu koto de shika kagayaku sube o shiranai sekai de
If you look up, you'll see the vast universe expanding before your eyes.
miagereba hora hiroi uchuu ga me no mae ni hirogaru no ni
But the rainclouds formed by your tears close up the path that leads to it.
kimi no namida ga tsukuru amagumo sono saki o tozashite shimau
But when you cry and the shadows look like they are about to disappear,
kimi ga naite sono kage ga kiesou ni naru toki ni wa
I will become the wind and reflect your heart.
boku wa sou kaze ni natte kimi no kokoro o utsushi dasu yo
I will stir up a storm.
arashi o okoshite