Special Lessons
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
You've started to moan with quite a voice now, Arisa.
Even if you...
praise me like that...
I won't be happy or anything!
Looks like you've even exceeded Saki in sensitivity.
As proof, look! Already like this!
You want to become like Saki, right? Hmm?
This is your reward.
What?
I'll use your butt hole.
St-Stop!
Hmm?
If you don't want it I can stop.
but then I’ll have to switch to Saki.
That’s...
I get it already!
Just do... whatever you want!
So tight!
This must be the result of your training so far!
It feels quite good.
It hurts!
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't worry. Your ass-pussy is happily sucking in my dick!
No way! That's...
My butt... my butt hole...
It's called an ass-pussy!
If you’re gonna become my slave, say it properly.
You're squeezing amazingly tight!
Interesting. I wonder how long you'll hold.
I'll be sure to discipline you thoroughly.
Just endure it. I have to endure it!
If I don't do this, horrible things
will happen to Saki-chan again!
This is nowhere near the end.
No! I can't!
Arisa, this is your first time getting
an electric massage right?
Here, I'll take some photos for the occasion.
Don’t!
Don't take photos!
Amazing! You're all exposed!
No... I have to...
Such a stupid girl.
No matter how you try to protect her,
Saki is already...
You crazy, perverted bastard...
Amazing! My dick is getting sucked in!
No! My body is moving on its own...
Your mouth-pussy has to be trained without rest, too!
It's going deep into your throat!
I can't take something so thick!
I can't breathe!
No!
If you're thrust so roughly, my butt will break!
I'll die!
I'm going to die!
It's hot inside!
You cum dump with pussies all over your body!
You're getting creampied in your ass-pussy!
Cumming!
Amazing! Semen's getting sucked out of me!
What's wrong? You're shaking already.
Stop it! I can't anymore!
If this goes on, you're gonna have
my dick shoved up your pussy.
I can't let that happen!
It’s... it's my first time!
I'm still a virgin!
C'mon, you have to get a grip of yourself.
No, no... No!
If you insert it inside yourself,
It'll be the proof that you've surrendered.
No, no!
No... my body is losing strength...
I'm really going to have my first time robbed of!
No!
Finally, you've fallen as my slave, Arisa!
Even though it's your first time, it's
going in and out so smoothly!
It's reaching deep inside...
There!
It's hot! It’s hot!
Cumming!
You're squeezing so tightly... I'm cumming!
Sucking hard on me again...
Cumming... deep... inside...
It's rubbing... so roughly...
Amazing... no...
For an honest slave, I have a reward.
I'll cum inside you again.
Cumming! Cumming!
No... I'll get pregnant...
I'll really get pregnant!
It's going all the way inside again and again!
No!
I'm going to cum! My pussy is going to cum!
It's going to suck in semen!
No! No!
Cumming!
He came...
Inside... inside me... so much...
I'll be sure to train you lots more from now on.
Look forward to it.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks.
She’s the new teacher, Majima Mikako.
The students think of her as an elder sister,
and her fellow teachers like her, too.
Charmingly beautiful and has the perfect seductive body.
Well raised to be a female loved by man.
In addition she's married!
It's not bad to have Saki and Arisa to play with...
but I’m about to be unsatisfied with
just having little girls as partners...
Ishizuka-sensei, this is...
This is Morimiya-san, Morimiya Saki-san, right?
Why?
I have no idea. It came from an anonymous address.
But I remember the location in the background.
Huh?
It's probably the old school building in the forest.
I'm planning to investigate the place right now.
Could you take me with you?
I can't stay out of this
I thought you'd say that.
It is a serious problem, after all.
I thought I'd as a reliable female teacher for help.
Ye-Yes.
Let's go right away.
Be careful.
Yes.
Sensei! What are you doing?
That video was something...
during Saki training...
something I... I had taken!
Eh?
What Saki went through...
I'll show it to your body!
You're an ore waiting to be polished to shine!
I've always had my eyes on you!
To make you my slave.
I got myself an aphrodisiac with quite a good reputation.
Let me test it on your pussy!
No!
Please spare me from that...
Please!
Don't put it in!
No! Darling, help!
No, don’t put it in...
Don’t lie, you're so wet!
No way...
C'mon, you can feel it, too, can't you?
Save me, darling...
I see. Then let's call your husband...
M-Mikako...
Mikako! Why!?
This isn't it! Darling... this isn't it!
What isn't it? You're moving your
hips on your own, aren't you!?
No... it's because of the drug...
This person gave me a weird drug...
I'm not doing anything.
You’re free to do whatever you want.
Please stop! Mikako!
Darling... I'm sorry... my body is just so hot...
I'm cumming!
If you just can't stop, do you want me to pull out instead?
Don't, it feels good!
My pussy feels good!
Yes...
Oh no, no...
Mikako...
Cum in front of the husband you love!
That's... Please spare me from that!
There! There!
Sensei, no! If you’re so rough...
In front of Darling...
Cumming, I'm cumming!
Cumming!
Mikako!
Wonderful.
Next, time for the finishing touches on Saki.
Master!
It's hot! My pussy...
How is it, Saki?
This is the true face of your mother, Rie!
Let it out!
No way... that’s...
Mom!
C'mon, c'mon!
No!
It’s good! It's really good... Master!
More... more...
Tease me more roughly with your dick!
Saki, become honest like your mother.
So rough...
Cumming...
Yes, yes!
Cumming, cumming!
Just like your mother...
Release your desires inside!
I-I'm... I'm cumming...
Cumming!
I... I can't take it anymore!
Now we've got everyone.
Well, finally it’s...
Time for the party!
Woah! Really?
Is this really alright, Sensei?
Whatever we want?
Yeah, no problem. I've prepared so many toys.
Wow.
Embarrass them with all you have.
Yes, sir!
I just can't wait!
Arisa-nyan! Arisa-nyan! Arisa-nyan!
Let it out! Punish my dirt cat-pussy!
In my mouth, too! Cum inside my mouth!
Sexy! She's so dirty!
It's so wet! So... So...
You perverted pussycat!
You...
This is bad, I'm cumming!
Let it out! Let it out inside me!
Cumming!
Mikako-sansei, great!
So embarrassing... you're so hard...
Violate me more with your dicks!
My face... If you feel like cumming let it out on my face!
I didn't know that Mikako-sensei was actually a slut!
Cum inside me!
Cumming!
It's alright! Use my boobs and my pussy
to squeeze out all your semen!
I'll get pregnant...
Let my face have some, too!
This feels so good!
I'm fucking someone's wife, yes!
Cumming!
Oh, again!
Give it to me! Give me all your semen!
Cumming.
Cumming on your face!
Just look, both Arisa and Mikako are so happy!
Stop it!
Now, it's her job to make you fall.
Your butt hole is free right now, isn't it?
Mom will fill it for you.
That's...
We've both become Master’s slave!
Saki's ass-pussy is squeezing so tightly!
Mom is feeling it, too!
No!
To think you'd get turned on from
your mom fucking your ass!
My body is so hot!
I'm cumming inside you!
No!
I'll cum!
If you cum inside right now I'll cum!
I can't let that...
I'll cum, I'll cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Arisa-nyan’s fellatio feels so good!
Let it out!
You slutty pussy-cat! It's creampie for you!
Cumming!
I'm cumming on Arisa-nyan's face!
Please do!
Please ejaculate onto Arisa’s face, nyan!
Amazing!
Amazing, nyan.
I'll make you pregnant, Arisa-nyan!
Cum! Make my pregnant! Give me semen.
Arisa-nyan! Give it to Arisa-nyan!
Ama-Amazing! I'm cumming!
Arisa-nyan! Cumming, cumming!
I'm cumming!
C'mon, sensei, you have to focus on giving birth!
No, it's coming out, it’s been born...
That's right, it's the product of our love!
I got pregnant!
I got pregnant from everyone’s sperm!
It's coming out!
It's born, it's born!
Look, Sensei's favourite Teddy was born!
That's wonderful isn't it, Sensei?
Teddy was born...
No, no!
So this is what it means to be connect by blood!
No...
When I was blessed with you, I was
already a slave of Master's!
If you want, you can join me and Master...
Cumming, I'm cumming!
Saki, I'm cumming again!
Be sure to tale all of it.
No!
Master!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Cumming, I'm cumming!
Wonderful.
With this, you will never be able to leave me.
I'll always adore as my slaves from now on.
kono te niwa mada orokasa ga iki wo hisome
In these hands, stupidity still holds its breath hiding.
migurushii jibun e no kakushin e
Towards the confidence, of the hideous self.
hana ni tsuita kaori ga kako wo yonda
The scent that the nose catches, calls for the past.
mouichido koko kara hajimaru sekai e
Towards a world, starting from here once again.
mezame hajimeteru shinario wo tadotte
Following the scenarios, that have begun to awaken.
furikazashita kono te ni
On this waving, brandishing hand,
yokubou wo matotte
Wrap lust and desire.
koware hajimeteita kokoro ni wa mou
The heart, that has already started to break.
tomerareru hazu mo naku yukkuri to
Slowly, yet unstoppably,
kuzure yuku
Crumbling down.