W
Special Ward
Clinical Study from the Darkness
As I thought, it's too weak.
And there's not enough of it.
Even though I can be either sex, as either a woman or a man,
I who lack reproductive power must make use of this medicine, for the purpose of leaving behind an offspring.
The red pill makes it easy for a woman's body to conceive.
The blue pill increases a man's genitals.
While having responsibility for the supervision of this Special Ward,
I assembled beautiful nurses for the purposes of this experiment.
These four are particularly suited to become my juniors.
And so, the first experimental subject...
Ow-w-w...
Really.
Are you okay?
Thank you very much, Shuuni.
Shinohara-san, don't respond day after day to the sexual harassment of the patients.
Also, you like them too much.
I'm sorry.
Kaname-san, it's nice that your boobs are so big.
I've never had my breasts touched by any of the patients...
Being jealous of having your chest touched...
You're a strange girl.
Onee-chan, you just don't understand my worries!
Shinohara-san, I wonder if could you come with me?
Yes... um, me?
Yes.
All right.
Then, I'll be going.
Come with me, please.
Yes.
I have to take this?
It's an experimental drug, though it's more like a nutrient.
Experimental...? Will it be okay?
Do you think I'd make you take a dangerous medication?
No, it's not like that.
No need to worry. Being a nurse is a difficult job,
so I thought you might want to lay down your load for a little while.
Besides, you and I have the same shape, right?
I guess that's true.
I'm sorry for complaining.
Thank you very much.
Somehow, my body feels hot...
Sensei, my body's flushed, and it feels like my skin must be pink.
The aphrodisiac put in to make sexual intercourse smooth is beginning to work.
Let your body relax, and yield yourself to what is welling up in your heart.
S-sensei... what are you...
You've run out of energy, haven't you?
No, sensei, please let me go.
When seen like this, your chest is really impressive.
Of course the patients would be excited by this.
No, that's not... For even you to say that, sensei...
Huge breasts are heavy and embarrassing, and I actually hate them.
That's not so. They're quite lovely.
With boobs as big and indecent as this, anyone would get excited.
That's cruel, sensei!
Oh? But I'm praising you
S-sensei, the chest is off-limits...
My chest... my chest is...
Your chest is what?
My chest... I'm weak, it betrays me.
Shinohara-san's is weak to her chest.
No! It's embarrassing!
Shinohara-san, your breasts are soft and have a beautiful complexion.
Something's weird...
Somehow, today I'm feeling... more than usual...
"More than usual"? That must mean that you've felt good before when men have touched your breasts.
No, that's not it.
I've never been touched by a man, although the patients touch me often...
Well, then, you must mean when you touch and fondle your own breasts.
Shinohara-san, when you masturbate, how do you usually caress yourself?
Masturbate? I've never...
Come now. Shinohara-san, you don't masturbate?
That's... I mean...
It's fine, there's no need to be embarrassed.
It's something everyone does.
As a woman, you have sexual desire.
Your nipples...
Shinohara-san, your nipples are quite big.
No, they're... they're strange, my nipples.
They don't usually get this big.
Usually when they stand up they're smaller!
Is that so?
Then, this must be a side effect of the medication.
My nipples feel amazing!
They're tingling!
Shinohara-san, you're so cute.
Sensei...
I've always been watching you.
I can't hold it in any longer!
Sensei...!
I, too, am bigger than usual.
More than that, I'm experiencing immense stimulation.
Sensei, please stop!
What should we say about you being this wet?
Sensei, that's...
Your penis is entering me!
It's like sensei's penis is real!
How is it? Like the real thing?
Yes, but it's incredibly thick and big!
It's my first time like this!
It's being done to me, but it feels really good!
This is the first time I've thought having a penis inserted down there felt so good!
That sex can feel this good...!?
You're so tight, it feels so good!
I can feel everything!
Sensei, sensei, your thing is amazing!
The thick, long penis is hitting all the way inside.
I can feel it at the entrance to my uterus!
Sensei, my breasts, my breasts...
To the boobs of the giant-breasted nurse... I'll do this!
You... you have the predisposition to ejaculate breast milk?
No, that's not it...
I've... never had breast milk come out before!
I see. Having the breast milk come out must be a side effect of the medication.
But... it feels good.
To have milk come out... it's a pleasant feeling.
In that case...
Sensei, you're sucking on my breasts!
Sensei...
Sensei!
Sensei is drinking from my boobs... just like a baby...
Sensei...
Sensei's penis is going in...
If it goes any further, I...
It's fine, Shinohara-san. I'll make you have an orgasm with me.
Sensei... Sensei!!!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
To have this much breast milk come out like this...
That girl... let's have her join in the experiment from here on, too.
It's not just the appearance and disappearance of the erection,
the amount of semen created during ejaculation has also increased.
The blue pill seems to do this.
Don't tell me...
This is my period?
I've never ovulated before.
Does this mean my first menstruation has come?
Shinohara-san.
Shinohara-san, just now... um...
What... is it?
No, it's nothing, I'm sorry.
Um... then, I'll be...
I'm sorry!
Because it was the first, it seems it was light.
From here on, it's going to be fine.
Now, to start the next experiment.
Ah, sensei...
This specially opened hospital room... was there something you wanted to talk to me about?
About that...
Sensei?
Sensei, what are you doing?
It'll be all good things from here.
This... my body is so hot.
It seems to be quite effective.
You're not used to something like this, I wonder.
S-Sensei...
My body is... burning up... I...
I'm starting to burn up as well.
This is... a penis?
Why do you have a penis, sensei?
If you lick it, I'll be so good as to calm your burning body.
That's...
This is the first time you've smelled an erect penis, right?
How is it, the smell of my penis?
That's...
When the smell gets into me, my head spaces out.
I won't be satisfied unless I lick it!
Sensei's big and hard thing...
It's bitter and salty like beach water, a strange taste, but...
Delicious.
For your first time giving a blowjob, it's quite good.
Maybe you're a true slut.
Sensei...
Just licking it doesn't satisfy me...
Do me, please.
All right.
What's this?
Don't tell me...
This is...
a clitoris?
What... my clitoris... is this big?
Why?
Unusual clitoris erection.
Perhaps another side effect of the medication?
Sensei...
Sto- Please don't rub my clitoris!
This stimulation is embarrassing, a big clitoris like this.
It's too sensitive!
What to do... this size appears to be the limit.
Hitomi-san, your clitoris is fat and hot.
Sensei, your... my clitoris...
My clitoris is just like your...
If you do that... This is the first time time I've felt such a pleasant feeling...
This is the first time I've put my penis against a clitoris like this.
Sensei... sensei...
Sensei... rubbing me with her penis like this... I'm feeling it too much!
Hitomi-san, stroke me with your hand.
L-like this?
That's good!
Sensei!
My clitoris... if you do that... I... I...
Hitomi-san, it's fine.
It's just like a man masturbating.
Cum with my penis on your clitoris like this!
Se-sensei!
I'm also... cumming!
I accidentally came outside...
Sensei, I...
Although you came, your clitoris is still erect like this.
Mine is too.
Sensei...
The real thing starts now.
Sensei, this is the first time with someone I love...
It hurts... Sensei, how horrid...
My first time... like this...
I've just lost my virginity...
This is only the beginning.
Compared with what came before, from now on this is a real sexual experience.
My clitoris!
Hitomi-san, of course your insides are tight...
It's so slippery it feels amazing.
It's my first time, but I'm feeling it...
There's the pain of having my virginity taken,
but the pleasant feeling is so many times stronger!
Sensei!
Sensei! If you do it that strongly, my boobs...
You're not going to have breast milk come out, too, are you?
Of course not, I'm not pregnant.
And with men it's impossible.
Shinohara Kaname's giant breasts created milk.
Naruse Hitomi's clitoris became inflamed.
The medication's side effects differ based on their genetic make-up.
Sensei!
Cum!
I'll cum with you, this time inside!
Sensei! Sensei!
Something hot is coming inside!
This sensation... it could become a bad habit!
And it's still hard.
Aside from the experiment, I'll let you enjoy this.
Sensei... what are you...
I'm borrowing this clitoris-penis.
I'm taking your male virginity.
Se-sensei!
Doing it the natural way feels this good?
This is totally different from a penis or vibrator!
Sensei!
Sensei's insides are hot and wet,
it feels like it's squeezing me!
That's right, this is the inside of a woman.
Just a little while ago, I felt the same thing while inside of you.
Sensei, the inside of your vagina feels so good...
For me, too, your clitoris-penis feels so good.
Sensei!
It's been so long since I've had sex as a woman, I can totally feel it!
The pleasant feeling in my vagina... I'm going numb!
Sensei, sensei...
Sensei, your insides feel too good!
Hitomi-san, do your best, I'm almost there...
Hold off!
But, sensei, the inside of your vagina is squeezing me so tight!
My clitoris feels like it's being crushed!
I can't hold off, it feels too good...
Me, too, having a clitoris inside my vagina feels amazingly good!
I'm about to cum, Hitomi-san...
Sensei!
I'm cumming!
Sensei's semen...
Doing it just like a woman.
That was fun, wasn't it.
It's Takayama, Nakamura-sensei.
She's out after all.
Hm? What's this smell?
It smells like squid.
Sensei must have brought a man into here.
Th-this means...!