After two deadly earthquakes, society plunged into
a state of chaos fueled by a hallucinogenic drug
called "milk", which acts as an aphrodisiac putting
the user into a state of intense euphoria.
To bring down the manufacturing plant of an organization
behind the production of milk, special duty agent
Rei, along with her partner Fuko, went to investigate.
However, the two were captured.
Rei, who was injected with an extra strong dosage of milk,
was raped repeatedly by men of the organization...
But she did not give in...
Rei & Fuko, special duty agent
Vol.03 Fertilization Training of Betrayal
Yamase-san...
We can't go any further.
Don't worry, Anna.
Big sis will get you out of here for sure.
But we have to find Fuko before that.
Well? How does your lover's semen taste?
You can't hold back?
You're soaking wet.
Just a little longer, and you can give
your virginity to your fiancé.
Fuko-Oneechan, I have bad news for you.
What?
It's about Rei-Oneesama. She's run away with her little sister.
Leaving you behind.
She did?
Rei-Oneesama only used you to rescue her sister.
But that can't be...
That's why she left you behind.
Poor girl.
We'll comfort you now.
Your mouth must love the semen of your fiancé.
What's that?
It's super strong milk.
We'll inject it into your virgin clitoris
and give you a thrilling time.
Stop it!
I'll show you what your darling Rei-Oneesama really looks like.
So hot!
When you were in the basement, she was having fun by herself.
Rei-senpai...
Oh no!
Rei-san...
Why?
I want it! I want more! More!
Right there.
This feels great!
I don't care what happens to Fuko!
As long as it feels good for me!
Why... Rei-san...
Hurry! Hurry, I want it!
Just like that. Take me from behind.
Yes!
Yes, move faster!
I want it rough!
Twirl it around!
The... the egg inside of me... Get it out!
Why, Rei-san...
Why did you betray me?
Yes.
She betrayed you, Fuko-Oneechan.
And yes, she even went so far as to seduce your fiancé.
No, she probably even sucked his dick.
Ya-Yamase-san?
R-Rei-san...
No! No! Stop it, Rei-senpai!
No!
Stop it, Rei-senpai! Don't take my Yamase-san away from me!
Fuko-Oneechan, just forget about
Rei-Oneesama and have some fun.
Some fun?
We'll get revenge on Rei-Oneesama.
Revenge?
That's right. I promise that the chance to get revenge
on Rei-Oneesama will come in time, Fuko-Oneechan.
Revenge...
Rei-san... revenge...
But before that, it seems like Yamase-san
is going to take your virginity for you.
Not so roughly... I'll cum!
I'm cum... I'm cumming!
Yamase-san...
Not so much... it won't... fit into my womb!
Yamase-san... come to me.
Anna!
Did they impregnate you?
I promise I will save you.
What beautiful scenery, Yamase-san.
So suddenly?
Fuko-san.
It's so swollen. Does it hurt?
It's so hot, Yamase-san.
This is my first time, so I might not be very good.
Yamase-san, does it feel good?
I feel it throbbing inside my mouth.
I'll let you cum soon.
Though some is already coming out.
Cum, Yamase-san! Into my mouth!
Yamase-san, I drank your semen.
Yamase-san?
Fuko-san, I want to cum inside of you.
It's my first time. So be gentle.
Okay.
Wait!
From behind? How embarrassing.
Be... gentle, okay?
I'm cumming!
It hurts!
Oh no! Yamasersan, you're too big!
You're breaking me!
Be... be more gentle.
Please!
D-Don't stop... please!
Deeper... Go deeper inside of me.
Yamase-san... your penis...
It's moving inside... of me...
No!
It feels great.
Yes. Yes.
I'm cumming... I'm cumming...
I'm cumming!!
So hot.
Your semen is inside my uterus. So much...
Yes! No!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
So much is flowing inside!
So hot! It's so hot!
I hope you get pregnant, Fuko-Oneechan.
With that ugly beast's baby.
Rei-san?
I came to rescue you.
They came inside of you, Fuko?
You, let Fuko go!
Or do you want your hands ripped off?
We're leaving, Fuko.
What about Yamase-san?
Please go... Fuko...
I love you...
Hurry!
Yamase-san...
Koryuu-sama.
As expected from Rei-Oneesama.
Shall we capture her?
No need to.
Fuko-Oneechan is brainwashed.
But letting them escape without any fight?
I will have you take responsibility for this.
I'm sorry, Fuko.
I wish I could have saved you before
you were raped by that beast.
"That beast"? You think of Yamase-san that way?
I love you.
Rei-san...
What?
Fuko? Don't touch that!
Fuko! Why!?
Run for it, Fuko. Hurry!
Anna!
Welcome back, Rei-Oneesama.
Koryuu!
Fuko?
Good work, Fuko-Oneechan.
Fuko... Why?
You were the one to betray me first.
Betray?
Where's Yamase-san?
He's waiting.
Waiting for you, Fuko.
So that's what this is about.
Fuko, they've got you fooled!
What's this?
These little guys detect what makes you feel good and bore
themselves into various holes to give birth to eggs.
Disgusting...
You don't see any of them in Anna's tank, do you?
That's because they're all inside of her.
First, let's make you feel good.
Rei-Oneesama's pussy sure has had lots of stuff go into it.
Including your fiancé's penis, let's not forget.
It's a lie! Fuko!
I hope you get impregnated by those disgusting beasts!
Wake up, Rei-san.
You always get all the fun.
Fuko...
But I also wanna have fun and cum a lot.
Fuko?
Aren't you okay with anything as long as it's big?
How can you say that, Fuko?
S-Snap out of it!
I must feed the little beasts from before.
Get away, Fuko!
No. I wanna cum a lot too.
Rei-san, your pussy feels amazing!
Inside of me... Ah, it's biting me!
Fuko... Snap out of it!
Rei-san, you were using me all along!
You rescued your sister, took my Yamase-san
away from me, and had all the fun yourself!
If you really want it so much, then I'll give you my cum!
Fuko? N-Not there.
But you want all your holes in use.
No way!
See? You actually like it.
No, I don't!
That's right! You want to be filled with cum, don't you?
Don't!
It's hitting me. It's hitting me...
It feels great for me too!
So this is what it feels like to ejaculate!
I think something's coming.
It feels amazing!
It's coming!
Ejaculating sure feels great.
Rei-san, how gross.
She can't even capture Fuko-Oneechan when she's on drugs.
A useless bitch like you should at least lactate
for us. Then maybe you can redeem yourself.
You girls take a good look at this.
This is what happens to women who are
no longer useful to our organization.
I once had dreams, but after my failures, I just gave up.
ano koro no akogare tsumazuite wa akirameru dake
There wasn't a side of me that didn't have feelings that were too young.
osana sugita kanjou jibun nante nakute
And so time passed, and the more I cried, the more I understood.
sou shite toki nagarete naite wa wakatta bun dake
And I also learned to protect myself and those things I loved.
mamoru koto mo oboeta daiji na mono mo dekite
I'm sure I'm ignoring someone else's pain so that I can rise.
kitto dareka no itami o mushi shite nari tatteru
In a world that only knows how to take pride in oneself by shaming others.
kuraberu koto de shika kagayaku sube o shiranai sekai de
If you look up, you'll see the vast universe expanding before your eyes.
miagereba hora hiroi uchuu ga me no mae ni hirogaru no ni
But the rainclouds formed by your tears close up the path that leads to it.
kimi no namida ga tsukuru amagumo sono saki o tozashite shimau
But when you cry and the shadows look like they are about go disappear,
kimi ga naite sono kage ga kiesou ni naru toki ni wa
I will become the wind and reflect your heart.
boku wa sou kaze ni natte kimi no kokoro o utsushi dasu yo
I will stir up a storm.
arashi o okoshite