Oh...Yeah! You're amazing, Pisuke!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Ah... Ma-kun.
Ah... Ma-kun, Great! Awesome!
Pisuke, please! Be my boyfriend!
Yeah, OK.
No! Ma-kun, I... I'm your girlfriend, right?
Well... maybe...
Hey, sis! You bitch! You know Pisuke likes
me! We were childhood sweethearts.
Ouch...
No! Ma-kun is mine! Why don't
you just listen to your big sister?
Which one of us do YOU want?
Yeah! Which one?
What? Ah... well...
I'm sorry. But my heart already
belongs to someone else.
W... What do you mean by that?
I can't believe it! Who?!
She's... Well... When I was kid...
I hurt myself and was crying. This nice
girl came over and took care of me.
That woman...
I want to see her again and tell
her how I really felt at that time.
Oh! Pisuke, that was me! You're talking about
me! Alright, it's decided. I'm your girlfriend.
Ah... this is great!
Oh! Pisuke, that was me! You're talking about
me! Alright, it's decided. I'm your girlfriend.
You liar! That was really
me! Me! Right, Ma-kun?
Oh, this is great too!
You liar! That was really
me! Me! Right, Ma-kun?
Me!
NO! Me!
Choose one of us!
Now!
Umm... I don't know. I
really don't know which...
I can't remember what she looked like! !
Nooooo! Pisuke! Ma-kun! ! You idiot!
Thank you!
C'mon... think about it.
How can you find her if you don't remember
what she looks like? It's hopeless!
You're right. But if I see her again...
...I think I'd recognize her.
I'd just be able to... sense it.
If not, I'll just ask her...
Ask her what?! Excuse me, are
you the girl from that time?
Yeah.
What a pain in the ass!
You'd just be better off screwing
around with someone you know.
N...no! Something like this only
happens once in a lifetime!
I want to make sure that when I lose my
virginity, I feel something extra special!
Well, I can kinda understand
why you're nervous about it.
Yuya...
What?
I think you used the word
''nervous'' incorrectly.
Really!?
MITARAI KADOHIKO MASAZO.
Dad... What's going on?
My son! I'd like to introduce you
to a young lady who's come to
our house to study martial arts.
She's the daughter of a
friend of mine in America.
Please welcome.. Sha Fong Lee!
I'm Sha Fong Lee! Nice to meet you.
Uh... Hi.
Check out my body too!
I came to Japan to study martial arts.
I want to improve my skills by learning from
a true master, your father, Mitarai-sensei.
Wh... what pretty eyes she has. I've never
met anyone with such beautiful eyes before.
Fong Lee came to visit us once
before when she was a kid.
Masahiko, do you remember?
What? No, I don't...
I think I remember us all
taking a picture together.
Really?
Yes. I remember we used to play
together when we were young.
Really? I don't remember.
But that means she could
be the girl from that time...
Excuse me...
What?
I assume that you've been
studying karate too, right?
Huh?
He's not his father's son. He
doesn't listen to anything I say.
I want him to take over the
Dojo when I'm older but...
Dad... I don't wanna hear this...
I know, but...
I see.
Hello, Masahiko!
Oh! Hello, Kyoko!
Masahiko, where's your father?
At the Dojo.
At this time?
Yeah... for a bit.
The Crotch Breaker!
Not yet! Let's do it again. Defensive stance!
Yes!
Really? All the way from America?
Yes. But after I told her I have no
interest in karate, her attitude changed.
I guess she only likes strong men.
Is she pretty?
Yeah, she is.
Masahiko, I made you a Chinese
feast. It has all your favorites. Eat up!
How is it, Masahiko? Good?
Yes! Yummy! Yummy!
Fong Lee's so happy!
WOW! I'm going to have you for dessert!
Masahiko. No! No! That's not a good idea.
Are you sure?
Well... Alright!
YEAH!
Oh, you're here, Kyoko.
I guess you've already heard from Masahiko.
This is Fong Lee. She's started training here.
I'm Sha Fong Lee. Nice to meet you.
I am Kyoko Saeki.
Oh, you're making dinner? Don't bother.
I'll make dinner as thanks for training me.
I make pretty good Chinese.
Please give it a try.
Ah... I... I usually make...
No, please. I'm staying here for free.
I should at least help out with
something around the house.
You're a guest. Please have a seat and relax.
G...guest...?
Silence...
CAFE SALLY
Welcome!
What? You guys?!
What do you mean by that?
We're customers. You work here
and that's why we came. As friends.
Alright. Alright.
Oh, how fun! Are these your friends?
Ah! Mitsuko! Well, he... hello!
Oh! Hello!
What the...?
What's the matter?
Stay and enjoy yourselves!
Th... thank you. I will.
What's going on?
Whatever. Sit down.
SKI RESORTS AND SPAS
CHEAP SKI VACATIONS
Well, that's it! I'll call the
travel agency tomorrow.
I'll pay for it up front. You
just pay me back later.
Alright!
I need to use the ladies' room.
Ma-sa-hi-ko!
What's up? You're acting all weird today.
I'm gonna change the subject here.
Where's Mitsuko?
She's taking a break in the back...
Good. I'm telling this to you and you only.
Have you heard that rumor
about the slut in Tsukinode Park?
Huh?
She attacked me yesterday.
I finally lost my virginity!
What?!
Listen, here's what happened...
Someone... Come here...
Someone...
What? I heard a voice...
Umm... Someone... Come here...
No mistaking it.
Sounds like someone needs help but...
That sweet soprano voice... so
inviting, asking me to come.
Someone...
There!
Woo, Hoo! I'm coming! I'm coming!
On my way! Yuya is all yours.
I'm Yuya. I'm on the way!
Is something wrong, miss?
Ahh... Quickly! Quickly! Rape me!
Here. Fuck me here with your big cock!
I want you to rape me like a madman!
C... Can I? Really?
Ah...! More! More!
Drive in deeper! Do it harder!
L...like this?
Ah... yes! That's good! Just like that!
Awesome! It feels like my dick is melting!
Ah... This is great! Great! You're amazing!
Really? I'm happy to hear that!
I feel a big a one coming on...
Ah... I can't hold this anymore. I'm coming!
It's OK. Let it go! Inside me. Come inside me!
Are you sure? I'm gonna come!
Ah... Me too! I'm gonna
come too. I am coming!
Ah... OH, YEAH!
WOW! Awesome!
You wanna do it again?
What?! You're still young! You can do it!
See! You're getting hard again.
If you keep that up, I'm gonna come again!
What? You're gonna come again?
That's fine. Do it right here!
Ah... Wait! Here I...
Awesome! This is your second time,
but look at how much you came.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
More! More! Pleasure me more!
I'm not letting you go yet.
What a horny bitch!
Are you sure it was really Mitsuko?
Yes, I'm sure. It was her.
I guess it's sexual frustration as her
husband's out of town on business.
My first sexual experience
and I came eight times!
It can't be! Mitsuko's not some tramp who
stalks virgin boys in the park at night.
It could be...
Huh? What's going on?
Nothing. Nothing.
OK. See you later!
See ya!
Don't forget the money!
You should go for it! Go for it!
What's that mean? Go for what?
Hmm... What's what mean?
Must be something dirty, I bet.
Now I'm worried.
Whoa! Mitsuko! How long
have you been standing there?
I've been here for a while.
Why are you so scared?
N... nothing. Well...
I envy students. You guys always
look like you're having a good time.
And what were you planning today?
Ah... we're planning to go
skiing this winter break.
So today we were working out the details.
WOW! I feel something touching me...
W... we... should have some kind of
fun. Otherwise... we ca... can 't study.
Study?
W... we'll get discouraged to... study.
Are you open?
Welcome! Please have a seat over there.
OK...
He saved me.
Gods... I am a bad man.
Deep in my heart, I still hold
dear the memory of that girl.
But I almost fell victim to
Mitsuko's erotic attack.
Of all the people. She's my
boss AND she's married!
I'm not like that. But... I'm going crazy!
Driven crazy by the girl in my heart.
I won't yield to temptation.
I'll forge an indomitable will and I'll
catch that shooting star someday.
Until then, please protect my spirit.
You are really applying yourself!
Huh?
Oh... Hello, Rei.
What's wrong? You don't look so good.
Well... that's because my spirit is unclean.
I'm here cleansing my soul.
I see... That's very good for you.
Work hard and it will pay off in the end.
That's some really welcome advice.
And in a beautiful figure!
Nanmaida. Nanmaida.
Stop it. Stop it. You
shouldn't be praying to me.
Thank you. Thank you.
What.. What's the matter?
My head... hurts. Feels like bursting!
I feel a ghost... There's an evil spirit near here.
Get away from me... now!
A ghost!? Are you joking?
YIKES! You're serious!
Noooo! It's eyes are glowing!
I'm getting so horny...
Why?!
How pathetic! Here you are
shaking... just from this.
You must be hungry for the touch of a woman!
Oh... Rei. N...no!
I've never thought I get this
kind of attention at a temple.
How awesome!
Ah... this is really great!
NO! My dick feels like it's overloading!
I can do this. Hold on! I can do this...
You're doing really well. How about this?!
I wonder how long you can take this?
Oh... Awesome! My dick can't handle it!
Good! Keep it up! You're my kind of man!
Enjoy the mysterious ways of a woman's body!
What an outrageous ghost this is!
There! There! There!
Please! Stop!
How are you doing? Still want to bow out?
No matter how strong you
are, it's only a matter of time!
Give it up! Let it all spill out!
There! There! There!
Umm... I can take this! I have the
girl from the past in my heart.
There! There! There!
I'm coming. I'm coming!
I came. I came.
You're a boy with a good heart...
Huh?
Thank you.
With your help, I've exorcised the ghost...
...which has been haunting me for so long.
I can now finally make
my way into the heavens!
What the hell?!
Thank you and good bye. I will
never forget your kindness.
I wish you a long and prosperous life.
What? You're leaving me like this?!
Whatever! Who the hell are you!?
Rei?
Oh, Masahiko? What happened to me?
And you! Why are you here?
What happened!? A ghost
got into you and we...
Ghost? Well... I can't remember anything...
Oh... OK! Whatever...
Yeah. Come in.
Time for a break.
Thanks, sis!
Getting ready for the test?
Well... we'll see what happens. Cake time.
What's wrong?
Nothing... special.
Really? Did something
happen at Pisuke's house?
Noth... nothing like that!
You're upset! I hit the nail on the head!
Now you don't wanna talk?
I feel like a retired businessman who doesn't
know what to do with the rest of his life.
What's that mean?
I told you about that Chinese girl
who's staying with the Mitarai's, right?
She's cooking for them and cleaning the
house. Doing what used to be my job.
It feels like there's no longer
any place for me in their house.
That's not a bad thing. Think about it.
Now you can use that time for yourself.
That would be good for you, no?
But...
Or is there some other
reason you go to their house?
Do you like Pisuke... or his father?
N...No! It's just they're both men
and I thought they needed help.
Sister...
Huh?
You know I've liked Pisuke since I was kid.
If anything ever happened
between you and Pisuke...
I'd never forgive you.
even if you are my sister.
You got it?
It will be morning soon in America.
Mom, Dad... are you having sweet dreams?
My training here has been very productive.
Check it out!
WOW!
Hey, little lady! Are you alone?
You are pretty cute!
Do you wanna come have a little fun with us?
Idiots! With your ugly faces! Get out of here!
Huh? What?
Do you really think you
can speak like that to us?
You may be a woman, but we don't
treat females with any respect.
You'll regret this!
Huh? Isn't that the girl
who lives with Masahiko?
Let's do this.
Hmph! That was amusing!
Maybe now you'll think twice
before disrespecting women again.
You scum! You don't fight fair.
You know that's right. I never fight fair,
and now I'm going to get a piece of you.
Let's do this.
Are you sure it was Fong Lee?
Yeah! I'm positive.
Damn it! I'd think Fong Lee could
handle something like this but...
Hey! Hey! Nice tits!
The real deal. A firm, trained body!
Time to have some fun!
Brother! Her nipples are getting hard!
She's excited. She's the kind of
girl who likes it rough like this.
Really?!
S... Stop it! Stop!
You guys! That's enough!
What the...?
M...Masahiko! Stop! You can't beat them!
Even if that's the case...
I have to try and save you, Fong Lee!
Masahiko!
Let's do this!
I did it!
Masahiko, you did it! I really don't know
what happened, but that was so cool!
Take care now!
Thanks, Yuya!
Thank you.
I... have to apologize Masahiko...
What?
I've treated you like a jerk.
As soon as I heard you don't practice karate...
I thought you were just some helpless wimp.
I'm sorry.
It's alright. I really don't care.
You're really pretty strong.
You really don't practice karate?
No, not now. But I learned a lot
from my father when I was younger.
But I never took it very seriously.
Masahiko, thank you for saving me.
Anyone would have done the same thing.
Especially for a cute girl like you, Fong Lee!
Thank you...
After that, Fong Lee and I got along great.
And I started going to the Dojo again.
I wonder why?
I used to hate training, but ever since
I started to train with Fong Lee...
I don't know why but I'm enjoying it.
My heart beats wildly, every time I think
that that girl I've been looking for...
...might be Fong Lee.
Dad?
Fong Lee, you're beautiful.
Ah... Masahiko, it feels so good.
I'm melting with your touch.
N...no! I'm embarrassed!
Don't be. No one's watching. Just you and me.
You're all wet, Fong Lee. This
is great. How does it feel?
No! Don't tease me!
NO! Ah, it feels good! Masahiko.. I am coming!
Put it in me, Masahiko. Fuck me!
Yes! There! It feels so great!
Deeper. Deeper. Fuck me harder.
Ah... I feel it so deep inside me.
How's that? You like it like that?
Yes... More! More!
Wow! My entire body feels like it's on fire!
Ah... Fong Lee. This is
amazing! You're the best!
Ah... Masahiko. I'm going to... I'm going to...
Oh... Fong Lee. Are you
ready? Let's come together.
Fong Lee... You're awesome!
Fong Lee went back to America!?
Yeah. So we'll take turns cooking
for the rest of the month.
And since I'm making breakfast
this morning, you'll cook dinner!
Forget that. Why?
Why did Fong Lee go back to America?
I don't know. I guess she had her reasons.
I think I can understand her,
being a martial artist myself...
She can't just...
She didn't even say anything
to me before she left.
That's not fair!
She said her flight leaves at noon.
She's probably still in the airport lobby.
Why don't you go ask her?
Excuse me! Don't you know
a shortcut or something?
No. I just moved here from the country.
I don't know the roads
very well just yet. Sorry.
Be careful, young man!
Fong Lee, why are you leaving me?
You might be that girl
who I've been looking for.
I don't think this is just a
coincidence. I had that dream...
Masahiko...
Why? We were getting along so well.
I want to keep on studying karate with you.
Masahiko, as you've studied karate,
I think you kind of understand why.
I want to compete against
you in the future someday.
For that reason, we can't
train at the same Dojo.
Masahiko...
For now, we have to train
separately and wait for the day...
we will meet again... in competition.
I don't like it!
There's no need to practice separately,
even if we will be rivals one day.
I'm a woman.
If I love someone, I can't
fight with that person.
No! We've known each other since we
were kids. What's the problem now?
There's no difference.
Fong Lee, do you remember that day
that summer, when we were still young?
You were wearing a straw hat at the time.
I fell down and you gave me
your hand and helped me up.
I need you now, just like I did that day!
Masahiko, you really love that girl, don't you?
What?
I've never once worn a straw hat.
It wasn't Fong Lee.
She's not the girl I've been looking for.
Goodbye, Masahiko. It was so nice to see you.
I'm a bit jealous of this girl you still dream of.
So the search begins again.
Who was that girl?
I wonder when I'll be able to find her...