FINAL EXAM
LAST DAY
It's over! It's over!
Now all we have to do is
wait for winter vacation!
I can't wait for our ski trip!
Well, Asuka's coming...
...but Kyoko is going too!
I absolutely LOVE older women!
Just what are you expecting?
That kid?
Must be him...
Cool!
Yuya... I've become
famous, all because of you.
Cool!
Yuya... I've become
famous, all because of you.
It'll be fine. I didn't say
anything bad about you.
It's all true.
It just...
That kid kicked those perverts asses.
...gets tiring.
I heard it was over in just a few seconds!
He's so cool!
Mitarai...
He is the kind of guy I've been looking for.
Pisuke!
How long are you gonna hang out here?
The movie's gonna start soon!
FINAL EXAMS ARE OVER! WELCOME TO
OUR EIGHTH ANNUAL FILM FESTIVAL
Huh?
Who are you?
Quiet! You're too loud!
I am Aoi Tsutsuse, a junior in Class B.
After I heard about your heroics, I decided
that I'm going to be your girlfriend.
What are you talking about?
I don't know anything about...
What a lucky girl I am...
touching the famous Mitarai's cock like this.
Hold on! Don't!
Masahiko, why are you squirming like that?
It's nothing. Nothing.
Does it feel good?
Stop this now!
If you'll be my boyfriend, I'll stop.
N... no. I won't...
Oh, is that so?
AUDIO-VISUAL ROOM
Don't follow me!
Mitarai!
Wait!
No! I won't wait for you...NO!
He's really become pretty
popular around here.
He should thank me for this!
I'm home!
ASUKA
What?
I bought cakes at Fran Belge. Let's have tea.
Later.
Did something happen at school?
Nothing...
Did you get into a fight with Masahiko?
I said nothing happened!
OK.
That would make me... happy.
He's a pretty popular guy.
Pisuke!
I love you, I love you.
Pisuke, me too. Me too!
Wow! You've got a great pussy, Asuka!
Pisuke! Pisuke!
Pisuke, I want you to feel good too.
Pisuke's inside me!
Pisuke! I love you! I love you!
Let's come together! Pisuke. Pisuke!
This can't continue like this.
Nothing will happen unless
I tell him how I feel.
Kaku?
Here.
Saito?
Miura?
Here.
Mitarai?
Mr. Mitarai?
Yes...?
Mitarai...
Please come see me after school.
What? I didn't cheat on the test.
I need to talk to you.
OK.
Excuse me.
Huh? Miss Hanako's not here.
She's the one who asked
me to come. Oh, well...
Miss... Hanako...
Oh, you're awake?!
What are you doing?
I just need a little sperm sample.
Sperm sample?
I am collecting sperm from
people with excellent genes.
You scored the highest on the last test.
I thought that exam was pretty hard, so...
That's why I'm doing this.
What are you thinking?
It won't come out easily...
and my hands are tired.
Guess I'll have to do this.
First Aoi and now Miss Hanako...
Why are they trying to take away my virginity,
which I'm saving for that special girl?
These must be the skills of an expert.
No matter how strong my will...
...my body is still very honest.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
What?!
Are you nuts?
I haven't even had a chance at any
more sex since that first home run I hit.
If we could, I'd gladly switch places with you.
Please do! ! Why are you always so lucky?!
Miss Hanako was a one time thing. But
you should seriously think about Aoi.
I don't need a stalker like her.
I have a girl already, here in my heart.
Hello.
Hello, Kyoko! How are you?
What's going on?
He's got a date.
A date?
He met this woman at some dating club.
Hey, I'm a single guy. I can have
one or two girlfriends, can't I?
You're right. It has been a while
since your wife passed away.
Good for you.
Thank you.
So, what's she like?
She's very pure and beautiful. It's hard
to find a woman like that these days.
Kind of like the friendship Bruiser
Brody and Stan Hansen have.
The point being... I'm deeply in love! !
Masahiko, she might be your new mother.
I'll bring her home soon
so be ready to meet her.
My father has a girlfriend. But me...
I'm still stuck with the memory of that girl.
Having dinner here alone...
Kyoko?
It's lonely eating by myself,
so have dinner with me?
Okay?
If anything ever happened
between you and Pisuke...
I'd never forgive you,
even if you are my sister.
Sorry, but Asuka's waiting for me.
That's right.
Kyoko could be that woman...
Kyoko's very weak though...
She's never gone outside
wearing a straw hat.
Mitarai!
You again?!
Mitarai! I don't get it.
My answer's still the same.
You can keep asking me, but I
don't have any feelings for you!
How awful!
Awful! You don't have to put it that way.
I just love you!
What? Ah... This is... I mean...
I... I mean...
I am not saying that I hate
you or anything like that.
I just don't think of you as my girlfriend.
You understand?
I'm shocked.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
I have one last favor to ask though.
Do one thing for me?
OK. If it's something I can do.
It's easy. Just turn around
and stand over there.
OK.
Is this good?
Yes. Stand there just like that.
OK. OK.
Hello? How long do I...?
Aoi...?
Aoi? What are you doing?
You know what I'm doing. I'm masturbating.
Masturbating?! But why?
If I can't be your girlfriend,
I can't have sex with you.
So, I'm getting off just looking at you.
What?
Mitarai... I love you. I love you so much.
Aoi, what are you going to
do if someone comes in?
I'm fine with that. Or would you like
to do me somewhere else instead?
Th... that...
You dumped me.
So this is the only way I can do it with you.
Ah... Mitarai. Mitarai.
I love you. I love you.
Mitarai, come here. Come here!
I can't control myself.
Ah... Mitarai... I'm so happy now.
Ah... That feels so good.
Mitarai! More! More! Lick me harder.
I'm happy to see you getting this hard.
Mitarai, I want you! I want you in me!
What? You're not hard anymore.
Hey...Mitarai?
I'm sorry. I just can't do it.
Mitarai...
Huh?
What am I doing?
I'm home.
Huh? Nobody's home.
MITO KOMON
He's hopeless. Always leaving the TV on.
That's weird... My father never
misses a MITO KOMON rerun.
Maybe it's a thief.
Miss... Miss Hanako?!
How's that? That feel good?
Great! !
How about this?
That's good too!
I don't believe it. His girlfriend is...
I won't allow you to come alone.
Yes, ma'am!
Hmph! What's so ''pure'' about her?
But they look...
...very happy.
Maybe my memory's playing tricks on me.
Maybe there really is no ideal woman for me.
Looking for her is like finding
a needle in a haystack.
I'll be better off just enjoying myself now.
How great is this?!
Yeah!
Sis!
So, you wanna go?
Yup.
Hey!
Wait for me!
Are you tired?
Yes, a little.
I haven't traveled in a while. How about you?
Not at all!
Such energy! You were skiing all day too.
I'm still young... not like you!
Hey!
You should go to bed.
I'm going to Pisuke's room for a bit.
We've been waiting. Come on in.
What's wrong?
You look depressed.
No, I'm fine. I'm good to go.
Alright... but I feel bad for Kyoko.
We know how weak she is,
but we still asked her to come with us.
I don't think you need to worry.
She likes to watch other people having fun.
Yeah. Is that so?
I have to tell him otherwise...
...nothing will ever happen.
So what did you want to tell me?
Hey, it's kind of hot in here.
You wanna go outside?
What?
Come on!
Wait a sec!
They're still out there!?
What are they doing?
It's really cold out here.
Let's go back inside.
No!
NO!
Asuka?
What's wrong?
Please stay and listen to me.
I... I...
I love you, Pisuke.
It's not friendship or some crush.
I love Pisuke!
You may think it's too late for this now...
...but I want you to think
of me as your girlfriend.
I understand.
I'll think about it.
I have to be honest with you though.
There is this other girl in my life.
That's why you can't give me an answer?
Sorry.
That's alright. We've been
friends for a long time now.
I don't think anything will
change right away anyway.
But do I know this girl you like?
I don't even know who she is.
What do you mean?
I was still kid at that time.
I got hurt and was crying.
The only thing I can clearly remember are
her very white hands and a straw hat.
I've begun to think that she
never even existed though.
So I've decided to give up on her.
Your confession opened my eyes.
I'm going to forget all about
that girl starting today.
It was my sister.
That girl was my sister.
Pisuke, the girl you've been
searching for is Kyoko Saeki.
That's not true! Kyoko's very weak.
...and she couldn't play outside
with us on those hot summer days.
That day... that one day...
she put on a straw hat and played with us.
The next day she came down with a fever
and wasn't allowed to play outside anymore.
That's...
I've known it all along.
Huh?
My sister loves you too.
I've been so stubborn, saying I loved you first.
You two truly love each other,
so I can't stand in your way.
Both you and my sister
are so important to me.
I want you two to be happy.
Asuka...
Now go see my sister.
Please, Pisuke!
Masahiko!
The woman I've been searching for is Kyoko!
It's you!
Am I dreaming?
I've been waiting for this day for a long time.
The day I'll finally make love
to the girl I've longed for.
I realized something too.
What?
I've been waiting for this
day to make love to you.
Kyoko... you smell good.
That tickles... It feels strange...
How's this?
Yes. That feels good.
You're so hard.
That means I getting turned on.
I'm glad.
I never expected you to be doing this to me.
Kyoko...
I'll do it to you next.
No, I'm shy. Not down there!
No. Ah... No!
Look, Kyoko.
I'm so embarrassed...
I'm gonna put it in now.
Does it hurt?
N...no. We're finally together as one.
I'm hot... So hot! My body's burning
up inside! It doesn't hurt anymore.
That's good.
Are you getting off, Masahiko?
It feels awesome. All
because I'm inside of you.
I'm so happy.
I feel strange... It feels good. It feels so good.
I'm gonna make you feel even better.
Good. That's good. That feels great!
Oh, yeah. Good. Keep going!
Your dick is so far in me!
Touching me so deep inside!
Kyoko, this feels wonderful! Just awesome!
Me too. Me too.
This is fantastic! My body
feels like it's melting!
I'm gonna come. Here I come!
Come... Come with me!
Yes!
This is how I finally ended up with the girl
I had been searching for my whole life.
Kyoko is the most wonderful
woman in the world to me.