And I think I did entrust you to allow me the rights of inheritance and all the responsibilities of being the chief priest...
M-Master...
Just continue like that...
So the target is a police officer this time, right?
Yes!
I'm Deputy Police Chief...
Kurubayashi... Aya...
Fine, I'll do it!
You're doing great!
M-Master!!
I... I'm...
Going to... going to...
We should head back soon.
Sure...
Sae's secret?
Tony's Heroine Series: Kanojo wa Hanayome Kouhosei? Cinderella Collection
Presented by Masurenai-Fansubs & biohrd
I'm back!
We have returned.
Sae, I bought you a cake.
Zero's room.
You shouldn't peep without permission.
Umm...
Jeez...
"You shouldn't peep without permission"
is properly written there, isn't it?
I'm sorry, I thought I should
clean the place up a bit.
After I opened the wardrobe...
Well then, I have things to pack. I shall excuse myself.
Well then.
Jeez...
It's because...
I guess, it looked good on you though.
Huh?
Umm... It's nothing!
Eat the cake already!
Thank you for the cake!
Hey...
Yeah?
Shinji, do you like that kind of clothings?
N-No!
I see...
I guess I'll get some advice from Zero-chan next time.
A-Anything but that! I begging you!
W-What the?!
Master, because of work, I'm arresting you to come along with me.
Shinji, you've shifted to a different employment agency already?
I... I guess so...
I'm Kurubayashi Aya.
You got my back, okay?
G-Gotcha!
You're late.
Hurry up and get into the car.
Sure thing!
Didn't know you're a hottie. You surprised me.
Oh my, is that a compliment? Thanks.
So, what do you want me to cooperate with?
I wanted become a detective, rather than be a police inspector.
What's that got to do with me?
A few days ago, I heard from a known source...
Then...
I'm thinking of accompanying you to wreck an illegal transaction.
Besides, it's really convenient to have you who's also an ex-police detective.
Oh, an illegal transaction crime scene...
Heh, what?!
Your blood of being an ex-police detective is dying for some action, right?
Fine, in return for helping you out,
after the work, I'll ask you out this once.
Oh my, am I good enough for you?
Sounds good, if we hinder the transaction.
There are goons standing on guard.
Leave this to me.
W-Who the fuck are you?!
Hey, hurry up and let's go!
How brutal...
How's this...
Let's rushing in and subduing them together?
No, it's gonna be bad if we mess up.
It's better to observe a little longer.
If only Zero was here now...
Gotchu!
Aya-san!
Hold it.
Don't cha dare move.
You caught the bait well.
This one is jackpot.
Quit staring like idiots and let's start with her.
Wha-What are you guys planning to do?
Take that!
Aya-san...
Aya-san, get a hold of yourself!
Aya-san!
Shinji-kun?
Where's this place?
I see... We got busted!
My bad... It's my fault...
No...
It's coz I let down my guard.
Plus, I made us rush things so I can get the credit for myself.
Anyway, let's think of a way to get out of here.
Damn it, it won't open!
I'm sorry, it's my fault that we're in this situation.
What are you saying?! You ain't being yourself!
It's coz...
We're toasted!
We're dead meat in this joint!
Shinji-kun...
Once we give up, it's game over!
You mustn't give up hope till the very end!
There are things I still have to do, and there's also someone waiting for me to come back home.
That's why we shouldn't give up!
You're such a diehard!
The skin on Ririya's palms feels good, but...
Once in awhile, the skin of a real girl feels just as good too.
As I thought, this shit can't beat the real thing.
Ya got that right!
How 'bout we make 'em squeal?
Who the fuck are you this time?!
Cu... Ya kinda cute though...
Don't, I'm really weak right there...
Amazing, you're overflowing non-stop.
D-Don't say such things...
No!
I love it!
Amazing!!
More...
More! Make me feel good!!
I want more!!!
I want it...
Hey, I want your thing.
Put it in, put it in...
Put it in already!!
It's finally in!
So good...
More! Fuck me more! Fuck me more!!
Good... It's so good! It's fucking really good!
Don't... Don't! No more!
Good, it feel so fucking good!
I'm about to cum! I'm cumming!!
I'M CUMMING!!!
Who's there?!
Master, I've come to fetch you.
Zero...
I apologize for my late arrival.
My entrance was late due to the annihilation of the organization.
I also brought some change of clothes.
Thanks a bunch!
It was just shown in the news,
but there was a female police officer who single-handedly beat up an entire fugitive organization.
Oh, is that so?
Sae, tonight let's do it...
Shinji, I agree...
Shinji!
This burn...
Yeah...
I got it when the orphanage was caught on fire, and you protected me.
Sae...
W-What do you want me to do?
Lick it gently.
S-Sae...
Sae, I'm... about to...
What the hell?!
Sh-Shinji!
What's happening?! What's happening?!
Master, it's our next job.
Higashi Asoubara Shinji,
The above mentioned person
is appointed as a
dispatched priest
at the Besho
Shinto Shine.
Master...
Just like that!
Just continue like that!
This time it's a shrine maiden, right?
Y-Yes!! The target is Shimuda Satomi!
She's the shrine maiden of Besho Shrine.
L-Last month, her foster father and her foster sister died in a traffic accident making her the shrine maiden.
Is she the only one left?
Fine! I'll do it too!
This job, that job...
They always interfere when I'm feeling it good with Sae!
P-Please forgive me!
I-I'm just doing my duty!
I-I'm about to!!
Shinji...
Master.
I apologize for being late.
Sure, thanks for your hard work.
What's this?
What's the matter, Master?
The offering festival will be held here three days later.
Today everyone went to the city to buy goods.
No wonder, even when the stalls are already set up, there's no one manning them.
You're...
I see. You're...
I'm Shimuda Satomi.
Please take care of me for this occasion.
No, please take care of me as well.
So you are acting in place of the head priest who passed away?
No, I don't have the requirements.
Requirements?
Also, I think I've already entrusted you the rights of inheriting all the responsibilities of the head priest...
You entrusted me...
Of course, we were dispatched for that soul reason.
Well then, I have some prepare to attend to.
Please wait in the shrine office at the back.
Hey, is this time's target really that girl?
Yeah, come over here when you have finished with your errands. See you later, Sae.
Damn that Zero...
Where did she go leaving behind her master?
Stop it, I beg you...
Please, stop it...
What's happening?
Stop it please!
I beg you!
You thought I didn't know?
I-If you do that...
Are you reminiscing your dead sister?
T-That's...
You had this kind of a relationship with your dead sister, right?
That's because...
My sister did it against my will...
It must be lonely being alone, right?
Being alone...
Although you say it was against your will,
this place of yours has already become this wet.
No... Stop it, please stop it...
Don't!
To think this place is starting to have such pleasure...
Saying that your sister did it against your will was a lie, right?
You're wrong!
I really was...
I really was forced against my will!
Then, let me do what I please.
If... If you continue to do that...
I...
How was it? Did it feel good when your sister did this to you?
It felt good...
So it was a lie that you were forced against your will, right?
You loved your sister dearly, right?
Yes, I loved my sister...
Being... Being embraced by my sister...
Made me really happy...
I-I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!!
Master, I've finished the preparations.
I was an abandoned child.
When I was abandoned at the shrine,
I was adopted by my foster father.
I was raised up by him.
I'm also alone.
When I was also young, my parents died in an accident.
It's the same as you.
But, as you can see, my body has already been soiled.
I can't replace my foster father.
That's not true.
You good the way you are.
That's a lie.
N-No!
No...
This posture... is really embarrassing...
N-No...
Not there...
Don't...
N-No...
Not there too...
D-Dont...
Don't do it...
No...
T-The feeling is too much...
NOOOO!!
No more...
It's strange...
I'm becoming strange!
I'm putting it in.
You're so beautiful. Have more confidence.
I will! I will, so...
You want it to be more intense, right?
Yes... I beg you...
Yes!
Yes!!
Good!
So good!!
It feels good!!
It's so intense!!
Good!
So good!
It's so good!!
A-Amazing! It feels really amazing!!
I'm...
I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum!!
Sa-Satomi...
IS GOING TO CUM!!!
It didn't appear, huh...
Apricot food
The head priest here is pretty cute, isn't she?
Huh? Oh, I guess...
Shinji, where the hell are you looking at?!
THAT HURTS!!!!!!
Ichijou
Come to think of it, Shinji.
That night, you were working with Zero-chan, weren't you?
Yeah! Right, right! It's just work.
Is it true?
Don't tell me you prefer Zero-chan more than me?
D-Don't say stupid things!
I only...
I only, what?
Lo.... Love...
Master, we have work.
You again...