It wasn't there, huh...
I'm going to cum...
It didn't appear, huh...
I'm cumming!
It wasn't her too, huh...
If you've wondering why I have so many nice meetings...
Master, we got our next job request.
It's because of this girl's...
ACT-1   I saw Zero.
Tony's Heroine Series: Kanojo wa Hanayome Kouhosei? Cinderella Collection
Sae?
Oh?
Was it my imagination?
Master.
Who are you?
I'm Zero, pleased to meet you.
Eh? Are you saying that my father is the only son of a millionaire...
and my grandfather decided to have me inherit the family business?
Even if I know that, it's difficult for me to accept it.
Both of my parents died in an accident when I was young, so I grew up in an orphanage.
Even if you say that now, I also have my own life.
I can't just say "Oh, I see".
I understand what Master is trying to tell me.
But Ichijou-sama won't change his decision once he has made it.
How can that be, that's unreasonable!
Also, I've already decided to marry my childhood friend, Sae.
That will definitely not happen.
Don't joke with me!
There is a way to solve it.
Eh?
Ichijou-sama said that if you can find a girl with a flower shaped birthmark on her neck,
he can grant you your freedom.
If he wants to find someone, why doesn't he just do it himself?
He's rich anyway, he'll be able to find many girls with that birthmark.
To find that girl, you must have the girl cum during sex.
He can just employ those hosts or AV guys to do that.
That birthmark will only appear when the girl is having sex
with the male of Ichijou-sama's bloodline.
Then, Grandpa can...
He can't, I guess...
Yes.
Then it has to be me?
But it's not gonna be easy to be able to do it just like that.
If it's about that, let me take ca-
Shinji, are you there?
Shinji!
Eh, who are you?
Err, no... about tha-
How do you do? I'm Master's cousin, Zero.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm asked to help Master through his relatives.
For the time being, I'll come by frequently and trouble them.
Then, I shall excuse myself for the moment.
Err umm...
About the discussion just now, I'll personally give you a detailed explanation later.
Eh, she disappeared.
What did she call you Master? Is she really your cousin?
It's true. She's just a bit weird...
You know I won't date any other girl than you.
I know, I believe you.
Sae...
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm sorry, you've to wait.
Until after we are married...
I understand, I'm sorry.
Just wait for a little longer.
I know.
Master, a new job request has just arrived.
Eh?
Then, I'm going.
O-Okay...
Damn... I'm already wet.
Shinji!
I'm sorry, Shinji.
I'm still...
Good, it feels good.
So good...
Shinji, don't fool around.
What exactly is this room?
It's a simulation room for Master.
In here, you'll be learning all the techniques.
Techniques?
To find the flower birthmark, you must bring the girl to ecstasy.
But I realize Master doesn't have much experience with girls.
Please use me as a simulation as you like.
Is it alright?
Come.
What should I do after this?
You've to pretend to be an external audit doctor, going to a clinic in the city.
And have sex with a girl named Sara Takaoka.
But I don't know how to be a doctor.
You don't have to worry. That's the reason for a simulation.
I'm going to...
It hasn't ended. This time, it's my turn.
Master. It's alright, you don't have to be in such a hurry.
L-Like this?
Yes, just like that.
You're doing well, Master.
Master, it's about time you put it in.
Master, for the first attempt, you've to put it in slowly and gently.
Like this?
Yes, just like that.
It's good, do it faster slowly.
Master, you're great!
Master, you'll be alright with this.
This is the workplace of Sara Takaoka, huh...
Well then, where is she?
As I thought, I can't hold it in any longer.
I see.
Excuse me, I'm Takaoka. Is there anything you need me to do?
I'm waiting for you, Takaoka-kun.
Uh? If I remember, you're the new doctor.
What do you need me to do?
I'm asked to validate the nurses and doctors.
Your working attitude is good. You have manners and you get good appraisal from your patients.
But there's something that you're weak at.
It's the injection.
Currently, your injection skills are not up to standard.
And that's why you can't get your official nurse license.
A-About that...
You don't have to lie.
Your mind still has the memories of the excitement you got from the syringe, causing you to shake your hands.
H-How did you know that?
Aren't you now still getting excited from it?
A-About that... I don't...
You mustn't lie. Your body is very honest about it.
T-There isn't such a thing!
S-Stop it!
As long you cooperate a little with me in my validation job, it'll end quickly.
Validate?
U-Umm...
Don't worry, this won't hurt you.
What's that? Isn't it a syringe?
What are you going to do with such a big syringe?
I'm going to do this.
W-Wait!
D-Don't...
You're excited, right?
I-I didn't...
Then, how about this?
Don't touch me there, I'm feeling it!
Don't, I'm going to c-cum...
I'm cumming!
The preparation is almost completed.
How is it? To have already been excited with such a big syringe but...
A male's syringe will surely make you more excited.
It feels good. I'm feeling the excitement.
You're right.
This way, you won't be excited because of the syringe,
and become a normal nurse.
I'm feeling it, I'm feeling it!
No, no...
I-I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
She doesn't have it, huh...
Sae-sama, how's the water temperature?
It's just right, thanks.
Then, let me wash your back.
You don't have to. You don't really have to do that...
Come, you don't have to be polite.
It feels kind of... awkward.
I should start a topic.
It-It's nice, Zero-chan's breasts are really big.
My breasts are a bit small.
There is no such thing.
Your shape is much better, very pretty.
W-Wait, Zero-chan...
My breasts are only big.
Ze-Zero-chan.
S-Stop...
Do-Don't...
Thank you very much.
Misaki-chan, you're on night shift today?
Yes, Shop manager.
Because if I don't earn money...
How are you earning money?
I want to have my own shop.
Welcome to the shop.
P-Please give me the special menu.
I understand.
The target this time is Mizuno Misaki.
She's working in a café; she has a strong desire for money.
Doing services to earn tips.
Services?
Yes, the special menu.
Thank you for your patronage every time.
If you really want tips, let me help you.
I don't know what you are talking about.
If you pretend to know nothing,
I'll cut the money from your pay that you pocketed till today.
Seems that pretending to know nothing is useless.
So, what do you want me to do?
A test of the new menu and the validation of your work.
New menu?
If you cooperate, I'll allow your secret job and also raise your pay by ten times.
Ten times my pay! Really?
I'll do it. Please let me do it.
It's perfect.
Hey, what are we going to do now?
Of course, eat the meal and validate your work.
Eh? W-Wait.
Don't, it's ticklish.
You shouldn't drop the desserts.
This is your punishment.
Don't, stop...
Oh, your juice came out.
No...
No...stop-
I-I can't hold it anymore.
Since it has came down to this, let's do it to the end, you pervert Shop manager.
How's it? It feels good, right?
Yeah...
Please do it to my place as well.
It's about time for you to put it in.
It feels good.
It feels so good!
Good, it feels so good!
It... It went deep inside me.
More... I want you to move more!
L-Let's cum.
She doesn't have it too, huh...
Zero?
So, how's the protagonist?
He has some misunderstandings, but I will definitely...
Never mind about that, it's interesting to wait.
But I don't have much time left.
I'll leave this to you.
What are you looking at?
Wow, it looks delicious!
There is a new dessert out for sale.
Hey, let's go and try it.
It's going to be bad for me.
Why is it bad?
For various reasons...
Are you hiding something from me?
No, I wasn't trying to...
Well, err...
I need to go to work.
Hey, w-wait, stupid Shinji!