The large cruise ship named "Northern Light"
is currently undertaking a certain
anticipated and planned cruise.
It is a special tour which only allowed
VIPs with invitations aboard.
Oh... Oops...
With a violinist like Otowa Saki-chan
and a popular idol like Kurusu Nonoka,
people are hyped up by their performance.
I got on-board for a part-time job
on summer vacation together
with Jun, my friend. However...
Miho, a request for room service
came from the VIP room.
Huh, again?
It seems that they're requesting for both of us.
No way...
You two are doing a good job!
Oh, Nadia-san.
Huh, what's the matter?
What's with those gloomy faces? What's up?
No, it's nothing.
The work could've just taken a toll on us...
Is that so?
Let's all have a break together
later, it'll be my treat.
Okay, thank you.
I can't tell her...
I never would've guessed that we
ended up going through all that.
Toriko no Shizuku
Captive Trickle (First Part)
Defiled Virgins in a Summer Luxury Cruise Ship
No... No, you can't...
Peasants like you should be grateful
to be able to stay here with
people of our standing!
P-Please not inside me!
I'm coming!
I'm begging you!
I-It's coming out!
I'm getting drained!
Here, here you go!
More! I want you to scream more!
No! S-Stop!
Here you go.
Look, your friend is working so hard.
Are you fine with doing nothing about it, Miho?
D-Don't lay your hands on Miho!
Huh?
I'll do anything in return, so spare her...
Jun...
That's the spirit.
Well then, I'll do as I please just like you said!
This cruise is composed of
company staff like me who are all VIPs.
All of us enjoy ourselves a lot playing in this room.
Your friend might break down
satisfying everyone here.
Deeper... Gobble it up even deeper!
I'm about to come!
Make sure to take it all in!
Th-There's still more to come!
S-Swallow all of it!
That's it.
Slurp and suck it all in!
Alright, savor the taste by gargling it.
Dammit, you can't even swallow properly!
When will you be able to do it?
You bitch!
You know what to do to help your friend, right?
I understand. I'll do it as well.
Huh?!
I will also...
...serve you using my body.
How did it end up like this...
No way... It's so huge...
Hey there.
Quit spacing out and start moving!
It's hitting me deep inside!
I understand...
Forgive me, Miho. It's all because
I offered you this part-time job.
I'm ramming her this hard, see?
It's alright...
I won't let you suffer alone...
This is too intense for me! No—!
No, stop filming this!
I think that you already know...
If in case you tell someone about this,
this video will spread out there like wildfire.
Okay, then... Let's record a clip
of raw sex creampie!
Here it comes!
No! Not inside me!
I'm begging you, anything but that!
"Boo-hoo, I'm gonna be given a creampie!"
Here's your creampie!
G-Good...
Oh... Looking good, aren't we?
Should I give you a creampie too,
just like your friend there?
You're gonna come in me raw!
Everyone, let this semen maniac
have all of your semen!
I'm begging you!
I want both of my pussy and mouth to be creampied!
Fill a pervert like me with your semen!
Well said, we'll get fired up when you beg like that.
Our stuff down here, that is!
I'm coming!
Give it to me!
I want to get a creampie
with a beloved VIP's semen!
Everybody, look!
They came!
Harder... Squeeze it harder!
I'm getting filmed.
All of my lewd parts are being filmed!
You're bad at this!
This is excruciating! I can't breathe!
Please come from this! Please come!
Do it more like this! You have to use more force!
Be grateful that your throat
gets to experience having
these superior genes of mine!
I'm coming!
Drink all of it. Gulp it all down!
I got myself drained empty.
There's a lot of hair...
This woman is outrageous!
Same here, this one is sopping wet!
No, don't!
No—!
What's up with this girl?
She's a pervert!
Her nipples are as hard as nails!
I bet that you can't hold it in anymore.
Aren't you drowning in pleasure?
No! I can't take it anymore!
I-I'm coming!
I'm about to come!
Wow!
Why? Even though I'm
getting raped horrendously...
You sow!
I'll make you come together with your friend!
I'm gonna come!
Miho, I'm gonna come from
getting recklessly raped!
I'm gonna come...
I don't want to, but I'm being pushed to orgasm!
Same here, I'll make her come
with you at the same time!
I-I'm coming...
Coming... Coming... I'm coming!
Here's a creampie!
Coming! I'm coming!
Here's one full load for you, and raw as well!
Afterwards, we kept getting
summoned to this VIP room
to get raped over and over again.
This tour is actually a way
for these men to find women
to prey on in the first place.
No...
I'm gonna leak, it's gonna leak out...
Please let me go to the toilet!
I'm begging you! Let me go to...
No can do, Saki-chan.
You were called over for this
very specific event, after all.
N-No way, that's...
You know about how to settle
your parents debt, right?
That money all went for your violin studies.
Yes... I will definitely pay it all back.
I will work hard on musical
performances and concerts...
Thank you for waiting, these are
Montefiore and Casa Passieno.
Huh?
That's would be far from enough, Saki-chan.
For now, use that body
of yours to settle the interest.
No way, I've been able to go by
just with musical performances.
Why did I end up with this?
Well, let's see... How are you down here?
Jeez, you keep on talking back.
This calls for a bit of punishment.
Stop! Please stop!
No, no.
Whine all you want, but we won't let you go.
Look, Saki-chan. They're not scary at all.
Feel good together with your friends
who share the same fate.
No!
Your dripping with fluids
from inside for some reason.
Stop! No more!
Please, you really need to stop!
This is something rare, indeed...
Spare me from this!
Why? Even though I'm suffering and hurting...
I-It's embarrassing...
M-My body feels like it's burning!
What the... Did you have an orgasm, Saki?
That is such a long orgasm!
Don't!
To think that you are actually such a slut...
Stop...
That was quite a shocking discovery!
I don't want this...
This calls for punishment.
Even this part of you is twitching.
You have such an indecent body, Saki!
No, no!
Perverted woman!
No—!
Wow, you're squeezing
tightly down here as expected!
No...
Th-That's my butt hole!
Of course, Saki-chan.
You can't!
That's because you are a pervert, right?
No way, you're so cruel.
Don't be rough on me, you'll tear me in half!
Your front slit is squeezing hard as well!
You're feeling good from
having your ass penetrated, huh?
No, you're wrong...
It only feels gross for me!
Stop...
Wow, this ass is sucking me in!
I'm begging you!
If you do that now, you'll drive me crazy!
Can you hear sound you're making
from gulping in the wine earlier?
Saki-chan...
Isn't that what you call pleasure?
I-I will shoot my seeds onto her lewd face!
I am... Uhh...
I'm not a dirty girl...
Lap it up with your tongue, come on!
We'll make you climax using
your mouth, pussy, and ass hole!
I'm coming... No...
You're so lewd! I-I'm coming!
There's still some more coming out! Catch it!
No!
Here too, I'll shoot it in your ass!
Your ass hole is so slippery!
No! No!
It's sopping wet!
Here, here, here, here you go!
No, don't!
I'm gonna leak!
You're squeezing hard!
She came, she came!
This girl is a stubborn one!
You're yet to satisfy me here...
Stop!
No more... I can't take it anymore!
I'll give you an anal creampie!
I won't hold back!
I see that she's insubordinate on our training.
We've just barely begun
on giving you our loving care.
Hey!
Looks like you're having fun here as well!
Someya-san, what's up?
There seems to be an interesting
event on stage tonight.
Save this one for later instead
and let's go there now!
Nonoka-chan, we heard about it...
...that you'll do a hardcore performance tonight!
W-Wait!
You see, we paid a ton to be on this cruise!
Hey...
Won't it be fine to give us
some steamy memories on board?
No!
But you're putting me in trouble right now!
M-Manager Higuchi, help me!
Forgive me, Nonoka-chan.
Just think of this as part of your job.
Bear with it just for tonight, alright?
N-No way...
I can't hold myself back anymore!
No!
What?!
What do you think are you doing all by yourself?!
Stop! Please stop!
Moreover, she's in her outfit!
No! No—!
They're huge!
Didn't that manager embezzle a huge
amount of money from their company?
That's right. After threatening him a little,
he allowed us to have an idol gangbang show.
I feel bad for that idol.
N-No way, why?
Alright, I'll make them grow even bigger in no time!
Everyone said that they loved me a lot, and yet...
I do love you!
I love you, I love you so much!
No—!
I love you lots and lots and lots...
No! Don't!
S-Stop!
I've been fapping daily as I watch
your videos, Nonoka-rin!
I want you to see the results of my daily grind!
I want you to at least see this!
I can smell something from you, Nonoka-chan!
It's the same smell when I'm rubbing myself.
Was it sweat? Was it?
Nonoka-rin gives off a strong
ammonia scent down here...
Don't tell me you stained yourself!
You're wrong!
No, let me go already!
It's alright!
I'll be rooting for a lewd Nonoka-rin!
Since we're here, I'll smear you
with this as my sign of love!
This is what's hidden beneath all this time.
That stinks! No!
I don't want that!
It's alright! Drink it, drink it!
Nonoka-chan...
Y-You're kidding! Don't tell me...
Don't worry...
We already are mutually
in love with each other!
No, I'm begging you!
Anything but that, I am still...
I'll be putting it in slowly, okay?
I can reach deep inside you!
I'm pushing hard against it, Nonoka-chan!
Can you feel it?
We really are tied together by fate!
How is my cock? Isn't it hot and
keeps digging in and out of you?
Ouch! It hurts!
Stop!
Hey, let us have our turn!
Look, this is a moment for us to indulge!
You should only look at me just for this moment!
No!
They're like blubbers!
Nonoka-chan, it feels so hot in between these!
I'm not like the other guys.
No!
I'm okay even if you don't live up our ideals!
No...
Just to meet me, you did this...
You rubbed several nasty guys using these tits, right?
It's alright!
I'm saying that I'll take you in
even if you were born that way!
N-No way! That's cruel!
I've been backed up so much!
S-Stop!
I'll make you exclusively mine, Nonoka!
Nonoka-chan, I will shoot it into your mouth-pussy!
No way, this can't be happening!
No! No!
Stop!
I've been tailing you for photos
for that shrine I made, Nonoka-chan!
No, don't come in me! I'm begging you!
You looked good in there!
You can't!
I'm getting sucked dry!
No! You can't!
Nonoka, you got so horny that you ended up coming!
That's good, I like that dirty side of you!
G-Gross...
Y-You belong only to me, Nonoka!
Don't be scared, do your best!
Stop...
I'll lend you my cock and make you come!
Pull it out... Pull it out already!
Like hell will I know any better!
If it's with Nonoka's pussy,
I'll come deep then pull out!
You really are good at this, after all!
The rumors online were true, weren't they?
Koni-chan, you perv.
I'll make you come a lot using my mouth-pussy, okay?
Give all of it to greedy Nonoka-chan!
I'll give it to you! I'll offer all of it to you, Nonoka!
It's coming out—!
This is great! Fucking you doggy style feels good!
I'm coming! Come, come, come!
No...
Stop!
You sure love semen, Nonoka.
I'll give you lots and lots more!
I've been using my video in any way I can.
I've been using it every day to fap for you, Nonoka-chan!
I'm coming again!
I can feel your throat, it's great!
Gobble it up even more!
I-I'm coming!
Deep inside again... Stop!
Nonoka-chan, you really are tightening up!
Stop... Please stop already!
I'm coming already!
I'm glad to see that you are delighted, Nonoka-chan!
This uniformity is unlike my palm...
Your hole down here is so voracious, Nonoka!
Stop...
Only feel good when you're with me, dammit!
It's alright! You can come just from giving a titjob!
Nonoka, the huge pervert!
Nonoka, the idol!
Please stop...
You belong only to me!
Jeez! You're such a dirty girl, Nonoka!
That was refreshing!
That's not good, Nonoka-chan!
If you keep doing that, I'll end up coming again!
Stop... No, no...
Nonoka-chan...
I can't hold myself back from just watching anymore!
I will at least have
Stop...
your first time in this hole!
Stop! Stop!
Ouch! It hurts!
Nonoka-hime's princess pussy is nibbling me!
Stop!
I really was planning to endure all these on the sidelines!
However, I'm...
No way!
I-I'm coming! Coming!
I'm gonna come, foolishly in love
with this princess pussy!
I'm coming from our "manager anal" sex!
Have faith in me, Nonoka!
You'll be able to overcome all of these obstacles!
Now is the time for you to truly become an idol!
Alright!
Let's do our best together!
We'll overcome this, Nonoka!
Are we gonna pour our semen there?
Let's do it! Let's give Nonoka
our support to push through!
No... No—!
Well, I've been in the back all the time.
You should've at least noticed me, right?
That's okay!
You can be honest to yourself and savor my cock!
Semen...
That's amazing, Nonoka-rin!
Everyone loves you that we
managed to gather this much!
Nonoka... Nonoka!
Nonoka, I'm coming!
Nonoka, this is...
This is what a true idol is!
Nonoka!
You're being admired!
Whether it's for me...
Or if it's for you...
It really has to be Nonoka, after all!
That idol gave us a great show.
Let's summon her to the VIP room next time!
So, how did things go?
Tozawa-san, how are things on your side?
Yeah...
We finally got our hands on this.
It's the data to lock Someya down.
Oh...
You did a great job back there.
Good job on luring those folks into the stage.
It will be the end of those
VIPs and Someya now, right?
Yeah.
It seems that they're also linked
on other huge stuff out there.
This was inside Someya's room.
This contains the names and info of VIPs
and the companies they're under.
If this goes in public, they won't easily
go off this without repercussions.
Yes! Yes! Yes! Let them have it!
Serves them right for ruining people down!
It won't be enough in exchange for the data,
but just settle with this instead.
Huh?
Oh...
What's up with this? Hey...
This hurts...
My bad...
But I'm not fond of having too
many people knowing our secret.
This can't be happening!
No, no way!
This isn't for real, right?
Are you telling me that I'm gonna die?
Be useful at least as shark bait.
U-Umm...
What are you doing out here, our dear guests?
What a tough luck you have, miss.
Hey!
Gotcha.
Wander around too much like that...
...and you'll end up...
...running into dangerous fellas!
No way!
No—!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization