Huh? What?
What's going on?
The last thing I remember is Yui being assaulted.
That's right...
Yui was...
Stop!
You...
That's right. And then Demura-sensei
came out of nowhere and...
I felt a strong shock...
Awake already?
Huh? What's...
Konomi-chan!
What the...
What's going on?!
Seriously though, I'd appreciate it if you
didn't cause me so much trouble.
Well, this is still a part of the mission.
I'll tell Takeshi to be more careful after he gets back.
I know that room...
You and I are strangers.
I'd prefer if you didn't cause such a ruckus.
Well, in any case, I've gotten what I needed.
I'll put the drugs in the usual warehouse by the
docks in the morning. Number four, got it?
Fine.
I-I'm gonna cum!
This works out. I wanted new test subjects anyway.
No...
Stay away!
Chains of the Slaves
(Part 2) Banquet for the Beasts
No, let me go!
All right, let's begin.
You sick bastard! What are you planning to do to me?!
I'm going to have you test a new
drug I've recently developed.
Oh, there's nothing to worry about.
The only side effect is pleasure.
What are you talking about?
Konomi-chan, what's wrong? Wake up!
No! What is this? It feels gross!
Don't! Stop it, Konomi-chan!
It's useless. She's already my slave.
What is this?
No! It's cold!
Stop!
What did you do to Konomi-chan?!
Well, you see, she got caught embezzling some money.
So now she's paying back by giving her body to my research.
How could you?!
What's happening?
Looks like it's starting to kick in.
Your body is starting to get hot, isn't it?
My body's acting weird.
It's getting hot and tingly.
Rinka-san, your nipples are swelling up so much.
It feels good, doesn't it?
S-Stop it!
This isn't right!
Well then, I think it's about time for me to join in.
Wh-What are you planning to do with that?
Girls these days should know what this is.
And what it's used for.
Stop...
Please, I beg you!
No!
N-No!
What is this?
S-Stop!
My body feels so weird!
I'm going crazy!
Does it feel good, Rinka-san?
No! Th-This doesn't...
No!
Stop!
It's so hot! The inside of my body feels like it's on fire!
Wh-What is this?!
I-I'm really gonna... lose it...
No, don't look!
Even the inside of your pussy is beautiful.
I-Isn't this enough?!
Let me go already!
Stop!
Don't rub that filthy thing against me!
Filthy? That's not nice.
After all, it's what's going to make you into a woman.
S-Stop!
It's so disgusting!
I don't want to lose something so
precious to a scumbag like him!
S-Stop!
Please! Take it out!
Please, I'm begging you!
It hurts so much!
A man's thing is inside me!
Mio, Yui... I'm not a virgin anymore...
No! Stop it, please!
I can't breathe!
Can you tell? My penis is knocking on
the door of your baby-making room.
No! No!
No! Stop! Take it out!
Stop!
Oh, I feel so bad for you, Ayukawa.
No matter how much you scream,
no one's going to come and save you.
It feels so messed up down there!
It's rubbing against me... I'm going to break!
Now all that's left is to pour my seed into
your womb and get you pregnant.
N-No! Anything but that!
I don't want to get pregnant!
Even if I cum inside you, there's only a
25% chance of you getting pregnant.
It might be a little higher depending
on the time of month though.
No! Please! Don't cum inside!
No! I don't want a baby! No!
No!
It's coming out...
Hot stuff is...
How could he?! He came inside me!
What? My body it's...
It's so hot...
What's happening?
I'm losing consciousness...
Looks like the drug's working perfectly.
This is where the real experiment starts.
No need to hold back.
Feel as much pleasure as you want.
N-No... I can't... I can't move...
If I don't do something, his thing's
going to go inside me again!
It's inside me again!
This guy's thing is inside me again!
No! Take it out!
No!
It feels disgusting!
It's so disgusting! I hate it!
No! S-Stop!
I'm going to break!
– Let me loosen you up a little.
– You're going to break me down there!
No! No!
Don't torment me any more than this!
Konomi-chan, stop!
I'm losing my mind!
What's going on?
I-It's coming again!
Something's coming!
My body's going numb!
N-No, I'm gonna break.
My vagina's gonna break!
If he cums inside me again,
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Anything but that!
No! No!
Don't cum!
At least cum outside!
No!
Hot stuff...
Inside me again...
Baby...
I'm gonna have a baby...
This is quite the show.
Rinka-san... And now even Konomi-san?
Is this good?
You have such wonderful breasts.
It's like you were born just to give tit fucks.
Y-You're exaggerating.
All right, let's have you swallow
this dick that you love so much.
Y-Yes...
I'll do it.
So tasty. Your dick is so tasty!
Please cum!
I love the taste of your dick and cum.
That's good, Asahina.
You've grown quite a bit in this short amount of time.
Thank you! Please, give me more, sensei.
S-So good!
I-If you keep doing it like that, I'm gonna...
Ah, no, this is too good!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Sensei, you're so good!
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
It's coming! I'm gonna cum!
Oh my god!
I'm cumming!
That was pretty fun to watch.
You have fun too?
Yeah, lots with her friends.
It was pretty great.
Might've been too much for her, though.
I see. Well, this slut's still good.
Hey, Mio.
P-Please wait!
P-Please stop abusing her any further.
Huh?
I-I'll...
I'll take her place...
If that's what you want, beg for it.
B-Beg for it?
Come on, now.
Show me your resolution.
Though I suppose a maid is more accustomed
to taking orders rather than giving them.
You gotta beg if you want this dick though.
B-But that's...
Say it.
So, what do you want?
I... I want... that thing...
Gotta be a little more specific.
Spell it out for me.
H-Huh? B-But...
We ain't so smart, you see?
If you don't spell it out for us, we won't
know what you're talkin' about.
What do you want us to shove into you here?
I-I-I...
P-Please put your dick inside my p-pussy.
See? You can do it if you try!
Now, let's give it to you right away!
All right, time to dig in!
You're hella tight.
Don't tell me you're a virgin?!
Th-That is none of your business!
I-It hurts! It feels like my stomach's going to tear apart!
If you don't make me cum quick enough,
I'm switchin' to the young lady over there.
I understand!
This time, I'll be the one to protect you!
It's getting bigger inside me!
Listen up, Maid!
I'm gonna shower your virgin pussy in my cum!
N-No!
What do you mean, no?
What are you supposed to say? Huh?!
I-I want it.
P-Please shower my pussy with your cum.
H-He didn't even say anything!
Move those hips!
It's inside me again!
Just stop!
So? Feels good, doesn't it?
I-It feels good.
Y-Your dick feels good!
So please don't take it out!
I will protect her, no matter what.
N-No! No!
Th-This...
Holy shit, it's so tightly!
She's ripping my dick off!
Please give me your cum.
Please cum inside me!
I-It's coming inside me!
Come on, we're just gettin' started!
Tighten that pussy!
No...
No, no more!
If any more cum is poured into me, I'm gonna...
No! Stop!
I-It hurts!
N-No! If you're that rough, I-I'm gonna break!
Hey, where's my "thank you"?
Th-Thank you for giving my womb your warm cum.
Good girl.
I'm sure we'll have even more fun in the future...
Huh?
My body... Don't tell me you...
What did you put into my drink?!
It took a lot longer to kick in than I thought.
I was really starting to get worried.
You were planning on using this house as a hideout
for the drugs you got from overseas.
Your operation was working pretty well for a while.
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
But you gave into temptation and
started using your own product.
Isn't that right?
I'm sure Nemura-sensei will be reprimanded for this as well.
But first... Farewell, Ebinuma-san.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: braden
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч