This can't be happening!
No, no way!
This isn't for real, right?
Are you telling me that I'm gonna die?
U-Umm...
What are you doing out here, our dear guests?
What a tough luck you have, miss.
Hey!
Gotcha.
Wander around too much like that...
...and you'll end up...
...running into dangerous fellas!
No way!
No—!
Toriko no Shizuku
Captive Trickle (Final Part)
Defiled Virgins in a Summer Luxury Cruise Ship
Do you think that you can just
get away with doing this?
I like that spunk.
You say that but you don't actually hate this, do you?
S-Stop! Cut it out!
Don't mess with me! I'm going to scream!
Are you sure?
Everyone will end up seeing you looking like that.
It's alright.
You'll end up raping me otherwise...
It seems that Someya hasn't laid
his hands on this woman.
Looks like it.
Huh?
Fine, then...
If that's the case, we'll train you ourselves.
What?
That's some hot stuff I got from South America.
We'll test it on your body.
Her body temperature started rising.
S-S-Stop...
This is still nothing compared to what's to come next.
N-No...
No...
Here you go.
Stop! No...
This will feel very good!
Stop... No...
This will go inside!
No...
Oh, it's super effective.
No! Don't...
I-I'm coming!
She boldly pissed herself!
This calls for punishment.
No!
Even pain will turn to pleasure from now on.
No... No!
Don't do that!
You can't take it off!
I'm coming again! I'm coming!
Isn't your pussy coming over and over?
Alright, I'll shove it inside now.
Here it goes! Here I go!
No—!
Damn, her insides are throbbing
and it feels so good!
Stop...
It's coming out!
Not inside!
Hey, hey... Are you crying?
Don't... Don't... No...
This feels so incredible!
Stop! No more! No!
I'm gonna come!
No...
No—!
Hey, how was it?
We're still far from done.
Then let's compare by our number of rounds!
Take this! Take this! Take this!
No... No way!
Here! Here!
Oh shit! D-Dammit! I-I'm gonna nut!
Alright! Time to switch.
Here... Here you go!
Wow, I feel like I can go on for many rounds!
Don't... Stop...
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Here you go!
Then we should all go to the main event!
Take this!
Stop!
Here!
I'm coming—!
That one definitely knocked you up!
Alright, keep fucking her non-stop.
So this aphrodisiac is the real deal, huh?
Even this part is as slippery as her pussy!
C-Come on...
Don't... Don't...
Here... Here you go!
You won't get any breaks!
Hey, take it deep in your throat!
It's coming out!
Hey, deeper! Stroke it deeper in your throat!
I'm coming!
It's coming out again!
Ohh... This is incredible!
Hey, come on!
It's coming out again!
Make sure to film this woman's coming spree!
Y-Yeah, I'm getting a good shot here.
Here, take this! Here you go!
I'll do the finishing touch with this! Here you go!
Did that soften her up a bit?
Uh-oh, did that actually break her down?
Nah, don't worry about that.
There are lots of women here to take her place.
We'll find them on wherever Someya is.
Hey, you're not moving!
Okay!
Didn't I tell you what to do earlier?
U-Understood...
I'm sorry, Nonoka-san.
I-It's alright, don't worry about it.
Nonoka-san's tits...  Her nipple got so stiff...
Miho-chan...
This is making her feel good...
She's feeling horny...
You're doing great, that's the way...
No way, I'm starting to feel it as well...
...even when we're both girls?
Miho-chan, hang in there!
We'll get raped again if we don't do as he said.
Everybody here is making you feel sensitive.
Yes... Uhh...
The way she touches me is far too
different compared to men.
If she touches me that way...
That's...
This is embarrassing!
All of my embarrassing parts are being seen.
They're filming me and Nonoka-san having sex!
Miho-chan, I'm starting to leak
more and more lewd juice!
Nonoka-san's pussy is so squishy and soaking wet!
Okay, shall we move on to the main event?
Yes...
Miho-chan, I'll push it in slowly.
Okay...
It's going in... Nonoka-san's dick is going inside!
Alright, let us see you gently shake your hips!
Understood...
I always dreamed about doing it with lesbians!
This is embarrassing!
It's coming out...
This is so sexy! I can't hold back... I'm coming!
I'm being violated by Nonoka-san right now!
I'm feeling very strange right now!
I'm sorry, Miho-chan!
I-I'll try doing it in a way that won't hurt!
What's this?
Miho-chan, that's amazing! I want it deep!
Aren't you two getting in the mood now?
You're reaching deep inside me!
I'm sorry, my hips won't stop anymore!
Miho-chan, if you go that hard on me... No!
Coming!
No way, we're fully exposed in this position!
The dick going inside us is in plain sight!
I-I can't take it anymore! I'm getting
more and more indecent!
I'm coming!
Nonoka-san, I'm about to come!
Even though everybody is watching us!
Wow... I'm coming!
Here you go!
Yes...
Well then, shall we now have
our own share of fun?
Hey, aren't you having some fun here?
Huh? Where are you guys from?
No way...
Do you really not remember, Someya-san?
Here! Here! Take that!
Bastard...
Do you think that you'll get away easily with this?
How unfortunate.
The list of clients that you blackmailed
are right here with me.
What...
I'm saying that the VIPs right here
aren't on your side anymore.
What?
You see, you took things a bit too far...
When the fellows you blackmailed banded together,
they started to have this idea...
That's the idea of having you gone.
Bastards... Shit...
Don't worry, we won't kill you.
We still have things to ask you, after all.
Miho-chan, we're saved!
Now we can finally be free!
Don't be mistaken, young ladies.
Huh?
We'll be putting you to good use from now on.
We won't forget about giving the VIPs a service.
This can't be...
Is this not over yet?
It feels good!
Make a bigger mess of Nadia's naughty pussy!
I can't get enough of this! I did it tens of times now!
Dear guest, your cock feels so hot and stiff...
I can't stop my hips anymore!
Take care of this as well.
Yes, understood!
A woman in her prime certainly
gives service at another level.
F-Forgive me...
My hard nipples are tingling.
A-Alright, I'll give your tit-pussy a creampie!
I'm feeling it from giving a titjob!
Thank you very much!
Please give your VIP semen to this slutty bunny!
I-I'm coming inside you!
Y-You're shooting it bareback inside me!
Let me go! Please let me go already!
What are you talking about?
We just got started.
No! No more!
Come on, beg for it next.
Please... Please make me come boldly!
Look... Here I go, Saki-chan.
No... No!
Loosen up.
You understand it. Right, Saki-chan?
If you put up with all this until the end,
the debt of your parents will be gone.
Compared to having your parents getting ruined,
this much is nothing! Am I right?
Ouch! It hurts!
No... Don't!
That's no good!
A little spilled out, Saki-chan.
Sorry...
I'm sorry...
Take this! This is your punishment!
Here you go!
Ouch!
There! There! There! There you go!
Mom... F-Father... Forgive me...
I'm sorry... Sorry...
I-I can't take this anymore...
I can't...
I'm shooting it inside!
I-I'm coming...
I'm coming!
Hey, this one is a perverted slut!
It's finally happening.
Nonoka-rin's ultimate live concert is starting.
Her best performance in which
she uses her whole body begins!
I'll embellish this concert with this proof of my love!
That's...
Look, Nonoka-rin.
I'll upload your stage performance
last time online, okay?
Wow, look at the shares.
Wow!
She's for our private use.
No! Th-That's gross!
Watching your own video
made you horny again, right?
C-Come! Show me your secret, Nonoka-rin!
Yes, I'm gonna come!
I'll come from my pussy in front of everybody!
Watch me come!
Film everything in camera and upload it!
I'm coming!
Coming! I'm coming again!
Coming! I'm coming from my pussy!
It's gonna leak!
That's erotic!
Wow!
Coming! I'm coming again!
I'll be taking very good care of you!
Wh-What are you...
You see, this thing
is a specially made item from overseas!
I'll put it in here first.
No!
S-Stop!
Now let's turn it on!
For example, something like 300rps
No! No, don't!
is possible with this!
No—!
That is wonderful!
No, don't!
No...
But isn't that expensive?
No, not at all!
Our special members can get this right now!
The price is reasonable!
That's harsh!
It's priced at 44 800 yen! What a fantastic deal!
I-I'm coming!
Really?
I'm gonna buy one!
Me too!
Alright, how many people wants to order? Two people?
Come on, what's wrong?
You have to hurry up and make him come,
or you'll have to entertain the guests all night long!
N-No, this is really bad! That's...
Your pussy beneath will spread wide if I do this!
O-Ouch! Stop! Stop—!
Shut up and take that!
Ouch! Ouch!
Start shaking your ass already!
Come on!
No, it hurts!
It hurts!
She's tightening up so much!
No, don't move!
You'll tear it up! Stop!
My ass will get stretched!
Shut up, you bitch!
O-Ouch! Ouch!
If you move that much, I'm gonna come!
No, I really can't!
I'm ovulating today!
It's coming out!
So this is the conception of Someya Jr.
Hey, what's the matter?
This ship's speed is unusually slow.
Tozawa-san,
This happens from time to time
due to the ship's fuel management.
Ohh?
I know about it...
These people aren't the only ones targeting this ship!
Coming... I'm gonna come again!
My contract will be over!
This is so intense!
I'm coming!
I-I'm getting sucked dry!
Wow, your tit-pussy is making me come again!
Coming... Coming! I-I'm shooting it inside!
Come! Come!
I'm gonna burst!
I'll shoot all that I saved up!
Oh... I'm coming!
No!
She certainly is a semen-sucking cum dumpster.
I'm coming! I'm coming again—!
Th-This is the sensation when
everybody's feelings become one!
Hey, I'm shooting it in her ass again!
The princess is singing just for me!
Not only her upper mouth
but her lower mouth as well!
Especially her lower mouth!
I'm coming right now! Nonoka-rin's
sexy blowjob face is making me come!
Such a face in agony...
...is for us to behold!
An idol exclusively for us finally came!
It really has to be Nonoka, after all!
Here! Here! Here!
Squeeze me tighter!
Isn't that great, Saki-chan?
You finally repaid a little bit of the debt with this.
To help you completely pay the debt sooner,
we'll make sure to have
ourselves sexually backed up.
Do your best from today onwards, alright?
Saki-chan! Hey, answer me!
No!
You always knew it!
You're so hot inside! You're tightening up!
Ohh... I'm coming!
Coming!
I'm coming inside a slutty loli!
This is my special bazooka!
No more...
We're starting to turn more and more indecent!
It's coming out!
I'm coming—!
I'm next!
Me too!
The aforementioned vessel ignored
the order to stop and is escaping.
HQ has given the order.
Use of warning shot on the vessel under suspicion has been approved.
Prepare for a prevalent engagement.
Roger. I'll let you handle the countdown and timing.
Roger.
A SakuraCircle Project Translated by: Tennouji