So about that next job...
Yunoki Mio.
She's a confident student council president
from a high-class household.
Her parents are overseas on a business trip. She's
living with a woman named Toya Shiori.
So it's easy pickings?
Our job this time is to intercept
a package from her parents.
She keeps close friends. They're Ayukawa
Rinka, Ikoma Yui, and Asahina Konomi.
A tip-off says we should be careful
and come prepared.
And that's where I come in?
Yes, we've also taken other precautions.
Anyhow, it's an easy job, but it can't
be done solo. Thanks for the help.
Prisoners' Chains:
The Lewd Bonds That Soil Their Virginity.
Um, excuse me.
May I help you with something?
Are you from the Yunoki household?
Special delivery from overseas.
Overseas?
My father must have sent it!
It's a heavy package, so we'll carry it to your door.
Thank you.
Shiori-san!
Welcome home, young miss.
We have a package from overseas.
Father must have sent it!
My, how curious. It's been a while.
We're putting it here for now, OK?
Thank you for your trouble.
Sign here, if you please.
Of course.
Oh, may I borrow something to write with?
Of course, I have a pen right here...
Here it is. Please use this.
Ojou-sama!
Ojou-sama.
Whoa, take it easy.
Put up any resistance
and her beautiful face gets all cut up.
No! What are you doing? Let go!
Quit struggling.
I think we're clear, but I'll say it anyway.
One false move and I kill the girl.
The package should arrive in a few days.
We're to wait here until then.
Eh? That's inconvenient, but...
Inconvenient?
I told Kouhei-kun that I'd work a shift tomorrow.
Like I give a fuck about your part-time job!
The client says to wait here, so we wait.
Besides, can't you just commute from here.
I guess you're right, but...
The package'll be here in just a few days. As long
as it's discreet, we can do this however we want.
We have to stay like this until the package comes?
So what do we do with these two?
"Do with them as you please", the client said.
"Just don't kill them because the cleanup is a pain."
Oh, "as we please"...
That means... we can fuck them?
Yes, but only one at a time.
We have to be ready at a moment's notice.
What, you're telling me to do her myself?
Takeshi, she's a lady.
Is that so?
Wh-What's that?
What say we fuck this ojou-sama?
No! No!
Stop! Don't touch me!
Don't struggle.
No! Stop it!
Your panties are simple but elegant.
That makes them even more inviting.
How does it feel, Mio-ojousama, knowing
that you're about to be raped?
You'll never get away with this!
Oh, but I will!
Don't touch me there!
No! Don't do this!
– No, stop! No!
– Just as expected, that's such a pretty pussy.
They're looking at me.
These thugs are looking at my body!
You're a virgin, aren't you?
It hurts! Stop it, please!
It hurts! Don't scratch me like that!
Come on. If you don't say it,
I'm going to use more fingers.
I haven't had sex before.
I am a virgin.
I haven't been with anyone ye...
You're taking pictures? No, stop!
Don't take those pictures of me!
Look, it's your virgin pussy.
Hey, Takeshi.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
No! Stop it! Anything but that!
Then shall we have that maid take your place?
No! Keep your hands off of Shiori-san!
All right then.
No!
Ojou-sama!
It hurts! It hurts! Please, take it out!
It hurts! It's going to tear! Stop it!
But you really must be a virgin! You're so tight,
and it feels like I could cum at any minute!
It hurts! It hurts! Stop it!
I'm going to fill you up with my hot semen.
No, wait! Anything but that!
Don't cum inside me!
No! No!
Don't do it! Please, stop!
Forgive me! Spare me! Don't cum inside!
Stop! No! No!
His hot semen is inside me.
No! No!
It-It's over.
You're done, right Kouhei?
I'm next! It's my turn next!
Please, just stop this!
Huh? There's no stopping me!
No! Why are you... No!
You're so deep ins... Stop!
Stop it! I'm going to break!
It's going to break!
Look! I'm going to cum deep inside your womb.
No, please don't! No!
No!
Hey, who said you could rest?
Give me a blow job.
B-Blow job? How do I do that?
What's that, ojou-sama? You don't
know something so simple? Here!
No! It smells!
Open your mouth!
Or do you want Shiori-san do this instead?
I haven't had enough yet.
Both of their thick "things" are going inside me!
I'm going to be violated again! These wicked
men are going to rape me again!
Ojou-sama!
But I absolutely must protect Shiori-san!
I will protect her.
It smells! This is disgusting! I might throw up!
No! I'm spent. Please stop this!
NO! Take it out! Please take it out!
I'm done for. Any more and I'll...
It hurts! I can't!
I can't take it anymore. Please stop. Please!
No!
I can't...
You'll attend school as normal.
We can't have people getting suspicious.
But Shiori-neesan stays here.
You already have a phone with GPS.
You have friends at school.
You know what happens if you try anything.
Mio, want to eat lunch together?
What's wrong?
You OK? You look really out of it.
I'm... uh, I'm fine!
Is this about the stalker you told us about earlier?
No, it's not. I have some work with the student council.
That's all. Let's eat together another time, OK?
Oh well. I guess it's just the two of us.
That was close. Those two have good intuition, so
I have to watch what I say. I'd better avoid them...
Eh?
Konomi-chan?
Oh, senpai!
Thanks for your hard work!
Konomi-chan, are you doing something
for the student council?
Yes, some of the numbers in the account book didn't
add up, so I was going over it with a professor.
Oh, I'm sorry to have caused you extra work.
Don't worry about it. You're busy, senpai.
Let me help you as much as I can!
Thank you. I'm counting on you!
Yes!
You told me to call at this time.
I trust Shiori-san is all right?
As promised, we haven't touched her.
That's all I wanted to know.
I'll be taking my lea...
Hang on a second, Mio.
What do you want?
Well, we were a little rough with you yesterday, so
I was just worrying if your pussy's doing all right.
I'm fine with but those worries of yours.
As your first partner, there's this "responsibility", right?
Now send me a picture of your pussy, spread wide open.
Wh-What are you saying?
A pic where you can see all the way inside.
Seeing that would put my heart at ease.
Stop joking around! This is a school! If I do that...
You have five minutes.
Just one minute late and you know what
happens to Shiori-oneesama, don't you?
Why? Why did it have to be us?
But if I don't hurry, Shiori-san will...
No, I have to keep it together!
I must protect Shiori-san!
Yes?
I received the picture.
Oh, leave your panties off.
Now, show us what you wore at school today.
To thing I have to bear this shame!
Huh, a message?
Received Message
From Yui
I'm at your door right now. I want to give you something, so please come outside.
Shiori, get inside, and stay quiet.
Don't do anything careless.
What are you doing?!
Yui-chan!
Let go of me! You...
Welcome, Yui-chan.
S-Stop it! Don't do anything to Yui-chan!
I agree. Please, spare her.
Hmm...
Mio-chan, if you want to take her place,
I can arrange for that.
I understand. I'll do anything.
Stop it, Mii-chan! Don't listen to these brutes!
Brutes?
For guys like you, that's putting it nicely!
I know that you're on the swim team.
So what?
You don't know who I am?
Even though you're on the swim team?
Like I'd want to know a guy like you!
Yui-chan!
You're always like this! Acting like
the people who fall through the cracks don't exist!
No! Don't touch me!
Shut up! I'll teach you a lesson!
Please, leave Yui-chan alone!
Mio-chan, would you be quiet for a sec? Besides,
it's Yui-chans fault for getting Takeshi angry.
There's no stopping him when he gets like this.
Don't look at me! Don't look!
No! You're disgusting!
No! Stop it! This is rape!
Ow!
– No!
– Remember me from swim team now?
Remember me from swim team now?
Don't go any deeper!
This brutish guy is taking my virginity!
Stop this!
– He's moving it inside me! It's... inside me!
– S-Stop!
Stop it, you! Don't move it like that!
W-What happened?
He came! He came inside me! That's...
No! NO! That's...
You... How dare you.
Eh? So you still want to go?
I wouldn't have it any other way.
I haven't had enough either!
You're forcefully...
No!
That's it! Use your hips!
Fuck you!
That's right, keep trying to look strong.
It hurts!
It hurts! It's going to tear!
You're going even deeper!?
Stop... Stop it!
No!
No! No!
He came inside me again!
But I'll protect Mii-chan no matter what!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
If I just float like this,
I'll think of a way out of their torment.
Or so I hoped...
Why are you slacking off?
Why are you here?
I'm the director. That makes me your senpai.
I came to offer some coaching to my cute kouhai.
Th-That's...
Get out of the pool. I'll give you a massage.
Stop it!
If you don't get serious about this,
I'm going to have you meet my friend.
No!
You...
It's going to break. It's breaking!
It hurts!
No! I can't...
Stop it! NO!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?