So, who's the next target?
Yunoki Mio.
She's a reputable Student Council President; a perfect little Princess.
Her parents are working overseas.
She's living together with a woman named Oya Shiyori.
So she's the perfect target, huh.
Our job is to deliver a package that was sent by our client under her parent's name.
She's got many acquaintances.
She's particularly friendly with Ayukawa Rinka, Ikoma Yuu and Asahina Konomi.
They see each other often, so we need to plan carefully.
So that's why I was called in?
Yeah, although everything else has been arranged.
It's an easy job, but I can't do it by myself...
That's why I've got your help.
Toriko no Kusari
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
The Obscene Bond that Defiles the Maidens
Oh excuse me, did you have any business with my place?
Are you a family member of Yunoki-san?
There's a delivery from overseas.
Overseas?
It must be from Father!
The package is heavy, so we will bring it in.
Yes please, thank you.
Shiori-san!
Welcome home, My Lady.
There's a delivery from overseas, it must be from Father!
Oh my, how unusual. It's been a while.
We will leave it here for now.
Thank you for your help.
Please sign for this delivery.
Very well, can I borrow something to write with?
Of course! I have my pen right here...
Oh here it is, please use this.
My Lady-!
My Lady...
Hey, settle down.
If you resist, it might mess up your precious Lady's fine face.
N-No, what are you doing? Let me go!
Don't make a fuss!
I think you know already.
Try anything funny and your fine Lady gets it.
It will take a few days for the goods to come.
Apparently we need to wait here for it.
Eh? That's a bit of an inconvenience...
An inconvenience?! How?
I've already told you that I've got work tomorrow.
Don't care, not my problem!
Our contact says we stay put.
Besides, just go to your work from here.
That's true, but...
The goods will arrive within a few days.
As long as we're careful not to raise suspicion, we can do whatever we like here.
Are they going to stay put until something arrives?
So, what are we going to do with them?
Anything we want, apparently.
We're not to kill them though, because cleanup would a hassle.
Oh, anything we want...?
Does that mean...
We can fuck them?
Sure, but because we may need to move them at a moment's notice,
we should do only one of them.
What? Are you volunteering?
Takeshi, it's got to be our Young Lady.
Oh, of course!
Eh? What...?
I guess we will be having the Young Lady.
No, don't touch me!
Don't resist.
No... Stop it!
Our Young Lady's panties are nice, but a bit tame.
But that's why it's so good!
How do you feel about getting raped, Lady Mio?
Y-You won't get away with this-!
Of course we will.
Eh? Don't touch me there!
N-No...
N-No, stop it... No!
Just like I thought, she's got a nice pussy.
T-They're looking at it...
These men are looking at my precious place!
You're a virgin, right?
That hurts!
Please! S-Stop it!
I-It hurts, don't churn up my insides!
Hey, if you don't say it, more fingers will be on their way!
I-I don't have any such experience...
I-I'm... I'm a virgin.
I-I've never done anything with anyone...
W-What are you doing? No, stop!
Don't take photos!
Here look; it's your perfect virgin pussy.
Hey, Takeshi...
Okay!
Eh... What...?
No, stop it! Anything but that!
Then should we swap over to your maid over there?
N-No, not that! You mustn't lay a finger on Shiori-san!
Is that so?
No!!
My Lady...!
I-It hurts, it hurts!
P-Please pull it out, it hurts!
You're splitting me apart!
Stop this, please!
As expected of a virgin!
It's so tight that I'm going to cum if I don't concentrate!
Please stop!
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't thrust, it hurts!
I'm going to cum inside...
I'm going to dump my hot, thick semen inside you!
N-No, wait...!
Anything but that! Don't cum inside!
N-No... No!
Don't do it! Please, have mercy! Please!
Not inside, don't-!
No-!
No!!
Your hot stuff is seeping into me...
No... No!!
I-It's over...
Hey, I can do it now too, right Kouhei-kun?
I'm next, it's my turn!
Please... Please, no more...
Are you kidding? There's no way I wouldn't!
Take this!
N-No, why?! Why would...!
No!
Not so deep, stop it!
Stop thrusting!
I'm going to break apart there!
Here we go! I'm going to cum right into your womb!
No, don't let it out, please! No!
No!!
Hey, who said you can take a break?
You can suck me off this time.
S-Suck off? W-What am I supposed to...
What? Our Young Lady doesn't know what it means? Here's a hint.
No... It smells!
Open your mouth!
Or should I just do it to Shiori-san?
No...
I haven't cummed it all out yet!
No, their thick cock is entering my mouth and down there!
I'm being sullied again...
My body is being messed up by these despicable men!
My Lady...
But...! I must protect Shiori-san at all costs!
Not Shiori-san...
I-It smells...!
This is disgusting, I might throw up!
No, no more... Please stop...
N-No! No more! Please pull it out!
I can't bare this! I'm gonna...!
I can't breathe! No!
Stop it, please! Please!
No!!
No... No more...!
We'll have our Young Lady going to school as usual.
Otherwise it may raise suspicion.
However, Shiori-neesan will say here.
Always hold onto your GPS tracked phone.
We have infiltrated our people into the school too, so no funny ideas.
You know what will happen, right?
Mio, let's eat lunch together.
Are you okay? You look dazed...
O-Oh yes, I'm okay.
Is this about the stalker you mentioned?
Oh no, I am just a bit busy with the Student Council work,
I have to go deal with something, so let's have lunch some other time?
Guess it can't be helped, let's just eat without her.
This is bad... Those two are clever, so it's difficult not to raise suspicion if I'm with them...
I must avoid them as much as possible...
Oh?
Konomi-chan?
O-Oh, Senpai!
Thanks for your hard work!
Konomi-chan, were you helping out the Student Council?
Yes, I was confirming some accounting discrepancies with the teachers.
I see. Sorry for making you help out like this.
Not at all! I know Senpai is busy,
so I will try my best to help!
Is that so? Thank you, you're a big help.
Of course!
You said to check in periodically, so I'm calling you now.
Shiori-san is safe, right?
Haven't laid a finger on her, as promised.
I've checked in now, so I'm hanging up.
Hey, hang on there Mio.
What is it?
Well, how do I put it? We were a bit rough raping you.
We're concerned about the state of your pussy.
You don't need to worry about such things.
I've got some responsibility for being your first, right?
So, send me a picture of your pussy spread wide open.
W-What are you saying...?
Send a picture so we can see your deepest parts!
My mind will be at ease if you do.
You can't be serious! I'm at school! If I do that...
You have five minutes after I end the call.
Even if you're a minute late, you know what will happen to Shiori-oneesama, right?
Why...? Why do we have to go through such hardship...?
But if I don't hurry, Shiori-san will...
No, I must get a hold of myself...
I must protect Shiori-san!
Hello?
I've received your photo.
Oh, don't bother putting your panties back on.
So, why don't you show me how you dressed all day at school?
W-Why must I bare such embarrassment...?
Huh? You've got mail?
I'm outside your place. Please come out,
there's something I wish to talk about.
Sender: Yui
Shiori, please invite our guest inside.
Make sure not to mess up.
What are you doing?!
Yui-chan!
Let me go, you...!
Welcome, Yui-chan.
P-Please stop it!
Don't do anything bad to Yui-chan!
I would like to say so as well. Please leave her be!
Well...
If Mio-chan will service us even more than before,
then I will consider it.
Understood, I'll do anything, so...
You mustn't Mii-chan! Don't listen to these scumbags!
Scumbags?
An appropriate name I would say!
We're aware that you're a swim athlete, you know!
Why does that matter?
You bitch, you don't even know me?!
You're even in the swim team!
Why would I know a man such yourself?!
Yui-chan!
You lot are always the same!
You don't give a crap about those that failed to chase their dreams!
No, don't touch me!
Shut up! I'll make you pay!
I beg of you! Please not Yui-chan!
Can you stay quiet, Mio-chan?
Besides, it's Yui-chan's fault for angering Takeshi.
He won't stop until he's done.
Don't look... Don't look at me!
N-No...!
That's disgusting!
N-No, stop! How dare you do this to me?!
It hurts!
I-I don't want this!
I've penetrated your tight athletic pussy!
Don't ram it in any further!
My first time went to such despicable man...!
Don't thrust!
It's moving inside me!
S-Stop-!
That thing is thrusting inside me...!
Stop it! You...!
Stop thrusting it in!
Eh? What...?
He came...!
He let it out inside me...!
No way...!
No, no! No way...!
You... How dare you...?!
Oh, you still want to resist? That's the spirit.
I haven't fucked you enough yet!
You're being so forceful-!
No!!
That's it, thrust your hips too!
Who would do such-!
That's right, that's the spirit!
So rough-!
I-It hurts! You're tearing me apart!
Don't tell me you're going to... not inside me...!
No! Stop it, stop it!
No!
No, no...!
No, no... Don't...!
No way, he came inside again...
But... I must protect Mii-chan no matter what...
If I did this, I thought I might be able to come up with a good plan, but...
What are you slacking off for?
Why are you here?
I used to belong here, so that means I'm your Senpai.
I came to train my cute underclassmen.
Y-You're kidding...
Why don't you come out? I'll give you a good massage.
Hurry up and get it over with!
If you slack off, I'll get onto your friends instead.
Stop it!
You damn...!
I'm going to break... Y-You're going to break me!
I-I can't breathe!
No...! more...
Don't cum! No!!
Hey, what are you two doing?!
Seems like a show with high RPM*! - Shikkaku Fansubs
*RPM = Rapes per Minute