My name is Yakumo Rio.
I lost my parents when I was young, and, along with my
younger sister Miyu, was taken in by my mother's father.
The family was slightly different from a typical one.
My grandfather was the leader of the Yakumo Group.
But Grandpa did his best to raise us
separate from the group's activity.
I lived a peaceful life with my kind
grandfather and a lovely sister.
But a shadow crept into that peaceful life.
Chapter 1: An Agreement of Humiliation
Contract of Imprisonment
Sisters Who Offer Their Bodies For the Sake of Family
Translation Snake | Everything Else: ShocWave | Presented by
Erobeat |http:// www erobeat.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
Recently, a new group called the Mitsuru Group trying to
destroy the Yakumo Group, has been messing around.
At a time like this, Grandpa... fell ill.
Even worse, bad things continued, and
In a meeting where all the groups in the region met,
Mitsuru was going to announce that it
will take Yakumo under its control.
And make all other groups as witness.
If this goes on, we'll lose our group.
At such a time, a certain person arrived at our house.
Leader of the Innami Group, Innami Kouzou.
He said that, although the Innami Group and
the Yakumo Group have their grudges,
he had a suggestion that would save the Yakumo Group.
He suggest that, if either I or Miyu would offer
our body to him until the end of the meeting,
He would talk the Mitsuru Group out
of their actions in the meeting.
Please don't worry about me. I'll be right back. - Rio
Strip.
If you can't do that, no deal.
To protect the Yakumo Group, although only temporarily,
became the woman of Innami's leader.
I understand.
If that’s how you do things here...
You have to be sexy doing it.
Hey, hurry up and strip!
Woah, huge tits!
Show ‘em here, too!
Quite a good body you have there.
That’s a deadly weapon to kill men!
Turn around!
Don’t you want help from us?
Show us already!
No!
Hey, over here.
Is it your first time seeing a dick?
For the establishment of our contract, squeeze out semen.
Something like that...
You can't do it?
So you came here thinking you didn't have to do anything?
I'll do it!
It’s your first cock, enjoy it well.
What is this... so hot...
Try fondling the balls with your other hand.
Stick out your tongue and lick it.
Lick it up from the base and then suck the tip.
Next, take it in your mouth and lick.
Disgusting..
Don't stop your hands.
No... it hurts!
Don't forget your first taste of semen.
Geez, swallow it properly.
Well, let's move on.
Let’s get you to offer your virginity to me.
Don't joke around!
Well then I can't help you.
Wait... I'll do what you say.
I'll be penetrating her hymen, look carefully.
No, don't look...
Guess that can't be helped.
I'm being raped by such a horrible...
Don't you forget your first man...
It hurts! No...
Rio-chan, hang in there! It'll start feeling good!
There’s noway that’s...
Be sure to take my essence deep inside.
Please... I beg you, not that!
Think about your position in this situation already.
Please... do what you want!
I can splash it into your pussy, right?
Yes, go ahead please!
Here we go!
Actually, please don’t do it!
Amazing pussy, I’m getting excited!
Please let go already...
No!
Let’s give everyone a better look.
No! Don't look! No!
No! Not so... rough.
I'll cum lots and lots.
No... please stop...
What's this... my body...
You want it right? Your pussy is trembling.
No! No! No!
Don't cum anymore!
It’s... over right?
No, I can't anymore!
This is how things are done here.
Amazing, Rio-chan, your pussy is great!
How's your second cock?
I don't know!
Here's my toast to the contract!
Don't joke around!
You're just a pervert... who's enjoying violating me!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
Your pussy doesn't feel bad anymore, right?
We should use this part, too, or it'll never end!
No! Stop!
The opening ceremony for your ass-pussy!
No way... my butt hole, too?
Stop! My butt is...
Does having your butt hole dug feel good?
It's just gross!
But you’re getting quite wet!
No...
It's squeezing tight!
No... I'm not squeezing...
They're the best tits ever!
Hey, drool over and then squeeze ‘em.
I don't want to do something so filthy!
Do as he says!
No, this is disgusting.
No...
Her reaction is decreasing...
Well, I guess she has taken dozens of dicks today.
Guess we'll just spray her all over or something.
I can't lose.
I have to protect Miyu and the Yakumo family with all I can!