Huh...? What's going on?
We witnessed Yui getting raped, and then...
That's right, Yui was...
Stop it!
You damned...!
That's right, then Demura-sensei showed up suddenly...
Then there was a big shock...
Have you awoken?
What...?
Konomi-chan-!
What the... What's going on?!
Good grief, I would rather that you didn't cause this much hassle.
Don't worry this is part of the plan.
I'll be sure to warn Takeshi when he's back.
That room...
You and me are nothing but strangers.
Refrain from making a disturbance.
For the time being, we've got what we needed.
The drugs will be at the usual place tomorrow, the warehouse on wharf number four.
It's fine.
I'm gonna cum-!
I wanted a new subject for my experiments too.
No, don't come any closer...!
Toriko no Kusari
Presented by Shikkaku Fansubs
The Obscene Bond that Defiles the Maidens
Episode 02: The Banquette of the Beasts
No, let me go!
Now then, shall we get started?
You freak! What are you intending to do?!
You're going to be a subject for testing the new drug I created.
There's no need to be afraid.
It'll just feel good, that's all.
What are you saying?!
Konomi-chan, what happened? Come to your senses!
No! This is disgusting!
No, stop it Konomi-chan!
It's no use, she's under my control now.
What's this...?
No! It's cold, stop it!
What did you do to Konomi-chan?!
She poked around too much regarding the spending of the budget.
So, I got her to help out, using her body with my experiments.
How horrible...!
W-What is this?
It seems that it's started to take effect.
Aren't you getting all hot and bothered?
M-My body, it's feeling strange...!
It's gotten hot, it's throbbing!
Rinka-san's nipples have gotten so pointy!
Doesn't it feel good?
S-Stop it already!
This... It's wrong!
Now then, it's time I helped out as well.
W-What are you going to do with that?
Kids these days will know what this is, right?
And of course, how it is used.
Don't do it, I beg of you!
No!!
No!
W-What is this...? Please stop!
My body's going numb, it's too much!
Does it feel good, Rinka-san?
Stop! This is...!
No, please, stop this!
My body's so hot... I'm burning up inside!
W-What is this...?!
I-I'm really gonna...!
No, don't look!
Rinka-san's pussy is beautiful.
Haven't you had enough? Let me go already!
Stop! Don't rub such vile thing against me!
How rude of you.
This thing is going to make you a woman, Ayukawa.
S-Stop it, it's dirty!
I don't want my precious virginity stolen by such vile man!
S-Stop it!
Pull it out, please! I beg of you!
It hurts, it hurts!
This scumbag's thing is inside me!
Mio... Yui... I'm not a virgin anymore...
No, please stop this!
I can't breathe-!
Can you feel it?
My penis is rubbing against your little baby making room.
No, no!
Stop, pull it out! Stop it!
Oh, my poor Ayukawa.
No matter how much you scream, no one's going to hear your cries for help!
N-No...!
I'm feeling strange down there!
I'm going to break from my crotch being rubbed!
Now then, all that's left is for me to pour in my seed juice and make you pregnant.
N-No, anything but that!
I don't want to be pregnant!
Even if I cum inside, there's only about a 25% chance anyway.
Although, it might be a little higher because of your age.
No! Please, don't cum out inside!
No, I don't want your baby, no...
No!
Your hot stuff, it's coming out...
T-This is horrible, he came inside me!
What's happening? My body, it's so hot...!
What's this... I'm loosing consciousness...
It seems the drug has taken full effect.
The experiment has just begun.
No need to hold back, feel good as much as you want.
N-No... My body, it's numb...
No, if I don't try harder, his thing is going to enter me again!
It's in again...! This scumbag's thing is inside me again!
No, pull it out! Stop!
It feels wrong, this doesn't feel good at all!
No, stop... I'm going to break!
I'm going to break down there!
I'll let you go soon, don't worry.
No, no!
Please don't bully me anymore!
Konomi-chan, don't-!
I'm going to lose my mind!
What's this...?
S-Something's coming, I'm going to cum!
My body's numb...!
N-No, I'm going to break, I'm going to break down there!
If he lets it out again, I'm gonna be pregnant! I don't want his baby!
No, no! Stop! At least cum outside me!
No!
The hot stuff's seeping inside again...
I'm... I'm going to be pregnant...
That's quite the show.
Rinka-san... Even Konomi-san too...
Is this okay?
Your breasts are fabulous.
It's like you were born to give titty fucks.
Y-You flatter me too much!
Now then, how about you put this beloved cock in your mouth?
Okay, got it!
Delicious! Your cock is tasty!
Please let it out!
I love the taste of your cock and semen!
That's it, Asahina.
You've developed well in such a short time.
Yes! Please give me more, Sensei!
T-This is amazing!
If you do that, I'm gonna...!
This is too much!
I-I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Sensei, this is amazing!
I-I'm gonna...!
I'm gonna cum!
Amazing!
I'm cumming!
They're giving us quite the show!
Were you having fun as well?
Yeah, with my buddy here.
It was quite amazing.
She's like this now, though.
Oh really? Bring her over here then.
Hey, Mio!
P-Please wait!
P-Please stop assaulting My Lady.
I... I will take her place, so...
Then, start by begging for it yourself.
B-Begging for it-?
You know what I mean.
Show us that you're serious.
Since maids are graceful, they normally can't say they want it.
But if you don't, no cock for you.
T-That's...
Say it.
C'mon, what is it that you want?
I... I want it...
You want it? Say it properly!
E-Even if you say so...
We're not all that smart you see.
So unless you're specific, we don't get it at all.
What did you want rammed in here?
P-Please put your c-cock inside my p-pussy...
Looks like you can say it if you try!
Now then, time to ram it in.
Thanks for the invite, I'm putting it in!
What's this? It's unexpectedly tight, are you a virgin?
That doesn't concern you!
It hurts! I-It's going to split my stomach!
If you can't make me cum, I'm going to swap with our Young Lady!
Understood...!
I'm going to protect My Lady this time, no matter what!
H-His thing is swelling up inside me!
Hey, Miss Maid!
I'm going to let your insides bathe in my semen shower!
Huh-? N-No!
That's not right, what should you to say in this situation? Huh?!
I-I want it...
P-Please let my pussy bathe in your s-semen shower!
No way... So suddenly...?!
Move your hips properly!
I-It's entering me again!
No more...!
How is it, does it feel good?
I-It feels good...!
Your cock feels great, so don't pull it out!
I must be the one to protect My Lady...
N-No, this is...!
This is amazing! It feels like my cock's going to be pulled off!
Give it to me... P-Please let out your semen inside me!
It's coming out again-
C'mon, we're just getting started!
Make sure to tighten up!
No, no-!
No, no more! If they pour any more semen into me, I'm gonna...!
No, stop it! I-It hurts!
N-No! If they do it so rough, I-I'm going to break!
C'mon now, where's your manners?
Thank you for pouring your semen into my w-womb...
That's a good girl, we'll be sure to have fun again later...?
My body... What the hell did you put in that drink...?!
It took longer to take effect that I thought, I was a little worried.
You two hatched a plan to deliver the smuggled drugs to this address,
and managed to successfully get it.
Shit... Shit, shit shit!
But you got careless and tried it out, and ended up overdosing on it.
...or something like that?
I'm sure Demura-sensei will be in trouble too.
But for now, it's goodbye to you, Ebinama-san...
...And they lived happily ever after! - Shikkaku Fansubs