So what was that about our next job?
Yunoki Mio.
She's the president of her student council and someone
that everyone trusts... a textbook rich girl.
Her parents are currently overseas on a business trip.
She's home alone with a woman named Toya Shiori.
Perfect timing, huh?
Our job this time is to intercept the packages
that the employer's sending to their house.
She's on good terms with many people, but especially
with Ayukawa Rinka, Ikoma Yui, Asahina Konomi.
We have some inside information on those
three just in case we need to devise a plan.
So the reason you called me over is because...
Yeah, 'cuz you never know what might happen.
It might be a simple job, but it's not a one
man job. I'm gonna need your help.
Chains of the Slaves
Disgrace and Dirty the Virgins
Oh, hello.
Did you need something from my home?
Are you a relative of Yunoki-san?
This is a package from overseas.
From overseas?
Oh, it must be from father and mother!
The package is quite heavy, so we'll
carry it to your door for you.
Thank you, please do.
Shiori-san!
Welcome home, miss.
We got a package from overseas!
It must be from father and mother.
Oh my, that's unusual.
It has been quite a while.
We'll leave it here for now.
Thank you for your troubles.
Could we get a signature?
Sure. Do you mind if I borrow a pen?
Of course, no problem.
My pen is... oh, here it is.
Please use this.
Miss!
Miss...
Not so fast. Calm down.
If you don't, the pretty lady over there
might get her face messed up.
Wh-What are you doing? Let go of me!
Don't make a scene.
I think you get it by now, but if you try
anything funny, we'll kill that girl.
They're sending the package over in a few days.
We're gonna wait here until they arrive.
Huh? I don't think I can.
What do you mean you can't?
I told you, I have work tomorrow, didn't I, Kouhei?
What the fuck does that matter?
We follow our employer's instructions. Also,
why can't you just go to work from here?
Yeah, I guess I could, but...
They'll be here in a few days. Just don't do anything
to draw attention to us here and we'll be good.
We're going to be stuck like this
until the package is picked up?
What're we gonna do with these two?
They said we can do whatever we want.
But they said don't kill them 'cuz cleaning
up after that would be a headache.
Oh, whatever we want?
So then that means...
We can fuck 'em?
Yeah, but only one of them just in
case we need to get away quick.
Huh? So, what? I gotta choose one myself?
Takeshi, the rich girl.
Yeah, good idea!
What?
Let's take the rich girl for a spin.
No! No!
No! Don't touch me!
Stay still.
No! Stop!
Your panties are pretty clean and plain.
But that just turns me on more.
So tell us how it feels to know that
you're about to get raped.
Don't think you'll get away with th...
Yeah, we do think we will.
Don't touch me!
No!
– No! Stop!
– You really have a pretty pussy here.
They're looking at me.
These men are looking at my private parts.
You're a virgin, aren't you?
That hurts!
Please stop!
It hurts! Don't finger it so much!
If you don't answer my question,
I'm gonna put another finger in.
I don't have any experience.
I'm... a virgin.
I haven't done that with anyone...
What? What are you taking a picture of? Stop! No!
Don't take pictures of it!
Look, it's your virgin pussy.
Hey, Takeshi.
Yeah?
What?
No, stop!
Please, anything but that!
Then should I do the maid instead?
No, you can't!
Don't lay a finger on Shiori-san!
Okay then!
Miss!
It hurts! It hurts!
Please take it out! It hurts!
You're going to rip it!
Please stop, I can't...
You really are a virgin.
You're so tight, I feel like I'm gonna cum any second now!
Ow! It hurts!
Don't move...
Stop!
I'm gonna drown your pussy with my raw cum.
No! Wait!
Anything but that!
Don't cum!
No! No!!
Stop! Please stop! Let me go!
You can't! Not inside!
No!!
There's hot stuff inside me!
No! No!!
Is it over?
Is it my turn now, Kouhei? It's my turn now, right?
Please! No more!
Like hell that'd be the end!
No! Why is this happening?
No!
You're moving so much! Stop! Stop moving!
You're gonna break it! You're gonna break it!
Here! I'm gonna cum real deep into your womb!
No, don't cum!
Please! No!!
No!!
Hey, who said you could rest?
Suck me off next.
S-Suck?
What should I do?
What? You don't even know what to do?
Like this!
No! It stinks!
Open your mouth!
Or maybe we should ask Shiori-san?
I'm not done cumming yet!
No! Their two big things are in my mouth and down there!
I'm being dirtied. These two men are messing up my body!
Miss!
But I need to protect Shiori-san at all costs!
I need to protect her!
It smells so bad, I feel sick!
I feel like I'm about to throw up!
No! I can't take anymore! Please stop!
No!!
Take it out!
Please take it out!
I don't want this anymore!
Anymore of this and I'm gonna...
It hurts!
No! I can't take anymore! Please!
Please!
No!!
I can't...
We'll have her go to school as normal.
It'd be bad if anyone got suspicious because she was absent.
But big sis Shiori over here is gonna stay with us.
Carry that GPS with you wherever you go.
We have friends at your school, so
don't do anything stupid, okay?
If you try anything, we'll know.
Mio, let's have lunch.
What's the matter?
Are you okay? You've been spacing out.
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Is it that stalker again?
No, I've just been busy with the student council.
Speaking of which, I have to go there for
a bit, so you two have lunch without me.
I guess that's that. Let's just eat then.
That was close. They're both pretty perceptive. If I stayed
with them any longer, I might have slipped up.
I should try and stay away from them as much as I can.
Huh?
Konomi-chan?
Oh, senpai?
Good to see you.
Are you here for Student Council work?
Yes. I was checking with the teacher about
some things that didn't add up.
Oh, I see. I'm sorry to have you do such a monotonous task.
Oh, no, it's fine. I know you're busy.
I'll help out all I can!
Really? Thanks. I'm counting on you.
No problem!
I'm reporting in. You haven't done
anything to Shiori-san, have you?
Yep, as promised, we haven't laid a finger on her.
Then, we're done here.
Wait a second, Mio.
What?
Well you know, we went pretty overboard yesterday.
Just worried about if we go you pregnant or not.
I don't need you worrying about me.
Just wanted to take responsibility as your first partner.
Send us a picture of your pussy.
What are you saying?!
I mean take a picture where we can see all the way inside.
At least that way I can rest assured
that you're not pregnant.
Stop joking around! I'm at school!
If I did that...
Do it in five minutes.
If you're even a minute late, you know what'll
happen to your precious Shiori, don't you?
Why? Why do we have to go through this?
But I need to hurry or else Shiori-san will...
No. I need to keep it together!
I need to protect her!
Yes?
Got the picture.
Oh and keep those panties off.
Now let's see what it's like after all those hours at school.
I can't believe I have to endure this embarrassing treatment!
Huh? A text?
Received Message
Sender: Yui
I'm outside your door. I have something I want to give you, so could you come out?
Shiori, let her in.
Can't raise any suspicions.
What are you doing?!
Yui-chan!
Let go of me! You...
Welcome, Yui-chan.
Please stop!
Don't do anything to her!
Please, I beg you as well. Please, not her.
Hm, let me think.
If Mio-chan over here is willing to give us even more service
than before, I wouldn't mind listening to your pleas.
Fine. I'll do anything.
You can't, Mii-chan! Don't listen to these scumbags!
Scumbags?
That describes you two perfectly.
I know about you, you're a competitive
swimmer, aren't you?
So what?
You don't know who I am?
How can't you when you're in the swim dub?!
Why would I know?! I don't get around
to knowing no-name scum like you!
Yui-chan!
All of you were always like that!
You never gave any thought to
the people who dropped out!
No! Don't touch me!
Shut up! I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
Please! Leave Yui-chan...
Mind piping down a bit, Mio-chan?
It's her fault anyway for making Takeshi mad.
Now that he's like that, he won't stop.
Don't look! I said don't look!
No! That's gross!
No! Stop!
How dare you do this!
It hurts!
– No! No!
– I took the virginity of the swim club's ace!
Don't come in any further!
My first time was really taken by this cowardly man!
Stop moving!
It's moving inside me!
Stop...
It's really inside my body?!
Stop it!
Don't move it so much!
Huh? What?
He came inside me?
He really came inside me!
This can't be...
No! No!!
This isn't...
How dare you!
Still got some spunk left, huh?
Wouldn't have it any other way.
I'm not done yet either!
So rough...
No!!
Good! Use your hips!
Why would I...
Whatever, just keep trying to act tough!
So rough!
I-It hurts!
It's gonna tear me apart!
No, are you gonna... not again!
Stop! Stop!!
No!
No, no!!
No, stop!
No!
This can't be... He came inside me again!
But I'll definitely protect Mii-chan!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
When I float around like this, I feel like
I can come up with a good idea to win.
Or at least that's what I thought.
What're you slackin' off for?
Why are you...
I grew up here. I'm basically your senpai.
I just came here to give you some
special lessons as your senpai.
N-No...
Come on out, I'll give you a massage.
Hurry up and finish!
If you slack off, I'm gonna go after your friends.
No!
You...
You're gonna break it!
It's gonna break!
Stop!
Don't...
Don't do it! No!!
Hey, what are you doing?!