Kirin Park
I hope that Onee-chan isn't being treated badly...
Please don't worry about me. I'll be off. - Rio
My precious sister...
I miss you.
Innami Commercial Affairs
Onee-chan?
Onee-chan...
Translation: Snake | Timing: MrMew | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net [ #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Contract of Imprisonment
Chapter 2: The Bond Between Sisters
Even as the day of the meeting approached,
The leader of the Inami group continued to
mark me with scars that would not go away.
Stop moaning and answer already!
If you get it wrong, it's creampie for you.
Now answer me, which penis is this?
How am I supposed to tell!?
Good luck, Rio-chan!
Squeeze your pussy and think harder!
The... the second one...
Wrong.
Here's the first go!
No! Please don't!
We're continuing until you get it right.
Please, let me rest...
I guess that can’t be helped. We'll spare you for now.
Miyu!
Onee-chan!
I didn't think that I’d be able to have
milady Miyu as my partner one day.
Stop!
Don’t do anything to Miyu!
Unfortunately, she’s asked herself
to become a scapegoat for you.
You guys lied to Miyu, didn't you!?
That’s not it...
Onee-chan looked like you were in pain, so I wanted to help!
What?
I’ll make you a woman.
Stop it! Don’t hurt Miyu!
What is this... it’s gross...
Watch closely. It's the moment your sister becomes a woman.
No...
It hurts!
Now you’re rod sisters with Onee-chan.
Miyu! Miyu!
Stop! Stop it!
Things are just getting started, be sure to taste it well!
It's too much!
Don’t move...
That place is... hot...
It s not "that place", it’s your pussy.
My pussy... is hot...
I’ll do anything, so please don’t hurt Miyu!
Really?
Yes.
Onee-chan...
Miyu.
This is my first order.
Yes.
Watch your sister get creampied!
You’re horrible! This isn't what you promised!
I pulled out once, the contract was made.
You liar! That’s such a dirty way to do things...
Shut up!
I’ll make your tight pussy drink lots of milk from my balls.
No!
Miyu...
Work hard, you guys.
There’s a punishment game for the
one that makes us cum first.
Wow, as expected from the experienced one!
Tease mine, too.
You’d better pay attention, or it won’t be a fair game.
You're quite good.
It's painful... but if I stop, bad things
will happen to Onee-chan.
I can't Miyu take the punishment.
Woah, Rio-chan is way too sexy!
I don’t care if It's such ridiculous things,
as long as I can protect Miyu...
With this, I can spare Miyu from horrible things...
Geez, you guys are useless.
Miyu!
As punishment, you don't get your creampie until later.
No way!
No!
We'll cum lots inside you, milady.
No! Onee-chan!
Stop!
I beg you, stop!
If she takes that many at the same time, she could break.
No don’t!
Miyu!
Please let me use my pussy...
To please your penises.
Woah!
I see the Yagumo sisters are quite close.
This tightness is incredible!
Does it still hurt?
A little...
Don't worry, don’t worry.
I'll teach you proper sex.
C’mon! Squeeze your pussy more!
You're tits are shaking really crazily!
Don’t joke around! It's because you’re moving!
Stop...
Enjoy it more like your sister is.
Miyu...
I don't want this, but...
When he rubs inside, it feels good!
Don't rub at weird places!
I found your weakness!
If you rub so much, I...
This time, it's my turn!
Don’t hold back, cum!
Who do you think is...
Your insides are really hot.
There's no way I’m...
Focus on your pussy, I’ll make you cum!
No!
Say "I'm cumming" when you cum!
I'm cumming!
I'll cum until I’m all empty today.
In the end, the Yagumo group went under
the control of the Innami group.
And we...
That's enough for now, you can take a break.
You're giving up already?
What did you say!?
I guess one person just can’t satisfy me.
Penis feels good!
My boobs feel good, too!
Let it out! Let out lots and lots!
Semen is coming!
Wow, looks like it can still go!
Hey!
Stop...
I said... stop...
C'mon, let's go back.
Back to our home.