That's a lie!
Have you not been told?
It has been agreed that should I
win the tournament,
I will marry you, Miss, and
take over the dojo.
I can't be with Sid?
No, I won't believe you!
Tournament of the Gods
Violent Battle
Are you an entrant in the
Tournament of the Gods also?
Yes...
Then I shall give you a warning.
Don't win.
You must NOT become the Champion.
Damn! Let me out of here!
Just keep quiet until you die
of starvation, okay?
Then I'll use your body as I wish.
Damn, at this rate, I won't make it
to my next fight!
Sid!
Azuki! How?
Selena told me that you still
hadn't come back.
I couldn't wait anymore.
What would I do if you weren't around?
I think I understand your
strength now, Sid.
I want to be with the strong you, Sid.
Azuki...
So, Sid, you have to win, okay?
So that we can be together forever.
Though I was possessed,
I have still wronged you.
It is only a matter of time until
this body collapses.
Please let me fight my final
battle without regrets.
Here I come, Azuki.
Come!
Are you okay, Azuki?
You finally beat me, Sid!
I can't believe it myself.
It's because you trained so hard.
You think so?
I was thinking that I wanted to give
you something, if you won.
To me?
Hold out your hand and close your eyes.
That was...
It's the Mizuhara Wind Technique.
But only the successor to the Mizuhara dojo
is allowed to know the Wind Technique.
It's only natural that you have it
now that you're stronger than me, Sid.
Azuki...
With that kind of technique,
you won't be any match at all for
your next opponent, Gaji.
What? Who are you?
Gaji was the foremost master
of martial arts in Japan.
I can hurt him, but I won't
be able to kill him.
But it is my duty to execute the traitors.
Gaji and Princess Shizuku have
deserted their country!
Now then, I have a proposal for you.
Kill Gaji for us.
It doesn't matter that he's a master.
With a wounded hand, even you
should be able to defeat him.
Then make his partner, Princess Shizuku,
your comforting pet.
Since she was raised as a
princess of Japan,
once her body is sullied by you,
she will no doubt commit suicide.
You can't be serious!
Do you think I could do
something like that?
I wonder about that.
Wait!
Sid!
Be careful, okay?
Gaji, I expected no less from our
army's ultimate swordsman.
Suzi, my destiny is to protect
Princess Shizuku.
For that you betray your country?
My mistress is Princess Shizuku.
If the Princess dislikes an arranged
marriage and abandons her country,
then to protect the Princess, I too
will abandon my country.
Gaji, you don't even care
about my feelings.
If I cross swords with you,
I will not emerge unscathed.
But my orders are to execute you
and Princess Shizuku.
Leave me be!
Your pity is unnecessary.
Gaji...
Welcome back, Sid.
Hey, where's Azuki?
I left Azuki a while ago.
Azuki!
So you finally came, boy.
How cowardly!
Let go of Azuki!
That depends on you, you know.
As promised, I've weakened Gaji.
As a result, all my men have died,
and I am now unable to continue.
As for the rest,
as soon as you kill him,
I'll let this girl go.
I don't remember making any promises!
You don't have the freedom to choose!
Damn...
So kill me.
If you don't kill me,
I'll chase those two
even to the ends of the world.
Why go so far?
You...
Can you understand the pain that comes
when the man you love betrays your
country for another woman!
Can you understand this pain?
Sid...
I beg of you. I can't stand it.
Let's go, Azuki.
But you have to win no matter
what, don't you?
Can you live with your regret if you lose
because you were worried about
your opponent's wound?
He IS strong.
But is it because of the wound?
His right side is weak.
Mizuhara Wind Technique!
Gaji lost, didn't he?
Sorry, but I couldn't lose either.
Please don't apologize.
Everyone is fighting to win.
By the way...
Please don't say anything.
I understand.
Wait!
No, I can't do it after all.
Please forgive me. I love Gaji.
To be loved by anyone other than him...
I just can't do it!
It's okay.
I have a girl I love too.
I wouldn't want her to have sex
with another guy.
I understand your feelings and Gaji's.
Gaji is hurt, but he'll be fine.
Please be happy together, okay?
Yes...
At last, the final round,
Sid.
Mizuhara Fire Technique.
For Sid, who's won all the battles
to make it to the final round.
It's a present from me.
Wind, Fire, Heaven.
The three techniques are all balanced.
This technique can nullify Bilicus's
Technique of the Heavens.
Then, if you use the Wind
Technique and magic,
you can fight Bilicus on equal
or higher ground.
Be confident and fight without regrets.
Thank you, Selena.
Sid, it's time for the fight.
Okay!
We shall now begin the final round
of the Tournament of the Gods!
From the Gate of the Devil, Bilicus!
From the Gate of the Dragon, Sid.
Well, Sid, you have been
victorious until now.
I give you praise for your efforts.
But this battle is different.
I will not hold back.
I will come, Sid!
Mizuhara Technique of the Heavens!
Mizuhara Fire Technique!
I have to win!
Mizuhara Wind Technique!
I won?
The victor, Sid!
Sid!
I won, Azuki.
Congratulations, I'm really happy.
Me too.
I can't believe it myself.
You've become stronger, Sid.
But you're as bright, caring
and forthright as ever.
The same Sid I've always loved.
It's embarrassing when you
say it like that.
You haven't changed a bit
in that way either.
Azuki, you smell like soap.
Sid, you smell like sweat.
Sorry.
I like your sweat, Sid.
We get to be together now.
You and I are going to become one, Sid.
Are you afraid?
Just a little.
Sid, just because we do it,
doesn't mean we'll change, right?
I think we will.
I think we'll become closer.
Really?
Let's make it that way.
We're going to be together forever.
I'm going to put it in, Azuki.
I'll bear it, even if it hurts.
Are you okay?
Azuki, here I come!
I'm sorry, Azuki.
For what?
You know. It hurt, didn't it?
But because your face looked like
you were trying so hard,
I was happy.
And I'm happy, because I got
to be one with you, Sid.
Now I get to be with you, Azuki,
to make you my bride when
we get back to the dojo.
Azuki, I won't ever be parted from you.
Tomorrow, after I go to the Champion's
House and meet with the mayor,
I'll come right back to the hotel
and pick you up.
I'll be waiting.
Azuki...
Sid...
It stood up again.
Oh no, really?
Azuki?
What?
Is it okay to do it again?
This time, I'll make you come too, Azuki.
Sid!
Sid! Sid!
Azuki!
You can do anything
litsunohika yume o
Image no mukou ni
Dekiru to shinjiite ite
Kizutsuitara
Onaji sora no shita
Kimi o mistumeteiru
Watshi o kanjite
Hashiridashitara
Kaze ga kawaru yo
Sukoshi kanashii
Kinou ga touku naru kara
Step by step
Hodokesouna shoes no himo o make
Kokoro o nandomo musubi naoseba
Kitto yukeru yo
You can do anything
Oikakeru yume no
Image utsushitte
Kagayaku hitomi ga suki
Wasurenaide
Donnatoki ni demo
Kimi o mistumeteru
Watashi ga iru koto
To be continued...