I wouldn't have thought that I'm
inside a VR game at first glance...
Clap clap!
Onee-san, do you need something?
Sorry...
I wanted to ask about my whereabouts...
Is something wrong?
We're inside the game, right?
That's right...
I'm glad! It looks like I got in properly.
Looks like I met someone strange...
Hey, I know that this is sudden,
but please have sex with me!
What are you talking about?!
I want to try having sex in a VR game!
There's no way we can do that!
This game is for all ages, that's why.
Want to try doing it?
You're too close...
I'm gonna research about the things you like.
I got it.
Would something like this be good for you?
Nin-nin!
What...
There wasn't a costume like that
in the premium item shop!
Do you feel like having sex now?
Never!
Then how about this one?
Ta-da!
You like costumes like these.
Right, Ryouta-kun?
It's a bull's-eye, right?
Even though sex in the game isn't possible...
Whether it can be done or not...
Trying it is something to look forward on!
Onee-san!
How do my tits feel?
They feel like the real thing...
Try touching my nipples.
I'm feeling it!
Even though it's just in a game?
Yes...
Please try licking them.
Boys all love breasts, right?
You're like a baby!
You're sucking as best you can.
You're so cute, Ryouta-kun!
How do my tits taste?
Milk won't come out no matter how hard you suck it!
That tickles!
Ryouta-kun, your dick got big!
Huh?!
Oh, it's true!
You got turned on from my tits, right?
Shall we take that off?
Take what off?
Nin-nin!
What happened? My pants disappeared!
My dick really grew big.
I've rewritten the program a little bit.
Just who are you, onee-san?
I can't bear this anymore!
I'm gonna make your cock feel good a lot, okay?
Your cock got hard as rock.
You want to do it this much, right?
This is called a titfuck.
Did you know about this, Ryouta-kun?
I read about it in comics.
You're a naughty boy.
The tip of your cock gives off a manly smell!
Your cock between my tits is
peeking upwards and it's cute!
Are you gonna come from my tit-pussy?
You can shoot it all out just like this!
But coming in the game is...
What are you saying?
You can come as much as you
want since we're in a game!
You don't have to hold back.
I'm coming already!
What a great amount of semen!
Just how much have you been holding inside you?
I really came...
Did that make you feel good?
Yeah...
Shall we do something that feels even better?
Better?
Let's go to another place.
Please close your eyes.
Like this?
Yes... You can open your eyes now.
This place is...
I made a link to another game and
made us jump to a different place.
Whoa! My clothes changed!
We can have as much sex as we like here.
Sex with onee-san?
Hey there!
You should call me senpai here!
Kouhai-kun.
Senpai, if you look at me that way...
It makes you feel horny?
You came this much even though
it's already your second time.
Kouhai-kun, you're so naughty!
Sadako-senpai...
Please let me have sex with you already.
Okay, okay!
Please fuck me raw using your
outstanding cock, kouhai-kun!
Your cock is hitting me deep inside!
Please hurry up and start moving!
Here it comes!
Even though your cock is slender...
It's long so it's knocking
in my pussy's deepest part.
It feels good!
You're shaking your hips with all your might.
That's so cute!
Even though we're inside a game...
This feels so good!
More... More!
Do it harder!
Use your cock on my dirty pussy!
Please make it slushy!
Senpai!
You're so cute!
Your piston fuck feels good!
I love your cock, kouhai-kun!
I'm coming! My pussy is coming!
Please pour your cock milk
deep into my pussy, kouhai-kun!
...into my pussy's deepest parts!
Squirt out your semen... Shoot them in!
Sadako-senpai...
That was quite an extraordinary fuck!
Ryouta-kun... You can still keep going, right?
Yeah... I want to do it more.
Alright then.
You're still this hard despite coming thrice already.
I have to give your outstanding cock a check-up.
No way!
If you rub it that much...
Your precum is oozing out at the tip!
Your cock got slippery.
I-I'm coming!
Are you going to come again?
We won't be able to properly do
a check-up if you come quickly.
But...
Jeez...
You're not allowed to come until I said so.
Just bear with it a little more.
Okay, you can come now.
Good job!
You got me so dirty...
I'm sure that you're exhausted already, Ryouta-kun.
Huh? Are you still hard?
My cock won't stop throbbing...
I might have really gotten sick!
This calls for an emergency treatment.
Please stay put.
You'll feel better in no time.
Your cock got even harder that before.
Can you see the place where it's going in?
Yeah...
I'm gonna start moving.
Is my treatment good?
Just let me know if it hurts, okay?
Your cock will feel...
better in no time!
I'm going to...
get your temperature from your cock!
I think your temperature is a bit high!
Relax your body.
Shoot everything inside me!
Shoot your semen and feel relieved!
I got poured in with semen again!
There, there.
You worked a lot hard today.
Yeah...
Good boy, Ryouta-kun. You're a good boy!
Are you gonna put your cock inside again?
No way, if you push from beneath...
I'll won't be able to forget
about your cock, Ryouta-kun!
I can't take it anymore! I-I'm coming!
This is what a VR sex is like,
Ryouta-kun!
He fell asleep from exhaustion.
...a dream?
Huh?
I already am out of the game, why?
Ryouta, you came again!
Who are you?
Eh... You really don't know?
Is that you, Sadako-san?
Bingo!
I'm a ghost that's an amalgam of many
deceased people, so I have many forms.
Hey... Let's continue from where we left in the game.
My tight loli pussy feels very good as well!
I can't come anymore after that.
Game and reality are separate things.
Is that how it works?
Hurry up and use that lively outstanding cock
and have a real raw sex with me!
Sadako-chan's loli pussy...
Your outstanding cock is inside!
I only had it put inside...
Hurry up and plunge it all in up to the base!
Ryouta's cock exclusively for sex...
It feels too good in the flesh!
Can you feel it?
This is what a child-making raw sex is!
Incredible!
You're sloshing deep inside me!
From your slender shota cock...
I'm gonna come!
I-It's here!
I'm coming!
Your outstanding shota cock
made me come!
That was the best!
From now on, I'll spread VR sex programs around,
and find myself some sex friends!
Toshidensetsu Series
The Cursed VR
A SakuraCircle Project
Encoded & Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization