My name is... Mary.
Soon, I'll be coming to take you to heaven.
Call from Mary-chan
"Mary, a loli demon, appears before virgin males
and leads them to the promised land?"
The rumors were true!
Hello?
My name is... Mary-chan.
I'm right behind you.
Behind me?!
You really are!
Nice to meet you, Mr. Sheep.
It's a pleasure to be here.
Oh, no. The pleasure is all mine.
Her eyelashes are so long, and they're as white as snow.
She's so frickin' cute!
Is there something wrong?
Oh no, nothing at all.
Mr. Sheep.
Mr. Sheep, what should I call you?
W-What should you call me?
Yes.
Um... Could you call me onii-chan?
Very well, onii-chan.
Onii-chan, would you turn around for a second?
U-Uh, sure. Like this?
Yep. Thank you, onii-chan.
Don't move, okay?
O-Okay.
Onii-chan, you're so hard!
Your dick's so cool, onii-chan.
Wow, it just keeps getting bigger and bigger!
Onii-chan, does this feel good?
Please excuse me for a second.
Onii-chan, it's starting to twitch.
Are you about to cum?
It's okay if you cum, onii-chan.
Wow, your dick let out so much juice!
We're only getting started, onii-chan.
Mary-chan, what's with the outfit?
I thought you'd like it, onii-chan, so I put it on.
Do you... not like this?
I like it!
I love it!
Really?
It doesn't look like it's turning you on, though...
Mary-chan, it's not what you think!
Your hand job took everything out of me, so...
Don't worry, onii-chan.
Just leave it to me.
Get hard again.
What's going on?
I just got hard again!
It's an aphrodisiac lotion.
Your dick is so yummy, onii-chan.
I-I...
You keep on cumming so much, onii-chan.
Onii-chan, how about you cum inside
your little sister's pussy now?
Okay, I'm gonna put it all the way inside me now.
Does my tight pussy feel good?
Onii-chan!
It feels so good!
Onii-chan, your hot dick is messing me up so much!
Let my pussy gulp down your milk!
This feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan, your dick is pouring its milk out inside me!
Onii-chan?
Would you like me better with bigger boobs?
They got bigger?!
I'll squeeze you even tighter, okay?
Onii-chan, does it feel good?
Onii-chan, are you gonna cum again?
That's fine. Cum as much as you want.
You came again!
One more time!
The musky scent of your cum is making my head spin, onii-chan.
It's so hot!
Wai... I just came... Mr. Sheep!
You're pumping your hot stuff inside me again!
Mr Sheep, please let me rest a little!
I can't move anymore.
You're inside me again!
You'll make me lose my mind at this rate!
I wonder if my heaven was to your liking, Mr. Sheep?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч