Hey, have you heard of Hasshaku-san?
Hasshaku-san
Hachishaku-san?
Hasshaku-san!
She's a large lady, over 240 centimeters in height...
She wears a white one-piece, and has a creepy laugh...
Eh? Is this a horror story?
Apparently she's appears around here!
Apparently she only appears before boys...
But those boys who meet her get their lower half eaten!
Stop! I seriously can't handle those kinds of stories!
Oh, but just hear me out!
Suehiro
Kakeru
Apparently when she eats  them, it's actually in a sexual way!
What's with that? Jeez!
Time to go home.
Mom and dad said they'll be home late...
Could that have been Hasshaku-san?
The boys that she comes across...
Get eaten from their waist downwards...
That boy was getting his cock eaten by Hasshaku-san...
Rather, was she sucking  his cock?
Were they doing the same thing as that lewd video...?
A hand? On a second-story window?
What should I do? She followed me home!
Am I going to be...
But before... Maybe she's just a ghost that does lewd things?
If that's the case, then...
Hasshaku-san, please come on in...
S-She's big...
But, she's super pretty...
Her breasts are big too...
Shall we?
Have you done this before?
Eh? D-Done what?
Guess not? Then...
What's this...? My balls are getting hot...!
No! W-What is this...?!
My cock is dripping wet and wrapped in warmth...
It feels so good!
My cock's really being sucked!
The hat is in the way, I can't see...
She's really sucking me with her mouth!
My cock... It feels so good!
It's very lewd...
Do you like seeing me sucking you off...?
Yes, it's very arousing...
What a lewd boy...
Amazing-!
D-Don't-!
My crotch feels like it's throbbing!
Some thing's gonna...! I'm gonna...!
It's coming!
It's coming out!
Amazing! My cock feels so good!
My cock feels so good!
S-So this is ejaculation...!
Did that feel good?
Y-Yes...
Now, put it here.
Eh? Um...
Put your cock between here.
Put my cock between her breasts...?
It feels amazing...
Who knew it felt so good being squeezed between breasts!
So cute...
You sure are going at it... Does it feel that good?
Y-Yes!
W-Why are we doing it like this?
Like this...?
No-!
It's to make it easier to thrust between my breasts...
My cock feels really good grinding your breasts like this!
You're being so rough!
It's going to peel my skin!
W-Wait!
There, there...
My cock-!
My cock's really sensitive-!
No, I'm going to cum again!
You came so much... It's overflowing from my chest...
I'm sorry... I couldn't hold back at all...
It's fine, don't worry...
My cock...
It's transformed into an adult one!
We're not done yet.
Only once you put it in my pussy, will you become an adult.
It's hot!
M-My cock, it melted and disappeared!
Don't worry, your cock is just thrashing about inside me!
M-My cock as gotten so big!
Wait! Please wait!
I'll make it bigger soon, so hang on!
I-I can't!
Your cock, it's great!
My cock, it's stimulating more from the increased size!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
Hasshaku-san...!
I'm... It's gonna...!
I-It's okay, let it out!
Let it out, cum inside!
I-I'm going to cum again!
I'm cumming!
Amazing... So this what it's like having sex...
It's gotten so big here...
We're not done yet...
It's your turn to make my pussy feel good.
It's my turn...
To thrust...
With my cock...!
H-Here...?
Is this alright...?
That's right...
Just like that, push it in...
Your cock, it feels really good...
My lower half wants to cum...
My hips won't stop!
Your pussy is making such lewd noises, Hasshaku-san!
It's the sound when my pussy feels too good!
My cock feels that good...?
I... I love your cock!
Hasshaku-san!
Hasshaku-san, your pussy...!
It's squeezing me, I'm gonna cum again...!
Do it! Cum in me! Drench my insides with it!
I'm cumming!
It's filling it up... Amazing, it's still shooting out so much...!
I might get addicted to this...
Right, good boy...
Make sure you do this and make lots of babies!
A long time ago...
There was a deity called Hatsushiyaku-sama in a small village.
Hatsuchiyaku-sama
When the males in the village would become of age,
They would have their virginity taken by Hatsushiyaku-sama.
Those that become intimate with Hatsushiyaku-sama in this way...
Became big and strong, and bought prosperity to the village.
However, along with the passage of time,
people began to forget about the existence Hatsushiyaku-sama as a deity.
If anyone was wondering what happened to Hatsushiyaku-sama...
She apparently travels freely, wherever she pleases,
fulfilling her purpose.
Remember to worship the lewd gods! - Shikkaku Fansubs