Well? It feels good, doesn't it?
You won't be satisfied with
normal sensations anymore.
Aquros, why do I have to do this?
Isn't it nice when things
like this happen?
Hurry up and come now.
Wasn't it great inside me?
Congratulations, now you are
an Angel Eater too.
What do you mean?
Next, have sex with this woman.
An angel!
I don't want to! Why should I?
I was forced to do it with you!
I'm going home now. Where's Selena?
You shan't be going home ever again.
Look.
Selena...
If you refuse to do as I say,
you and your beloved partner,
will meet a fate even more horrible.
Now, have sex with that angel.
No! Please don't.
No!
Tournament of the Gods
Battle of Hope
Now that you have become an Angel Eater,
you will absorb the power of angels
and become even stronger than before.
With that strength, you will rescue
Deras from Lagunard Labyrinth.
Deras?
That's correct.
If you are able to rescue Deras,
then I shall return you to
your normal body,
and I shall set you free with Selena.
The Lagunard Labyrinth is
connected to Hell.
The demons who guard this place
are much stronger than the monsters
you have been fighting.
Aquros has turned the champions of the
Tournament of the Gods into Angel Eaters
and sent them to this labyrinth.
Most have died while
investigating its depths.
The only ones left alive
are Gentobo and I.
And of course, the new addition, you.
Champion Sid!
What is this pain?
It's the reaction to the
angel eating power.
This medicine will ease the pain.
Why did I do that?
It's one of the medicine's side effects.
In suppressing the reaction
to the angel eating power,
the medicine creates an abnormally
high sexual desire.
The woman you had sex with
was the partner of a defeated
participant in the tournament.
He couldn't pay the penalty,
so she is working for free,
as someone on whom to work out
your sexual desires.
That's...
There's no choice but to fight.
Fight and grow stronger.
Selena, I will save you.
Azuki...
Deras, please hang on.
No matter the cost...
Deras Gata:
A master criminal who violated two hundred
angels with the fallen angel Aquros.
Located on the 67th floor of
the Lagnard Labyrinth.
Azuki, I'm trying so hard.
You'll praise me, won't you?
And, one year has passed...
This year's Tournament of the Gods
Champion is Azuki Mizuhara!
I won!
Now I can go see Sid!
Are you Deras?
I've saved Deras.
Now, hurry up and return
my body to normal!
I know of no way to return you to normal.
What did you say?
The agreement was that, if I saved Deras,
you would return my body to normal
and let Selena go!
If I hadn't said that, you wouldn't have
heeded my orders, would you?
And Selena is over there.
Selena!
Then you're safe?!
Selena?
It's no use.
That woman is no longer the
Selena you knew.
She is now my devoted female slave.
What are you saying?
Sid, I am now being used by
Champion Gentobo.
Sid, if you want me, I shall hand
myself over to you.
Oh that's right, you liked your girlfriend
better, didn't you, Sid?
Azuki!
This is a present from me to you
for rescuing Deras.
But isn't it admirable?
She came here after winning the
tournament just to see you.
Azuki has nothing to do with this!
Set her free!
Oh, you don't like my present then?
But since you cannot return to
your normal physical self,
you must take the medicine that suppresses
the reaction to the angel eating power.
You have no choice but to obey me.
With Deras, I will conquer
this whole world.
You shall live your whole life
fighting for us.
So seal your allegiance to me now
by violating that woman!
Selena!
Run now! Sid! Azuki!
Sid!
Azuki?
Selena told me everything.
I wanted to see you!
Selena, will this...
To deceive the enemy, act as an ally.
Azuki has a supply of the medicine.
Right now, you have to get away from here.
We'll find a way to return your
body to normal later.
You deceived me, didn't you?
Never underestimate me!
I would die before I would be your slave!
What a farce!
Do you truly believe that your battle
technique can overcome me?!
Sid, leave this to me.
Take Azuki and go.
I can't leave you here, Selena!
I'll follow you.
For now, just leave!
Selena, you must escape!
I won't let you get a step further!
Kurtz?
Welcome home, Kurtz.
Was it cold outside?
Kurtz? Do you mean Kurtzwell?
What are you saying?
Forgetting your own name!
How weird, Kurtz.
I'm not Kurtzwell.
Sorry, dinner's not ready yet.
Even though we've been
married almost a year,
I'm still not good at planning things out.
I'm sorry. Do you hate me now?
Well, I...
Please, Kurtz? Don't hate me, Kurtz.
I... I... by a lot of men!
No! Kurtz, save me! Kurtz!
No! No...
Sid...
She shared Selena's fate
and couldn't take it!
This can't be!
Francesca!
Why Francesca?!
Why would the Champion's partner receive
the same treatment as a loser's partner?
From the beginning, Aquros used us
and the people dear to us.
We were only tools to her desires.
Her only choice!
Sid, the exit to town is heavily guarded.
For now, hide in the Lagunard Labyrinth.
Aquros's henchmen won't easily
be able to follow you in there.
What about you, Kurtz?
Don't worry about me.
Hurry up and go!
Sid...
The Mizuhara Technique of the Heavens.
I borrowed it from my dad.
Is it okay to give it to me?
It was a promise.
Sid, you won, so he'll let you
have Mizuhara Dojo.
Sid, it's the reaction!
Hang on, the medicine...
No, I can't!
But that pain is...
I can't.
If I take the medicine,
I'll rape you, Azuki.
Sid...
I'll be okay.
It'll stop in a little while.
I can endure it that long.
Sid, I...
What's wrong, Kurtzwell?
You have such a terrible look on your
face.
It's not like you at all.
Francesca. Return our bodies to normal!
Oh, you found out then?
I'm so sorry.
It wasn't long before your wife
became a little "strange".
I'll kill you!
Are you all right, Sid?
Well, it's better, but it doesn't
go as far as "all right".
I'm sorry, Sid.
Why are you apologizing, Azuki?
So you're Sid?
I've come to retrieve you on
the Demon Lord's orders.
Demon Lord?
You've committed the heinous crime
of freeing Deras from Hell.
For that sin, the Demon Lord will
mete out punishment.
Wait!
Azuki has nothing to do with this!
You're the Demon Lord?
Sid, you have killed many monsters
in the Lagunard Labyrinth,
violated the persons of numerous women
and freed the evil one,
Deras Gata, from Hell.
For these crimes, I sentence you
to five thousand years in Hell.
That's not fair! Sid was tricked!
I know the whole of it,
but a crime is a crime.
I understand.
But Azuki has nothing to do with this.
Please return her to the other world.
No way!
I don't want to go!
I want to be with Sid!
Lord Demon, if Sid's going to Hell,
then I want to go with him!
You can't!
You're innocent, Azuki!
I can't take you to Hell!
No! I'm definitely going!
Sid, you promised that we'd
always be together!
Please, Lord Demon, let me go too!
You want to be with Sid that much?
Yes!
Then I shall give you one last chance.
Defeat Deras and Aquros
with your own hands.
Do that, and I shall take the
angel eating power from Sid.
You have until the next reaction
to atone for your crimes.
Really?
Sid!
Go now!
So you were hiding in the
labyrinth after all.
You won't get away again, Sid.
I'll kill you and have that
woman for my slave.
Gentobo, we've been deceived by Aquros.
There's no reason for us to fight!
You're a naïve kid!
I wanted to become an Angel Eater.
What did you say?
Do you think the world will let you go
your own way peacefully?
There are as many morals and ideals in
this world as there are people.
Well, I shall begin now, brat.
Kurtzwell!
Sid?
So you've come, Sid.
Selena!
Sid...
She's such a handful!
Rebelling against me!
Aquros, why do you do such horrible things?
So that we may be together.
Deras and I love each other.
But I am angel, and he is
a malevolent deity.
Our love is not allowed in this world.
So we will conquer the world
and create a world where
we can be together.
For that, I would do anything!
That's not right!
But, so that I can be with Azuki,
I have no choice but to defeat you both!
It seems that we have
no choice but to fight.
I'll show you our power!
Sid!
That's impossible!
We can't just randomly attack.
All of you're attacks just
ricochet off Aquros.
First we have to defeat Aquros!
But how?
I'll be the bait.
Then you break her shield with
the Fire Technique.
Azuki!
I'm going!
Sid!
Deras...
Aquros...
Die!
Sid!
Sid, I'll be waiting for you in Hell!
We did it, Sid!
You did well.
As promised, I shall return you
to your normal body.
But when I do this, all the power you have
acquired here will be lost to you.
Is that acceptable?
Sid!
What's happening?
It's the pain reaction.
This causes greater pain than
becoming an Angel Eater.
No way!
The pain can be alleviated
with the medicine.
But the side effects will be
greater than before.
If you leave him as he is, there is
a chance that he will die.
The only one that can reach him is you,
but then your life may be in danger.
Only you can choose.
Sid?
You can't, Azuki.
I...
Azuki...
Sid, I'm not afraid of dying,
if I'm with you.
So, Sid, for ever and ever...
Are you awake, Sid?
Selena...
Where am I?
The Mizuhara Dojo.
Bilicus brought you home.
Sid, you've been sleeping for three days!
For three days?
What about Azuki?!
She's all right.
Right now, she's making dinner for you.
Selena, I did an awful thing to Azuki.
Don't worry about that.
Hurry up and go see her.
Azuki...
Sid...
Sid!
Azuki, I'm sorry...
It's okay.
It was all for me anyway.
Sid, I won't be parted from you again!
Azuki, we'll always be together.
What's the matter?
Fighting like that is not fit to inherit
the Mizuhara Dojo!
Yes!
Geez, I can't believe he's the one
who won the tournament.
Really!
And after you and I went through all that
play-acting just to get him to enter.
What a waste! Right, Azuki?
I'm satisfied, because Dad finally
believed in Sid's strength
and promised to let me be with him.
Work hard, Sid!
FIN