Anyone still here?
Oh, Hasegawa-kun?
A young girl like you shouldn't
be loitering around here.
It's getting late.
Um...
It's dangerous, you know?
I-I'm sorry.
I'll go home right away.
Goodbye!
What's this?
Ah, now I get it.
No wonder you were
waiting here for so long.
I-It's not what you think.
That's just a...
He's not coming.
I already sent him home, after all.
Huh? Why would you do that?
Why indeed, I wonder...
I'm going home...
Not so fast, young lady.
Stay still!
No talking in the classroom.
L-Leave me alone.
S-Stop!
Wh-Why are you doing this?
Stop it!
Teacher, please help me!
Hm, what do you mean?
Don't you know?
I'm technically a teacher too.
No, stop!
N-No!
No, I don't want any of this!
No, not there!
If you keep doing that, I'll...
I-I'll pee myself!
You're so mean.
I'm not a toilet you know?
Peeing in the classroom?
You're such a bad girl.
A bad, bad girl.
I'm confiscating your panties!
Look at that, I can see
your pee hole perfectly.
No, don't look at it!
Something hard is hitting me...
It feels weird.
It's going inside me!
It hurts!
Stop!
Don't put it inside me!
It hurts so much!
I told you not to put it inside me...
Ouch!
Please, stop moving!
My butt hole?
No, don't touch that!
Stop stirring it up like that!
Jeez, no talking in the classroom, remember?
Pipe down a bit!
You know, I love cute little girls like...
Hm?
Hey, you, what's the matter?
H-Hey!
Hanako of the Toilet.
Seriously, teacher patrols?
What age do the others think we're living in?
It'd suck if I saw a ghost or something.
A-A ghost?
Man's Bathroom
Out of use
Knock first!
It came from in here...
the bathroom?
Knock first!
Anyone in there?
Yep!
How stupid.
What the heck?
Um, this is a bathroom, right?
Who are you supposed to be?
A real, live human, huh?
You did well to come in here.
It's a real damn ghost! I'm gonna die!
You...
Would you like to have sex with me?
Sex?!
How'd we get to that topic?!
Well, y'see, I've been thinking that
it's about time I passed on to Heaven already.
I'm bound to this area, so I've found
it difficult to search for a partner.
It's quite the troubling affair.
There's just no freakin' way.
I'm not some one-way ticket to Heaven!
Besides, I'd never do it with a little girl like you!
Is that right?
You see, I was raped by a man
I didn't even like and died in the process.
Man's Bathroom
Out of use
Knock first!
And it just so happened that the place I died
in got remodeled into a boy's bathroom.
How vexing.
So, if I have sex with a man I want
to have sex with, I should be able to pass on.
Or so I think.
But I'm a teacher!
Good grief.
If a teacher like you existed back when I was alive,
it might never have come to this.
So let's just do this, okay?
I said, no!
I'll never lay my hands on a student!
You ignorant wretch.
Very well. How about this?
If you're unable to get a boner after
everything I do, I'll let you go.
I-Is this spectral binding?!
I wonder how long you'll be able to resist.
Don't! Stop that now!
See? You're already erect.
It's so big, too...
I wonder if I'll be able to fit it in my mouth.
Th-This sensation is...
Oh, so that's what happened.
I grew from your sperm.
And now I feel more powerful than ever!
Wh-What exactly are you?
I have a name, you know.
I am Hanako.
Hasegawa Hanako.
Ah, so you're Hanako of the Toilet!
How dare you tack "toilet" on to my name.
Sorry...
Good grief.
Something just fell.
Th-This is nothing.
Let's go.
Not only did you get hard,
but you came as well.
You'll listen to what I say now.
Being outside is amazing!
Why are we in the pool?
Gazing upon the moon whilst in a pool
is a rite of youth, is it not?
Hanako-san?
Now, give it to me.
You promised.
Please be gentle. I'm not a virgin.
Please comfort me with your huge, strong dick.
Alright.
Here I go.
H-Hanako-san?
Are you okay?
I apologize.
The memory of fear from the last time
I did this is still vivid in my mind.
Then let's just stop now!
Don't be ridiculous.
You're just like the man
I loved back when I was alive.
You're the only one who can
dispel this fear from me.
Hanako-san!
You dummy, you're going too fast!
You're rubbing me so intensely inside.
No, I'm gonna...
I can feel your hot stuff filling me up inside!
Hanako-san!
Look, I've grown again thanks
to your strong spiritual energy.
Do you feel satisfied?
Of course I'm not!
Let's go to the next place!
What happened to all your energy?
Is it wrong that we're having
sex in the gym's storage room?
How are my hip movements?
How does it feel to have your tip
getting played with so deep inside me?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you really this pathetic?
Is your dick the only good thing about you?
And just when I could take it all in, too.
Come on, pour your hot stuff inside me!
You don't have to hold back, just let it go!
It feels so good!
I'm going to get hooked on this!
How's this?
Getting raped from a bed in the infirmary.
Even better, getting raped in that position.
S-Spectral binding again?!
How does it feel to have your asshole toyed with?
Still, I'm falling head over heels for this giant.
Could we take a break?
What are you saying?
We're only just getting started.
I just finished growing into an adult.
I can finally fit all of it inside me.
Let's have some fun, adult sex now!
Here, how's this?
How does it feel to be raped as if you were a woman?
You're so pathetic and yet,
you still call yourself a teacher?
You came so many times already,
but I haven't even cum once.
You fucking useless horny man!
I am a teacher!
Don't you dare look down on me!
W-Wait!
You're being too rough all of a sudden!
No, no, no!
I was so surprised,
I turned back to normal...
You dummy!
Hana-chan!
No, don't move right now!
You're cute just the way you are now!
Don't say such embarrassing things!
I-I'm cumming!
Please ascend to Heaven with my dick!
I will! I'll definitely ascend!
Please give me more of your hot semen!
Did I satisfy you?
You fool.
That ends today's remedial lessons.
Weren't you going to ascend?
I suppose.
It's all thanks to you that I can walk around freely.
You were so passionately
courting me last night, after all.
Courting? I was just taking care
of you out of concern as a teacher.
I know.
That's why...
To Mr. Okada
Please take this.
This is how I feel.
Hana-chan...
Thank you.
Hana-chan?
Are you going to ascend?
No, you can't!
I just started falling in love with you!
Wait, what happened?
Look, I broke my binding to the school!
That's it?!
What are you saying?
It's a big deal, I'm free now.
But we don't know what will happen in the future.
I'll need you to keep giving me your energy.
So that means we'll be together from now on?
Indeed. We'll be together until you die.
Although we might be together even after death.
Oh, well...
You really are such a big fool.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hdr
ediror: aux
quality control: fyurie