Sid, I'll do as Dad said.
I'll enter the Tournament of the Gods.
I decided to become Bilicus's partner.
I promised Dad.
He said I could be with you then, Sid.
Azuki...
Sid, I see it.
Is that the Tournament of the Gods?
Tournament of the Gods
Blue Storm Battle
Sid...
If you keep staring, they'll think
you're from the country.
Selena, I'm not a child anymore!
I'm sorry!
No, excuse me.
Sorry!
Let's see, the entrant is Sid, and
his partner is Selena, right?
Yes!
Maybe you two are lovers?
No! Selena is like my older sister!
Well, we're all signed up.
Let's have a pre-victory celebration!
You're overhasty, Selena!
What are you saying?
Your state of mind is important in
this kind of thing, you know.
And if you don't win, Azuki will
have to marry Bilicus, right?
Yeah, I have no choice but to win.
If I win, then I can be with Azuki.
It's my promise to Azuki's father.
But Azuki is...
Sid!
Azuki!
You're going to be in the Tournament
of the Gods too, Sid?
Yeah.
Fight hard, okay?
I'll be rooting for you!
I'll definitely win!
You were the weakest one even at
the Mizuhara Dojo.
You'll never get through even the
first round of the tournament.
That's not true!
Sid will make it through
all the rounds and win!
Then I shall look forward to fighting you.
Well, Miss, let us go.
Now that Sid has entered the
Tournament, he is our enemy.
Well, see you, Sid.
You have to win, okay?
Please try not to lose in a fashion that will
dishonor the name of the Mizuhara Dojo.
So let's go ahead with the
pre-victory celebration!
It's on me tonight!
I'll definitely win, Azuki!
And then...
Geez, you drank so much.
Selena,
why are you taking you're top off?!
Because it's hot!
I'm a man, you know?!
And a young one too!
I know.
I also know that you're still a virgin.
You're in trouble if you underestimate me.
I've been like a mother to you
for a long time!
So be even more understanding!
Or else, you know...
It's okay.
I'll make you a man, Sid.
Just as your father made me a woman.
My father did?
I loved him.
That's why I asked him to make love to me.
But that happened after your mother died.
Or else, even though I loved him...
Selena...
So...
But this is totally different.
It's for Azuki too, you know?
What?
Azuki is probably still a virgin too, right?
Probably.
The first time for a girl is a very
painful thing, you know?
And if her partner is a virgin who doesn't
know his left from his right...
Wouldn't you feel bad if her important
first time was like that?
And it seems you're not saying
"no" down here.
I want you too, Sid.
But I don't know what to do.
It's okay.
I'll teach you.
Now, take them off.
Won't you take them off for me?
That's it. Slowly, as if to highlight it.
Also, so that you don't make
your partner nervous.
If you can make them anticipate it,
even better.
Next, hold your partner to
take away their anxiety.
Then let your partner know
"my body is excited."
Slide your body against theirs.
Go ahead, touch me.
Wow! It's so soft!
That's it, gently.
Ouch! That hurts, Sid!
Sorry.
You're using too much force.
Understand, girls are very delicate here.
Gently, like this.
You look for where your partner
reacts the most.
Yes, it feels good.
How pathetic.
That's not true.
Although you let it out,
it's already healthy again.
Welcome! I'm your waitress, Sayaka.
Please, have a menu.
Thank you.
Sid, I'll treat you.
Really? Then a tofu-cake for me!
Are you going to be participating
in the tournament, Sir?
I was the partner of a
participant last year.
But we lost a battle.
So I've had to work at this
bar for free since then.
But that's only until this year's
tournament is over.
I'll be allowed to return to
my hometown soon!
Oh, that's how it works.
Who's he?
That man is the Champion, Krank.
No one can defy the Champion in this town.
Sayaka!
I'm being called, so...
Welcome, Champion.
Sayaka, you're as cute today as ever.
So console my "son" as usual.
Yes.
That...
No, Sid. He's the Champion.
There's no way you could
beat him right now.
But...
I can't wait anymore.
So this is the level-up dungeon,
Lagunard Labyrinth.
Sid, be careful, okay?
Don't try to do the impossible.
I'll be all right.
After all, my goal is to
win the tournament.
There's no use dying during training.
Do your best, Sid.
My husband who died in the
tournament rests in this grave.
Please return my husband's sword to me!
I've seen this girl before.
Thank you, Sid.
Please guard your life, so that the one
who loves you won't suffer.
The jewel on Kara's forehead is
supposed to be very valuable.
Moutaijin of the Thieves' Guild
put out a reward for Kara.
She hides in the labyrinth.
So it's time for the first round.
Selena, will I really be able to win?
You'll be all right.
Have some confidence.
There's still time before the battle, but...
Azuki!
I'm going to go get something
to drink, okay?
But we have drinks here.
Stupid. She was being considerate.
Do your best, Sid.
It's a victory charm.
Thank you. Now I'll definitely win!
Introducing the young warrior, Sid!
So hurry up and screw me!
Even I know what happens to
the loser's partner!
I bet you're scared, because you've
never had a girl before.
I have so had one!
Then why don't you get started?
Not that I'd feel anything with
your pathetic technique.
I'll make sure you feel something!
It doesn't feel good at all.
Sorry.
No!
Azuki!
What are you doing in a
place like this, Azuki?
I saw you win in the first round,
and I decided I couldn't sit there
and chance losing.
So I decided to train in
this labyrinth too.
But you should have been able to
kill that monster easily, Azuki.
Practice was different.
No matter how many times
I killed the monster,
it kept coming after me.
I never thought about it until now.
For the first time I realized my
opponent is a living creature,
and all of a sudden I got scared.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Have you ever been scared
when you fought, Sid?
I'm scared.
But I want to become stronger
so that I can protect those
that are important to me.
So...
Sid...
Sid, your strength is different than mine.
I'll think about it for a while.
Hold on. I'll help you.
Good, you've come to!
You saved me?
I'm Sid. You are?
I am Kuraiya.
You fell into a trap meant to catch me.
You?
You're the one on that wanted poster!
But why me?
I heard that the Kara fear people.
Because you fell in the trap
meant for me, and...
you tried to save Chururu.
It seems it's been discovered that
I'm hiding in the labyrinth,
and traps have been set
all over the place.
Yes, the thieves have posted
a reward for you.
You should be careful.
The humans are after the jewels
in our foreheads.
But the Kara can't live
without their jewel.
But that's...
To kill such kind people just for jewels...
To humans, we Kara are just
another type of monster.
That's not true.
Monsters attack people, but you saved me.
You're my treasured friend.
You'll be my friend?
I'm so glad!
It's been just Chururu and me for so long.
Thank you, Sid.
Sid, did you know this?
When Kara are reborn, they become
either an angel or a devil.
If possible, I want to become an angel.
Well then, be careful.
Sid, please do your best.
Thank you, I'll come again!
What?! A Kara in the labyrinth?
Yes, the customers were saying
that one was caught.
It can't be Kuraiya!
The red jewel on your forehead means
you're still a virgin, right?
Well, moi knows that the one that
knows men, the blue stone,
is the one that brings the higher prices.
Looks like moi's going to have moi some fun.
Looks like you're a little late.
I just handed the Kara girl over to the
Moutaijin a while ago.
What?
Bro, I don't even know how many
times I've done it.
It's the orders of the Moutaijin.
The more she does it with men,
the more the jewel on her forehead shines,
and the more the price goes up.
Kuraiya!
Kuraiya, are you okay?
Sid...
Oh my cute pee-ons!
But weaklings who lose to one little
boy aren't MY pee-ons.
You! How dare you do such horrible
things to Kuraiya?!
Like you think you're going to
last against moi?
Here I come!
No way!
A little sword attack just
will not work on moi!
Shit!
That you think to defy moi with
only your puny strength!
Really! That's why moi hates kids!
Sid!
I'm all right.
I'll save you.
Sid.
For a Kara, for me,
you're risking your life in battle.
My only friend!
I won't let you kill him!
With the power of this jewel, I'II...
Kuraiya!
Kuraiya! Kuraiya!
Kuriaya...
You!
Moi's important jewel!
That it was used on a brat like this!
This can't be happening!
Sorry, Kuraiya.
I wasn't able to protect you.
Kuraiya...
Sid, it seems that I did become an angel.
Thank you, Sid.
You can do anything
The dream of one day
Is not your imagination
Believe that you can do it
If you're hurt
We're under the same sky
I'm watching you
Feel my presence
When you start running
The winds of fate will change
It's a little sad
Because yesterday gets farther away
Step by step
Wind up the unraveling threads
If you put your heart into it
You can go where you want
You can do anything
Chase the dream
Show your imagination
I like your shining eyes
Don't forget
In any circumstances
That I am watching you
That I am here for you