Is someone still here?
Oh, it's you Hasegawa-kun.
You mustn't be here this late.
For a little girl as yourself to be all alone...
Um...
It's dangerous.
I-I'm sorry!
I'll go home!
Goodbye!
This is... Oh, I see.
Your recipient didn't show.
No, that's-!
No, he won't be coming.
Since I sent him home.
Why would you do such...?
Yes, I wonder why?
I'm going home!
Wait a second!
You mustn't make a scene in the classroom.
D-Don't come closer!
N-No!
W-Why would you do such thing? Please don't!
Help me! Sensei-
What is it? Don't you know? I'm a teacher as well.
N-No!
No, it's dirty!
Not there, no! If you pull that-!
I-I'm going to wet myself!
How awful! I'm not a toilet, you know.
For you to wet yourself in the classroom... What a naughty girl.
A truly naughty girl.
I'm confiscating these soiled panties!
How's this? I can see your pee-hole!
No, don't look at me there!
Something hard is...
It's... It's entering me...!
Ouch!!
Stop, it hurts! Don't put it in-!
Ouch...!
I said not to put it in...
I-It hurts!
Please, don't thrust into me!
My butthole! Not there, please!
Don't stir around the insides-!
Jeez, I told you not to make a scene in the classroom.
Settle down!
I actually prefer little cute girls like yourself-
Hey you, what's wrong?
Hey... Hey you!
Urban Legend Series
Hanako-san of the bathrooms
Episode 1
Seriously, since when do teachers have to do the watch duties?
I hope no ghosts will pop out...
I-Is that a ghost?
From here? The bathroom?
Please knock!
Excuse me?
Come in!
Please knock!
How silly!
What the hell?
Isn't this the bathroom?
What do you want?
A human being?
I'm surprised you made it in here.
A real ghost?
I-I'm going to be killed!
You...
Would you not care to have sex with me?
Sex-?!
Why are you talking about suddenly-?
It's nothing major. I just felt that I should move on to the afterlife in due course.
I haven't found a suitable candidate as I'm bound to the place.
I was in a pickle!
This isn't right!
Besides, I couldn't do such thing to a little girl like yourself!
Is that so?
I was raped by a man that I did not love.
I died during the incident.
And on top of that, the place was turned into the male bathroom.
How annoying.
So that's how it went.
If I could have intercourse with a man I love, I can pass on to the afterlife.
Possibly.
But I'm a teacher!
Good grief... If there were teachers like you around, I wouldn't be here like this.
So please help.
No way! I couldn't do such thing to someone like a student!
You stubborn imbecile!
Fine!
Then how's this?
If you can resist getting an erection I will accept defeat.
I'm paralyzed!
S-Stop it at once!
Are you sure you couldn't do such things to students?
Hey! You mustn't-!
Stop it!
Oh my, you've gotten so hard from only licking.
It's indeed very menacing.
I wonder if this will fit in my mouth...
This sensation...!
I see, my body's grown from inducing the semen?
I also feel power flowing through my body!
What the hell is this thing-?!
I'm not a 'thing', my name is Hanako. Hasegawa Hanako.
Oh, the Hanako-san of the bathrooms?
It's rude to call a girl such things!
I'm sorry.
Jeez...
You dropped something.
I-It's nothing. Shall we go?
Since not only did you become erect but came as well.
I'll have you do as I say.
Being outside sure is nice!
Why did we move to the pool?
A secret rendezvous at the pool... Isn't it youthful?
Hanako-san?
C'mon, let's do it. You did promise, after all.
Please be gentle.
Though I am not a virgin...
Please console me with your big penis.
Yes.
I'm putting it in.
H-Hanako-san! What's wrong?
Sorry.
I'm still traumatized from last time...
Then let's stop at once!
Don't be silly!
You look similar to a man I once loved.
You are the only one that can help me through this.
Hanako-san!
T-This is too sudden-!
It's too big! It's churning up my insides!
I-I'm gonna-!
Y-Your hot semen is entering my stomach!
Hanako-san!
Would you look at this! I've grown again from your sexual energies.
Are you satisfied?
Of course.
Not!
Let's us continue!
What happened to that energy from before?
A one-on-one in a dark gym shed.
Doesn't this excite you?
How's my hip grinding?
How does it feel to stir around my deepest parts?
C'mon, say something!
You're pitiful!
Is it only your penis that's grand?
Since you can put it in fully since I've grown...
C'mon, c'mon! Spurt your thick semen deep inside me!
You don't need to hold back, just cum!
It feels so good! I'm gonna get addicted!
Then how about this?
Getting forcibly raped in the school infirmary.
In that position.
I'm paralyzed again-!
To be turned on from your butt... How's this?
Nevertheless, what an adorable penis.
Please give me a break-!
What are you talking about?
We're just getting started.
I've grown this much. It would be a waste not to try.
It's finally in.
Should we not enjoy some adultly romance?
Hey, how's this? How's this?
Jeez!
For you to get excited from being like this...
How pitiful of you.
And you're a teacher as well.
Even though you've came countless times,
I haven't had the pleasure yet!
You damn pitiful sex-fiend!
Don't make fun of teachers!
No! This is too sudden!
No, no! No!
That was too intense! I've turned back into my original form!
Idiot...
Hana-chan!
You can't thrust now-!
You're the cutest in your usual form!
Don't say such embarrassing things!
I-I'm coming-!
Let's go to the afterlife together!
I will! Let's go together!
Pour more of your thick semen inside me!
Were you satisfied?
You idiot...
This is it for today.
So, weren't you passing on to the afterlife?
I guess.
But, I can move about more because of you.
And it's hard to turn down such intense courtship.
Courtship?
I was worried about you, as a teacher.
I know, that's why...
Please accept this. My feelings.
Hana-chan...
Thank you.
Hana-chan?
Are you passing on now?
I don't want that!
I've just fallen in love with you!
What happened?
See? I'm no longer bound!
That's all?
What are you talking about? I'm now a free spirit!
Eh?
However, who knows what will happen.
You must continue to give me your life essence.
Does that mean we will be together from now?
Of course, until death do us part.
Even if you die, we might still be together.
Um, well...
You really are a silly person!