All the characters depicted
are 18 years old and above
please take me
Is that an abandoned cat? That's sad...
It really is...
Hey, Hana-chan! Can't you just take it home?
There's no way that I can!
Well, we're ghosts so we can't raise a cat...
I know! You don't have to tell me that.
I have friends, I have someone I love...
I'm quite happy but in the end, I'm just a ghost.
I'm aware that being together
with the isn't possible...
Being unable to save a single kitten
reminded me of my own futility.
I never saw Hana-chan this sad before!
Maybe something happened
between her and Okuda-sensei.
It can't be helped...
Should we lend her a hand?
So you prefer bigger breasts, huh?
Your breasts were small earlier,
but they got bigger now!
I can transform specific parts of
my body back and forth at will.
You like titjobs, right?
Your cock is so big that it's sticking out of my tits!
Alright then, I'm going to start giving you service.
It's bulging so much!
Just how backed up are you?
Squeeze me more!
Your order is accepted!
Your cock is so hot that it feels
like it's gonna burn me!
How is it?
Are you enjoying my tits?
You can come just like this.
Please spray your hot semen on my tits!
Wow, you sure came a lot!
You got me so soiled and sticky!
Please make me feel good next, okay?
Please pound my lewd pussy
using your sturdy cock!
It's pounding me!
Your cock is so stimulating as it slides inside me!
I love the shape of this cock!
This could deform me inside!
Please shake your hips however you want!
I can barely keep myself conscious!
Please make yourself feel good
to your heart's content!
Your cock feels too good!
Please... let's come together at the same time!
I got sullied by your semen!
Oh, I wonder who it is.
Oh, Mary-chan? I want to ask you a favor...
Yes, you can ask me anything.
I want to ask for advice about Hana-chan...
Yes, count me in.
Does it feel good?
Not this pose!
Your tail-cock is so cute!
I'm coming!
You can come.
That was an incredible ejaculation.
There's plenty of it dripping on my tits.
Are you alright?
I want to make you feel good next, Hasshaku-san.
I understand.
Make me feel good a lot, okay?
It's going in!
I can't wait any longer now,
so hurry up and start moving.
Okay!
Here it is!
Kakeru, you're doing great!
Your pussy is squeezing more than usual!
That's because you're giving your best, Kakeru!
It's alright, come!
Fill my womb up with your semen!
I-It's coming out!
Here it comes!
Sorry for disturbing your delightful moment.
Mary-chan, what's the matter?
I actually came here for an advice.
That's not good.
I'll help Sadako-chan!
Umm...
Are you all friends of Hana-chan?
Well, that's right...
Sensei, you were busy lately
so Hana-chan said that she
wanted to give you a reward!
Huh? I never said anything like that!
Weren't you worried about it?
We're gonna help you out so cheer up!
Saying that out of the blue...
Leave it all to us!
That's right!
All of you...
Don't I have any say about this?
Before we proceed,
I'm Mary-chan, the phantom love doll!
Uhh...
You should just give in.
There's no way they'll stop
now that it came to this.
Even if you say that...
Oh my... You're sleepy down here.
I'm out of gas down here at the moment.
It's alright!
What the hell was that?!
My drool acts as an aphrodisiac, you see.
Mary's aphrodisiac is as amazing as always.
Wait!
Does it hurt?
I got so stiff...
It's a highly potent drug that'll get you stiff
until your balls are empty!
Come without holding yourself back, okay?
Hey, stop that!
You are quite stubborn.
Fine, then.
Me too,
I want to
try something.
I'll do this...
...and voila!
And then, I'll do this...
How is it?
I'm copying Mary and made
just a part of my body grow up.
Isn't it sliding in between the tips of my nipples?
Do adult tits feel good?
I'll bet that it feels like it's gonna melt!
It's hard as a rock...
You sure love tits, huh?
Your pleasure passes through my breasts!
It's alright... Shoot it out!
That's incredible!
You finally got in the groove.
It's too early to get worn out.
The night has just begun!
I have to tell them to stop, but...
Okuda-sensei...
Having a cool cock on top of
being a hot guy isn't fair!
Hey there! You can't have him!
I think I understand now why
Hana-chan is so into you!
Your cock is so stiff even now...
Imagine if there are two Hana-chans...
Won't that be amazing?
Huh?!
Transformation complete!
Alright then, what do you
want us to do?
I want you to suck it.
Al...
...right!
The tip got wet just like a woman's...
Does it feel that good?
I can't!
You came with such an amazing amount!
So the amount of your come doubles
when there are two Hana-chans.
I ended up doing it again.
I'm supposed to be a teacher. I'm the worst!
I'm doing this because I wanted to.
Bad things are bad!
Let me handle this.
Is that what burdens you.
Relive your past and forget all your troubles.
My body shrunk!
Now you're a boy through and through.
Now you just have to
show the girl you love about how you truly feel.
Okay then, we'll be on our way.
The only thing left is for you two to be lovey-dovey!
Do your best.
I always wanted to ask this...
What am I for you, Hana-chan?
Maybe I'm just a replacement for the
boy you used to love or something.
You imbecile! There's no way that it's true!
I...
I, Hasegawa Hanako...
do cherish you from the bottom of my heart.
Me too...
I love you!
Hana-chan...
Your cock is throbbing, Megumi-kun!
I wanted to have lots of sex with you...
Oh no...
I'm happy!
Me too, I wanted us to do this a lot!
Do it today with all your strength!
You could've always done it more intense...
I'm scared that it might make you remember
about the time you were raped if I do it hard!
So that's why you always
hold yourself back at sex.
You're too kind for your
own good, Megumi-kun!
You could piston fuck my pussy
and make yourself feel good...
It feels like your pussy is gonna
snap my cock off... What's this?!
That's because I love you a lot, Megumi-kun!
My pussy doesn't want to let go of you!
Hana-chan!
Just wait for a second!
My body went back to normal?
Sorry, I'll pull it out immediately!
It's the cock of the man I love...
I'm not scared at all!
But...
You should properly have sex
with me even if you're an adult,
or else I'll curse you for eternity!
I love you!
Wow!
It's bulging on my belly from inside my pussy!
Don't hold back and pound my
loli pussy with all your strength!
I love you perverted cock!
I'm coming!
I'm going to take it all, so shoot everything out!
Spurt it out!
Spurt it out while you're thrusting your cock!
You're planting a lot of your seeds into my pussy!
Hana-chan, let's be together.
Here?
In my apartment.
Do you mean living together?
Yes.
I know that I am but unworthy of you.
Even so, please take care of me from now on.
Despite feeling this much happiness,
I somehow can't shake this feeling of anxiety away.
I wondered why I have to be a ghost...
What's with this?
Sorry, it's been abandoned and I saw it yesterday.
I couldn't bear leaving it alone.
Could it be that you're allergic
to cats? What should I do?
I'm not...
I'm not!
Why are you crying, then?
It's just that I'm filled with happiness
and all my troubles are gone
that I don't know what to do.
Hana-chan...
Let's think together for the kitten's name.
Okay!
Toshidensetsu Series
We want to show our gratitude for being able to get to know about all these awesome urban legends.
— the whole staff
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization