I can't believe this is VR.
Clap! Clap!
Do you need something, Miss?
Excuse me.
May I have a moment of your time?
Something wrong?
This is inside a game, right?
Yeah...
Excellent! Seems like I was able
to enter without any problems!
Oh boy, I found a weirdo.
Excuse me, I'm sorry for the sudden request, but...
Please have sex with me!
Wh-What are you saying?!
I want to try having sex in VR!
That's not possible!
This is an all-ages game.
Wanna try?
You're too close...
I'll research what you like.
Search complete.
How's this?
Nin-nin.
Wha...
Those aren't clothes you can buy in this game!
Are you in the mood for sex yet?
I'm not!
Then how about now?
Ta-dah!
This is what you like, isn't it, Ryouta-kun?
I'll take that as a yes.
But you can't have sex in this game.
Finding out whether we can or not
will be part of the fun.
Miss?!
How are my boobs?
They feel real!
Please try touching my nipples.
I can feel it!
Even though we're in a game?
Yes.
Try licking them.
All men like boobs, don't they?
You're like a baby.
You look so cute when you're trying your
hardest to suck on my boob, Ryouta-kun!
How's my boob taste?
Milk won't come out no matter
how hard you suck, though.
That tickles!
Your dick has gotten big, Ryouta-kun.
Y-You're right.
My boobs turned you on, huh?
Let's take off those clothes.
Take them off?
Nin-nin.
What happened?! They disappeared!
And my dick is actually hard!
I just rewrote the program a little bit.
Just who are you?
I can't wait any longer!
Let's make your dick feel real good.
Your dick is getting really stiff.
Looks like you're more than ready to go.
This is called a tit fuck.
Did you know that, Ryouta-kun?
Yeah, I saw it in a manga once.
You're not so innocent, huh?
There's a strong male smell coming from your tip.
Your dick's getting bigger
between my boobs. It's so cute!
Are you going to cum in my boob-pussy?
Go ahead and cum.
Cum in a game?
What are you worried about!
You're in a game,
so you can cum as much as you want!
No need to hold back.
I-I'm...
Wow, there's so much cum!
How much were you saving up?
I really came.
Did it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
Let's do something that feels even better.
Even better?
Let's change the scene.
Please close your eyes.
Like this?
Yes. You can open them now.
Is this...
I linked this to another game and transferred us there.
My clothes changed!
If we're here, we can have as much sex as we like.
Sex with you?
Hey, you need to call me "Senpai" here!
My cute junior.
Senpai...
The way you stare at me makes me...
Makes you horny?
You still came so much even on your second time.
You're so dirty.
Sadako-senpai, please let me have sex with you.
Okay.
Please fuck me raw with your amazing dick!
Your dick's hitting me so deeply!
Please start moving!
It's coming!
Your dick's not even that thick, but...
It's long, so it's rubbing against the roof of my pussy.
It feels so good!
And you're trying so hard to move your hips.
It's so cute.
Even though we're in a game...
It feels too good!
More! More!
Do me harder!
Please use your dick on my dirty pussy!
Fuck me hard!
Senpai!
So good!
Your thrusting feels so good!
I love your dick!
I'm cumming!
Please give me your dick milk deep inside my pussy!
Give it to your senpai! Give it to me deep!
Shoot out your hot cum inside me!
Sadako-senpai...
I'm seriously going to get addicted to this...
Ryouta-kun, you're not done yet, are you?
I'm not. I wanna keep going.
Copy that.
You've cummed three times now, but you can still get hard.
I think this amazing dick needs closer inspection.
N-No...
If you keep rubbing it like that...
There's pre-cum leaking from your dick.
Your dick's gotten all wet.
I-I'm gonna cum!
Already?
I can't do my inspection if you cum.
But...
Geez.
No cumming until I say you can, okay?
Just hold on a little longer.
Okay, you can cum.
Very good.
I'm all dirty now.
You must be exhausted after all that, Ryouta-kun.
Wait, you're hard again?!
I can't stop it.
There might be something wrong with me!
Looks like you need some first-aid.
Please stay still.
I'll make it all better.
Your dick's even harder than before.
Can you see it coming inside me?
Yeah...
I'm going to start moving.
How's my treatment?
Please let me know if it starts to hurt, okay?
I'm going to make your dick... feel better in no time!
I can feel your body temperature from your dick!
You might be... running a little bit of a fever.
Try relaxing.
Shoot everything you have inside me!
Cum and make yourself feel better!
I was cummed in again!
Good boy.
You worked really hard today.
You're a good boy, Ryouta-kun.
A very good boy.
You're going to put it inside me again?
Having it thrust inside me from this position is...
I'm... never going to be able to forget your dick, Ryouta-kun!
Oh, no! I'm cumming!
This is sex in VR, Ryouta-kun.
I guess he was so tired he fell asleep.
A dream?
Huh?
I'm out of the game! Why am I...
You came again, Ryouta.
Who are you?
You really can't tell?
Are you Sadako-san?
Ding-ding.
I'm a collection of ghosts in one,
so I can become any shape and size I want.
So, let's pick up where we left off in the game.
The pussy out here feels really good too.
I can't cum anymore.
The real world's separate from the virtual one.
Yeah, I guess...
Take your amazing dick and put it
inside me so we can have real, raw sex.
Sadako-chan's loli pussy...
Ryouta's amazing dick's inside me!
Just putting it inside you makes me...
Come on, shove it all the way inside me!
Your dick's perfect for sex! It feels so good in real life too!
Can you tell?
This is real life! Raw sex!
So good!
It's rubbing me so hard deep inside!
Your dick's gonna make me cum so hard!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Your amazing kid dick made me cum!
That was the best!
I'm gonna spread this VR sex program
and look around for some sex friends!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hibrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч