I can't believe I'm inside a VR game.
Clap, clap!
Miss, do you need something?
Excuse me.
Yes, I'd like to ask about something.
What's wrong?
We're inside a game, right?
Yeah.
Oh good, then.
It seems I was able to infiltrate successfully.
A weird person, huh.
Umm... sorry if this is sudden,
but could you have sex with me, please!
What are you saying?
I want to have sex in a VR game.
We can't do something like that!
This game isn't age restricted, you know.
Wanna try it then?
You're getting close.
We're researching something you'd like.
Finding it out now.
How about this, then?
Nin-nin.
There's no item like that in the player shop!
Do you feel like having sex now?
Hell no.
Then how about this?
Tada!
So this tickles your fancy, Ryouta-kun.
Guess I hit the jackpot.
We can't even have sex inside the game.
To find out,
we'll have to try different things out.
Miss...
How are my breasts?
They feel like the real thing.
Try touching my nipples.
It's making me horny.
Even though we're inside a game?
Yes.
Try licking it.
Boys sure do love breasts.
You look like a baby.
Sucking so vigorously like that. You look so cute.
How do my breasts taste?
I won't lactate even if you suck that hard.
That tickles.
Ryouta-kun, your dick,
it's starting to get erect.
Oh, it really is.
So my breasts turned you on.
Want to undress?
Undress what?
Nin-nin.
What? My clothes just disappeared.
My dick is also getting big.
I edited a few lines of code in the game's program.
Just who are you, miss?
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm going to pleasure your dick a lot, okay?
It's gotten so stiff.
So you're totally into this.
This is what you call a tit fuck.
Did you know?
I read it in some manga.
Such a pervert.
Your dick is starting to emit a man's scent.
It's poking out of my breasts.
So cute.
Are you about to cum with my tit pussy?
You can cum anytime you want to.
Cumming in a game?
What are you saying?
You can cum without restraint because we are in a game.
No need to hold back.
I'm about to...!
So much cum.
How much of it have you been building up?
I came.
Did it feel good?
Yeah.
Why don't we do something even more pleasurable?
More pleasurable?
Let's change places.
Close your eyes.
Like this?
Okay, you can open them now.
This place is...?
I linked to another game, and chose an appropriate place within it.
Whoa, my clothes have changed!
We can have as much sex as we want here.
Sex with you, miss?
Hey, you have to call me senpai here!
My dear underclassman.
Senpai, if you keep looking at me like that...
You'll get horny?
It's your second time, and you still came this much.
My dear underclassman's such a pervert.
Sadako-senpai, please let me have sex already.
All righty.
Please fuck me raw with your nice dick.
Your dick is pushing deep into me.
Hurry. Please move already.
Here it comes!
Your dick...
Your dick is so slender, and yet...
It's long, and it keeps on hitting my depths.
This feels great.
You keep pushing with such vigor.
That's just so cute.
We're inside a game,
yet this feels amazing.
More, fuck me more.
Fuck me more intensely!
Make my slutty pussy...
a mess with your dick!
Senpai!
My underclassman!
The way it pushes in and out feels great.
I love your dick.
I'm cumming. My pussy's about to cum.
I want your creamy dick milk inside me, my dear underclassman!
Fill my pussy up.
Pump it all into me!
Sadako-senpai.
This is becoming addicting.
Ryouta-kun, you can still do it, right?
Yeah. I still want to do it.
Got it then.
It's been three times,
and it's still big and stiff.
This wonderful dick needs an examination.
Stop...
If you keep rubbing it like that...
Your cowper secretions are starting to flow.
It's becoming drenched in your fluids.
I'm going to cum!
Cumming again?
We can't examine it properly if you cum so soon.
But...
Oh, jeez.
You can't cum unless I give you permission, okay?
Just a little bit more.
Okay, you can cum now.
Good boy.
Considering how I'm covered in semen, I
guess you're almost at your limit, right?
Wait, it's still eager for more?!
My dick won't stop twitching.
I think I've contracted some sort of illness.
I guess it's time to take drastic measures.
Just hold still.
You'll soon feel relieved.
It's gotten even stiffer than earlier.
Can you see where it's in?
Yeah.
I'm going to move.
Is my treatment to your satisfaction?
Let me know if it hurts, okay?
I'll make your dick feel well soon.
I can feel your body's warmth emanating through your dick.
I think it's a bit on the hotter side.
Just relax, okay?
Go ahead and release it all inside me.
Cum it all inside me to relieve yourself!
You came inside me once again.
There, there.
You worked so hard today.
You're such a good boy, Ryouta-kun.
A nice, good boy.
Are you pushing it in again?
No, if you fuck me from below like that...
Your dick will forever be etched in my mind.
Oh no...
I'm cumming.
This is how we can have sex in a VR game.
Ryouta-kun.
Looks like he finally gave in to his fatigue and fell sleep.
A dream...?
Huh?
I'm already logged out of the game, so why?
You came again, Ryouta.
Who are you?
Huh? You don't know?
Are you, Sadako-san?
Bingo!
I'm an amalgamation of spirits,
so I can take many forms.
Hey, shall we continue our game?
This tight loli pussy also feels amazing, you know.
I can't cum anymore.
The virtual one and this real one are different.
Really?
Come on, fuck me raw for real with that super dick of yours.
Sadako-chan's loli pussy...
Your super dick is in!
Just putting it in feels...
Come on, push it all the way in.
Your sex specialist dick,
feels superb when it fucks for real.
Can you tell?
This is how raw sex works.
Incredible.
I can feel it pushing hard into my depths.
I'm cumming from this young boy's dick!
I-I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
This super young boy's dick just made me cum hard.
This is the best.
I'm going to try to disseminate this new VR sex app,
and find new sex friends!