Is somebody still here?
Oh, it's you, Hasegawa-kun.
You shouldn't stay this late in here.
For a girl like you to be alone in here.
Umm.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry.
I'll go home now.
Goodbye.
This is?
I see.
You're waiting for someone.
No, that's not what it is.
That's actually.
I'm afraid he won't be coming.
I already told him to go home.
Why, sir?
Who knows?
Why indeed.
I'm going home!
Oopsie.
Here we go.
Can't be noisy in the classroom now.
D-Don't come closer.
N-No.
Why are you doing this?
Please no.
Any teacher, please save me.
Oh?
Have you forgotten already?
I too, am a teacher, you know.
Sensei, please stop.
No, I'm dirty down there.
No, not there!
Stop, that spot is!
I-I'm about to pee!
How terrible.
I'm not a toilet, you know.
Peeing in the classroom.
Bad girl.
Such a bad girl.
I'll be confiscating these panties you peed on, then.
Look? Your pee hole is completely exposed.
No, don't look there!
No, something hard is pressing on me.
It hurts.
It's trying to push inside me.
It hurts!
Stop, it hurts!
Please don't put it in.
It hurts.
I said please don't put it in.
It hurts... it hurts!
Please.
Don't move, please!
My butthole!
Stop, please don't do that!
Please don't stir it like that.
Good grief.
I already warned you not to be noisy inside the classroom.
I'll have you be quiet this way
I, you see,
would very much like a cute girl such as you to be.
H-Hey,
hey you,
what's wrong?
Hey... hey!
Teachers on night duty, huh.
What era to they think this is, right?
I'm starting to feel the creeps that
something's gonna come out.
Something... really came out?
Man's toilet
Knock first please
Do not use!
Inside here?
A toilet?
Hello?
Come in.
What a fool.
What is this place?
Huh?
Isn't this supposed to be a toilet?
And who are you?
A live human, I see.
Quite good of you come over to this place.
It's the real deal.
She's gonna kill me!
Hey you,
don't you
want to have sex with me?
Sex?!
How did we reach that ridiculous conclusion?
Well
I've been thinking of finally resting in peace.
I'm a bound spirit, so even if I want to look for a partner,
I can't actually leave this place.
It's been quite troublesome.
I can't, I absolutely cannot!
I can't do something that reckless!
Besides,
I can't do that to a girl like you!
Is that so?
You see,
I was paped by a man whom I did not harbor feelings for,
and then I died shortly afterward.
To make matters worse,
that same spot was eventually rebuilt as a restroom for men.
Much to my annoyance.
And so.
That means if I can have sex with a man
I like, I can finally rest in peace.
I think.
But, I'm a teacher!
Good grief.
If I had met a teacher like you before,
all of this would probably have never happened.
All the more reason for me to do this.
I said you can't!
I can't lay my hand on someone who looks like a student!
You really don't understand, I see.
Very well, then.
Let's do it this way, then.
If you can resist getting a boner,
then I shall accept that you really are a man of restraint.
I-I can't move!
S-Stop!
I wonder if you can still stand by your earlier declaration.
Hey!
You can't do that!
Stop that!
See?
I didn't even need to suck, and it already grew very stiff.
And it's even grown to such a monstrous size.
I wonder if I can fit this into my mouth.
This sensation!
Wow... now I understand.
My body grows when I consume cum.
Moreover,
I feel like an enormous power is welling up inside me!
Just... what are you?
Stop addressing me as "you".
I'm Hanako.
Hasegawa Hanako.
Oh! Hanako of the toilet!
How rude of you to associate a girl's name with "toilet".
I'm sorry.
Good grief.
Something fell.
Th-This is nothing.
Let's go.
Because not only did you get a boner, I even made it cum.
So you'll have to do what I say.
It really feels nice outdoors.
Why are we in the pool?
The night sky, the moon, and the school pool.
All necessary ingredients for a youth, don't you agree?
Hanako-san?
Now then, let's do it.
Because we had a deal.
Please do it gently.
I may no longer be a virgin,
but please let me comfort myself with your erect dick.
Okay.
Here I go.
Hanako-san, what's wrong?
Pardon me.
It seems my body still cannot forget
the fear that I felt on that day.
Then let's stop this right now!
Stop saying such foolish things!
You.
You actually resemble the boy that I liked before.
You're the only one whom I can depend on to overcome this.
Hanako-san!
Wait... this, this is just too fast!
It rubs hard as it bulges.
My insides are being rubbed raw.
I-I can't... I can't restrain myself any longer!
Your hot stuff is pumping inside me!
Hanako-san!
Look.
I grew up again because of your strong libido.
Was I able to satisfy you?
Of course...
you haven't!
Let's go to our next spot!
Where's that burning passion that you had earlier?
Is this combination of clothing for a P.E.
uniform not enough to turn you on?
Well?
How's the movement of my hips?
How's the feeling of getting rubbed up to the very tip?
Come on, say something.
Are you really this pathetic?
Is your dick the only wonderful thing about you?
I've been taking it in me very deeply for a while, and yet,
there, there!
Pump your thick thing into me more.
You don't have to hold it in.
So please cum already!
That felt good.
I'm starting to really love this.
Now then, how about this?
To be forcefully violated right at the school infirmary.
And you're even in that position.
I-I can't move again.
To be aroused while your ass is caressed like this.
Here, how's this?
However, I'm starting to really like your thing.
I want to take a short break.
What are you saying?
We're just getting started, you know.
You already made my body grow this far.
Finally, I got it all the way inside me.
Now, why don't we pleasure ourselves like the adults we are?
Here, and here.
Here, and some more here!
Good grief.
To be aroused in a feminine position while having sex.
You look quite pathetic right now.
You always say that you're a teacher
as an excuse for a lot of things,
but you haven't really fulfilled my conditions
to make me satisfied, see?
You good-for-nothing beta!
Don't make a fool of a teacher!
Wait... stop.
It's too intense all of a sudden.
No, please, stop, stop stop.
Stop!
It startled me so much that I returned back to this form.
Fool.
Hana-chan!
No, don't move now.
I like you best in that form!
Don't say such embarrassing things!
I'm cumming.
I want you to rest in peace, with me!
I will.
I will already.
Let's rest in peace together!
Cum more inside me.
So, are you satisfied now?
Fool.
That's it for today's extra lessons.
So.
Aren't you supposed to rest in peace already?
You're right.
Though, it's all thanks to you that I'm
able to walk around like this now.
Besides,
for you to have confessed to me in such a manner.
Confessed?
I was simply worried about you as a teacher.
I know.
Which is why...
To Okuda-sensei
I want you to accept this.
In it, are my feelings.
Hana-chan.
Thank you.
Hana-chan?
Wait, so you're moving on for real now?
I don't want that!
Not when I've finally fallen in love!
What... happened?
Look, the seal was broken.
That's all?
What are you saying?
I'm now free, you know.
However,
something may still happen in the future.
So you'll have to give me your cum from now on.
Which means, we're together from now on?
Yes, indeed we are.
Till death do us part.
Or maybe even beyond that.
Well.
You really are a fool.