Why do I even have to watch this cursed video?
Come on, I'm beggin' ya. You're the only one
who wouldn't get creeped out, Eguchi.
I'll treat you to Korean BBQ, okay?
I doubt it'll really be that scary.
Somebody help me!
Oh no!
Uh, um... Can you hear me?
What do I do about this...
If she came out of the TV, then is this
some kind of supernatural thing?
She looks just like a normal girl.
I'll just take a small peek and see
if she's really supernatural or not.
Wh-What are you doing?!
Sorry to be blunt,
but you came out of the TV, right?
Yes! I apologize for my late introduction!
I'm Sadako, the girl from the cursed video!
Who?!
To be precise, I'm the human form
of many different ghosts and curses.
You're the real deal?
That I am.
Does that mean you're going
to curse me or something?!
Not at all. I don't have enough power left for that.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
Ahem. With the decline of physical media,
the prevalence of my video fell.
In addition to that,
with today's technology and special effects,
people are starting to think that
my video isn't genuine, or it's fan-made.
That's true. Nowadays, people don't
really believe that cursed videos exist.
How do you think spirits die?
Speaking logically,
it'd be if people forgot about them.
Exactly.
That's how it is, huh?
You really drew the short straw.
Very much so.
Well, now that I understand,
could you go home now?
No. Starting now, you and I will have sex.
What?
We don't have much spiritual energy left.
If we are to survive, we must:
Change into a porno,
and continue our existence that way!
Let's go, everyone!
Okay, onii-san! Let's get started!
Wait! Changing into that would certainly help,
but why should I have sex with you?
Ah, good question. Judging from
your computer's contents... Hm, I see.
This kind of girl is your type, right?
What's going on?
I'm a gathering of different spirits,
so it's easy to change myself however I want.
Come on, stick out your tongue.
It shouldn't be a problem if you shoot
it I guess, since it won't be spread around.
Oh wow, your dick is so big!
You're a virgin, aren't you?
Your dick starts to twitch when
you're on the verge of cumming.
Come on, if you don't tell me what you want to do,
I'll just make you cum like this!
Sadako-chan, suck my dick.
Roger!
Your dick's so big, it might not fit.
How about it?
Does it feel good?
Your cum is so thick!
My pussy started throbbing
after I drank your cum.
Since you're a virgin, I bet you want some
of this high school pussy, don't you?
You can take a closer look.
This is a high school girl's pussy.
Look how wet it is.
Ah! You're too excited!
Are you trying to get me
pregnant with your breath?
Me, get this loli pussy pregnant?!
I don't mind.
Come on. Let's have baby-making sex!
This loli pussy is gonna eat up your virgin cock!
Your dick is popping a girl's cherry.
You're gonna break it!
Your dick is just too big!
It's not even all the way in, but you already
reached the back of my pussy.
Well, let's not waste any time.
I'll make you feel good.
Does it feel good?
Hey, look at my developing boobs!
Don't you think you came
a little too much, onii-san?
How'd it go? You get all of that?
Great, I can't wait.
That's... a computer, if I remember correctly.
You can use that to send music
and other things to the world, right?
Wh-What are you doing?
It's com...
No, that was too sudden!
I can't believe you're using me like an onahole!
It just feels so good!
Onii-san, you're the worst!
You're basically using my pussy to masturbate!
There's so much hot stuff
pumping into my baby room!
Sheesh, you virgin. It feels better
if you use your hips more during sex.
I've never done it before, though,
so I don't know how to use them that well.
Just try it.
You don't have to be in such a rush.
Okay, now, try moving.
It feels better like this, doesn't it?
Oh, the "virgin piston" is here!
Do it! Fuck me more!
I like this position! I love it!
I'm cumming!
There's so much virgin sauce inside me.
Sadako-chan?
Thank you very much, onii-san.
She really was part of the supernatural, huh.
Hey, Eguchi! I found something amazing!
What now?
I found a video of you in a porno!
See? Doesn't he look exactly like you?
It's becoming a big rumor around campus!
Actually... isn't this you?
2nd year Eguchi. Report to the faculty room immediately.
– I repeat, 2nd year Eguchi. Report to the faculty room immediately.
– Are you for real?
– I guess the video lived up to it's reputation. My social life died completely.
Kiss.
Ripping and uploading videos is a crime.
Downloading or watching those videos,
while fully aware, is a crime as well.
If you don't follow those rules,
your social life will end up like this guy's.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч
God damn! Forgot my cell, what the hell!
Hm? A girl in a school uniform?
Onii-san?
Onii-san, you're amazing!
You're going all the way up to my womb!
Your cum is shooting out inside me!
Thank you for your cooperation.