All characters who appear in this
video are over the age of eighteen.
Please take me home
Abandoned cat?
Poor thing.
Seriously.
Wait, Hana-chan?!
You're not thinking about taking it home, are you?!
O-Of course not!
There's no way we can take care of a cat. We're ghosts.
I know that.
I might have a friend, a person I like,
and fun times, but I'm still just a ghost.
The path of the deceased and the living
shouldn't tie with one another.
It's vexing that I cannot save the life of even a single cat.
I've never seen Hana-chan this depressed before!
I wonder if something happened
between her and Okada-sensei?
I guess that's it then. I'll have to save the day!
I knew it. You do like bigger boobs, don't you?
Your boobs grew!
I can change parts of my body at will.
You like titfucks, don't you?
Your dick's so big, my boobs can't hide all of it.
Let me start servicing you then.
It's gotten so hard.
How long have you gone without shooting a load?
Squish them tighter on me!
Your wish is my command.
Your dick's so hot. I might get burned from it.
So? Do you like my boobs?
You can cum.
Please give me your hot cum, onii-sama.
You came so much!
You've gotten me so sticky.
Now it's your turn to make me feel good.
Please fuck my dirty pussy with your huge dick, onii-sama!
It's so long!
Your dick's going so deep! It's making me feel so good!
I love the shape of your dick!
I don't know if I can forget it!
Please move your hips as you'd like!
Don't worry about me!
Please just make yourself feel good!
Your dick feels too good, onii-sama!
Let's... let's cum together!
Your cum's filled me up, onii-sama.
Oh? Who could that be?
Hey, Mary-chan?
Could you do me a favor?
Sure. Ask me anything.
Hana-chan needs your advice.
All right. Leave it to me.
Feel good?
This position... feels too good!
Your tail-dick is so cute, Kakeru.
I'm cumming!
Go ahead and cum.
You came really hard.
There's so much dripping off of my boobs.
Are you okay?
I want to make you feel good this time.
All right.
Make me feel real good, okay?
It's coming inside!
I can't wait any longer. Hurry and move it!
O-Okay!
It's in!
Kakeru, you're doing really well!
Your pussy's gripping me even
tighter than usual, Hashaku-sama!
It's because you're trying so hard, Kakeru!
It's okay. Cum!
Fill my pussy up with your cum!
I'm cumming!
It's coming!
Sorry to bother you in the middle of your fun.
Mary-chan, what are you doing here?
Well, I'm actually here for your help.
That's no good.
I'll help out Sadako-chan!
So... all of you are Hana-chan's friends?
Well, you could say that.
You're just so busy recently, sensei.
Hana-chan wanted to show her thanks!
Huh? I never said that!
There's something on your mind, isn't there?
I'm here to help. Let it all out!
But this is so sudden...
Please, leave it to us.
Yep, that's right!
All of you...
So I don't get a say in this?
This might be a little forceful,
but I'm the love doll ghost, Mary-chan.
Okay...
You should just give up.
There's no stopping them now that they're like this.
But, still...
Oh, what? Are you feeling down?
Yeah, I've been tired recently.
Just leave it to me.
What is this?!
My saliva doubles as an aphrodisiac.
Your aphrodisiac is amazing as usual, Mary-chan.
Wait!
Does it feel good?
How'd I get so hard?
I made it so that you'll be hard until your last drop.
So please cum without reserve, okay?
Hey, stop that!
You don't know when to throw in the towel.
Well, this works out. There's something... I'd like to try...
Like this!
Then I do it like this...
What do you think? I learned from Mary
how to make a part of my body bigger.
You can feel the tips of my nipples
digging into you, can't you?
Do adult breasts feel good?
It seems like they do.
You're so hard. You must really like boobs.
I can feel your pleasure through my breasts!
Go ahead! Cum!
Wow!
Looks like you're back to your usual self.
It's too early to be worn out!
The night has only just begun!
I should be telling her to stop this, but...
Okada-sensei?
It's not fair for you to be hot and have a good looking dick!
Hey, he's mine!
I think I get why you're so into him, Hana-chan!
It's already a pretty amazing dick, but...
If I transform into Hana-chan... don't you think
we can make this even more amazing?!
Transformation complete!
So?
What do you want us to do?
I want you two to suck it...
O...
...kay!
Your dick is getting as wet as a woman.
Does it really feel that good?
I'm gonna...
Wow, you came so much.
He came twice as much for twice the Hana-chans.
I did it again...
I'm the worst teacher ever.
I'm doing this because I like to.
But it doesn't change that this is wrong!
Leave it to me.
So that is what you're worried about?
Forget about your troubles and return to a simpler time.
My body shrunk?!
You are a boy.
All you need to do is tell the girl
you love how you really feel.
Well, we'll be off now.
You guys can be lovey-dovey by yourself now.
Best of luck.
I always wanted to ask, but...
What am I to you, Hana-chan?
I can't help but think I'm just
the fill-in for the guy you liked.
You fool! Of course you aren't!
I...
I, Hasegawa Hanako...
love you from the bottom of my heart!
Me too!
I love you too!
Hana-chan...
Yes!
Your dick's rock hard, Megumi-kun!
It wants to have so much sex with you, Hana-chan!
I'm so happy! I want to have lots of sex with it too!
Do me hard! You can do whatever you want to me!
I was always worried that if I was too rough,
you might remember the time you were raped.
So that's why you were always so reserved.
You're too nice, Megumi-kun!
You could've just fucked me as hard
as you wanted and made yourself feel good!
It's like my dick is melting inside of you! What is this?!
That's because I love you, Megumi-kun!
My pussy's crying out,
saying it doesn't want your dick to leave it!
Hana-chan!
Wait!
My body's back to normal?
Sorry, I'll take it out!
But this is the dick of the person I love!
I'm not scared at all.
But...
If you don't fuck me in your adult form,
I'll haunt you forever!
I love you!
So good! It's hitting all the way into my stomach!
Don't hold anything back! I love your perverted dick!
I'm gonna cum!
I'll take it in!
Give me all of it!
Hold me tight! Hold me tight
while kissing me with your dick!
I can feel your seed filling my womb!
Hana-chan, let's live together.
Here?
In my apartment.
So you mean cohabitation?
Yes.
I'm not too inexperienced,
but please look after me for eternity.
I'm filled with so much happiness,
but I can't shake this unease.
Why do I have to be a ghost?
What's with the cat?
Sorry, I found it abandoned yesterday.
I just couldn't leave it there.
Wait, are you allergic to cats?!
Oh, no!
That's not it.
That's not it!
Then why are you crying?
I'm just so happy right now.
All my worries just disappeared.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Hana-chan?
How about we decide on a name for the cat together?
Yeah!
translator: hikarucon
timing: kurosagi
typesetting: shiroyasha
editor: redbottomskies
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч