I'm Mary.
I'll deliver you a slice of heaven.
Urban Legend Series
Mary-chan's Phone
Episode 4
She appears before sexless males, and takes their virginity...
The lovely loli sex-doll phantom, Mary-chan.
The rumors were true.
Hello?
I'm Mary-chan.
I'm actually right behind you.
Huh? Behind me?
Oh my god!
Nice to meet you, master. I'll be in your care tonight.
Likewise, thank you.
Her long eyelashes, and her fair snow white skin...
She's super cute!
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Master!
Master, how would you like to be referred to?
Eh? What I want to be called?
Yes!
Um, can you call me Onii-chan?
Understood.
Onii-chan.
Onii-chan, could you face the other way?
Sure, how's this?
Perfect. Thank you, Onii-chan.
Don't move, okay?
O-Okay...
You're so energetic here, Onii-chan!
You cock's so rad, Onii-chan.
Amazing, it's getting even bigger...
Onii-chan, does it feel good?
Please excuse me...
Onii-chan, you've started to twitch...
Are you going to cum?
You can cum whenever, Onii-chan.
There's so much of your cock milk, Onii-chan.
We've only just started.
Onii-chan!
Mary-chan? What's with that costume?
I thought you'd like these so I brought them along, Onii-chan.
Do you like it?
I do, I love it!
Really? But...
You don't seem too energetic there...
Mary-chan, that's not it!
You've just wrung dry from before, and...
It's fine, Onii-chan.
Leave it to me!
Here, don't be tired!
What the-! I'm suddenly erect!
It's an aphrodisiac lotion!
You're delicious, Onii-chan.
I'm gonna...!
You came way too much, Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, is it time to cum inside my little sister pussy?
I'm going to take it in deeper, okay?
Does my vacuum pussy feel good?
Onii-chan...
Does it feel good?
Your burning-hot cock is making lewd sounds in me, Onii-chan!
Let me suck up your cock milk, Onii-chan!
I-It feels so good!
I'm cumming, I'm gonna cum!
Your cock milk's entering inside me!
Onii-chan...
Do you like big breasts?
Your breasts just grew?
I'll hug you tighter, okay?
Onii-chan, does it feel good?
Onii-chan, are you going to cum again?
It's okay, let it all out!
You came again! Just one more shot!
I'm getting dizzy just from the smell of your thick semen, Onii-chan...
It's hot-!
Wait-! I just came!
M-Master!
Y-Your hot stuff is entering into me again!
Master, please let me rest for a little while...
I'm at my limit...
It's thrusting into me again!
I'm going to go crazy if we keep at it!
Master, how was my slice of heaven?
Call your local pizza store for your slice of heaven! -Shikkaku Fansubs