Hey.
Do you who Hachishaku is?
Hachishaku-san?
That's what I said.
She's a gigantic 240-centimeter woman,
who usually wears a one-piece.
She also lets out this very creepy laugh that sounds like "po".
What? That's like a horror story!
She's been rumored to be wandering around these parts lately.
I remember she only shows herself to boys,
but she usually eats them all the way to the waist.
Wait, stop!
I can't handle that kind of stuff, you know.
Just listen a bit longer.
Suehiro Kakeru
Actually, what they meant by "eating all the way to the waist",
is that she was doing something dirty to them.
What's that supposed to mean?
– How lame.
– I'll just go home
– I'll just go home.
Mom and Dad both said that they were coming home late.
So that's... Hachishaku-san?
Said to eat boys...
all the way to the waist.
So she eat's boy's peepees?
Or maybe she fellates them?
Like what I've seen on some porn video.
A hand, on the second floor?
What should I do?
She followed me!
Now I'm about to.
But, perhaps Hachishaku-san has
been follwing me since earlier.
A youkai that just does dirty things.
In that case I...
I welcome you here, Hachishaku-sama.
So tall.
She's very beautiful, though.
Her boobs are big too.
Wanna do it?
Have you done this before?
Eh? What?
Not yet it seems.
Well then.
What is this?
My balls feel so hot.
What in the world is this?
My peepee's being enveloped by a warm thing and wet thing.
It feels good.
She's actually sucking my peepee.
I can't see her. The hat's in the way.
She's really sucking on it with her mouth!
My peepee... feels good!
It's so...
dirty.
Do you like looking at how I blow on it?
Yeah. It kinda makes me aroused.
Such a lewd kid.
Oh wow!
Oh no, oh no.
My peepee feels all tingly.
Something's... something's!
Something's coming!
It's bursting forth.
Amazing.
My peepee feels so good.
It feels so good.
So this is cum.
Did it feel good?
Yeah.
Then, we do it with these next.
Umm.
Your peepee goes here.
My peepee goes inside her boobs?
This is... amazing.
So it feels this good between boobs.
How cute.
You're moving wildly. Does it feel that good?
Y-Yeah.
Why am I positioned like this?
It goes like this.
This is... to let the peepee... fuck boobs easier.
Huh? It's rubbing really hard in between.
Wait, this is too intense.
The foreskin's getting peeled back.
W-Wait!
My peepee.
It's so sensitive now.
Oh no, I'm about to cum again!
Such vigorous cum.
It's splattered all over my breasts.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to restrain myself.
It's alright.
It's just fine.
My peepee's become like an adult's!
Not yet.
You're an adult, once you get inside my pussy.
So hot!
My peepee just melted completely inside.
It's okay.
Your peepee is twitching wildly inside.
I-It feels like my peepee's getting bigger!
Wait. Just wait!
I'm about to make it even bigger,
so just keep it in.
I can't!
Alright, just let it out.
The part where it gets rubbed is bulging more.
I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum!
Hachishaku-san.
I'm about to!
It's okay, just cum.
Cum, cum it all inside.
My peepee's about to let it all cum out.
It's coming out!
Amazing.
So this is sex.
It's really become something.
We're not done yet.
Now it's your turn to pleasure my pussy.
It's my turn now.
My turn,
to move my peepee.
In... here.
Is it in here?
Just push it all the way in.
Your peepee,
feels so... good.
It moves just like when I came.
And my hips just won't stop!
Your pussy is making really dirty sounds!
This is!
The sound it makes is completely different when it's so horny.
My thing just.
It just can't help but love your peepee so much.
Hachishaku-san!
Hachishaku-san, you're... your pussy is.
Go ahead and squeeze my thing so much that I!
Just go.
Cum.
Fill me with your stuff.
Everything's coming out!
Amazing, it's cumming inside, and it just keeps on cumming.
I can totally get into this.
Good boy.
We just need to keep copulating like this.
A long time ago.
A god named Hachishiyaku-sama lived by a village.
Hachishiyaku-sama
All the young men in the village are required to relinquish
their chastity to her before coming of age.
Those who have shared the pledge with her,
become much stronger,
and bring forth prosperity to the village.
However,
with the passing of time,
people eventually forgot about her,
and her whereabouts have since remained a mystery.
As to how Hachishiyaku-sama is doing after that.
She now freely travels along the country,
while going about her duties.