Why do I have to watch a cursed video?
Come on, man.
You're the only one who has
the hardware to watch this, Eguchi.
I'll treat you to some yakiniku.
So, please?
You'll definitely die, mister! Don't watch! Don't watch!
I bet the contents are pretty lame.
Somebody help!
Ow!
Umm, huh?
Hey, can you hear me?
What should I do now?
If she came straight out of the TV,
does that mean she's a paranormal entity?
It's like she's just an ordinary girl.
She is a paranormal entity.
I'll just check this out a bit.
Wha... what are you doing?
To be fair, even though it was
shocking for you to get cummed in like that,
you just came straight out of the TV and into my room.
Indeed!
Apologies for the late introduction.
I'm the well-known girl of the cursed video, Sadako.
Wait, that's just bull.
Specifically, I'm actually the embodiment of all
the malice accumulated from all other cursed videos.
Are you the real deal?
Yup.
Which means.
Am I about to get cursed, then?
Nope. I no longer have such power.
Huh? What do you mean?
Ahem.
To put it bluntly,
with the advancement of video media, us
agents of cursed videos soon fell into oblivion.
On top of that, video editing has also advanced so much,
that people just end up labeling anything
that's supposed to be a cursed video as made-up.
True, cursed videos nowadays aren't just instantly dismissed,
but people no longer have the
hardware to watch them in the first place.
What do you think is equivalent to death for a spiritual entity?
Figuratively, I guess that's to be
completely forgotten by the people.
Indeed.
I see.
You sure have it hard.
Indeed.
I get your situation already, so can you go back now?
No!
I'm about to have sex with you!
What?
We only have very little spiritual energy left,
and there's only one single course
that can lead to our survival.
To live on as an AV!
Everyone, it's time to work!
Now mister, let's start copulating.
Just wait a sec!
I agree that AV's can be a pretty
effective way to gam awareness,
but I don't recall agreeing that I would have sex with you.
I know.
Hmm, according to the porno
files you have on your computer.
I see.
This is your preference, right, mister?
What in the world's happening?
I'm just an embodiment, remember? So I can
freely use parts of myself to take any form that I wish.
Come on, stick out your tongue.
Well, even if it's a video I guess people
won't be watching it that way, anyway.
I think it won't really spread that far.
Your dick is so big!
You're still a virgin, right, mister?
It's twitching as if it's about to cum.
Come on, you'll cum if you don't give me proper direction soon.
Sadako-chan.
Suck... my dick.
Roger.
Your dick is too big, I don't think it'll fit.
About to cum?
Does it feel good?
Your cum is really rich and thick.
Now that I drank your cum,
my pussy is twitching like crazy.
The virgin dick and the **** schooler virgin pussy.
You'll definitely want to check it out, right?
Try to get up close.
This is a **** schooler's virgin pussy.
It's so wet already.
Mister, you're getting aroused too much.
Are you trying to impregnate me with your breath?
Impregnate... this loli pussy?
Go ahead.
Come on, I really want to start this hot copulation already.
This loli pussy, is about to take in your virgin dick completely.
Your dick has just penetrated through a girl's most private part.
It's penetrating through!
Your dick is too big!
It's completely filled me before I can even take it all in.
Now I'm about to pleasure you until you're speechless.
Hey, does it feel good?
Mister, look at my still-growing boobs.
Mister, you came too much.
Well? Did you get all that?
I'm looking forward to it.
That's...
a PC, right?
It's a device that can make the world go
round with music, writings, and other stuff, right?
Wh-What?
It's pushing inside!
No, this is too sudden.
Y-You're using me like some sort of onahole.
It feels a lot better this way.
Mister... you're the worst!
It's as if you're just masturbating using my pussy!
You're cumming directly into my womb.
You're really quite the virgin.
It's a lot better if you properly use your hips to fuck, you know.
I'm a virgin, so I really don't know if I can move my hips well.
Just do it!
You don't have to rush.
Now then, try to move, Mister.
It feels a lot better this way, right?
The virgin has started his wild piston move!
More.
Yes, fuck me more.
I love this.
I absolutely love this!
I can't hold back anymore!
Out comes your virgin cum.
Sadako-chan?
Thank you very much, Mister.
So you're really a paranormal entity after all.
Eguchi, come check this out.
I found something really amazing.
What's that?
I found a porno vid that matches
all of your preferences perfectly!
See? Looks like you, right?
This rumor has been traveling around the campus, though.
Oh wait, don't tell me this is actually you?
Second year student, Eguchi Takashi-san.
Please head to the student counseling office immediately.
I repeat.
Second year student, Eguchi Takashi-san.
Is this for real?
The video that will curse you with death.
Looks like.
It actually killed my... social life.
Illegal downloads are beyond the law.
Of course, it's illegal itself to know that it's illegal!
If you don't heed my warning,
you're going to "die" as well.
Roll, roll!
I'm really such a dunce to have forgotten my phone!
A girl in a school uniform?
Mister.
Mister, you're amazing!
It's penetrating me deeply.
It's pumping cum directly inside!
Thank you for your cooperation.