Hey, do you know who Hasshaku-san is?
Hasshaku-san
Hasshaku-san?
Apparently, that's her name.
She's a really big woman,
around 240cm tall, and wears a white dress.
She has this weird laugh, too...
"po po po po".
Huh? Isn't that like, horror?
I hear she's been appearing around here recently.
I heard that she will only show herself around guys,
but for the guys she does appear for, they get eaten up.
Hey, stop! I'm really not good with scary stuff!
Wait, listen to this.
Suehira Kakeru
The truth is, they don't actually get eaten.
Instead, it's something lewd.
What the heck? That's so weird.
Time to go home.
Mom and Dad did say they'd be back late...
Suehira
What was that? Was that Hasshaku-san?
She's "eating" that guy...?
Hasshaku-san eats the dicks of the guys she meets.
Or, she sucks them?
I've seen it in porn before.
A hand... on the second floor?!
What do I do?! It's coming closer! At this rate, I'll...
Maybe Hasshaku-san is the kind of spirit
that does lewd things with people?
If that's the case, then I...
Hasshaku-san, please enter, if you'd like.
She's huge!
She's beautiful, though.
Her boobs are really big, too.
You wanna?
Have you done this before?
Huh?
Done what?
That's a no, then.
All right.
What's going on? My balls are on fire!
Ah...
What is this?
My dick is all wet and now it's being
wrapped in something warm.
It feels so good!
She's really sucking my dick.
I can't see what's going on because of the hat.
She's really sucking my dick!
My dick feels so good!
You look so dirty.
Do you like the way I look when I suck your dick?
It gets me really excited.
You lewd boy.
Wow!
S-Stop!
The tip of my dick is getting tingly!
Something's... Something's...
Coming!
Something's coming out!
That feels so good! My dick feels so good!
Is this what "cumming" is?
Did it feel good?
Yes...
Then this is next.
Um...
Put your dick here.
Put my dick in there?
Wow...
Being between her boobs feels so good.
You're so cute.
You're moving a lot. Does it really feel that good?
Y-Yes!
Why this position?!
It's easier for your dick to do dirty things in this position.
My dick is rubbing against you so hard!
This is intense!
My foreskin's pulled back now!
W-Wait!
– My dick...
– There. There.
My dick feels really sensitive!
No! I'm gonna cum again!
You came so much.
It's flowing out over my boobs.
I'm sorry.
I can't hold myself back at all.
It's okay. That's perfectly fine.
My dick... it looks like an adult's.
You're not an adult just yet.
Let's put your dick inside,
and give you your first adult experience.
It's so hot!
I think my dick just melted.
It's oka...
Your dick is just moving around inside me.
M-My dick's getting bigger for some reason!
Wait! Wait!
If your dick is getting bigger,
you need to try and hold back. Hold it back.
I... I can't!
Your dick feels good.
My dick's getting bigger!
I'm gonna cum!
My cum's gonna shoot out!
Hasshaku-san!
I can't...
It's fine. Cum.
Shoot it into me.
I can't hold back! I'm cumming! My dick is cumming!
Wow.
So that's what sex is like.
It's still like this though.
That's because we're not done yet.
This time I want you to make me feel good.
This time, I'll...
I'll be the one.
I'll be the one moving my dick!
It goes here, right?
Is this right?
Yes. Now, push it in, with all your strength.
Your dick feels really... good...
My entire body wants to cum.
I can't stop moving my hips!
Hasshaku-san, you're making
really dirty sounds down here.
Th-That's...
That's the sound it makes when it feels too good!
Does my dick really feel that good?
I love your dick!
Ha-Hasshaku-san!
Hasshaku-san... Your pussy is...
It's squeezing me so tight, I'm gonna...
That's fine. Cum!
Fill me up with your cum!
I'm cumming!
Cumming in your pussy feels so good!
Wow, there's still more coming out!
I feel so tired now.
Good boy. Good boy.
We're going to have so many kids.
A long, long time ago.
There lived a so-called god, named Hashiyaku-sama.
Hashiyaku-sama
When the village boys reach a certain age,
they are brought to her to become men.
Afterwards, they become stronger,
and bring prosperity to the village.
But, as time went on, people began to forget
about her, and where she dwelled.
So what did she do after that happened?
With a new sense of freedom, she wandered around,
and continued fulfilling her duty.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч