Why do I have to watch that cursed video?
I'm begging you! You're the only one that still has a VHS player, Eguchi!
I'll even treat you to barbecue!
Please?
You will die if you watch this! Do not watch! Seriously, don't watch!
Urban Legend Series
The Cursed Video
Episode 2
It's probably not important, but...
H-Help!
Ouch!
Um, what?
Hey, can you hear me?
What am I supposed to do?
She has to be something supernatural to come out of the television...
She seems like a normal girl...
I'm just going to check...
...if she's real.
Hey! What are you doing?
This might be strange to ask after cumming in your mouth.
But you came out of the television, right?
That's right!
I forgot to introduce myself.
As you may well know, I'm Sadako of the Cursed Video.
I actually didn't know that.
Technically though, I'm an amalgamation of the many spirits who reside within the video.
You're a real ghost?
That's right!
Does that mean that I'm going to be cursed, too?
Nope! I don't have such power anymore.
Eh? What do you mean?
Ahem! To explain this simply, due to the decline of the VHS media,
the existence of those of us whom reside in cursed videotapes has been forgotten.
Additionally, due to the huge advances in video media these days,
most people now believe that the existence of such videos was merely a rumor.
That's true. Whether or not people believe such videos exist,
no one has a VHS player these days anyway.
What do you think the concept of death  means for a ghost?
In terms of their existence, does it mean simply being forgotten by people?
You're correct!
I see... Things must be tough.
Yes...
Now that I understand your predicament, can you leave now?
No! You're going to have sex with me!
Our powers wither by the day...
To continue existing in this world, we have only one option!
To continue existing as a porn video!
Everyone! It's your time to shine!
C'mon Onii-san, let's film some porn!
Hold on!
It's true that a porn video has the potential to spread...
But I haven't agreed to have sex with you or anything...
I'm aware of that.
If I consider what kind of porn you have saved on your computer...
I see.
Is something like this more to your tastes?
W-What's happening?
Since I'm an amalgamation of many different spirits, I can pick and choose many forms!
C'mon! Poke out your tongue for me.
Even if it's porn, no one actually watches VHS tapes.
It probably won't spread that far.
Your cock is so big, Onii-san!
You're a virgin aren't you, Onii-san?
You're throbbing so much and you're about to cum!
Hey, if you won't tell me what you want to do, you'll just end up cumming like this!
Sadako-chan, please suck my cock.
Understood!
Your cock's so big that it might not fit...
How is it?
Does it feel good?
Onii-san's semen is so thick!
My pussy's quivering because I drank your cum!
Any virgin would want to have a good look at a junior high girl's virgin pussy, right?
Take a closer look.
This is what a junior high girl's virgin pussy looks like.
It's dripping wet!
No! Onii-san, you're too excited!
Are you trying to deflower me using just your mouth?
I can deflower this loli pussy?
It's okay...
Let's have raw, impregnating sex!
Your big, virgin cock is about to enter my loli pussy!
Onii-san's big cock is about to break my precious hymen!
It's being torn apart!
Your cock is too big, Onii-san!
It's not even all the way in and it's hitting my deepest parts!
Now then, I'll make you feel really good!
Hey, does this feel good?
Onii-san, look at my developing breasts!
Onii-san, you came too much!
How goes the filming? All good?
I look forward to it!
That's a computer, right?
Everything from music to daily activities are digitized and transmitted worldwide now, right?
No! What?
No! Ouch!
No! What are you doing so suddenly?
You're using me like an onahole!
It feels better like this!
No!
Onii-san, you're the worst!
I'm being used as a living sex toy!
Your hot semen is entering my babymaking room!
This is why virgins are so...
It feels better to have sex properly and just thrust together, right?
I'm a virgin, so I'm not experienced with things like this.
Just do it!
You don't need to be so flustered.
Now try thrusting, Onii-san.
It feels better like this, right?
Oh no!
Here comes Mr. Virgin's piston!
More! Thrust it inside me more!
I love this! I'm loving it!
Let's cum together!
Your virgin cock milk is flowing out!
Sadako-chan?
Onii-san. Thank you very much!
So she really was a supernatural being...
Hey Eguchi, c'mere! You'll want to see this!
What is it?
I've found porn with your doppelganger in it!
Huh? What?
Doesn't it look like you?
There's been a rumor going around campus.
Actually, isn't this really you?
Attention: second year Eguchi Takashi-san.
Please report to the student advisory council.
I repeat: second year Eguchi Takashi-san.
Is this for real?
A cursed video that will kill you if you watch it.
It seems that now my social life is dead.
Unauthorized uploading is a crime!
Of course, watching it knowing that it's illegal is also a crime!
If you don't listen, Onii-san, I'll...
...have you killed. Socially.
Sorry! I'm so silly for forgetting my smartphone!
Oh? A high school girl?
Onii-san...
Onii-san, you're amazing!
It's hitting my deepest parts!
It's spurting out inside of me!
Thanks for your cooperation!
Now that you've seen the video, you've been cursed!