I... am Mary,
and I am here to escort you...
to heaven.
Often appearing before virgins,
and offering to take their virginity.
The Western Loli and Love-making Specter, Mary-chan.
So the rumors were true!
H-Hello?
I'm Mary.
I'm behind you.
Behind me?!
You're really behind me!
Pleased to meet you, Mr. Butler.
I hope we can get along tonight.
I hope so, too.
Those long eyelashes and supple skin,
she looks so cute!
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Mr. Butler,
how would you like me to address you tonight?
Address me?
Yes.
Well... can you call me "onii-chan"?
Request accepted.
O-ni-i-cha-n.
Onii-chan, can you turn around?
Like this?
Yup. Thanks, onii-chan.
Please don't move.
Okay.
Your thing looks so lively!
It looks quite cool.
Wow, it's getting even bigger.
Does this feel good, onii-chan?
Excuse me for a bit.
It's starting to twitch.
About to cum?
Just do it, onii-chan.
Your dick just squirted lots of its sticky stuff!
We're just getting started, onii-chan
Mary-chan, that outfit?
I thought this might perk you up some
more, so I prepared this in advance.
Do you hate it?
I do!
I love it!
Really?
But, your thing isn't yet lovely enough.
Mary-chan, it's not what you think.
You just squeezed quite a lot after your handjob, so.
It's alright, onii-chan.
Leave it to me.
Up and at 'em you go.
What's this? My boner suddenly returned!
It's an aphrodisiac lotion.
Your thing tastes quite good, onii-chan.
I'm about to!
You're cumming so much, onii-chan.
Alright, now try cumming inside your dear lil' sis.
I'm putting it in.
How do you like my super tight pussy?
Onii-chan.
Is this good?
Your big dick is rubbing hard inside.
Let me have lots of your dick milk.
Oh yes, oh yes!
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum!
It's pumping your dick milk inside me.
Onii-chan,
would you prefer if I had bigger boobs?
They became bigger?!
I'm going to squeeze it harder.
Does this feel good, onii-chan?
About to cum again?
Go ahead. Just cum whenever you like.
It squirted out again!
One more!
My head's starting to get fuzzy after cumming so much.
So hot!
Wait, I just came.
Mr. Butler!
Your hot stuff is filling me again.
Mr. Butler... please let me rest for a bit.
I'm at my limit already.
It's pushing into me again.
Any more and I'll totally lose it.
How's the heaven I bestowed upon you, Mr. Butler?