International Syndicate group
Leader of Japan's branch of Golden Convergence, Mr. Okubo,
Has captured one of the holy maidens, Tsuchinomico, to break the Seal of the Magatsugami.
She was raped by his servant, Mr. Kaga.
Hinimico, Homura, was attacked by Quon and was shot with a mysterious feather.
However, a mysterious man by the name of Hiroto came to her rescue in time.
She had to have intercourse with him in order to cure herself from the poison.
Although she questions, in the mean time she finds herself asking for help to Hiroto.
Mr. Okubo holds the mirror that foresees everything
Hiroto and Homura drives around the city night, looking for a safe place.
What destiny awaits for the other two micos, Shizuru the Mizunomico and Asuka the Kazenomico...
Tokitsu?
Yes.
So, what are the results?
We were not able to assassinate both of them...
However we did manage to insert the Sylph's Feather inside the Hinimico's body.
If you are the one reporting this...
I assume Quon is no longer living.
What about Mr. Yamazaki?
Chasing Hiroto Nanbu.
He should be engaging him soon.
Please tell Mr. Kaga to execute his plan.
What are we going to do?
We need to wait for their move.
They will move if we wait.
Besides...
We need to do something about that feather quickly.
What's wrong?
An Assassin.
I'm going to hide you with the car to a different realm.
Listen, no matter what don't tell the guy there your name.
Other wise, you will be stuck.
Hey, wait!
What... do you mean?
Lets get this shit rollin', Mr. Nanbu.
The killing that is!
Where... is... this?
Huh, what, what's this on my body!?
That is your spiritual complex.
It's your soul taking shape.
W-Who!?
Shit!
No worries.
It is a strong field, but if I summon a demon...
I can go...
Through it!
N-No!
What is... this!?
D-Don't...
Don't!!!!!
What's wrong Mr. Nanbu, running away!?
T-This is!
Tatarimuramasa, what a wonderful katana.
It inflicts damage on Hiroto Nanbu.
The mico of Death and Rebirth, Hiniomico.
A beautiful body like ones of a virgin.
No...
You tell me to stop, but...
Your nipples are getting harder!
No... that's not true...
There's no need for a resist!
Fall into the lust...
Just like what you've done with Hiroto.
W-Why do you know that!?
I know everything about him.
We are an existence like Ying and Yang.
There is no way out of here...
You are going to be in this realm with me eternally.
Your taunts... aren't scaring me!
You may have been alone your entire life.
But it's not the same emotionally in this realm...
Accept me, that's the only option!
S-Stop...
That's right!
The only way you can survive here is for you to accept me!
If you continue to resist, you will fall into eternal hell beyond your imaginations.
I... I don't want this, but...
Cumming...
I'm cumming!
Come to your sense though the ecstasy.
Please, don't!!!!!!
The only way to escape your Ioneliness in this realm is to become my obedient slave.
Hi... Hiroto...
You still have hopes of him saving you...
Well then, lets continue with the ceremony!
Tell me your name!
Become part of me!
And your eternity with me!
Hiroto.
What a pity, Hiroto Nanbu.
Even a man like you stands no chance against me, Yamazaki the 1000 Man Killer.
Sorry to say, but you're finished!
What!?
W-Where did you get that katana!?
1000 Man Killer you say?
You think you're strong because of it?
I'll show you the true way... of using a katana!
Nonsense!!!
Tell me your name now!
You will then be saved!
No, I will not tell you!
You are tough...
Lets see how tough you will be after seeing this.
Y-You're...
She was killed by Hiroto... this is part of Quon's soul.
I will make you happy with this new toy I have.
N-No!
Then hurry up and speak your name!
But before that, let me have some fun.
Here...
What beautiful lips.
It's great, really great...
This is just the beginning...
Really beautiful lips...
I can't wait to try the ones down there.
No, that's too big!
See, it went in!
Lets see about this end...
D-Don't!
Here I go.
Speak your name now!
Then you will be mine.
I can't, Hiroto told me not to!
Cuming, I'm cuming!
What a fool, used up all its energy.
Can't do much with a left over soul.
Is... this?
Correct, these are the souls I've eaten.
C, can't be!
Say your name just like what they've done!
Grab on!
Hi, Hiroto?
Grab on to my hands!
Hurry!
Hiroto!
Damn you Hiroto, getting in my way at the last second...
Homura... wake up, Homura Kamishiro!
Hiroto?
You alright?
Why did you hide me there!
That place... was more dangerous!
Sorry, but... there was no... other...
What's it Hiroto? Hiroto!
Huh... blood?
It's almost severed, we have to take you to a hospital!
N... no use.
Doctors... won't be able to do anything.
B-But...
Hiroto... Hiroto, Hiroto!
Nice to meet you, Fortune.
Or should I say Shizuru Tsukuyomi?
W-What!?
I can't move?
But of course, the mirror now has your soul.
You fell into this obvious trap.
Your sense is 10 times more sensitive.
T-This is...
Doesn't this make you want to cum?
I'll have fun with you!
Lets see what happens when I touch here...
I'm wet!?
D... don't!
Don't, stop!
You're so wet!
H-How stupid of me falling into his trap.
C-Can't be, cumming!
First one...
This is getting fun!
P-Please forgive me...
What are you saying, we're just getting started.
Can't you feel my thing!?
You think I'm going to stop now!?
Doesn't this feel better than your usual sex?
I can stick it in deep as I want.
But we need to spice this up a bit more.
Lets have them attend.
H-Hey... stop!
No, if you guys keep doing that I'll...
No, no!
I'll fuck your body and soul senseless!
It's not over yet!
Come on, cum!
I'll unload a big one onto your soul!
Cuming, cuming!
No, I'm going to... disappear!
Mizunomico is now ours!
Huh, where is this? I didn't drink any alcohol...
I brought him to my room, but...
I don't know what to do.
So cold!
The mico of Death and Rebirth, Hiniomico.
Power of Death and Rebirth...
I don't know if it's true, but I have to warm him up.
Why do I feel so nervous?
It's nothing new...
So cold.
I'm starting to feel strange...
I-I can't, why am I feeling so horny...
Huh, isn't this that dangerous place?
No, this place is different.
Hiroto, where is this?
This is inside of my memory...
Memory?
W-What is this feeling.
Words can not explain this...
A memory of the endless battle between my brother.
What do you mean?
My brother and I can not die.
Even as an undead, our battle continues for eternity!
That's!
What's this...
Stop, it ripping me up inside!
Loved ones passed away, even the hated ones.
There's no meaning to this battle or my life...
However, I can not die even after loosing the feelings of despair...
You've always been alone...
Is there anything I can do?
I can't heal my wounds due to the evil presence.
I need your help.
Heal...
I will... I will heal your wounds!
It's warm...
Is this the power of Hinomico?
Share me more of your powers.
It's just a kiss, but I'm...
If you touch me right there!
I never felt like this before!
It feels good!
OK, Homura?
Yes, please...
C-Can't be, I'm going to cum already!?
W-Why!?
Cumming, cumming!!
He only inserted, but I came already...
Here I go...
D-Don't move yet!
I'm enjoying this...
Is it because it is with Hiroto?
N,-No... I can't help myself.
I never felt this happy...
I think...
Do I... Hiroto?
No, I'm going to cum, hard!
I'm cumming again!
Again!!
Cumming, I'm cumming again!!
I'm going to cum!
Cum, cum, cum! Cum inside me!!
It's getting warm... inside!
Hiroto, your wound...
Yes, thanks to you I'm better.
Good...
Thank you.
No problem.
I heard Mr. Yamazaki is dead.
As usual, you find out quick.
Tatarimuramasa was of no use?
No, wounding Hiroto Nanbu was a success.
As the mirror foretold, he's merely moving along with the future already predicted.
I see...
Looks like the seal is strengthening and starting to devour the Tsuchinomico in order to break the seal...
It's thanks to the feather inside Hinomico.
The excess power from Hinomico...
is strengthening the power of the seal.
It looks like the Zero-Section still thinks you guys are trying to break the seal.
Mr. Kaga has reported that he successfully captured Mizunomico.
So, everything is going according to plan...
Yes, Mr. Tokitsu should be encountering Kazenomico soon.
A passed pawn increases in strength as the number of pieces on the board diminishes.
This is merely the beginning.
I was sleeping?
I haven't slept like this in 100s of years.
Thank you, Homura.
What's wrong?
Fortune has disappeared.
It's highly possible that she's been kidnapped.
Fortune?
Also Mizunomico!
I'll tell you details in the car.
Looks like we will be entertained for a while, Mr. Nanbu...
The fight is just starting...
Hiroto Nanbu, my little brother!
The gate is opening...