No...
Ahh...
No!!!!
No.
Did you wake up?
Was I... sleeping?
Yeah. It's not nice sleeping while I'm in the shower.
Sorry, so sorry
Well, better than those girls who take my wallet and bail.
Forget about that, why don't we...
You are beautiful...
Looks like you're ready.
Here I go.
I'm going to move.
I'm going to... cum!!!
Ohh, cum!!
Here.
What, this much?
Looks like you need it so...
Really?
Yeah, you're different from the other girls.
Thank you, but you might hurt yourself by being too nice.
Umm, ok...
I have found you, Hinomico...
Come in.
Thanks for coming.
Avenger
and Fortune.
What gives for summoning us?
Tsuchinomico has been kidnapped...
Kirara Amano, student. A Spiritual Hybrid Nomad.
Kirara...
You're saying someone is trying to break the seal of 'God'?
I'm sure of it.
According to the legend, four priestess are needed to break the seal.
Each of the girls have a spirit within their bodies.
They are known to us as, Tsuchinomico, Hinomico, Kazenomico and Mizunomico.
They probably know where the seal is if they kidnapped Tsuchinomico...
That's right. All evidence of its existence was burned during the world war
...but it's now awakening from the darkness.
We have to protect the other three and stop them from breaking the seal.
What do we have to do?
I have already sent out Duke to protect Kazenomico.
So, two others left...
One of them is right next to you.
Fortune, no... Shizuru Tsukuyumi is the Mizunomico.
Normally, we wouldn't have an untrained person to...
No, I don't think about running away from my destiny besides, don't you need my powers?
I know...
What do you mean?
We have found out she's in Tokyo, but beyond that...
I'm sure I can be of a help finding Hinomico with my power as Mizunomico.
Alright. Avenger, please find Hinomico and protect her.
Let me ask one thing...
Is our enemy...
Yes.
Looks like they are moving, Mr. Ookubo.
Yes, I am aware. Everything is going as planned.
Hiroto Nanbu.
Yes, code name Avenger. We go a long way back... you too right?
That is right, that's why I ask you to do this.
I thank you very much.
Thanks to this mirror you brought, I have found out whereabouts of all the micos.
With the God's power, we will kill that 'man.'
I hope so.
Kaga, begin.
Did you wake up!
Wha.. What is this!?
Let go!!
Not so fast.
Please forgive me!
Your mouth says no, but your body says yes.
Look at you, you are so wet little cutie slut.
No...
The God's first sacrifice must be a virgin, or else, he might get mad!
No, please... not like!!!
Your servant, Kaga. He's really good.
Who would've though that Spiritual Hybrid, the combination of spirit and soul, is the key to breaking the seal.
Heh, soon Tsuchinomico will fall.
You are almost finished.
No, please don't!!
It's my first time... and I'm being raped... but it feels so good...
By the way, Robert, the organization has marked you as a traitor and are hunting you down.
I don't mind.
Besides, I never accepted Golden Combustion as my partner.
I will let you take care of Hiroto Nanbu's murder
I wish you luck.
Stupid dip-shit, not even thankful.
Why just not use what you can?
Soon, Kuon will encounter Hinomico.
Homura Kamishiro, correct?
Who?
I have found you, Hinomico.
How do you know about?
Please... come with me.
Are you going to come with me now?
If you don't run away faster, I will get you!
Someone... help me!
Why? Why won't anyone look back!?
No one can see you or me, it's useless calling for help.
You are at a dead end.
What to do, dead end!
Have you given up yet?
That's it, Stay still!
How is the power of the wind, Sylph's Feather?
It will overload your power of fire.
Beautiful eyes...
You are so cute... I love a strong girl like you...
It hurts, right? If you don't take care of it soon, the salamander combined to your soul will explode.
You don't want to die such a pitiful death, right?
Come with me, now.
No!!!!!
Hold it right there.
Hiroto Nanbu!
Are you alright?
Shit, looks like I have to do this...
Die!
What!?
A person came falling down!!
Call the ambulance!
Shit...
Can you walk?
Y-Yes...
How will you take care of this ticking time bomb, Mr. Nanbu?
Squadron Alpha currently in front of the manor. It's clear.
Kuroda here, roger.
Hey Rei, lets go eat somewhere.
Squadron Beta, please report.
Squadron Beta, we are currently on the move... All clear.
Kuroda here, roger.
There's a beautiful Italian restaurant near by, Rei.
Please, don't talk to me like I'm your friend.
We are in a mission right now, and you are under me.
You look so cute even when you're angry.
Wha...
It's alright... my field is still up. It's ok.
What are you?
We have to get to know each other better.
What are you talking about...
Damn, was starting to become good too.
Yes? What? Yes, I understand.
What's wrong?
My partner has secured Hinomico.
That's great news.
But looks like it isn't.
Next will be here.
Who are you!? Who was that girl!?
I am Hiroto Nanbu, a special agent.
Special agent?
The ones after you can not be hurt by guns or knives. That is why I came to protect you.
Shit, why me...
Shit, Sylph's Feather is becoming bigger.
What?
It's only temporary, but I have to cast a spell on you.
Please stop! Don't touch me!
But, if you stay like this...
Hell no! Why do I have to let you touch me for free!
Bitch, stay like that until you no longer can hold it.
Who would want a tard like you touching...
Huh... what? My body...
I'm... getting wet?
Not here...
Is it that Feather's fault? I can't hold it in...
No, my body... I can't hold it!!!
Please... help me...
Alright, I'll start now.
What is that?
This is the seal of the Ox Lord. I will put this in your uterus and control the chi.
Penetration!?
This is the only way.
But...
Don't worry, no one can't see.
That's not the issue here...
I'm going to start, be quiet.
Hold on to this.
Huh, ok.
Don't move your hips.
But my body...
Is moving on its own...
Are you done!?
Almost.
No... I'm cumming!
It failed...
Huh, then...
It's your fault.
But, how can I...
Alright...
What are you going to do?
I transferred the power in me.
Does that mean...
Yes, I will directly give you the powers.
No!!
Stop! Here I go
Are you alright?
Please... finish it quickly.
Are you done?
Stay put...
Cumming!
You should be fine for a while.
Yes... I feel better.
Um...
Hmm?
T-Thank you very much, Mr. Nanbu
Don't worry about it, my mission is to protect you.
By the way, call me Hiroto.
Hiroto...
Is it Tokitsu?
Yes...
How are the results?
We were unable to murderthe two, but Sylph's Feather is inside Hinomico's body.
If you're reporting about this... it is a pity to loose Kuon.
It was foreseen by the Sacred Mirror
The Sacred Mirror and Sylph's Feather are both working impressively.
We have to thank Robert. By the way, how is it with Yamazaki.
Currently, Yamazaki is pursuing Hiroto Nanbu. He should be showing us a movement soon.
Please tell Kaga to proceed too.
While Hiroto Nanbu carries Hinomico, a ticking time bomb, we are going to kidnap Mizunomico...
Yes, all is going as planned...