Sorry for calling so suddenly.
No, you don't need to worry about it.
Well then, take care.
Okay.
I'm going to become a better man at Shintenji,
and then meet Rikka again.
I'm sure, I'll be able to make up for my past.
See you later.
Original Animation Disc
Tropical Kiss
Even flat-chested ones are human! You dare gauge a woman by her breasts!?
Of course you don't, idiot!! By Rikka -Chapter-
Oh, Kaito-kun.
Nagi-san.
I see, so you're moving in today.
Yes. Are you on your way to work?
Yeah, and there are a lot of things to do.
Please take care of yourself, okay?
Thank you.
Oh yeah, I've been wanting to ask you something.
What is it?
The name of this place, Aloha...
Is there any explanation to it?
Aloha has many meanings,
and could either mean affection, trust, closeness,
gratitude, thank you, goodbye,
or even a simple hello.
A word that says you're A-OK.
I see.
But, in here, Aloha specifically means goodbye.
It's a word of farewell?
No, a word spoken to guarantee you'll meet again.
As in "see you later".
So it's a word of reunion.
That's right.
Lots of people from different places come here, right?
Many people only get to be together here...
But it also implies people could also meet
again here, at some other time.
A good example would be our reunion, right?
Well, that's true.
Excuse me.
Hello there, I'm Saotome Nagi, the manager of this establishment.
No way...
What's wrong?
Nagi-oneechan...
Huh? Could you be, Kaito-kun?
I'm sure there are others who would be surprised to see you.
What do you mean?
That's something you'll have to look forward to later.
It really is an "aloha".
Okay, I'll introduce you to everyone.
Please to meet you.
As of today, I'm...
Kaito?
Why?
Kaito-san, I'm sorry...
I don't know what to say.
Why are you here?
Innocent
stick-out-tongue
Hanabi, Matsuri-chan, and even you Rikka?
Kaito...
There are others whom you’re acquainted
with already besides Hanabi-chan?
Hey...
What's going on?
You idiot!
Why, why?!
Rikka, calm down.
I am calm!
Don't lie to me.
Are you alright?
My clothes are wet.
Other than that?
I'm fine.
I see.
It's all because you were acting violently earlier.
Of course I would.
Of course what?
You just disappeared without telling me.
I'm sorry.
You idiot.
I never thought that I'd get to meet you again this way.
A reunion, huh?
Nagi-san, I think I've experienced your "aloha" now.
Even so,
Hanabi,
Matsuri-chan,
and even Rikka...
Even if you confess to me suddenly like that,
I'm sorry.
Let me think about it.
I'm really happy that you were able to accept me.
You're too much of a nice guy, you know?
I don't get to see people like you nowadays.
Hey, Kaito.
Shinta.
At least knock before coming in here!
I knocked three times already, but you didn't respond.
Really?
Sorry about that.
Don't mind it.
Anyway, wanna eat?
Oh, so you're acquainted with Kaito as well.
Yes, we used to work at the same place.
I see, I see.
So Hanabi-san is a childhood friend of Kaito-san.
It's the first time that we've all met, but it seems we already
have something in common with each other.
Kaito, what's wrong?
You used to eat a lot more before.
I'm just trying to savor the taste.
I see, and you're Shinta-kun, right?
It's Hououin Suzaku.
His actual full name is Tokoro Ten.
He lives near my place, and is Aloha's customer number 01.
I see, so that's why he's called Shinta.
I said it's Hououin Suzaku.
Nice to meet you Shinta-kun.
Hmph, I don't want to get along well with demons.
Demons?
What do you mean?
Women are demons.
Do l need to explain further?
So, Shinta-san, could you actually be gay?
Are you nuts?
That'd be like admitting that I'm a total virgin.
Wait, why?
I like girls.
I love girls!
Only 2D ones though.
I even dare say that there are no real girls in the world!
I see.
So that's what you mean.
That's right.
Well, you're about to work with us anyway,
so I hope we still get along, idiot.
Please to meet you, idiot-san.
Just call me Shinta please.
Hanabi?
My name?
I introduced myself earlier, you know?
I didn't hear.
Oh, then I'll repeat it for you.
I am Hinata Hanabi, Kaito's childhood friend.
Do you really have to emphasize that?
Just a childhood friend, eh?
Just...?
Well, I'm...
Aoi Matsuri, right?
Yes...
I know.
I heard yours.
And you didn't hear mine?
Yep.
I see, so you're that Hanabi.
That Hanabi...?
Hey, Rikka...
I've heard a lot of things from Kaito.
Huh? What did he say?
This is bad.
Rikka knows everything about the issue between me and Hanabi.
Lots of things.
Well...
Wait, what's your relationship with her?
Rikka was my neighbor in the apartment complex that I lived in.
I left home while carrying the despair
I felt when Hanabi dumped me.
After that I started living alone.
Actually I just slept at home,
and simply went to work again and again during my waking hours.
I was depressed...
Depressed that she dumped me.
That was when I met Rikka.
You really left home just because you were
dumped by your childhood friend?
I shouldn't have talked to you about it after all.
You're too much of a nice guy, you know?
I don't get to see people like you nowadays.
Of course you wouldn't.
You mean I wouldn't normally see people who run
away like that without any sort of plan, right?
Why don't you try living a little easier?
Easier, huh...?
Was she really that good for you?
Stop teasing me already.
You're laughing too much.
Yeah, and it's the first time in a long time.
This is great drinking with you is the best!
Oh, so that’s only the extent of our relationship?
Hey, Rikka...
What does that mean?
It's nothing, don't worry about it.
I'm asking Rikka-san!
Read the situation already.
I've heard that there are many cases of things
catching fire with no real reason here...
I see, and?
If this place sets alight, I'd like to save you somehow.
Well, thank you.
So, let me have it.
Wait, you're asking for my keys?
That's right, you have a spare, right?
I have, but...
Then give it to me.
Okay then.
Thank you.
This is mine.
Then he took something very important from me.
Shinta, my bad!
Hey Rikka!
It's the truth!
Well yeah, but...
You can't do that Kaito.
You have to properly return it to her.
Why are you trying to stick close to me?
We won't it into the photo if we don't stick dose, right?
You're taking a photo of us?
A selfie is just too lonely.
Is that so...?
Hey, I'm going to snap this just once so stop fooling around!
That's because it's a disposable camera, you know?!
There I got it.
The thing that I took from her, isn't something
that could ever be returned.
So, what did Kaito take from you?
That's...
That's going to be your fifth shot already!
Why don't you slow down a little bit?
Just give me the tequila bottle.
Whatever you say.
I wonder how many minutes more are you going to last...
So this is it, huh?
What?
The reason why you're so edgy today.
Shut up.
You're still dragging that now?
I can't just forget a girl that I've adored
from the bottom of my heart.
You don't know anything about girls, do you?
Sorry about that then, I have no experience with them, you know?
Why don't I teach you then?
You're going to teach me?
That's right.
How are you going to teach me?
What are you going to do?
Something nice.
Rikka, could you be...
You finally realized?
You’re just kidding, right?
You think?
Rikka, just wait...
You're not satisfied with me?
Oh yeah, Hanabi looks a lot prettier,
and more importantly has bigger tits!
Then let's seelf that's true.
So?
How does it compare with Hanabi's?
Like I'd know that.
I haven't held her breasts yet.
Then mine is small?
You're not satisfied with it?
Well?
Hey...!
I won't be able to stop if you continue doing this.
You don't even have the guts to do that.
If you had, then you would have been doing
this with Hanabi instead of me, right?
But unfortunately, reality isn't that nice.
The one in front of you is me,
not Hanabi.
And I'm sure, the one Hanabi is with right now is...
Stop that!
Every thing's over...
Onii-chan!
What?
This voice, it's the voice of my beloved little sister!
Natane's voice!
I've finally found you!
Natane!
Onii-chan!
Natane, why are you here?
I came to meet you.
I left Papa and Mama behind.
You came alone? That must've been hard for you.
It was.
I got to Hokkaido by hitching on a truck.
I tried hitching on a ship next,
but it was actually heading for Russia.
I tried to get back on track, but I ended up in Italy.
When I hitched on a plane there, I accidentally went to Brazil.
It was really hard.
Natane, you sure worked very hard.
That's literally traveling the world just to meet her brother.
More like hitching around the world I think.
It's amazing that you actually reached this
place, or even came back to this country.
My wish to be with Onii-chan guided me here!
Guided you to a shortcut back to Japan?
Natane!
Onii-chan!
Tropical Kiss!
Nagi-san says that you can live with me in the meantime.
That's good, right Natane?
Okay.
Something that can't be returned, huh?
Do you feel good?
Yeah.
You can do whatever you want.
Whatever I want...
That's...!
They're getting stiff.
Hey, make sure to fondle them a lot.
Make them bigger, okay?
No, not there...!
That, that's...
What is this?
Hey, wait...
Does it feel good?
I don't know, but...
It feels weird.
It feels weird?
You don't feel aroused from my fingering?
No...
Something's coming...
Kaito?
It's okay, right?
What's that?
A man's symbol, what else.
I've never seen it as big as that.
Oh, so you don't have as much experience as I previously thought.
Hey, I can't just let it stay like this any longer.
Wait!
that's wrong?
Nothing...
This is...
Blood...
Hey, Rikka, this is...
Don't pull out.
But...
You plan to stop at this crucial moment? How terrible of you.
So it's your first time too?
So what?
Idiot! Why didn't you tell me?
If I did then you wouldn't have...
That's...
I was completely wrong at that time.
That's why I said you don't know anything about women.
Rikka...
With that, I'd just taken her very first time.
Anyway, this hurts like hell.
Your dick is just too big!
That's...
So, what about you?
How do you feel?
It feels good.
How unfair.
I think I really need to pull it out.
I said it's okay.
Just go all the way.
I got it.
Does it still hurt?
It doesn't anymore.
She's such a good woman, and I've just...
Why are you crying?
Because I'm happy.
Happy?
That I'm able to do something like this to a great woman like you.
To give my first time to you...
Too late for you to thank me now.
Yeah, I'm such an idiot.
Yeah, you're an idiot.
But the bigger idiot here is the one who's with you right now.
I don't know if I can,
but I'll try to be as gentle as possible.
No need.
Huh?
You don't need to be gentle with me.
Make it more painful for me.
Make it so painful that I'll never forget!
Carve the feeling into my heart!
I got it.
Rikka, I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming!
See you then.
See you.
Kaito, we wanted to confirm something with you.
The thing that you took from Rikka...
That siren sounds very close.
You're right.
Kaito, forget that...
It stopped.
I've heard that there are many cases of things
catching fire with no real reason here...
Could there be a fire nearby?
Hey, Kaito!
Kaito-san, we still need to talk!
No way...
Why?
No!
Hey Rikka, what are you about to do?
They're going to burn!
Look! It's already too late for that!
No! My room hasn't completely burned yet!
What are you going to get in there anyway?!
An important ring? A passbook or something?
Something more important!
I'm asking you what it is!
Just let me go already!
Rikka!
Really? What a relief.
So she's safe... Thank you very much.
Well then, take care.
After that we were put in an ambulance and taken to the hospital.
Nothing really happened to me,
but Rikka fell unconscious,
and Nagi-san said she did not wake up even
after she was brought to the hospital.
Nagi-san came to see me as soon as she could.
I then returned to the office alone, and waited.
Kaito...
Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Rikka too?
Yeah, she's on her way here With Nagi-san.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad you two are fine.
Yeah, I'm really glad.
Well, I'm going back to my room now.
If she drops by here,
tell her that I have "it".
"It"?
She'll understand.
Everyone, good night.
Good night.
G'night.
Weeks later
So, Nagi-san told you to bring that?
Try putting it on anyway.
No.
Why?
I can't work in those clothes.
Please!
Just try putting it on!
If you say so...
Done.
I thought it would suit you well.
Jeez, this is embarrassing.
Can I change back already?
Nope.
Why?
I want to ogle at it more.
Does this really look good for you?
Yeah, it's cute.
Well, if you say so...
...then I'll keep wearing it.
Seriously?
But!
Only when you're around, okay?
But that would defeat its purpose.
Wait, would I really show this cute Rikka to other men?
I can't let that happen!
Got it already?
Okay, I'll tell them that it's no good for you.
Thanks.
Okay, let's have sex.
Huh? Why?
You wore that for me, right?
Well, that's true, but what does it have to do with sex?
You wore that for me,
and now you'll perform a service for me in it.
Service? What am I supposed to do?
Lick me down there.
Lick?
Give me a blow job.
No good?
Okay, okay.
I don't think I can do this after all...
Don't back out on me now.
It's really big.
Just do it however you can.
It's my first time, I don't think I can do this properly.
I'm okay as long as you're the one doing it.
Well then...
What's wrong?
It felt really good, I was just startled.
Really? I'm happy!
Then I'll try to make this "service" more enjoyable.
My entire body feels like melting.
Rikka, I'm about to...!
Is this really her first time?
She's really good at this!
I can't hold it anymore!
Hey, Rikka...
Are you okay?
It's my thanks to you.
Me?
My thanks for saving that important piece of our memory.
I'm thanking you for that.
I see.
What are you two doing?
Natane?
You're awake?
I heard some weird sounds earlier.
You said she was a sound sleeper.
She usually always sleeps soundly!
It's because of these weird sounds you made!
I can't help it!
Hey, what are you two doing?
Well, umm...
We were wrestling!
Wrestling?
Yeah, we're kind of into that stuff right now.
Right, Rikka?
Y-Yeah!
I love wrestling, so I'm doing it with him!
Is that so?
Sorry we disturbed your sleep.
We're going to stop now.
Huh? We're stopping now?
You still want to continue in this situation?
But my boy down here is...!
My boy...
Save it for another day.
N-No way!