Your  pussy squeezes me with so much energy.
My penis might end up being damaged.
Incredible!
The sensei's dick fills me up, all the way.
What an incredible pussy you have, it is the best.
It's hard to find words to describe this great feeling.
Listen ...
I am the only one...
That can pierce your filthy cunt ...
No other guy can enter you.
You can see it right?
Our juices are united.
It is inside...
The cock of the sens ...
It is so deep in me. So deep.
Kanzaki Aoi.
You are mine.
Inside ... So great ...
No...
It's too ...
No. .. Slower ...
So no ...
Do not come inside...
I will come inside anyway.
We will continue like this ...
We will do a toast, since soon you will be able to give milk with these breasts.
No, I do not want a baby ...
Stop...
So hot ...
It's hot ... inside ...
It's hot...Inside...
My stomach is full of all the sensei's  hot cum...
True Blue Episode 2 Fansubbed by Broodwarjc
I was surprised it was by choice...
That wimp, he's really useless.
No...No...
I am coming...
Master,  I am coming soon...
Which means that soon we can make a new life.
Although, it would be good if you got pregnant today...
it would affect our fucking.
But you are so calm.
I will take responsibility.
No.
You will be a mother Aoi.
No, I do not want to be a mother ...
No...
No more...No...
Again inside...
Again he cums inside...
I am going to have many babies ...
Thanks for the food.
Sorry, Akihito-kun...
Aoi, it seems is not feeling very good.
I see...
I've had enough of school ...
The smell of sweat can be somewhat intense.
Especially a damp smell.
That's depraved ...
Take someone else's underwear ...
These are the ones you wore...
When you saw my cock for the first time.
Although you are no longer a virgin.
We still have much to do.
Do not make your master wait...
The panties you wore yesterday were bold.
So now I want to see some that have a stamped animal.
That strange feeling I had...
Since yesterday I was worried about something, but ...
Aoi...
Fuck.
G-Good morning...
Yes...
R-Really...
Eh?
Nothing ... It is a good day ... Today ...
Yes...
I see you're up early Kurusu.
In the morning you have to say 'good morning'.
The girls however have to do another service
You have already washed your pussy well?
Stop, please ...
Aoi!
Shoda!
Akihito!
They saw him attack the sensei.
I do not understand your reasoning  but ...
But, for no ...
reason are you allowed to use violence.
Hitting a teacher ...
is too much.
Since Shoda-sensei did not want to punish you.
Only this time you can go unpunished.
If something like this happens again.
I'll be sure to call your family ...
And we will take drastic measures.
Do you understand?
Do you understand!?
Yes...
Akihito has always tried to protect me.
And I also want to protect him ...
Aoi, really ...
it is on the subject of Shoda.
Aoi?
Yes...What?
We talked about Shoda.
But...the will of that man...has corrupted me.
His...
Are you listening, Aoi?
Aoi?
I'm sorry. The physical education period is about to start.
Get changed quickly.
I won't forgive you, if you are late for class.
Yes.
You just wait and see what I can do to Aoi.
Excuse me now, please.
I feel ashamed.
Idiot.
But I can't rub myself alone.
How cruel ...
It is...
Because you said so ...
Aoi later you have private class...
I'll be waiting in my office.
I do not want...
So you want me to teach our Kurusu where I put my fingers?
I may get hit again.
I will make you an incredible woman.
So keep rubbing.
We see that you need men.
There it goes.
Jo, no...
Aoi?
Aya-chan is sufficient ...
It's okay to say you are huge.
They are not huge ...
Furthermore compared with Aoi I am small ...
Now that I think about it, Aoi looked very tired.
If she studies too much, she will be sleepy.
Placing yourself in front a man this way is dull.
If you were a virgin it would be normal for you to be ashamed.
If you were a virgin.
Seeing my great cock, has already made this area wet.
You suck it, you already know how.
Also today, it is incredibly hard.
It stinks...
But it looks very delicious ...
Your depraved girlfriend sucks well...
Kurusu.
Aoi,  am almost there.
Aoi!
No, not there.
Aoi, are you aroused when I touch you here?
What...Is this feeling...
Although it was embarrassing to me ...
When he licked my ass like that somehow ...
I got excited.
Incredible.
No.
Stop now, please ...
Does it feel good?
Do you like it Aoi?
That is not so! That is not so! No, Aoi?
Yes! Yes!
Then let's clean out your filthy juices.
You made me this dirty.
It feels good ... His finger ... It feels so good ...
My ass feels good.
That pleasure ... My pussy is hot.
Thrusting his finger in my ass like that, makes my pussy juices come out, cannot control my pussy.
I'm cumming... I'm about to cum!
In...Incredible...
Since we have used adult liquid.
We will do more intense things.
Stop...I beg you...
Not there ... In my ass no...
A girl has two virginities.
I will teach a new pleasure to you.
It is... incredible.
No... Stop...
I feel that ... I'm going to die ... I will die ...
In the end Aoi-chan did not come?
She did not return.
They'll see ... They will see.
Speaking of her not coming, does she have a secret boyfriend?
I am close...
Sensei! Sensei! Sensei!!!
What is it?
Incredible...
His cock is fucking me ...
I'm coming, I'm coming...
Don't stop, I'm about to cum.
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!!!
The sensei's hard penis makes ... My pussy ...
My pussy cums!
Shit...
Shit!
Akihito, help me.
Save me.
I ... I no longer recognize ...
If you do not want ...
If you do not want to, then ignore Shoda.
I cannot do that. Sensei knows everything ...
All my secrets.
My measurements ...
When I am with you...
He made me confess to all sorts of perverted things.
Besides ... My body is starting to get used ...
My pussy and Sensei's penis move as if they were one.
Enough!
I understand.
I'll protect you, Aoi.
Akihito.
I wonder if she has recovered.
Aoi, we can start again.
As we were before.
Although I say it now, I have already made a promise to Akihito.
Your pussy.
I am going to screw your pussy! So hurry!
Is practice today?
Why?
Since going to secondary school.
My panties have always been noticeable.
My breasts were bigger.
And I always emphasized them.
Meanwhile my butt ...
That is enough.
What is clear is that you have always been outstanding.
Somewhat normal, since you have a very gifted body.
You clutched my body without practice.
This is for trying to run from me.
Acting like a virgin, even at this point.
Your body understands who it must obey.
Yes, my body feels as if it belongs to its master.
And it fully succumbs to his will.
Let's make a change.
Now, I wonder what Kurusu would think?
As usual, his penis enters me with a monstrous force ...
My whole body ...
So far it has been captive to the potency of this man ...
This cock has taught me the happiness of a woman.
My love ...
... I'm all yours.
Aoi...
What happened? You cannot fill me...
Do it faster to fill me.
Hey ... If I do it myself. Will your dick grow faster?
My pussy, will drive you crazy...
Hey, hey ...
Kurusu, is there watching us.
Come on ... Come, come, come.
Answer what I said.
Do not bother me Akihito.
Why ...?
Why that guy!?
Why do you hate the sensei?
My master  is a wonderful person.
And with a great cock.
You hate me, Aoi ...?
It is true that we fought often but, we ...
I love you. I love you Akihito.
But right now I'm totally happy.
Hey ... Enough is enough, right?
Now it's your turn.
Do me like you do, and fill me all up.
Kurusu, see if you can satisfy Aoi like me.
But know it will not be easy.
So try to conquer with your cock.
No, this is a joke.
Aoi.
This is a joke. Right?
I, well I do not want.
So small, you can not satisfy me.
Akihito's cock does nothing for me.
We see that you have not lived up to expectations, Kurusu.
This ...
As I thought only my master's penis can satisfy me.
Akihito's is not as hard and as thick as his.
It won't even reach the bottom.
You are always honest when you have my penis in you.
Have you noticed the difference between the two?
Akihito's was so small I could not feel it enter.
While your cock penetrates me and reaches deep...
So deep...I will cum.
Forgive me Akihito.
But sensei's penis makes me happier.
It makes me enjoy it more.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
Compared to yours, I prefer the sensei.
It makes my pussy feel enormous pleasure.
And not just his cock.
I love sensei. I love Shoda-sensei.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
But. His cock. His cock.
Fill me with your penis juice Sensei!
Fill my hot and thirsty pussy!
You want to become pregnant?
You want to have my baby?
Okay?
I want to have it.
Are you sure, Aoi?
I said I want to have it.
Yes, I want to have sensei's baby.
I will have sensei's baby.
Give me your semen, your semen.
I will take all of your semen in my dirty pussy.
Original Japanese translation by Frost Yume Fansubs.
Spainish to English translation by Broodwarjc.