Arahama-san, your big thing has really built up a lot of cum, right?
Misako, wait that's...
Misako... I'm about to cum.
Just cum a lot, Arahama-san.
Now, that's enough.
Jeez, Arahama-kun, that won't do.
You still have to cum on my big tits, you know.
Ryouko-san, hey...!
Misako, just watch from over there and
witness Arahama-kun's grand climax.
Ryouko...!
This is bad, if you squeeze it like that I'll...
You're really enjoying my tit fuck, aren't you?
Since I feel happy, I'm going to do lots for you.
No, Ryouko, I'm about to cum!
Okay, you're through.
Nope, when it comes to breasts I can
also offer some serious competition.
Look, mine are quite big too.
Tease them, okay?
Just let your dick in and out of my breasts as you please.
Oh wow...
Move over old lady!
Kotori?
Arahama-san's dick is mine!
Hey, Aina, his dick will be taken away
from you if you just space out there.
Here, suck on it too.
O-Okay.
Arahama-san, does your dick feel good?
You all, are just coming in one after the other!
If this goes on, I'll really be...!
Arahama-san...
Amazing, his dick is starting to twitch.
It's okay, just cum inside my...
No, I'm the one pleasuring Arahama-san,
so don't take him away from me!
Just cum, Arahama-san.
Release it all in...
You sure came a lot.
I'm glad.
See? I’m Arahama-san's number one after alI.
Hey, Misako-chan, I just can't let that pass!
Arahama-kun's dick really wanted to cum in my tits!
I was already about to make him cum earlier!
No fair, no fair!
You're amazing, Arahama-san.
That’s an amazingly ecstatic expression.
This isn't fair.
And he even came a lot....
Why in the world did it turn out like this?
I don't think I can really handle all five
of them at the same time anymore.
I admit, all of these five girls became my sex friends.
She's Shimizu Misako.
This one is Yanagi Ryouko.
This is Endou Makiko.
This very lively girl is Hoshino Kotori.
And last but not least, Kamishima Aina.
Every one of them is really great
and somehow all of them are in love with yours truly.
Having five sex friends sure brought
lots of trouble and issues before.
But our relationship as such still managed to remain the same.
However...
Hey, Arahama-kun.
You're going to insert your huge dick inside me this time, right?
Wait, you can't do that.
I'm next in line.
No way!
Even I want to have sex with Arahama-san, you know!
Will you old ladies please shut up?
I totally lose in the breast department,
but my tight and soft pussy is the best for him!
Umm.... I want to do it too!
Wait, all of you pipe down please!
I understand how you all feel,
but I don't think I'll live if I don't exercise some moderation!
Why?
You promised that you'd make all five of us feel good, right?
I did say that, but...
Doing it every single day with all five of you at the same time,
is well... unexpected.
This already goes beyond what I'm capable of doing.
Don't say that.
You haven't made me feel good this week, you know.
And I was even looking forward to it...
I also want to have sex with you!
I'm sorry...
But, I have work tomorrow.
I just can't go on having sex with each
and every one of you all night.
Arahama-san, you won't fuck us tonight?
A-Anyway, I don't think my body can handle much more of this!
I now have a different view on my actual situation!
Just allow me to think this over for now, please!
Okay, you're all dismissed!
Dismissed!
Original Animation Disc
Sex Graved Demons Project!
What These Girls Want Is An Erotic Heavy Rotation
We were all kicked out in the end.
*pout*
What did he mean by that?
The part where he said he would think it over?
Before that.
That he now has a different view on the actual situation.
Does he not love us anymore?
And now he cheats with other women?
No way, it'd be anything but that.
That's definitely not it.
Then what is it?
Explain it to me so that I will understand!
Well...
It's true that Arahama-kun has been quite
stressed out over the past few days.
We may have expected too much from him.
Expected what?
Why, sex of course.
He had originally enjoyed having sex with us at a leisurely pace.
We may have tried to tie him up to his word too much.
Tie him up?
It's usual among lovers, right?
One party gets tired of the relationship
because;the other is being too clingy.
And it ends with "Hey, let's break up already."
That can't be.
Everyone's too passionate as they compete with each other
and we all tried to get closer and closer to Arahama-kun.
Pushing ourselves onto him, always asking him for sex.
He might have felt too much pressure from it already.
Well, it's true that Arahama-san does things at his own pace.
At this fate, he might really get sick
of us and find other sex friends...!
Hmm, I guess that's possible.
That’s definitely not good.
Which is why, what he said holds true in some sense.
I think we may need "that".
A plan that will not make him feel too pressured by us.
Rules that will help maintain this relationship.
So Arahama-kun,
would you like to eat something at my shop?
What's up?
Just follow my lead, okay?
Here, thanks for waiting.
Wow, this looks delicious as always!
So, why is Aina here?
Um, I'm really sorry for what I did before.
Nah, don't worry about it.
I was just a little tired at that time.
Is this the reason why you called me here?
Of course.
We all discussed it afterward.
And we agreed that we're also quite at fault.
So, what did you discuss?
That we were all so happy that you said you'd love us all equally,
that you'd make us all feel great.
And we just basically clung onto it.
Well, everyone does love you, so we really can't
help it if we want to have sex with you.
But we thought we might be asking too much.
So, we decided to let you off during weekdays,
and only do it on the weekends.
We would all take turns every time.
Just when did all this...
So that's why suddenly no one has come to see me.
That really scared me though.
It gave me room to rest, at least.
Of course, if you're the one who wants to do it,
even if it's a weekday we'd all definitely agree.
Just like before.
I think that idea is really great.
Because I really don't think I can do all five of you.
So, it's the two of you this weekend, huh?
Yup, and that's the agreement, it's just fine
if we get along together today, right?
Of course.
I did get a long rest in the past few days anyway.
I'm really sorry.
No, I didn't mean to say that out of spite.
So you don't need to apologize like that.
I never really hated anyone, and I still want to have sex.
Though having five partners every day is just...
So, it'd be a cinch with just the two of us?
Why don't I prove it to you right now?
Oh my, are you sure?
Then, I'll have to take hold of this opportunity.
Well? How are my boobs?
I'm going to get your dick big with these in no time.
It's really stiff.
I bet it would squirt lots of cum later.
That's great, Ryouko.
You're the best!
It's not just my boobs, you know.
See? This is my tit fuck plus blowjob.
Oh look, your dick's starting to twitch.
Ryouko, I can't hold it in anymore!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
You came a lot.
Now then, next round is here.
Copy that, here I go.
Arahama-kun, you're pushing really hard.
You just came but it's still this stiff.
This is the best, and I'm about to cum already.
Please, push it inside some more.
Jiggle my breasts some more.
Penetrate my womb more!
Okay, I'm going to speed up the pace!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum too!
All while being fucked straight in the womb!
It's coming out...
Your cum is pouring into my womb.
Okay, you're next Aina.
Aina, what's wrong?
Your pussy is already this wet.
Oh, you're right.
Were you aroused by our sex act earlier?
Then, it’s now your turn to feel great.
I'll help you.
Here I go, Aina.
This is amazing.
Aina-chan, all of it is going straight inside you.
Oh no, Arahama-san,
If you move your dick like that...
Lots of fluids are squirting out.
Well then, I'm going to join as well.
Ryouko-san...!
Aina-chan, your breasts are really beautiful.
See? It feels great to be penetrated while being fondled.
Don't Ryouko-san, I'm going to go crazy with this.
Aina, your insides feel really great.
No, Arahama-san, if you push hard like that I'll...!
You're about to cum, right?
It's okay, just cum whenever you want.
Me too. I'm about to cum!
Arahama-san, Arahama-san!
I came.
While being cummed inside my womb by Arahama-san.
It feels like I haven't had sex like this with him for a long time.
Maybe this taking turns thing isn't bad at all.
I'm looking forward to next time.
Though, I don't want you to cum too much, okay?
"Sex Friend Convenience"
So, It's Kotori and Makiko this week, eh?
I've been waiting for such a long time.
Hey, Arahama-san, is it true that you're
going to give us lots of sex today?
Y-Yeah.
I'm excited to know what you have in store for us.
Arahama-san, make us feel good, okay?
Okay, we're about to start your favorite masochist play.
Though, you can't really hear me speak.
I can't see...
Arahama-san.
We're starting with Kotori.
Eh? What?
Arahama-san, what are you going to do?
Kotori, just stay put.
What is this sound, Arahama-san?
What is this?
It's going in.
This vibrating big and thick thing is going inside me.
Not yet.
The good part is still about to come.
What is this? My insides are getting stirred up.
This is just...
No, pull it out...
My pussy's going crazy!
That's great Kotori, it's starting to get really wet.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum hard with this!
Arahama-san, I'm cumming!
Then cum!
Just cum Kotori!
You came great there.
But we're not done yet.
Well? You can see how my thing enters you with this, right?
And thanks to that vibrator, your pussy is now this wet.
Oh no, this is embarrassing Arahama-san...
Embarrassing? I don't think so.
You were the masochist getting all
aroused with that vibrator earlier.
Arahama-san, your dick is amazing.
You mean yours is getting amazingly wet.
Did the blindfold make it even easier for
the masochist Kotori to get horny?
If you keep on pushing hard like that...
My pussy will just keep on cumming when it's wet like this
and it's even making very sloppy sounds!
Arahama-san, Arahama-san!
Oh wow, your dick is getting really wet with my pussy.
Amazing, my love juices are squirting like crazy!
Make it louder, make those sounds louder!
Your dick is hitting me deeply
It feels great, I'm happy.
Being penetrated by your dick!
You're about to cum, right?
Okay, then cum as much as you can!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Wow, that was really intense.
Good girl, Kotori.
You were cute back there.
Arahama-kun, you’re there, right? Right?
Yeah, I'm here, Makiko.
Now, here's the dick you've been waiting for.
No words are needed to start sucking.
As expected of my obedient, Makiko.
But, how about this?
There, I'm going to thrust it all the way to your throat.
Your mouth right now is just another pussy for me!
Your blowjob is the best, Makiko.
Here I come!
Hey, you just spilled it all.
Too bad for you Makiko, because you're
about to be punished for that.
I'll be taking this.
Arahama-kun, no...
Where are you touching?
In my ass? Wait, no way...
It hurts, it hurts...
Arahama!
Your hole here feels very tight.
It's quite hard pushing it in if it grips me this hard.
My ass feels amazing.
Your big dick is filling it in completely, widening it.
I'm being penetrated while blind fol...
What things are you imagining, Makiko?
Just continue shaking your hips!
Oh no, I'm going to cum with my ass.
I see, you're about to cum.
Then I shall grant you your wish.
Reach your climax with anal sex!
It's hot, your cum is flowing inside my ass.
Okay, Makiko.
What kind of erotic expression do you have now? Let me see.
Hurry...
Makiko, what a lewd face you have there.
Did it really feel that good?
Yes, it did.
Hurry and get it over with already...
So, how about you, Kotori?
You want to taste my dick again, right?
Yeah.
I'm still not satisfied.
Me too, violate me more, Arahama-kun.
Please! I beg of you!
Violate me more and more and more please!
Of course, the night is still young.
So, it's just you today.
Something wrong with just me?
Well... it's been going in pairs for the last few sessions.
Of course there's nothing wrong.
Jeez, well I did hit the jackpot you see.
And I'd also love to take the opportunity to be alone with you.
I see, so that's part of the turn rotation rule, huh?
Yes.
So, what does Misako, our winner, want to do?
This is important for you, right?
I can take you anywhere you want.
I'm happy, but it's alright.
There's no need for special gimmicks, as long
as I can spend some leisure time with you.
It's been quite a while since I actually got
the chance to spend some time with you.
So, the fact that I can be with you all day
already makes me happy enough.
I see.
That's how it is for you.
Yes, besides...
While waiting for my turn,
I've reconfirmed just how much I love you.
Everyone else probably feels the same way,
so it inevitably ended in a competition,
but I guess some days really should
be allotted for rests and breaks.
Let's just take our time here and relax.
Is that so? Thank you Misako.
Though, I was actually the one who
said I was going to pleasure you all.
So I'm going to pleasure you too, just
like how I pleasured the others.
Arahama-san...
Misako, you're beautiful.
Arahama-san, my breasts feel great.
Misako, let me hear your cute voice more.
No, it's embarrassing.
No it's not.
Because you're really beautiful.
Your thing here is already craving for me.
Do you want it in?
Yes.
Your big thing came all the way in.
Misako!
Arahama-san, I love you, I really love you!
Misako, I'm about to...!
Me too, I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
Misako, Misako!
Arahama-san!
I think... I am a really lucky guy.
What's wrong? Saying that all of a sudden.
Well, a nobody like me just happens to be loved by all of you...
I've been thinking for the past few days.
That all five of you really think dearly of me.
That's why I want to really try and make you all feel good.
And I did promise it before.
Eh? But...
Of course doing it every day and all night is out of the question.
Even for someone like me,
it's just impossible to be interested in other
women besides you five anyway.
Of course, I plan to cherish the affection everyone has given me.
So that I can be with all of you from now on.
I have to really try hard and do a lot for that...
Arahama-san...
At least that's what I want to say.
Was that embarrassing?
No, of course not.
I want everyone to hear exactly what you said.
Why don't we call everyone over then?
I'm fine with that.
Well, if it's okay with you then....
But, this one-on-one day is important for you, right?
I'm okay.
You do want to have sex with everyone, am I correct?
Of course I do, but...
If I can get a few rests in between.
Okay, you're right.
So we're stuck with this in the end, huh?
I'm happy, but...
Oh yes...!
Let's just accept it.
I completely welcome this idea.
Yes, I'm happy.
Arahama-san, you're penetrating deep inside me!
Make yourself feel good with all of us.
Arahama-san, just cum.
Cum lots inside us.
Here I go, everyone!
Thank you, that felt really good everyone.
I don't think I can ever love anybody else except you girls.
What? Was that a marriage proposal I just heard?
It is, it is, it definitely is!
Arahama-san, is that true?
I heard it as well.
He really said it, that he can never love anybody else except us.
Arahama-san.
Eh? Eh?!
Well, let's just take it that way.