Everyone, are you ready?
Y-Yes!
Yes, of course.
I'm good to go here.
I'm also ready.
Now then, here we go!
Yay!
it's the sea!
Yahoo!
There!
Makiko, here I go!
Hey!
Let's tan while we still have time.
Arahama-san! Hurry!
Let's play too!
Alright, alright, just wait.
No need to rush.
We went to the beach.
If you were to ask how things turned out this way,
it all happened like this...
It's so hot.
Yes, it really is.
Arahama-san, don't you have an AC or something in here?
Sorry about this.
Say, Arahama-kun,
are we really going to spend the entire day here?
That's what I initially thought.
But it really is too hot, though.
I'm going to prepare some barley tea.
Qkay, sorry about this, Misako.
It's so hot, I don't think I can make it.
I wanna splash a bucket of water on my face.
Can't agree with you more.
This heat just makes me want to go to the beach.
Wait, to the beach?
Arahama-kun, did you say the beach?
You just mentioned 'beach'.
You said it.
You said it, right?
Y-Yeah, I did, but...
Is there something wrong with that?
To the beach he said!
He said he'll take us to the beach!
Wh-What?!
Alright! To the beach!
I have to buy a new swimsuit.
Oh, I know a good store!
Which beach are we going to exactly?
Let's see...
Tarika, Tahiti,
oh, and Tarau is good too.
H-Hey!
Original Animation Disc
Ah, ah, ah! Under the sun
squirt, squirt, at the Outdoor Bath. Chapter!
Sex Friend Convenience?
Ah, ah, ah! Under the Sun
Squirt, squirt, at the Outdoor Bath
Chapter!
And that's how we came here.
Whether it was a misunderstanding or a trick,
before I could even tell what was happening,
these pumped up girls spurred me on,
and we all headed to the beach.
Oh yeah, this might be the first time I've
gone somewhere with all of them.
We usually just hang out at my place,
so I guess this is fine too.
And so, after quickly deciding on this weekend,
we then started our two-day swimming
and outdoor hot spring trip.
I'm pooped already.
Let me rest for a bit.
You've been hard at work.
Are you alright? You seemed to collapse all of a sudden.
You totally have no problems with this, huh?
You bet.
I've been saving up for times like these.
It's what we adults need, right?
Anyway...
Don't you have anything else to say?
That swimsuit looks really sexy.
I kind of want to do it with you right now.
Thanks.
Look over there,
Everyone else looks fantastic, don't you think?
I agree.
You want to have sex already, right?
Y-Yeah.
Ryouko-san, that's not fair!
J-Just wait!
We can't do it with these many people around!
Then we can do it somewhere where
there aren't any people, right?
I'm going to pleasure you really good today, okay?
Feeling good yet?
Yeah, of course.
Are you feeling aroused here too?
Oh, it's getting bigger.
I don't think there's any guy who wouldn't
feel the same way in this situation.
Then, I'll take those feelings...
And presto!
Your big thing is finally out.
Getting aroused in an outdoor setting already, I see.
It's really stiff.
See, it feels great getting a handjob from me, right?
Yeah, your hands feel really smooth.
It makes me go, wow!
How cute.
Ryouko, Ryouko...!
I can feel it.
You can't hold it in anymore, right?
Next, I'm going to give you a tit fuck.
Just moan whenever you want.
I don't care if somebody else is watching.
Stop kidding me!
The more thrilling, the more arousing it gets, right?
So, how does it feel?
Feels different from any other pair of tits, right?
Yeah, it does.
And when I do this...
Here we go.
Feels good, right?
Well?
This is really something...!
I know, right?
I can really tell that your dick is starting to feel good.
It's getting all twitchy between my breasts.
Here, I'm going to pleasure it even more.
These tits are about to squeeze this dick dry.
No fair, I want to do it with him too!
Our vacation's just getting started.
It's okay.
Once he cums from this, I'll let you girls switch.
Right now though, it's my turn.
Oh crap...
I'm going to cum!
No, not yet.
You have to let me suck it some more.
Ryouko, I'm really going to...!
Just go ahead, I'm going to finish this first round.
I can't swallow it all.
Finally refreshed.
You came a lot.
Your fresh cum tasted great.
Now I want to lick it all.
Hey, I'm next!
Let's have lots of sex!
M-Me too!
I-I want to have lots of sex with Arahama-san too.
Alright, I'll take on both of you!
Hey, hurry up and do it already, Arahama-san.
I'm embarrassed, and yet I feel completely horny.
Here we go.
I'm going to fuck you first, Kotori.
Arahama-san...!
Go all the way inside me.
You don't have to tell me that!
So, how does my dick feel?
It's big.
Definitely big.
And fucking me with it just feels...
Feels what?
Feels so good that I'm going to shamelessly moan.
I'll get so horny that somebody else might notice.
Well, let's hear it then.
That shameless moan you were talking about!
I'm going to moan.
It feels so good.
Getting fucked by you feels so good.
It feels so good, that my moans are...
Oh no, I can't hold back!
Kotori-chan, you're amazing.
Your voice is echoing loudly.
No, this is embarrassing!
Everybody is hearing me moan!
They can hear me having sex!
Yeah, just let them hear it.
Let everyone out there hear it!
Arahama-san, you meanie!
But,
I really feel horny this way!
It really looks like it feels good.
I want to do it already.
No need to hurry, because you're up next.
I'm getting penetrated all the way by Arahama-san!
I'm... I'm...!
You like doing it outdoors, right?
Look, it's gripping me really tightly.
Don't..!
No, not there, please!
It feels too good.
This is...
My embarrassing part's completely exposed!
I'm about to cum!
Me too.
Alright, here I go.
Arahama-san, Arahama-san!
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum!
Your cum is all the way inside.
Your cum is...
You were cute back there, Kotori.
Next is Aina, right?
No, don't pull out yet.
Don't pull it out yet!
Just rest up there for a bit, Kotori.
Sorry for the wait, Aina.
Y-Yes!
Please cum lots inside me too.
It came twice already, and yet it's still big and hot.
Fuck me.
Please, fuck me.
Aina, let me hear more of your sweet voice.
Go deeper inside me, Arahama-san.
Completely pleasure yourself inside me.
Now I'm starting to moan too.
Just like Kotori-chan...
Aina, I love your meek expression too.
Alright then, go as wild as you can!
Y-Yes!
With your dick, I'm...
Slowly becoming a slut.
Do you hate sluts, Arahama-san?
Do you find the slutty me shameful?
Of course not!
I love the slutty you, Aina.
So show me more of your slutty self, Aina!
I'm happy!
I'm slowly becoming sluttier and sluttier,
as you continue to fuck me.
Your dick feels so good!
Oh no,
your dick feels so good, that I...
It feels really good to be penetrated this deeply.
Please fuck me more!
Your dick feels very good...
Doesn't it feel great?
More, fuck me more intensely!
Aina?
H-Her moans are even more outrageous than mine.
But...
It's great being fucked deeply by Arahama-san's dick like this.
I can't just stop anymore.
I never thought having sex like this outdoors could feel so great.
Oh yes!
I just love how it fucks me.
More, I want to feel more of your dick!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
My mind and my pussy are already losing it.
I'm cumming.
I'm really about to cum!
I'm cumming too!
You sure came lots inside me.
Now that's my Arahama-kun.
Three times already, and yet you can still cum so much.
How was it, Aina-chan?
Y-Yes, umm...
It was just so amazing, and I just kept cumming.
Your expression looks really perverted.
He kept on making you cum I see.
Well, I guess this really ends the first round.
Yeah, I couldn’t agree more.
No, you can't just do that!
Eh?
You need to have sex with us as well!
That's right.
It'd be troubling if you didn't do it with us as well.
Sex Friend Convenience?
How beautiful.
The sunset looks gorgeous.
The wind feels great too.
The scent of sea salt that surrounds the hot springs is wonderful.
I haven't felt this relaxed in a long time.
The view is really great.
Misako.
Can I...
...go first?
Look, when I do this...
Well?
Yeah, it feels good.
The way your breasts rub against me.
True, I really feel horny,
...as I continue rubbing my breasts against you.
I can feel your nipples getting harder and harder.
Even your thing here, it's already...
I can't hold back any longer.
Can I put your dick inside now?
Okay, I can't wait for it any longer, either.
Here I go, I'm putting it in.
It's in.
Your dick is inside me now.
Just stay put there.
I'll handle this.
Your thing feels very hot.
It's opening up my insides.
Misako, are you alright?
Does it feel too tight?
I'm alright.
Your dick might be realty big,
but something like this is already...!
This is my thanks,
for taking me on this wonderful trip.
Oh yes...!
Your thing is rubbing hard inside.
Oh no, it's starting to feel even better.
This is amazing, Misako.
The way your hips move is...!
Your dick inside me, it's...
Getting stiffer, bigger...
Oh no, I can't stop.
The way your dick rubs me feels so good,
that I...!
I don't think it's fair that you're the only one moving around.
So here I go too!
This is amazing, Arahama-san.
I love you, Arahama-san,
and I love this!
I'm supposed to be the one pleasuring you.
But it's I who ended up....
I'm totally fine with that.
So let's just pleasure each other, Misako!
Oh yes, this feels good.
Arahama-san, kiss... kiss me.
Kiss me!
Arahama-san, just keep on fucking me.
Penetrate me deeply.
Let's, let's keep on pleasuring each other.
You're going wild inside me, Arahama-san!
I'm about to cum.
Me too.
Here I cum!
I'm, I'm cumming!
Your cum,
Your cum is...!
It feels hot...
I just came,
and you came lots too.
Arahama-san, thank you very much.
I'm already tired of waiting.
I really want to have sex with you already.
Wait, not so suddenly!
But...!
I can't wait a second longer!
Let's have lots of sex together.
I get it, I get it already Makiko!
It's already this wet.
Your tongue is now licking my pussy.
It feels really good.
Keep doing that to my slutty pussy.
Just keep licking it.
Please...
Hey, Makiko, what are you doing?
You have to do your own share!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to pleasure you too.
I shall now clean this dick with my tongue.
Why does this big thing taste so erotic...?
Oh yes...
Your tongue just feels so good in my pussy,
and your thing here just keeps on getting wet.
This dick of yours is really big and delicious.
And I'm sure it feels great for you too...
Arahama-kun, just keep on licking deeper.
Keep on licking harder.
I just came...
But I'm not yet satisfied with this.
Same here.
I haven't even cum yet.
I'm sorry, then next I'll...
Please make yourself feel good inside my pussy.
Penetrate me however you want.
Just keep on fucking my slutty pussy.
I'm going to put it all the way in.
Alright, bring it on!
It's all the way in.
It's inside me now.
Arahama-san, push it in more from below.
Leave this to me.
Here we go!
The way you penetrate me is incredible.
And the way you fuck me is just wonderful.
Well?
Does my pussy feel good?
Hey... are you getting aroused with it?
Yeah, it's the best.
I'm glad.
Just keep on fucking me.
Fondle my breasts too.
Oh yes...
My pussy and breasts are really getting aroused.
My hips keeps on moving on their own,
as my body craves more for your dick.
Here, we're not done just yet.
I'm going to cum hard!
I'm going crazy for your dick,
right down to my very core!
I'm happy, I'm really happy.
I'm cumming.
I'm about to cum real soon.
Yeah, I'll make you cum.
And I'm going to cum lots on my own!
Arahama-kun, I’m cumming.
It's coming out.
Your cum is coming out...
Wow, you really came lots.
There's lots of your thick cum.
I'm really pooped.
I really don't think I can go for another round.
Thank you, Arahama-kun.
I love you.
Aww, the first day's finally over.
Yeah, it went by really quickly.
But it was fun.
How about you, Arahama-kun?
Is your summer complete now?
Yeah.
The occasional vacation doesn't seem so bad after all.
We also had fun.
Arahama-san, thank you very much.
No, you don't need to thank me.
I'm good as long as everyone enjoyed it.
But, to think that we're already going home tomorrow...
Feels Kind of sad.
It is just a two-day, one night event anyway.
Nothing we can do about it.
It's okay, Aina-chan.
If it's for a trip, he'll be glad to take us on one again.
Oh, I think that's great.
I wonder where he will take us next time?
Alright!
Let's go overseas next time!
Right, if we're doing this, let's go all out.
Jeez, there really is nothing I can do.
Hey, we can still go somewhere tomorrow, right?
Let's all go!
It looks like there's a beautiful waterfall near this places.
Shall we go there?
Oh, a waterfall.
Let's go, Arahama-san.
Please, please... please?
That's a great idea.
Why don't we all go there?
Yeah, why not?
I agree.
Wow, I can't wait to go!