copyright 2012 serious business fansubs
if you paid for this fansub, you were ripped off!
Tsui no Sora (Endsky)
Does not human life continue eternally?
Even if one's body is destroyed, their life shall become motes of essence,
which shall gather in a new body and live on.
What foolishness. Don't you get it?
Not just humans... but all life must come to an end.
And so shall this universe come to an end as well...
You're mistaken! Eternal life, the circle of metempsychosis, they are-
I am not mistaken. The mistaken one is you.
I know, I shall show you...
Wh, what are you doing?
I shall introduce you to the most sublime experience in the world...
No, stop it. Nooo!
sorry i don't feel like subbing the ero shit
Mamiya, for the sake of the motes of essence which remain in me, I shall destroy this body.
So that the world's end of which you speak may be held back...
Hey, Yukito! Wake up already!
We're going to be late!
Jeez, every morning you're like this...
Oh, it's you, Kotomi...
Oh, they're white today. The color of purity, how nice...
You pervert!
Hey, Kotomi. Kotomi. Kotomi!
Why are you still mad?
Because you're always such a pervert, that's why!
It's my nature as a man, you know.
What's your nature as a man?!
You don't understand my feelings at all...
Huh? What'd you say?
Hey, just now, I couldn't hear you... what did you say?
Ah, Yukito... over there...
What? Ah...
Police cars... and is that an ambulance?
What happened?
Kotomi, let's go check it out.
Kotomi...
Yukito... why did something like this happen...
Seems like Zakuro was killed by falling from the rooftop.
Yeah, I hear the police are treating it as a suicide.
But she wasn't acting suicidal...
If it were a suicide, wouldn't she ordinarily have left a note or something?
Ah, but I hear she was really popular with the guys.
Could it have been a jealous lover?
But there wasn't any sign of a struggle on the rooftop.
Attention. We will be holding an assembly of the whole school.
All students, please come to the school yard.
I will repeat...
Man, today's pretty gloomy...
I don't even remember anything from class...
Kotomi, cheer up...
I guess that's an absurd thing to ask.
After all, Zakuro was your friend, and now she's dead...
And on top of that, no one knows why...
Yukito... thanks for worrying about me.
But I'm all right now.
Kotomi...
I said I'm okay, didn't I? Anyway, I have club activities, so go home ahead of me.
Club activities? At a time like this?
Before my mood gets any worse, I'm gonna try working up a sweat.
I understand, Kotomi. Let it all out.
But, let's go home together today. I'll be waiting here.
Thanks, Yukito. Then, see you later!
What are you doing over there, Yokoyama?
Hurry up and change.
Ah, yes. I'm sorry. I'll get changed right away.
Zakuro, just what happened to you?
None of us know what to believe anymore...
Kotomi, who was always so cheerful until yesterday, is so sad...
Minakami. Are you thinking of Takashima?
Ah, yeah.
The circle of metempsychosis. Endsky.
Eh? Ayana, what are you talking about?
Mamiya hasn't come to school lately, has he?
Ah, Mamiya? Isn't he the biggest loner in our class?
I wonder what happened to him.
I've seen him once in a while.
Eh? So he has come to school?
Yes, but not to the classroom.
Then where?
I'm not really certain, but probably...
Well, whatever. Besides that, Ayana, do you know anything about Zakuro?
Hmm. Seems like she had something to do with Mamiya...
With Mamiya? What do you mean?
Mamiya... was involved in something weird.
Endsky, or something.
Endsky? What's that?
I don't know either. But, Mamiya was definitely obsessed with some strange idea.
Strange idea?
Yeah. It seems like he approached Takashima about it.
But, when she returned to the classroom after talking to him,
she was just studying normally with everyone...
Something like that happened, huh?
But what does that have to do with her committing suicide?
I'm not sure. But, you had better be careful of Mamiya.
Once in a while, he has these scary eyes...
I'm sorry, Yukito. I made you wait...
Seems like you cheered up.
Yeah. A little, now that I've sweated it out.
Shall we head back?
Kotomi, sorry about this morning. I was just messing with you.
If you buy me a hamburger, I'll forgive you!
Oh u!
'Cause I'm already hungry...
Kotomi's holding in her sadness...
Understood. Let's go get a combo!
Yukito, I love you!
Huh? Yasuko Yokoyama went missing in the night?
It seems like it. Her parents just came to school, along with the police...
Kotomi, did you notice anything odd about her during your club?
No, nothing. We were just practicing on our own as usual.
Hm? Ah... where's Kotomi?
She's always here to yell at me in that energetic voice...
Well, I guess it's my turn.
Oh, Yukito.
Morning. Is Kotomi still asleep?
Well...
What is it?
In the evening, she got a phone call from Yokoyama in her kendo club...
She went to meet her, and she still hasn't come back...
wat?
Something strange is going on at your school...
And she's gotten involved in it...
Call the cops, lady!
I'm gonna go check it out!
Ayana!
Oh, Minakami. Morning.
Ayana! Tell me where Mamiya is!
Please, tell me!
Why are you so worked up?
Kotomi's gone missing this time!
Huh? Kotomi is missing?
Yeah. I just had her mom call the police.
Hey, Ayana. Where has Mamiya gone?
I'm not positive, but I think he's... at the pool.
The pool?
Yeah. When the indoor pool was built, the outdoor pool was retired.
There's no water in it right now.
And I saw Mamiya go down into the drainage channel of it once...
That's it! Ayana, I'm going on ahead! Explain things to the police!
Very well, that's enough! Now have a taste of me!
Nooo!
Cry just like that! No one's going to come save you!
Fuck you, Mamiya!
Minakami, why are you here...
Yukito...
You freak! Do you understand what you've done?
Endsky...
What?
I can see it... Endsky...
Endsky is... that which visits the eternal darkness...
Mamiya... you...
Can't you see it, Minakami?
Look... it's right over there... Endsky...
You're nuts...
Zakuro? Is that Zakuro?!
Don't come! Don't come near me!
Mamiya, it's all right now.
This is not a world of eternal darkness...
Endsky is... the way it has been from the beginning...
This universe... has no beginning, nor end...
Lies, lies! It will end! It must!
Kotomi, are you all right!
Yeah. Thank you, Yukito.
It must have been scary.
But, when you came to rescue me, Yukito...
I was really happy... thank you...
That's a little embarrassing...
This is your reward for protecting me...
I'll give myself to you...