Ayaka sure used to be our idol, but to think she was taken away by Endou!
Damn it! Look at you two, getting all happily married before we do.
Endou, seriously, congrats man.
Thank you, senpai.
Yeah, about that.
Prove to us that you really love her!
– Kiss! Kiss!
– Ayaka.
– Hiroshi-kun.
– Kiss! Kiss!
Nice!
Akaka's lips are sexy.
So, how many times do you fuck each day?
I-I can't answer a question like that!
I guess these things really do happen though.
Being reunited with someone from your old social circle.
You usually call that a miracle!
I'm jealous!
Good for you, Endou.
Make Ayaka happy, ok?
O-Of course.
Though I'm honestly not that confident.
Congrats to you too, Ayaka.
Endou's a good guy
so I don't think you were wrong to choose him.
Ogata-kun.
That's right, Endou's a fine choice!
Speaking as Ayaka's first guy, I'm proud of you!
I-Idiot! Watch your mouth, Fujiwara!
Did I say something wrong?
It's just that as the guy who took Ayaka's virginity, I...
Yeah, that's not something you say!
Sorry about that, Ayaka.
I-It's been 10 years already. Isn't that behind us now?
No need to worry about keeping these guys in check, Ogata-san.
That was cool, Endou.
That's our Endou. These things make you a man among men.
Like I was saying, Ogata, you worry about things too much.
You're playing the good guy, but you've
done it with Ayaka a few times, haven't you?
I know you, man! When Ayaka and a guy'd
break up, you offer to "just talk about it"
then you two'd slip into a hotel.
I-Idiot, Fujiwara! What are you talking about?
The facts are the facts. Just tell us!
Didn't you once say that you two were physically
compatible and that you two could do it a lot?
I never said that! I wouldn't say something like that!
– What are you smiling for, asshole!
– Ayaka.
The past really doesn't matter, you guys.
I mean, just last night we had sex three times.
Hi-Hiroshi-kun, what are you saying?!
Way to go, Endou. I envy you fresh-wed, happy idiots.
But that's real reassuring.
Even now, remembering that time gets me hard.
You remember it too, don't you Ayaka?
That night I got dumped by my girlfriend.
When you listened to me go on about my breakup,
you asked, "Shall I help you forget your troubles?"
That was honestly my favorite time having sex.
But good for you, Ayaka, that such a
big-hearted guy was willing to marry you.
Honestly, if I knew your past, I'd be hesitant to marry you myself.
What's wrong, Endou?
I... I...
I'm gonna get some air.
What's up with him?
That's not like him. He's not offended is he?
You idiot, that was him, desperately trying to tough this out.
How do we fix this shitty mood, Fujiwara, Sakazaki?
Quit making a fuss, we're just drunk, right?
He'll forget about this, soon enough.
To think...
To think that Ayaka, she's...
What am I thinking about here?
What am I thinking about, and why do I feel like this?
I'm sorry.
Hiroshi-kun.
I...
You must hate me after hearing all that, don't you?
Why...
Why did you have to be three years older than me?
If only you'd joined the circle earlier.
I wouldn't have done it with anyone else.
Ayaka.
It's all right. Don't get so down on yourself.
Hiroshi-kun.
I was a little shocked at first, but it's honestly fine.
I've know for a while that you've liked sex
plus it had me kind of aroused...
Oh Hiroshi-kun!
Guess that makes you a pervert!
Guess so.
Wait, Ayaka!
You said you were aroused, didn't you?
I though I'd just see for myself.
Wow, you're right.
You really have gotten hard.
That's.
You got this hard listening to how I did
it with Fujiwara-kun and those guys?
Did you?
You're such a perverted husband.
S-Sorry, Ayaka.
Ayaka!
I'm gonna cum!
But I can't cum in a place like this!
Hiroshi-kun, sorry for being such a lewd wife.
You prefer shy, modest women, don't you?
I think you...
I like you as you are... beautiful, cute, and extremely sexy.
I'm... really happy to hear that.
At this rate, you're going to make me cum!
Don't cum yet. If you do I'm withholding sex for a week.
That's harsh!
Well... Well I
I want to feel good right now, too.
Ayaka.
Please, Hiroshi-kun, put it in me.
Right here, I want you to
really fuck me hard!
Hi there!
So sorry to interrupt you two.
That was a true masterpiece.
"Fuck me hard!" and all.
You two are newlyweds and all, but fucking in the lobby's a no-go.
Please, let us off the hook already.
Come on Ayaka, you ask them too.
I can't. It's too embarrassing!
Come on, Ayaka.
Don't be so embarrassed.
After all, we've all had sex with you before.
There's no point in covering yourself.
But honestly, I'm jealous, Endou.
After that, I want a cute and sexy wife like Ayaka too!
You said it!
Guys who stay single are really idiots.
Because Endou, you get to take
this perfectly-ripened
sexy, plump, lewd body
every day, whenever and however you want
to your heart's content.
Now I wanna fuck. I really wanna have sex with a woman!
If that's how you feel.
Shall I
lend you Ayaka tonight?
Just kidding! It's a joke, just a joke.
That would be awful to say seriously.
You had me there, Hiroshi-kun.
Cut it out with the dark humor!
Damn, that was a joke? Talk about killing the mood...
Damn it, Endou.
But
if by chance.
Ayaka says she's ok with it...
I wouldn't mind.
Geez, let's stop talking about these kinds of things.
Oh, that's right.
I'll fetch us some more beer.
I could use a little more to drink.
Oh, me too please.
Just buy us 10 or so while you're at it, would ya?
Can't say I didn't see that coming.
Ayaka
help me with this beer run, would you?
I gotta say
they're sure taking their time with that beer.
Come to think of it, they kind of are.
Oh, Ayaka.
This beer sure is heavy!
Carrying everyone's beer like this was really tough!
You guys too, drink up!
Oh, that's right.
I've got to buy my mom a gift.
But she never really likes the gifts that I pick for her.
Say, Ayaka, help me pick out a gift for my mom, would you?
I'm clueless with gifts, so I know she'd prefer one that you pick.
When you're 30+ and living with your
parents, you really worry about these things.
A "gift"...
There aren't any stores open at this hour, are there?
Come to think of it.
Do you guys play Bakémon Go?
My phone's too old for that.
Endou?
Um, well
I did install the app, but...
Well that's boring.
Bad luck, there weren't any stores open.
What did you expect?
Even then, Sakazaki.
You sure took your time.
We were looking for a convenience store or something close by.
We didn't find one though.
Alright, I'm going to go catch some Bakémon.
Ayaka, you used to play Bakémon, right?
Let's look for some rare Bakémon together.
"Gotcha! Bakémon was caught!" and all.
Ogata's too old for this.
What does he even like about Bakémon?
I hear that if you play, you get really into it though.
First you use some "magic" or a special
technique until they go soft in the knees.
Then you come come in hard from behind, to your heart's content!
Bakémon eh...
Hearing about it kind of makes me want to try.
I'll have Ogata teach me about it.
Sorry, but your old phone just won't cut it.
Guess I can't play then.
Where'd those two go?
They'd better show us some rare Bakémon when they get back.
Sorry for the wait.
We caught a pretty rare Bakémon!
It was hiding in some hole though, so it took some effort to get to.
Oh that's right. I reserved the open-air bath.
That sounds great!
Wow, this one's pretty nice.
Feels good!
Alright, let's jump right in.
Oh, I forgot to say this but.
Usually when you reserve a bath like this, it's mixed bathing.
Haha, is it OK for you to be bathing with your newly-wed wife?
Ayaka.
Come on in, Ayaka!
Come on, Ayaka.
We're going to give your pervert husband a show.
Endou, your new wife's body is the absolute best.
Sorry Endou, but we're going to play with
this body to our heart's content tonight.
Three months into marriage, and you're
committing adultery right in front of your husband?
You always were really lewd.
Endou-kun, sorry about this.
Once you get a taste of this body, you can't just be a gentleman!
And here's a question for Ayaka-san!
Just how many dicks have you sucked today?
I-I don't want to say.
Tell us!
Our dicks and your husband are all ears.
I-I can't.
Come on, how many?
Hiroshi-kun's and yours. I sucked four.
Four dicks in one day? Just how much fun were you having?!
Bu-But Hiroshi-kun said it was OK.
Well in the end, we've created a super-perverted, affair-loving wife.
Come on, take it deeper.
Show your true colors and suck it like you did before.
Me too. Take me in deep like before.
Yeah that's it.
Sorry Endou, this can't be helped.
We're making her feel so good right now
if she starts ignoring your affection, I won't feel guilty at all.
Hey, hey. Tired already?
The fun part's just starting.
You're thoroughly warmed up down here.
Come on, tell Endou just what was in here a little while ago.
A cock. I had a cock in me.
Fujiwara-kun, Sakazaki-kun, and Ogata-kun
I did it a lot with those three.
And they filled me over and over!
Ayaka, your husband's watching.
Do you think it's OK to be used like this by other guys?
It's not! It's not OK.
It's definitely wrong to have other people inside me.
You do understand, after all!
And still you're doing it!
Here she comes!
Cum more than last time.
You perverted, loose woman.
Let's have Endou see who you really are.
You're fingering me too intensely!
Look what's leaking out, Ayaka.
The white stuff we spewed inside you.
Make sure you tell Endou that
before, when he wasn't looking, every one of us here came inside you.
Hiroshi-kun, sorry!
Fujiwara-kun, Sakazaki-kun, and Ogata-kun came inside me!
I took their cum inside me!
I'm being played with by everyone!
Sorry, Hiroshi-kun!
These guys' cocks are making me feel so good!
I can't get enough of you, Ayaka.
This makes me really want to drive it home.
Alright, Ayaka. Finally, let's have Endou watch some vanilla sex.
Don't blink, Endou
because we're about to use your Ayaka as a sex slave!
Ayaka!
Look Ayaka, Endou's watching.
He's watching us violate you, and he's getting aroused!
I'm done for. I can't think straight!
We're not done yet! There's still more to come!
This brings back memories!
Back when you joined the circle, I took advantage of your innocence.
In the first week after you joined our circle, you were
dating the overbearing leader-figure, Fujiwara.
That's right, we were drunk and had unprotected sex.
I was really surprised then to hear you were a virgin.
But it only took a week for you to completely
change into the kind of super pervy woman I like.
After you'd been thoroughly played with by Fujiwara, you got tired of him
and started playing with lots of other guys?
You'd draw in guys left and right.
You got in trouble with guys every week.
You'd sneak out and have guys hit on you and play with you
and the next morning you'd call me, crying.
So I'd come and pick you up at 07:00 in the
morning. I'm really generous, aren't I?
I... I understand. I can't take this!
Just cum. Let's show Endou how you look when you're cumming.
Back in college I used to "comfort" you like this.
Hiroshi-kun.
I... I...
Ayaka.
Next up is the "touchback" you love, Ayaka.
With this forceful position, Ayaka's gonna cum in an instant!
Ayaka's pussy really is the best.
She's experienced, so her pussy really grips you nicely when you put it in.
Don't you have anything to say to your husband, Endou?
Hirosh... Hiroshi-kun.
Say what we talked about before. You're what to us?
I'm Fujiwara-kun's, Sakazaki-kun's, and Ogata-kun's sex slave.
Hiroshi-kun, everyone's played with my
body, and I've been made into a sex slave.
I love you most, Hiroshi-kun, and do I want to be a good wife for you.
But before that.
Ayaka.
Can I still be these three's sex slave?
Can I still do erotic play with other guys?
Please, Hiroshi-kun!
Ayaka, I...
I love you, Ayaka.
I love you like you are now, just the way you are!
Hiroshi-kun.
Even if you're a slut and a bitch
and even if you're a shitty woman who has tons of affairs.
Ayaka, you're the woman who arouses me the most!
Hiroshi-kun.
I'm cumming!
We're taking the car back. Are you sure you don't need a ride?
It's fine. Ayaka and I are taking the train back.
Ok then, let's travel together some other time. I'll send you an invite!
Man, this onsen was quite the trip.
Hiroshi-kun.
You hate me now, don't you?
Not at all, Ayaka.
I've fallen in love with you even more.
You're going to keep getting me excited, won't you?
You're a pervert after all, Hiroshi-kun.
You too, Ayaka.
Translator: hanime.tv
Timer: hanime.tv
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч