Yes! Just like that!
Keep going! Deeper!
I'm cumming!
Cum!
Ejaculate in me!
I'm... cumming!
What is this... this feeling...
Ever since I drank that tea, my body's been...
I really want to fuck a woman.
Akito-san, please take care of my daughter too.
Papa...
Please make me a woman.
Make love to me just like you did to mother.
Alright, here I go.
It's coming inside!
I'm moving on my own down there!
It's trying to welcome your dick, Papa!
It means that you've begun to accept Akito-san.
Your heart and body will begin to change.
It's wrapping around me so tightly!
It's sucking me in!
This is too fast! This is too much!
There's a lot of warm stuff coming out!
I'm being rammed inside while Papa's
peeing his semen inside me!
Please don't hold back.
Make my daughter remember the taste of
your semen by filling her womb with it.
I'm gonna...
With Papa's dick and Mom watching me, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna have the happiest climax in the world!
I'm cumming!
I love you.
I'll give you my everything.
With this, we move one step forward.
I feel bad for doing this to you, but...
I'll be using you as I wish.
#2 The Feelings of Those Two
No, stop. We can't.
I won't forgive you.
Just accept it already.
My body isn't your plaything.
So get out already.
Get out!
I already know all of your weak spots.
Stop playing tough and try begging
for it like you did earlier!
No!
Stop!
My husband's conning back soon, so...
At this rate, you'll never be satisfied for the rest of your life.
Shit, guess I have no choice.
No. If this goes on...
I can't...
It feels so good that I'm gonna lose my mind!
He's spreading my womb!
Don't! Don't accept Takeo-kun! Don't!
I think it wants my baby.
So, does it?!
Tell me you want my child!
Accept me... Accept all of me!
Stop this...
I'm gonna cum!
Alright, here I go!
I'm gonna cum inside you!
Dear... Akito-kun!
Don't!
Why'd you stop me?
Shit.
Dear, you're so big.
Yeah, it's because I'm finally going to
have sex with you after all this time.
It feels like you're going to burn a hole through my hand.
It's so hot and tense.
I can't believe you're this wet just from stroking my dick.
It's because of what I just did with Takeo-kun, I think.
I was able to get away with this somehow,
but how am I supposed to explain that?
You feel the same way I do, don't you?
Dear...
I'm gonna return the favor.
What's going on?
She's like a completely different person.
I don't remember her ever being
this vigorous in sucking my dick.
Please fill my stomach with your cum.
Yeah, I'll do just that.
Dear, I can barely focus when you do that!
You're getting so hard!
I mustn't forget.
This man is my husband and the man
I should be having children with.
You want me, don't you?
Yes, I want you!
I want you.
I want you in me so bad.
Sorry, I know I'm pathetic, but I'm gonna cum!
That's fine.
Just cum
Akito-kun...
Miyuri!
You've been holding this much back all this time?
You've gotten pretty good since the last time we did it...
What are you trying to say?
I-It's just a joke.
But anyway,
let's continue, Miyuri.
Dear, it's already pretty late...
I need to think of my husband... Only of Kazuto-san.
No! Akito!
Don't die! Akito!
Sayoko-san!
I'm fine!
I just sprained my wrist.
I think it was a bad idea to have called
her over to help care for him.
Right, you fell down during a test of courage.
When I heard about that from Miyuri-san,
I almost had a heart attack!
Akito-kun! Akito-kun!
Grab onto me!
It's really not a big deal.
It's not something that needs to be nursed.
But you're still somewhat handicapped
right now, aren't you?
I came all this way. I'd like to help you at least a little.
So please don't worry and go to work.
Then... I leave him in your care.
Thanks for today.
It wasn't a huge injury or anything, but...
I think Miyuri-san just blew it out of proportion.
That sounds just like her.
Your injury's something you got while
trying to protect someone, isn't it?
How'd you know that?
I can tell.
I know everything about you.
And I know her true feelings as well...
How about we take a bath together like old times?
Does it hurt at all?
Do any of your wounds hurt?
They tickle, but... they're fine.
Oh man, Sayoko-sans skin feels so heavenly.
And so kind...
You probably can't wash yourself very
well with your hand like that, so...
I'll wash you here too, okay?
Sayoko-san?
It's getting so big! It feels like it's gonna explode.
If you get too aroused, you're gonna get a head rush.
You're so much bigger than when I used to do this for you.
Akito... you've really become a man.
Oh no, I can't believe I'm already this
wet just from playing with his dick.
I want to see you cum, Akito.
Shoot everything out.
Sayoko-san, I... I can't...
Cum! As hard as you can!
Akito! Akito!
Sorry.
I came all over you.
You came so much from me.
Hey, Akito? Come here, okay?
Akito, your dick is so perverted.
It's rubbing against all my weak spots!
Hey, how about we go to my room?
If I keep getting teased like this, I feel like I might go crazy.
Akito-kun?!
I knew it. He's not here.
It can't be... Sayoko-san?
I’m not gonna let you have your way with him!
So good!
I can tell the shape of your dick so clearly!
It's digging inside me so much!
I like your dick so much!
I love it!
Both my womb and I have been waiting for you for so long!
We both want to be loved by you!
Me too! I...
I want to... become one with you, Sayoko-san!
It's fine. Cum inside me.
Make me your woman!
I'm cumming!
Miyuri-san, you were able to experience
happy moments like these, weren't you?
I really am so... jealous.
Sorry to have made you stay with me so late.
I honestly can't believe we kept going until this late.
Miyuri-san?
I'm not going to let Akito-kun come here anymore.
You aren't suitable for him.
Are you trying to say that you are then?
He's not your toy!
Don't hurt him more than you already have!
My toy? He's not...
I don't think of him that way, I...
More than your husband?
I've already prepared my body and mind to bear his child.
What about you, Miyuri? Who's child do you want?
Akito's or your husband's?
I... The baby I want to have is...
Takoyaki
Cotton Candy
Yakitori
Miyuri-san is my brother's wife.
But she's also my first love.
What should I do?
I knew you'd be here.
Miyuri-san?
This is the first place Kazuto-san and I kissed.
I decided to give my answer here and now.
I want to restart our relationship from square one.
Is she trying to open up her true feelings to me?
I want you to only look at me.
Even if that ends up hurting a lot of people...
I can't change the fact that I fell in love with you.
I love you. I really do.
I won't run away anymore, so...
Please make love to me.
In the place where my husband first loved me.
I... I...
Sayoko-san...
No! I can't decide between the two
of them when I love them both!
You don't have to give me an answer right now.
I'm scared to hear your answer.
I'll just show you how much I love you from here on out
Akito-kun, your dick is filling me up!
Right when you put your dick inside me, I got so horny!
I want your dick so badly, my hips won't stop moving!
If you keep moving like that, I'm gonna cum!
Don't! Hold it in longer.
I want to be connected with you even for a second longer!
So hold it in!
No, I'm gonna... I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!!
My womb's getting closer to your dick!
It's kissing your dick right now!
If you keep knocking so hard on my womb like
that you're gonna make me cum again!
I can't hold it in!
Your cum's overflowing!
I'm gonna get pregnant from all this cum while
you keep ramming your dick inside me!
I've always loved you, Miyuri-san!
Don't say that or I'm gonna cum!
I'm really gonna cum!
Please give me your child, Akito-kun.
I want to give birth to our symbol of love!
I can't... hold on any longer!
Cum! Cum!!
Cum in the deepest part of me!
I'll give you my precious egg!
I'm cumming! I'm gonna plant my seed in you, Miyuri-san!
I'm cumming!
You're still not done cumming!
All this cum is gonna get me pregnant with your baby.
Now that Akito-kun's painted me in his colors,
I feel like my very being has been completely reborn.
I've changed from the person I wanted to be...
To the person I really am.
You really got this wet just from pouring
drinks for your customers?
N-No.
This is because I couldn't stop thinking about you...
Is that the truth?
I have to make sure that your eyes
don't wander to different guys.
That'd never...
I've only had eyes for you from the start.
I've only been able to think about your dick.
Please make me pregnant whenever you want.
I'll bear your child.
Sayoko-san...
Don't think about anything. Cum inside.
Please, I beg you.
Here I cum, Sayoko-san.
I know this feeling.
I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Don't make me jealous.
As long as you keep loving me like
this, I think I can promise that.
Restrooms
Sayoko-san...
Just as I thought, I really can't choose
between the two of them.
Akito-kun...
Does this feel good?
It feels amazing!
I feel like I'm gonna melt!
You're this big already?
What a bad boy.
Anyone'd get like this the way you're handling it!
Whether it's my hands or mouth, whatever you
desire, I'll comply, even if it's my pussy or ass.
So just...
savor me as much as you want, okay?
Akito-kun!
You're so hard!
Your dick's so amazing, I can't hold back my moans!
Everyone's gonna hear me!
Well you do love my dick, don't you?
You keep hitting me in my weak spots!
Stop... that feels too good!
No, I want you to feel even more pleasure.
You like it when I do this, right?
You like it when my pussy gets this wet, don’t you?
That's...
You're so cute!
Come on, let it out already.
Squirt your baby milk.
You...
Don't think I'm still the same little boy living
in the shadow of his older brother!
Akito-kun, this isn't fair!
You're shoving against my pussy so hard... It feels too good!
This man is my soul mate.
His existence fills my heart and my body.
I want his baby.
I want him to impregnate me!
I'm gonna... cum!
Cum! Fill my womb up with your cum!
I love both of them equally.
I'm back.
Welcome back, Dear.
Sorry I'm so late.
It's fine.
You're cold, aren't you?
Let me warm you up.
Sounds good. But be gentle, okay?
Miyuri!
Akito-kun, I love you!
I love you!
You're just licking and sucking me on the outside,
but I'm getting so horny deep inside!
Next up, is this.
That's... I'm weak there.
I'm weakest there!
Don't forget about me though, okay?
I'm quite aroused myself.
Yeah, of course not.
Akito-kun!
I'm so glad that I'm yours!
Please love me harder!
Please love the both of us!
Yeah, I'll pump you both full of cum.
I'm going to cum too!
Me too! I'm going to cum!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: oblivionshasow
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч