Can't believe our idol Ayaka got swept away by Endo.
My wife has become the cum dumpster for our club's friends at the hot spring
Damn it.
How dare you find happiness before us.
But seriously Endo, congratulations.
No, I should be thanking you guys!
Endo, show us some damn proof that you love Ayaka.
– Kiss! Kiss!
– Ayaka?
– Hiroshi-kun.
– Kiss! Kiss!
Look at 'em go.
Ayaka's lips are so hot.
So how many times a day are you two having sex?
I-I can't tell you guys that.
But man, coincidences really do happen. Can't believe
we all just happened to be in the same hot spring.
That's what people usually call a miracle!
So damn jealous.
Congrats, Endo. Make sure you make Ayaka happy.
Yeah! I'm kinda low on confidence though.
Congrats to you too, Ayaka.
Endo's a good guy. I don't think you chose the wrong guy.
Oogata-kun...
Yeah, you can't go wrong with Endo.
As Ayaka's first time, I couldn't be more proud.
Y-You idiot, what are you blurting out, Fujiwara?!
Huh? Did I say something weird?
I'm just speaking as the guy who took Ayaka's virginity...
That's exactly what I'm telling you not to say!
Sorry Ayaka.
W-Well we're talking like tens of years ago, right?
You don't have to walk on eggshells around us, Oogata-san.
You're so cool, Endo.
That's the Endo I know. This is
why you're a man among men.
See, Oogata? I keep telling you that
you're too much of a worrywart.
Anyway, you did it a lot with Ayaka too, didn't you?
I know you did!
Whenever Ayaka broke up with a guy,
you'd be there to give her "advice".
You two go to a hotel and then have a counseling session.
Y-You idiot. What the hell are you saying, Fujiwara?!
It's the truth, isn't it?
Just say the truth.
Didn't you brag a lot that your two bodies were so
compatible that you could just do it over and over again?
No! I never said that!
Why the hell would I ever have said that?!
– Fujiwara, you bastard!
– Ayaka...
But that doesn't really matter at all.
After all, yesterday we did it three times.
H-Hey, Hiroshi-kun! What are you saying?!
You got it in you, Endo. I'm so jealous
of you two newlyweds.
Hearing that makes me relieved.
Well, you know, thinking back now
on those times I get really hard.
You remember that night that I got dumped by my
girlfriend and you asked me if I wanted you to cheer me up?
To be honest, that time was probably
the best sex I've ever had.
But it's a good thing you found yourself
a guy who has this accepting of you.
If it was me, I'd probably have second thoughts
after hearing about your past.
Huh? What's the matter, Endo?
I-I'm gonna get some air.
What's his problem?
I thought he'd have come to terms with it already.
You idiot, that was him putting on airs.
You ruined the damn atmosphere, Fujiwara, Sakazaki!
Man, this is just the alcohol talking.
He'll forget in no time.
Ayaka... you can't have... Ayaka...
What's the matter? Hey hey. What
the hell am I thinking right now?!
I'm sorry, Hiroshi-kun.
I, um...
You probably hate me now, don't you?
B-But why...
But why did you have to be three years younger than me?!
If you joined the club any earlier, I would've...
I would never have had sex with any other guy!
Ayaka, it's fine. Don't get so down on yourself.
Hiroshi-kun...
I was a little shocked, sure, but I'm seriously okay.
Well, also... thinking about how hot you were
back then kinda turned me on a little.
Jeez, Hiroshi-kun. That makes you a pervert, you know?
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
Hey, Ayaka?!
You said you were turned on, didn't you?
So I thought I should see if you were telling the truth.
You were.
You really are stiff right now.
Th-That's...
Did you really get this big from hearing
about how I had sex with those guys?
Is that it?
I really have such a perverted husband.
S-Sorry, Ayaka.
Ayaka!
W-We can't. Not here!
We can't!
I'm sorry Hiroshi-kun. You don't want
a wife this perverted, do you?
You like girls who are more shy and modest girls, don't you?
Th-That's not true.
I love you, Ayaka.
I love how you're so beautiful and cute.
And I love how dirty you are Ayaka!
You mean it?
That makes me so happy.
Ayaka, you're gonna make me cum!
No, not yet. If you cum now, no sex for a week.
Th-That's not fair!
Well I want to feel good right now too!
Ayaka!
Please, Hiroshi-kun. Take your really hard
stiff dick and make me feel good.
Put it here. Right here.
– It's going so deep inside me!
– Ayaka!
Hey there.
Sorry to bother you when you're
in the middle of something.
That was beautiful.
You two were just fucking it out.
Seriously, you might be newlyweds, but
doing it out there is totally wrong.
Please just give it a rest.
Come on Ayaka, you ask too.
I can't go on. This is too embarrassing!
Come on, Ayaka. Don't be so embarrassed.
We're all connected by sex here, right?
No point hiding anything anymore.
But man, I'm jealous, Endo.
I really want a cute an dirty wife of my own now.
Yeah, seriously.
Single guys are real idiots.
Because guys like you Endo can just do whatever you want to
that amazing sexy, curvy, luscious body of your wife every day.
I'm so jealous. God damn I wanna fuck a girl right now.
Then how about tonight, I lend her out to you guys.
Hi-Hiroshi-kun?
Just kidding. Just joking, guys.
Don't take me seriously.
Jeez, Hiroshi-kun, cut back on those heavy jokes.
Oh what, that was a joke?
That really puts a damper on the mood.
Endo, you bastard.
But if Ayaka says she doesn't mind, then neither do I.
Geez, let's stop ruining the mood any further.
I'm gonna get some more beer.
I could use some more.
Sorry, could you get me some more too?
And get ten more on top of that.
Fine, whatever.
Ayaka, sorry but could you help me carry the beer?
How long odes it take to get some beer?
Yeah, they're kinda late.
Oh, Ayaka...
Damn, beer's heavy.
Buying everyone's beer was rough.
Hey you guys should drink up too.
Oh, right, I need to buy a souvenir for my mom.
But whenever I buy her a gift, she's never satisfied with it.
Hey, Ayaka, sorry but you could help
me choose a present for my mom?
You'd probably know what my mom
would like more than a guy would.
Man getting over thirty really makes you care more.
Really? A souvenir?
Hell, there ain't gonna be any shops open right now.
Hey, by the way, do any of you play Bakemon Go?
I got a flip phone. What about you, Endo?
I have it installed, but...
That's boring.
Damn, that sucked. Nobody was open.
Yeah, of course not.
Didn't it take you a little too long
to figure that out, Sakazaki?
Tried looking for some nearby convenience stores.
But couldn't find any in the end.
Okay then, I'm gonna try and get some Bakemon.
Ayaka, you play too, right?
Let's go look for some rare Bakemon together.
Gotta catch 'em all!
Oogata's pretty old. What's fun about
playing that game at his age?
It's a game that you get hooked on easier than you think.
First, you use magic or abilities to weaken
them until they're weak on their knees.
And then after that you just fuck 'em from
behind. And then it's just fun time forever.
You're talking about Bakemon, right?
When you put it that way, I wanna play it now too.
I'll have Oogata bring me up to speed later.
Sorry to break it to you, but you
can't play it on a flip phone.
Oh, so I can't play it then?
Where'd those two go off to?
I wanna see the rare Bakemon that they caught.
Sorry for the wait.
We got a pretty good, rare Bakemon.
But it was hiding in a hole, so it took some effort to get.
Oh, right. Did you know that they
rent out open-air baths here?
I like the sound of that!
Hey, we're all here. Let's go!
Oh, this is pretty nice.
I bet it feels great too.
Then let's get in already!
Oh I forgot to say this, but the rental open
air baths are mixed bathing only.
Oh man, is it really okay for us to share
a bath with a newlywed wife?
A-Ayaka...
Come on, Ayaka. Get in already.
Come on Ayaka, show your perverted husband everything.
Endo, your new wife's body is really the best!
Sorry Endo, but we're gonna have
fun with this body all night.
Ayaka...
You're in trouble. Three months into your marriage and
you're already cheating in front of your husband?
Ayaka's been a little slut since the beginning after all.
Sorry Endo. Seeing this body makes
me lose all self-restraint.
Alright Ayaka, a question for you.
How many dicks have you sucked today?
N-No. I can't...
Come on, answer him.
Your husband's just dying to hear the answer.
I-I can't.
Come on. How many did you suck?
With Hiroshi-kun's and all yours, four total.
Four in one day? Damn you get around.
B-But, Hiroshi, he said I could do it.
Well I guess as a result, we've witnessed
the birth of a slutty, cheating wife.
Come on, take it deeper.
Suck it like a dirty whore, like you did earlier!
Me too! Take it in until it hits your throat!
Yeah, this is the good stuff.
Sorry, Endo.
After feeling this good, I can't even feel guilty or
even care about how you're feeling right now.
Hey, hey, tired already?
The night's only just beginning.
You're already done warming up down here, aren't you?
Come on, see?
Come on, tell Endo what was just in here.
Dick...
I had a dick put inside me.
I had Fujiwara-kun's, Sakazaki-kun's,
and Oogata-kun's dick inside me.
The three of them... the three of them did a lot inside me.
Ayaka, you really think it's okay to let other guys
use this even though you have a husband?
No. It's not okay. It's really not okay.
Having other dick's inside me is really not okay.
So you do understand that.
So that means it was a conscious decision!
Look at you go! You're letting even more out than before.
You dirty woman. Make sure you let Endo see all of this too.
No... Stop!
You're being too intense!
Ayaka, it keeps on coming.
The white stuff we shot into you earlier is still coming out.
Make sure you tell Endo.
Tell him that you let everyone here cum
inside you somewhere he couldn't see.
Hi-Hiroshi-kun, I'm sorry.
Fujiwara-kun, Sakazaki-kun, and
Oogata-kun all came inside me.
I let cum that wasn't yours inside me.
I let everyone play with me!
Hiroshi-kun, I'm sorry!
I'm letting myself feel good with dicks
that aren't yours, Hiroshi-kun!
This is too good.
You make me want to fuck you up even harder than before.
Alright Ayaka, let's show Endo how we do it raw.
Endo, don't blink, okay?
We're gonna make your Ayaka, our cum dumpster.
Ayaka!
Come on, do it faster. Endo's watching.
Get him excited from watching you get fucked!
Oh no. I can't even think about anything anymore!
Come on, we're not done playing yet!
Hey, this brings back memories.
You came into the club a pure, innocent girl, but
we made you into something much dirtier.
Oh right, just one week into her being in the club,
she was already with the president and you.
Yeah, exactly.
After doing it four times, I was pretty surprised to
find out how much of a slut you were back then.
Well I guess a week later, you were changed
to become a complete whore.
Yeah, then you got bored of her and she started
playing with a lot of other guys, right?
Yeah she just kept going around and there was
trouble every week with a different guy.
At night she'd just go around flirting
and playing with guys all the time.
And then the next morning, she'd call me up in tears.
And then I'd take the first train to go and see her.
I'm such a nice guy.
Oogata-kun. This... this isn't good!
Cum! Show Endo what you look like when you cum!
I "comforted" you all the time in college just like this!
Hiroshi-kun! I... I...
Ayaka...
And now it's time for your favorite position-doggy style.
I did you so many times in this position.
And you would always cum so fast.
Your pussy really is the best, Ayaka.
It's already used to my dick, so it fits me perfectly.
It wraps around me almost instantly!
Come on, don't you have something
to say to your husband, Endo?
Hiro... Hiroshi-kun...
Come on, tell him what you told me earlier!
What are you again?
I'm Fujiwara-kun's, Sakzaki-kun's, and
Oogata-kun's cum... cum dumpster!
Hiroshi-kun, I... I've been played with by them so much.
And now I'm their cum dumpster!
S-So, I love you more than anyone in the world
and I want to become a good wife, but...
But before that,
Ayaka...
Can I continue being their cum dumpster?
Will you let me have sex with other
guys every now and then?
Please, Hiroshi-kun.
Ayaka... I...
Ayaka... I still love you!
Hiroshi-kun!
Even if you're a total slut or a goddamn bitch...
Even if you're a hopeless piece of
human garbage woman, Ayaka...
The only one who can turn me on
this much is just you, Ayaka!
Hiroshi-kun!
I'm cumming!!
We're gonna drive back now. You sure you
don't want us to drop you guys off?
Yeah, we're good.
We're gonna take the train back.
Got it. Well, let's get together and
have another trip sometime.
I'll be sure to invite you two.
Oh geez, this hot springs trip was a mess.
Hiroshi-kun...
Hm?
You definitely hate me now, don't you?
Don't be stupid, Ayaka.
I think I love you even more now, Ayaka.
You're gonna keep me excited from now on, right?
Hiroshi-kun...
You really are a pervert, Hiroshi-kun.
That goes double for you too, Ayaka.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч