Tarou-san, did something good happen?
Huh? Why do you ask?
Your face seems to imply so.
Like something fun, no...
Like you're on to some mischief.
Oh... Was I making such a face?
It's like you want to do something bad.
Try not to go overboard, alright.
We've been married for four years now.
We get along so well that we even take baths together.
We have sex about once a week.
My husband helps with household
chores on his precious days off.
The lifestyle I am having now is fulfilling.
I should be satisfied.
That is until I met that man named Kuroda.
Alright, then. Enjoy yourself.
Okay.
I'm about to go meet my former
classmates from our hometown.
That's the lie I went with.
If I'll say "I'm about to cheat on you",
I wonder what kind of face Tarou-san will make.
Tsuma ga Kirei ni Natta Wake
The Reason Why My Wife Got Prettier
Volume 2
I'm going to meet with her.
Kuroda
We met at the entrance.
Is this for real?
Are we really doing this?
Then, should we check how those thing are first?
O-Okay, I understand...
It's been vibrating inside me the whole time.
My legs are losing their strength...
Hiro-kun, I'm begging you!
I met my ex-boyfriend again about
ten years after in a class reunion.
He was my first man.
He's a man who knew my body well.
That I am a sleazy, indecent,
and sex-loving woman...
That I am wearing a good wife
mask in front of my husband...
And that I love cocks the most...
I want... I want a cock!
Sit down here, Misako.
I'll stand out if I'll sit on this thing!
The rocking horse is shaking
back and forth... Oh no!
Aren't you feeling good despite what you said?
Okay, then...
I want your cock, Hiro-kun!
I want it!
I want this... So thick... More!
Then swallow it deeper!
Cock...
Cock... Cock!
Do you want to suck me dry of semen that much?
It tastes fishy!
Only a woman like you
keeps on sucking hard despite
saying that it stinks, Misako!
That surely is a mouth-pussy!
Alright, next will be...
You sure are loving this...
I'm going to meet with her.
Kuroda
We met at the entrance.
Make her masturbate next.
This is... This is way too perverted!
Alright...
Hey, perverted woman!
Someone might actually end up seeing you like that!
This is embarrassing! My pussy...
Even my pussy is exposed!
No... No!
Hiro-kun, your cock...
It's way thicker than that toy!
Isn't that obvious? Stop comparing mine to that!
Come on, say where you are
and what is being done to you!
Say it!
We are in the park!
This is a park where children and families go
during the day!
In such a place, I'm...
I'm having my pussy penetrated
with pleasure by a cock!
Even though I have a husband,
I'm having my ex-boyfriend's cock
that's bigger and thicker than his!
Forgive me! His is more manly!
It's going in my pussy as he spanks me!
Tarou-san... I'm sorry!
What goes inside women's head is scary!
This feels good! Adulterous sex feels good!
That's right!
I'm gonna come already...
Coming... Coming... Do it inside!
Alright, then...
I'm coming!
I'm coming, Misako!
Come! Come, come!
Tsukamoto
Rintarou
Misako
This is the perfume that Tarou-san likes.
I'm home!
Sorry, that took me long.
Welcome home.
Oh... You made supper?
They're only simple dishes, though.
My wife returned.
Unaware of me watching in secret,
my wife wears the same mask as usual.
When I looked at her,
I kept pushing this issue a day after another.
I felt that the time when it'll end
for both of us draws near.
I'll be late from work, but look
forward to my surprise.
It's a fact that Misako and I
already went to a point of no return.
And now...
On our marriage anniversary,
my home will meet its end.
Will I go through with breaking up,
or will I stand my ground as I have been doing before?
Which one is the right choice for me?
Or was it already too late to choose either of the two?
In a married couple's sacred chamber,
that adulterous pussy
will be sullied by a philanderer!
C-Cut that out!
So, even a perverted degenerate of a woman like you
still have some qualms about this.
And on top of that, isn't today your anniversary?
You're such a bad wife! Seriously...
Th-That's because...
That's because...
And now, I finally
desecrated our matrimony chamber with my infidelity.
Will I be able to go back again today
to the facade of a devoted wife for Tarou-san?
All while having a mere body
in heat and craving for a cock...
I-I can't see anything.
I'm scared! This is scary!
What are you gonna do to me?
Wh-What's this? What are you gonna do?
No, this is embarrassing...
No... No...
Does this... Does this smell belong to Misako?
Despite spending all those nights with her, I never knew
about this strong womanly stench!
Want me to fuck you, Misako?
Yeah, I want to... I want you to fuck me!
This feels amazing!
N-Not yet!
If I'll come right now...
That is such a lovely face you're making, Misako!
That cock-loving womanly face of yours... Misako!
Why won't you show me that
when doing it with me?
Misako... I'll spray it all over your face
today so stick your tongue out!
Hey, I'm coming! Here's a shower
of semen that you love!
It feels so hot! What an amazing amount!
I love semen!
This is... This is...
Gratifying!
I sprayed my semen on my wife's face for the face time!
Oh, shit! I want to shoot more!
I want to shoot it on her face!
I wanna smear her face and let it harden
until nobody else can recognize her!
This is the end.
This is over! Let's end it now!
I want it...
More, I want more!
I'm begging you...
Give me more of that thick and incredible stuff!
Hmm?
Huh?
Huh?!
Can you see...
...this face of mine?
D-Darling?!
T-Tarou-san has been making such a face...
At the moment when we saw each other's face...
This mask... This mask of mine as a wife...
I felt it breaking in pieces.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization