Part                        1
Oh my, what’s wrong?
I was so pleased to see you finally and now you’re just sighing all the time!
I’m a working member of society.
Of course I'm burdened all the time.
Just leave me alone.
Awww, you’re no fun.
And I thought we were such good friends.
And also... I was your first, wasn’t I?
Well? Wanna taste my body? It’s been a while.
Naturally, I’ll keep it a secret from your w-i-f-e.
Please stop it. I would never cheat.
Ohhhh, is that so?
You’re no fun.
I’m MARRIED! Of course I wouldn’t cheat.
But she left you, didn’t she?
... How did you know that?
Geeeee, I wonder.
Shall I have a drink with you?
What about your business?
I’m closing up shop for the night.
I need to be there for my cute little friend to hear his problems.
Now, you don’t need to...
Let me help.
Hey, Oba-san...
My supervisor yelled at me at work.
And Akane won’t come home.
And I... I guess I’m just a loser.
You shouldn’t say that.
You’re just going through a little slump.
It’s been five months since your wife left, right?
Yes...
Just forget about your wife... Forget about Akane and find a new woman!
Isn’t it for the best?
But I couldn’t!
I loved Akane so much... I could never forget her.
I could never!
Akihiko, don’t stare at me like that.
It’s embarrassing.
Don’t say that!
You’re pretty, Akane.
Really?
I’m so happy.
Your pussy is so pink.
Aw, don’t spread my legs.
You’re soaking wet.
Not so rough...
Go slower.
Be gentle!
Did that hurt?
No... It didn’t hurt, but...
Just be more... Be more gentle... I want you to lick me gently.
Awesome! Wow!
Yes, right there! Feels great!
Right there!
Suck harder!
This feels great!
Yes, right there!
Right there... Put your tongue in deeper.
What’s wrong?
Sorry.
I can’t...
You’re already hard.
It’s okay. Put it in.
Please? Akihiko, put your dick in.
Akihiko!
Your dick... So nice.
It feels great!
Yes!
All the way... It’s hitting my uterus.
I’m cumming. I’m cumming...
Oh, it feels so great!
Oh no. I’m cumming, cumming!
Your dick is making me cum!
Akihiko... I love you.
Akane...
Aki-kun. You’re hard.
Sorry.
It’s okay.
You’re still young.
But I’m surprised your marriage even lasted two years.
You were both nineteen when you got married.
You probably got caught up in the moment, had sex, and got married right after. Right?
Well... Good thing you had no kids.
You were raised by your father alone.
Didn’t you long for a mother?
I’d feel sorry for your kids to suffer the same fate.
Don’t you agree?
Yes...
You’re right.
Now, don’t be so sad.
You’re making me sad.
Fine!
Drink up tonight!
It’s all my treat.
I can’t drink that much.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Drink up and forget everything.
Where am I?
I’m naked?!
Oh dear. You’re already awake?
Oba-san?
Good morning.
But our 'night' continues.
Where am I?
The bedroom in my apartment.
But never mind that...
Oba-san! What are you...
Your dick is a tent pole.
Looks delicious.
No... Don’t...
Aki-kun, you still love tits, don’t you.
I don’t...
Don’t lie to me.
Long ago, you’d suck my tits for hours, remember?
Yeah...
Touch them like you used to.
They’re a bit saggier than before.
But I’ve still got a nice bust, haven’t I?
Yeah...
And now, me too...
The shape and flavor haven’t changed a bit.
Don’t...
It’s been so long, it’s extra sensitive.
No...
Oba-san, I’m gonna... I’m gonna cum.
So yummy.
You’ve had it building up since your wife left
So much thick stuff came up.
And it’s still so hard.
Akane... I’m sorry.
Listen, Aki-kun!
I’m doing this for you!
You need to forget her as soon as possible!
But I can’t...
Forget her!
Listen, Aki-kun.
She cheated on you with one of your supervisors and ran away with him.
She’s a stupid woman who left you for another man.
There’s a girl in the same department as her who comes to my bar.
I heard the story from her so I know it’s true.
It can’t...
I’m sure you realized it.
Yeah... I thought it was strange...
But still!
Aki-kun...
Now that you know the truth, have you gotten over it a little?
A little...
I will do whatever I can to help you get over this as soon as possible.
Okay?
So work with me.
Okay... I will.
Very nice.
It’s inside.
How do you like my insides, Aki-kun?
So warm... And it feels so good.
The same as before?
Yes.
It’s so slippery and I feel like there’s a pulse.
Yes! Yes, Aki-kun!
Your dick... It’s so hard!
So hard and thick!
Just like before!
It fits my pussy perfectly!
Oh yes!
My pelvis is moving on its own.
Oba-san... You’re too... Rough!
But it’s been a long time for me... Since I felt a dick.
It feels too good!
I’m cum-... Cumming!
That reminds me... After you took my virginity you had sex with me almost every day for four months straight.
But then you suddenly found someone else and got married.
Why did you get a divorce?
When we had sex the last time...
You told me, 'I found someone else. Sorry... This will be the last time.'
And you cried while having sex with me.
I’m sorry... Sorry I seduced you and made you who you are...
Today will... Today will...
Be the last!
So deeper... Go deeper inside of me!
Today is the last time!
So please... Mess me up tonight!
I’m unable... To have children.
When he found that out he got a lover right away.
And as soon as he got her pregnant, he left me.
But because of that, his company went under.
Karma, maybe?
Hey, stop it.
Don’t hug me so gently. I’ll cry.
I don’t want to cry!
I have work so I’m leaving early. – Akihiko
I’m exhausted.
I’m home.
... Well, not like anyone’s here to hear that.
Well then, I’ve got three days off after today.
Gotta stick with it.
I can’t take it.
Sleepy.
I’m gonna die from fatigue.
Thanks for breakfast.
Good morning.
What’re you doing so early in the morning?
What? Why, your wake-up blowjob, of course!
Made a nice wake up, didn’t it.
And... Why are you dressed like that?
It’s my nightie.
Your nightie?
I used your bedroom.
You came in the middle of the night?
Oh, don’t you remember?
You came all over the place.
First I got you with my mouth, remember?
Then, when I got on top,
You came inside of my pussy plenty.
Now that you mentioned it, I think I had a sex dream about Akane...
Who could that be so early?
Coming!
Mom?!
Akihiko-san... I have something very important to talk about.
W
Tsuma no Haha Sayuri
Um... What do you have to talk about?
And what’s wrong?
You look so sick.
Who is that woman.
Oh, sorry.
She’s my aunt, Fujino-san.
She’s family... Sort of.
Nice to meet you.
'Aunt'?
Even though she’s inside, she’s in the company of a young man...
Dressed in a top that exposes her nipples?
I wonder if Akihiko’s family life is that 'open'...
So this is his wife’s mother...
Um, this is for you...
Please read it.
I just can’t...
What’s this?
Divorce papers.
Sh-She can’t!
She also sent this.
Mom, please give these to Akihiko-kun.
Oh, yes, right.
I’m living at the seaside with my new boyfriend now.
Bye!
Mom?!
Mom!
Wh-Where am I?
That’s right.
I’m... In Akihiko-san’s house.
Akihiko-san?
Maybe he’s on the second floor...
Yes!
This feels great, Aki-kun!
Move more from the bottom.
I will!
What are you kids doing!
What are we doing? Sex, of course!
You still don’t know what it is at your age? Sayuri-san...
But you two are nephew and aunt, aren’t you!
Well, we...
That’s indecent!
Your daughter is the indecent one!
Oba-san!
Aki-kun, you stay quiet.
Okay...
If your daughter hadn’t cheated on him and left him...
He wouldn’t have done this.
What do you mean?
It’s a bit awkward here, so let’s talk in the other room.
... Okay.
Sorry for the wait.
The misunderstanding has been cleared up.
Oh.
“'Misunderstanding'?
Come.  Don’t be embarrassed and come in.
I’m so sorry.
I had no idea you went through that.
Clearing up a girl’s irresponsible behavior is a mother’s responsibility.
I want to make it up to you, Akihiko-san!
You can’t...!
What?!
You don’t want me?
An old lady like me... I must not have much sex appeal to you...
That’s not at all true!
You’re still very sexy and beautiful!
What a relief.
I’m so happy.
Well then...
What?
How is it?
Am I alright?
It feels great.
Akane had small breasts, didn’t she?
This is my only specialty.
This feels great...
This is the first time I’ve been tit-fucked...
I... I...
Amazing!
So much...
With just that much, you’re not really satisfied, are you, Sayuri?
No...
In that case, what do you want?
Tell him.
In my pussy... I want your still-hard cock thrust in.
Please? Will you?
Mom...
Akihiko-san...
Akihiko-san!
Wow!
Mom...
This feels great!
Akihiko-san!
Mom, your insides feel great!
Don’t worry.
Does it hurt?
No.
It feels great.
So move faster.
Move rougher.
Yes!
Oh... Faster!
Rougher!
All the way inside!
Hit me!
This feels great.
Your dick... It’s been ten years since I’ve felt a dick.
Yes!
Deeper... Deeper, please!
It’s hitting my uterus!
Yes!
Harder!
Yes...
Oh, yes!
My pelvis is moving on its own.
Ohhh...
This dick feels so great.
I’m dizzy all over.
This violet ecstasy is piercing through my whole body!
I can’t take it!
Oh no!
I’m cumming!
Cumming!
Aki-kun!
Over here!
I’m up next.
Put your dick in me too!
Love me lots!
If you don’t...
If you don’t, something’s gonna happen to me!
Hurry!
Yes...
This ringing... It’s Akane!
What the hell...
Akane!
Huh?
Um... Who are you?
Who’s that?
Nice to meet you!
First, I’ll need you to die!
To be continued...