Yes! That feels good!
Just like that, deeper!
I'm cumming!
Cum! Cum for me!
What is this feeling?
After drinking the tea they gave me, my body...
It wants to embrace them.
Akito-san, please tend to our daughter as well.
Papa, please make me a woman.
Please make love to me as you do to mother.
I'm coming.
It's...
You're moving it inside me.
Papa, your dick is going inside me!
Your body's starting to recognize
Akito-san's touch.
The feeling starts inside you
and begins to change you.
You're clamping down on my dick.
It's nice and tight!
You're being so rough! It's so intense!
Something warm is coming out!
Papa's sperm... it's going deep inside me!
That's fine. My daughter's womb is taking your
sperm. Please make this memorable for her.
I'm cumming!
Having Papa's dick inside me
while Mama watches...
This is the best feeling in the world!
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
I love you.
I'll give my all to you.
This is a step in the right direction.
Sorry about this, Akito-san, but
I'll be using you to my heart's content.
#2 Two Lovers' Feelings
No! You can't do this! I'll never forgive you!
Just accept it already.
My body isn't for you to do with as you please!
Get off of me. Get off!
I know just where you like it. Quit being
stubborn and ask for it like before.
No!
Stop it! My husband's coming
out of the bath at any minute!
Keep this up and nobody's going to have any fun.
Tch, guess it can't be helped.
No! At this rate, I...
It feels so good.
It's like my dick has a mind of its own!
My womb is opening. No! I
can't give in to Takeo-kun!
Feels like your body wants my children!
What do you say to that?
Tell me you want my kids! Take my sperm!
No! I'm going to cum!
Here I come! I'm cumming inside!
Darling! Akito-kun!
Why'd you yell his name? Damn it.
You're so big, darling.
I was just thinking that it's been
a while since we've had sex.
I hope your palms haven't been too rosy.
It's so hard.
Touching me got you so wet!
I'm wet from having sex with
Takeo-kun just earlier.
I'm glad he didn't find out, but I can't say that.
We feel the same about each other, don't we?
Yes, darling. We do.
What's this? Miyuri's like a whole different person!
She's taking it so passionately in her mouth.
Cum lots for me, alright?
I'll do just that.
Darling, I'm going to lose it!
You're getting so hard!
I've got to remember. I'm Akito-kun's
wife, and I'm going to have his kids!
You want it here, don't you?
Yes, I want it!
I want you, gushing inside me!
Sorry. I shouldn't cum so soon,
but I'm going to cum!
That's fine. You can cum whenever you like.
Akito-kun!
Miyuri!
You were really pent-up, weren't you?
In the time we haven't been together,
have you gotten better at this?
What do you mean by that?
I-I'm just joking!
More importantly.
Miyuri, let's get back to it.
Darling, it's already quite late.
I should only be thinking about
my husband, Kazuto-san.
No, Akito! Don't run, Akito!
Good morni...
I'm fine, so.
My sprain! Be careful!
I guess I shouldn't have asked her
to nurse him back to health.
That's right.
During the test of courage, you fell into a ditch.
Seeing you down there had me worried!
Akito-kun! Akito-kun, take my hand!
Honestly, it's just a light injury.
You don't need to dote on me like this.
But you're still injured!
I'm already here, so I want
to help you however I can.
So please don't worry about him, Miyuri-san.
Alright, I'm leaving him in your care.
Thanks for today.
It's not a big deal, but I guess Miyuri-san
made it sound like one.
That sounds like her alright.
After all, you got that injury while looking
out for someone, didn't you?
How'd you know that?
I know everything about you.
And I know how Miyuri-san really feels about you.
Akito, shall we take a bath together,
for old time's sake?
Does it hurt? Is your injury OK?
It tingles a little, but it's alright.
Ah, Sayoko-san's skin feels so good. She's so kind.
I don't think you can clean yourself
thoroughly with that injury, so.
I'll take care of this too.
Sayoko-san!
It's so big it looks like you could cum at any
minute. You'll cum if you get any more aroused.
You've gotten so much bigger since
last time I did this for you.
Akito, you've become such a fine man.
Oh no! I'm getting so wet from
just touching his dick.
I want to see it when Akito cums!
Squeeze it night out of the tip!
Sayoko-san, I'm going to cum!
Cum! Cum for me, Akito!
Sorry, Sayoko-san. I got some on you.
You came so much with just my hand.
Hey Akito, come in here.
Akito's dick is so good! He's hitting
all my sensitive spots!
Let's move this to the bedroom, alright?
If we keep this up, I'm going to lose it!
Akito-kun?
He's not here. Did Sayoko-san
do something with him?!
I won't let her have her way anymore.
That feels so good!
I can feel the shape of your dick!
He's filling the cracks in my heart!
I love you, Akito-kun! I love you!
I've been waiting... my womb's
been waiting for you, Akito!
I want you to love me!
I want to become one with you, Sayoko-san!
Cum inside me. Make me your woman, Akito!
– I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
– I'm cumming!
Miyuri-san, even though you've enjoyed
Akito's blissful company for so long...
You'll still be jealous, won't you?
Sorry to keep you so late.
I didn't think we'd make love for as long as we did.
Miyuri-san!
I won't let Akito-san come here again!
You're unfit for him.
You're saying that you are?
Akito isn't your toy. Don't hurt
him any more than you have.
Toy? My love for Akito-kun is real!
So you love him more than
you love your husband?
I made love to Akito, prepared
to conceive his child.
Miyuri-san, between your husband and Akito...
Whose children do you want to have?
I want... I want to have...
Miyuri-san is my older brother's wife.
She was my first love.
What am I supposed to do?
Here you are.
Miyuri-san.
This is the place where I had my
first kiss with Kazuto-san.
I decided I'd give my reply today,
right here in this place.
I want to fall in love with you all over again.
Miyuri-san's telling me how she really feels.
I want to spend the rest of my life with you,
even if I hurt other people's feelings in the process.
I can't stop loving you.
It's love. I love you.
I won't run from my feelings anymore.
So please embrace me
in this place where I first fell
in love with my husband.
I... I...
Sayoko-san, I can't! I can't just
pick one of you to love!
You don't have to reply just now.
I don't want to hear it yet.
I'll show you thoroughly just how much I love you.
Akito-kun, your dick fills me so well!
Your dick feels so good! My hips
are moving on their own!
If you do it like that, I'm going to cum!
Hold it in just a little longer! I want
this moment to last forever!
I'm going to cum! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
My womb is ready for him. His
dick is rubbing against it!
If you grind against it like that, I'm going to cum!
It's leaking out!
If you cum like that, I'll get pregnant! You're
thrusting into me like a piston!
I've always loved you, Miyuri-san!
If you say that, I'm going to cum!
I'm really going to cum!
Akito-kun, I want your child!
I can't hold back anymore!
Cum! Cum! Cum deep inside me!
Miyuki-san, here I come!
Give me all of it.
Akito-kun, I'm going to have your children.
Akito-kun's given me another life.
It's like being completely reborn!
From the woman who lived only for her husband
to the real me I am now.
You're so wet down here from just
pouring the guests their drinks.
That's not it. Thinking about you got me like this.
Is that so? I've got to keep you
away from other guys.
From the start, I've only had eyes for you, darling.
I was only thinking about your dick.
Cum whenever you want.
I'm prepared to have your children.
Sayoko-san.
Don't think about anything. Just cum inside me!
Please give me all kinds of happiness!
Here I come, Sayoko-san.
I can feel it.
I'm going to cum. Him cumming! I'm
definitely going to get pregnant!
Don't make me jealous again.
If we passionately make love when you're jealous,
I'm not sure I can promise you that.
Sayoko-san.
I couldn't choose just one of them to love, after all.
Akito-kun, it feels so good!
It's so good I could melt!
It's gotten so big. How naughty.
You're rubbing me like that.
You can use my hands, mouth,
pussy or ass. I'm all yours!
So...
Use my body to your heart's desire!
Akito-kun!
It's so hard! I'm starting to let out lewd cries!
Someone might hear us!
You really love my dick, don't you?
It's because you hit all my sensitive spots!
I'm almost there!
Not yet! I want to make you feel even better!
You like this, don't you?
At this rate, you'll cum using my pussy!
That's...
Come on, cum for me.
Let it all out!
How's this?
I don't want to be thought
of as a pathetic husband!
Akito-kun, this position... You're stirring up
my pussy. It's making me feel so good!
I was destined to be with him.
He satisfies my heart and my body!
I want his children. I want him to get me pregnant!
I'm cumming!
Cum deep inside me!
I have an equal love... for both of you.
I'm home.
Welcome home, darling.
Sorry for coming back late.
Don't worry about it.
You're cold, aren't you? I'll warm you up.
Gently, please.
Miyuri.
Akito-kun, I love you. I love you!
I'm only being touched and licked,
but it feels so good inside!
Tonight, I'm focusing right here.
I-I'm so sensitive there! It feels so good!
Please don't forget about me.
I'm aroused too, you know.
Of course.
Akito-kun, I'm glad I'm yours!
Please love me more! Please love us more!
Alright, I'll support you both!
Akito, I'm cumming too!
And me too!
Translation: ObscureReference
Timing: ObscureReference
QA: Dorans
softsub: торрент иваниваныч