Akito-kun?
Wake up, breakfast is ready.
Nee-san?
Yep! Come on, go wash your face,
and we'll have breakfast together.
#1 Depravity with a stranger
Potatoes... Where are they?
Oh, nice view.
I clean everyday, but it gets dirty again so quickly.
Nee-san! Cover up a little!
Stop looking where you shouldn't be.
S-Sorry.
This isn't good. I can't keep looking
at my brother's wife like that.
Akito-kun. What would you prefer?
Eggplant or cucumb...
Cucumber is good.
Welcome home, Akito-kun.
So, for dinner...
Anything's good.
Geez, Akito-kun?
Why have you been ignoring me so much?
Nee-san, what are you doing?
You two are as close as ever.
Welcome home, dear. You're back early today.
Yeah, my appointment with the local doctor went well.
Let me introduce you.
This is Takeo, his son.
We'll be looking after him for a bit.
What's up?
This is all very sudden.
Well, the doctor is busy and we owe him, so...
– I thought it was a good time to return the favor.
– Damn, I'm lucky.
Name's Takeo. Thanks for takin' me in, pretty lady.
I'm his wife, Miyuri. I hope you have a good stay.
Oh, you as well, sup.
Great, let me show you around.
Akito-kun?
Fuck! What's his problem?!
Guy was nothing but disrespectful!
Piece of shit thinks he can
get friendly with my nee-san?!
I'm coming in.
Huh? Wai...
Nee-san, don't come in here nak...
Swimsuit?
It's been a while, but if I'm wearing this,
I can wash your back.
Akito-kun.
I appreciate this, but if my bro finds out...
That man doesn't wake up once he's asleep.
That's not the problem here.
I'll leave as soon as I'm done, okay?
Does he get this treatment every day?
In the time I haven't seen him,
he's really grown into an adult.
Tell me if there are any itchy spots, okay?
Y-Yeah.
There's nothing actually itching,
but I definitely have something itching to go.
Ever since then,
our relationship and feelings have changed.
Nee-san?
Sorry.
Next is your front.
Wait! You can't...
S-Sorry.
Just seeing you like that aroused me.
Oh, so you're interested in me?
Isn't that obv...
I've been interested since the first time we met.
I see.
Nee-san, this isn't going to end well.
But it feels better like this, doesn't it?
Every time I touch him, my body reacts.
I shouldn't be doing this. He's my brother-in-law.
But...
Hey, even if we're siblings by law,
how far do you think we're allowed to go?
How far? What do you mean?
That's...
Come on, relax.
Oh my god.
You held back your anger towards Takeo, didn't you?
This is my way of saying thank you.
I'll make it so you're not mad anymore.
This way you won't hurt yourself
worrying about me so much.
It kind of looks like his.
You can let it out whenever you want, okay?
I'll keep rubbing it for you as much as you want.
I'm not gonna be able to hold myself back.
I wanna be inside you, nee-san!
You can't.
If you do that, you'll turn me on too.
I can tell.
If we go that far, I'll fall even deeper in love with you.
I've loved you for so long.
No, don't say any more.
Hurry up and let it out.
I... can't...
I'm cumming.
Your naughty dick is being a good boy now.
This taste. It's been so long.
My head...
My head's about to burst!
I remember drinking with his wife.
This is what happens when you try to out-drink me.
Here, Takeo-kun. Drink this.
Ma'am?
Miso soup is great for hangovers.
I've never had a stranger care so much for me before.
One day, I wanna find a woman like her,
come up from behind, and stick it in her.
Honestly, it'd probably be better if I put clams in it, but...
Wh-What are you doing?!
You smell so damn nice.
Stop! Stop this!
Takeo-kun, stop it! I thought we were friends!
I've wanted to connect with you
ever since I first laid eyes on you.
I promise I won't do you wrong.
No, don't touch there!
Nee-san!
Get the fuck away from her.
That hurt.
Fuck, calm down.
That was just a joke. A little joke.
Nee-san, we can't.
This is thanks for this afternoon.
Nee-san is all over my dick.
He's filling up my mouth.
I want it inside me, knocking on my womb.
Nee-san, I want to have sex...
I want to become one with you!
I feel the same way.
I want to share the pleasure with him.
Nee-san, I love you.
I love you so much!
Geez...
Nee-san! I'm cumming!
This isn't good.
I can't hold my feelings back anymore!
That felt really good, nee-san.
That's not fair.
It's not fair. I love you so much too, Akito-kun.
Is that...
The one thing I shouldn't have said..
Come here, Akito-kun.
You're sure about this?
It's something that will never be forgiven.
Nee-san!
I... I...
Please, just put it in me.
It's going inside!
How about you call me
by my name when we're like this?
Miyuri-san...
Miyuri-san! Miyuri-san!
Akito-kun, not like that!
This is too different from the sex I know!
My pussy is begging for his dick.
I've always... I've always loved you!
Me too! I love you too! I love you so much, Akito-kun!
If you keep fucking me like that,
you'll make me want to have your child!
It's coming! I'm gonna cum!
Miyuri-san, let's do it together!
Cum all you want inside my womb!
I'm cumming!
Miyuri-san. I'm so happy right now.
Me too.
I love you.
I never knew that making love
with Akito-kun would feel so good.
I want him to make love to me again.
I wish it would be night already,
so I can have sex with him.
I feel like I might lose my mind.
Excuse me?
Sorry, we're not open yet...
You look well, Sayoko-san.
Akito!
You should've told me that you were back.
I know, I'm sorry.
I'm not letting you leave.
I have to get back soon. Miyuri-san's waiting for me.
Inseparable, even after she got married. I'm so jealous.
Yeah, but didn't you get married to Ginji-san?
You're right. But, you're special.
Knowing you, you're still in love with Miyuri-san, aren't you?
How do you know that?
Don't you remember?
I took your virginity the day she got married.
It's easy for me to tell.
Well... Didn't you promise not to say anything?
Listen, Akito. If you ever feel sad, come see me, okay?
I'll comfort you again.
What do you mean?
When a woman comforts a man,
there's only one thing that it could be, right?
We can't, Miyuri-san!
Akito-kun!
Not out here!
I was just so happy when you came out to get me.
I just couldn't hold myself back.
What about your birth control?
This is practice for when I'll have to get pregnant.
Make sure you tell me when you're about to cum, okay?
Otherwise, we might make a baby.
I can't believe we're doing this at your workplace.
There's no way I can stop myself now!
Even if you wanted to, I wouldn't let you.
Your dick is poking into my womb.
It's making a path for its cum.
Don't put a baby in me just yet.
A baby between you and me...
Make sure you don't let it out inside me, okay?
This is just practice, okay?
I really want to tell him to just pour his cum
into my womb. I want to beg for it.
Your dick is getting bigger. It wants to cum, doesn't it?
I want to get you pregnant Miyuri-san!
No, you can't. Please, don't.
I want to get you pregnant with my cum!
Wait, Akito-kun. You can't!
Miyuri-san, I'm...
There's so much cum going inside me!
Sorry, I came inside.
It's fine. It felt so good.
Unlike when I do it with my husband,
I'm actually feeling good.
It came out perfect today as well.
But maybe I made it a little too early.
There's still thirty minutes before everyone wakes up.
What's wrong with me?
I can't stop thinking about this dick.
I want to be connected with Akito-kun more.
This can't go on, I'm married!
What's happened to my body?!
No, I can't stop. Akito-kun! Akito-kun!
Good morning, Miyuri-san.
Good morning. You're earlier than usual today.
Yeah, I smelled something good, so I woke up.
I want him.
That's not something I should want, though.
I need to stop this relationship.
So breakfast for today is...
Hey, Akito-kun?
Miyuri-san?
I'm scared.
I don't think I can hold back my feelings for you.
I'm sure you can do it.
You're really responsible.
That's not true.
I'm forgetting what it means to be a woman.
If this keeps going, I won't be able
to think of anything but you, Akito-kun.
Does that mean...
So...
Let's stop having sex.
I get it. I was just being too naive, huh?
I'm gonna get some air.
Please forgive me.
If you ever feel sad...
Sayoko-san.
Akito, come here.
Sayoko-san, I was rejected by Miyuri-san.
You don't have to say any more.
Let me comfort you.
Akito-kun, where did you go?
I feel so restless and I don't know why.
Akito!
Akito, your dick is so hard!
It's so amazing!
Do me harder! Harder!
Am I better than I was before?
Forget about everything and just focus on the pleasure.
Sayoko-san, I... I...
It's fine. It's our sex reunion, let's have fun.
Sango
Every time you thrust your dick in me,
I feel it spreading me apart.
I don't care what I am to you,
but right now, just cum inside me.
Do you want this? Please give me your baby, Akito!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Sayoko-san, I'm... cumming!
I'll be your woman, so come whenever you want, okay?
Yeah, thanks, Sayoko-san.
Did one of the cups fall?
I guess we were a bit too rough.
Wouldn't you agree? Miyuri-san?
Akito-kun, why were you with that woman?
I was wrong.
Even then, I still loved you.
I was wondering what you were up to,
and I find you masturbating in his room.
You don't want your husband to find out, right?
Delete that!
They can do whatever they want to your body.
How do you know that?
You were so loud, it was hard not to know.
That can't be...
Blame yourself for giving me a chance to do this.
Comfort me.
No...
Come on, tell me you want my dick.
You... Akito-kun!
If you don't say it,
I might upload the pictures to the internet.
Please put your dick inside me, Takeo-kun.
I like it. This is fucking great!
Wait, where's the condom?!
If you keep thrusting it in me like some
wild animal, I'm going to lose my mind!
I've liked you since I saw you.
I like you, Miyuri!
No, don't say that!
I wanna pump my child into your womb!
I wanna become one with you!
No! If you cum inside me, I might get pregnant!
Your cum's gonna shoot out into my womb!
Tell your husband.
Tell him that you like my dick more than his!
There's no way I could ever say tha...
Come on, say it! Miyuri!
I won't say it. No matter what!
But... does it really matter anymore?
Miyuri!
Dear... Akito-kun... I'm sorry...
Your dick is better than both my husband's and Akito-kun's!
Please, let me forget about everything!
Finally honest, huh?
Your dick is going deeper than
both my husband's and Akito-kun's!
You're mine now.
You're my woman!
I'm gonna get you pregnant, Miyuri.
I promise you!
You're going to plant your seed inside me with your dick!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll take good care of you, too.
Will I ever be able to...
go back to how things were before?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: biskoi4
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч