Once every week, my wife
Misako pampers me like a child.
We've been married for four happy years.
Until I barely noticed that something
feels peculiar about her.
That's right.
I feel that my wife has been
getting prettier lately.
My wife... Misako is...
And moreover, the man with her is...
What should we do?
If you want to, I know an attorney...
I can introduce you to that person right away...
More! Keep on thrusting!
Good! That feels good!
That prudish wife of mine was
making such an indecent face?
What is this feeling?
Even though my wife's infidelity
is right in my face...
I am... I am...
I'm not that fond of sex.
That's what my wife said.
I act in accordance with my wife.
I'm satisfied just with lying down
and sleeping beside her.
That's the kind of man I am.
It's not that I am sexually frigid.
Well, my sex drive is low when I leave it
up to my own body to decide.
I tried to be cautious not to
lose control of my emotions.
And at that time,
as I look at my wife's infidelity
with my very own eyes...
...I got aroused.
Your cock... I love your cock!
I'm coming... Coming... Coming!
I'm coming—!
To confirm these feelings of mine,
I made an appointment with her lover,
and thought up a certain plan.
Tsuma ga Kirei ni Natta Wake
The Reason Why My Wife Got Prettier
Volume 1
Tarou-san?
What's the matter, Tarou-san?
Huh? Oh, nothing...
I've been lying on Misako's lap
Thank you.
through the whole afternoon.
Aren't you gonna drink coffee?
I felt my nether region heating up
while she was cleaning my ear.
She's acting like usual.
I'm sure that she had some sort of past.
While having that side I never knew about,
she acts in a usual manner like this.
"The truth is, I know about everything."
What will happen if I suddenly
whisper that on her ear?
I don't think that she will be
able to talk her way out of that.
I have overwhelming leverage
so there's no way for me to lose.
Then, what will I do after I win?
This everyday life of ours ever so
delicate and barely kept intact...
I'd rather not put an end to it.
This is erotic, you know.
That's right.
In exchange for overlooking
my wife's affair with that man,
I demanded him to give me
a copy of their sex tape.
And then, today...
To tell you the truth, people who
have such a fetish like yours
are not that rare.
Here's the recording from last night.
Really...
If anyone actually sees this, you're on your own.
How does this smell, Misako?
I-It's the worst stench I ever knew.
Is she gonna suck it?
Will Misako... Will my beloved wife
suck a cock that isn't mine?
Sh-She's sucking it!
Misako, both of your upper and lower mouths
always loved gobbling my cock even way back then.
Misako has never done fellatio on me yet.
I never asked for one either.
Good! Isn't that great!
What a lewd butt you have!
It's such a nice view no matter
how many times I look.
You're such a beautiful woman
with an indecent body!
You're an inborn pussy woman!
Hey, do you want a cock?
A-A cock?
Cock... I want a cock!
Here, here, here, here you go! It's deep inside!
You won't get satisfied unless
I push it in deep, after all!
I realized it just from her moan
when he penetrated her.
Misako right there is getting much more pleasure
than when she's having sex with me!
And so am I...
Misako! Misako!
Yes!
No, no, this is bad after all!
Th-This is bad—!
As I watched my wife's infidelity, I...
I never cared about getting both my hand
and clothes covered with semen
as I wholeheartedly moved my right hand...
I felt as if I threw something away
which I can never get back anymore.
I want it... I want to see them
having sex again as soon as possible!
So, how did it go?
Yeah, well...
I'm feeling hatred and grudge for you.
I even thought about killing you...
However, even more than that...
Goddammit, I feel like I'm
way beyond saving anymore!
Whoa there!
Let's not resort to our fists, please!
I only did what you requested to me
will full sincerity.
Should we keep going on
with this? Will you be alright?
Let's go on with it.
I'm telling you to keep sleeping with Misako.
I understand.
Then, I won't hold back on using Misako's "hole".
About a week after that,
I received the second video.
Oh my, this wine is easy to drink!
It's delicious!
Oh? I'll have some, then!
Here you go, Tarou-san
My wife is in her usual good mood.
And behind that very same face,
she made such a wild expression
which the video caught.
My nether region responded accordingly.
How cold! Come on, let's smooch!
No! No kissing...
Even if it's with your first even man?
This is the taste of your first man's kiss.
I even know about your pussy mole!
Jeez...
You won't even let me kiss you before, right?
They've been doing all that,
but she hasn't been allowing him to kiss her?
Has she been protecting her lips as my wife?
Shit, that bastard Kuroda!
That face of hers aroused my cock, made it hard
and drip even more!
This really makes me remember about that.
I loved how you looked when
you're craving for sex so much!
You'll undo the front part of your
blouse, and have your tits spill out!
You'll leave your skirt on
as you take your panties off!
We fucked quite a lot while
you're wearing tights!
Look, it's the cock you're craving for!
It's the piping hot and huge cock that you love!
I feel hot...
I'm burning hot inside!
I want you to put it in.
Put it in—!
Here you go, class rep. Misako!
It's the thick and ginormous cock that you love!
More... More!
I want more of your thick
and hard cock, Kuroda-kun!
I want to have my soaking wet pussy
pounded and muddled into a mess!
Y-Your cock is going in and out of me...
Kuroda-kun's thick meaty cock!
I can't get enough of that droopy face of yours!
That huge gap between your usual
prim face and that depraved expression!
Hey, pull your tongue out.
Damn, what a lewd way to move your tongue!
No, no, no...
No—!
Y-You're stretching my insides wide open!
Here, does my cock feel better
than your husband's?
Come on, tell me!
No, I don't want to! I absolutely won't!
Say it! Say it, Misako!
I'll go crazy if you keep
fucking me with that cock...
Tell me! Tell me!
How am I compared to your husband?
It's better!
You're way better than Tarou-san!
Hiro-kun, your thick meaty cock is way better!
At the same moment as Misako screamed in ecstasy,
my own cock which I'm holding in my hand spurted.
Forgive me, Tarou-san...
What... What an outrageous appearance!
What an outrageous appearance, Misako!
I gritted my teeth and held
my tears back in frustration,
but my hand is seeking to please my cock!
It's as if my cock is a separate organism!
Much to my own amazement,
I watched my wife's infidelity
as I masturbate, and then...
I ejaculated one after another.
Even when I just ejaculated an amount that
I never ever had in my whole life within a day...
When I look at her face,
both my heart and body won't settle down.
I badly want to have sex!
I want to have sex with Misako!
This voluptuous waist...
It looks so tender and possessing
such elastic plumpness.
Misako...
Hey, Misako... I wonder if you're awake.
Hey, Misako!
If it was Kuroda, I wonder if
he'll go straight to wake her up,
then forcefully and recklessly penetrate her.
I don't have the guts to do that!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization