Tsuma no Haha Sayuri 2
...
Oh...
Who’s that?
Not sure...
Just die!
Hey, you, are you okay?
Akihiko-san, I think you should choose your girlfriends more carefully.
But I’ve never seen her before.
So what are we going to do about her?
Should we call the police?
Oh, what’s this room?
It’s a room my dad used from time to time.
But now it’s more like a storage closet.
But what are we going to do about her?
She must have some reason.
I figured we’d just let her sleep for a while.
You’re being naïve!
What if she throws a cleaver at us again?!
She’s right, Akihiko-san!
That’s attempted murder already.
B-But, she had been hiding the cleaver, and it didn’t seem like she had anything else...
What the hell are you saying?!
If a girl puts her mind to it, she can even hide a weapon in her pussy.
I think you watch too much h-anime.
And what’s with that getup?
It was my only option!
I found it in my room.
Right, Aki-kun?
Aki-kun always did love seeing tits poke out from tiny underwear.
Th-That’s not true at all.
See? He’s blushing.
Never mind that, the question now is what are we going to do with this girl?
She almost killed us all.
Are you sure?
I’m very sure!
Yes... I was going to kill him and then kill myself.
Take me to the police if you want to.
I have no reason to live anymore.
I have nothing!
Looks like you have a story.
Tell us.
He was... My husband left me for someone named Akane.
Akane again?
She said she was used to seeing this sort of thing because of all the escort stuff she’s done.
But I wonder if it was okay to leave those two alone.
Hey...
Mom, what’re you doing?
You sure are young.
You came so much yesterday and you’re already hard again.
Wait, Mom...
No! You’re divorcing my daughter, so call me “Sayuri”!
I am no longer your mother-in-law. I’m just a woman.
Isn't that right?
Y-Yes.
Remembering yesterday makes me so wet.
Touch me.
Wow.
You’re much wetter than last night.
When you made love to me last night after ten years of nothing...
As a woman, not as a mother, my eyes opened.
Please.
Thinking of what my daughter did makes my heart feel like it’s going to burst.
Make love to me. Make me forget!
You’re the only one I can rely on.
Mo... Sayuri...-san
I was unable to conceive so we went to a fertility clinic.
Even the doctor said it was probably my husband’s fault.
But even so, my mom blamed me – said I was the reason we couldn’t conceive.
What the hell?! That’s unforgivable.
I'm infertile too, so I understand how you feel.
Onee-sama!
“Onee-sama”.
Akihiko-san, yes. This feels great.
I’m almost...
Me too, I’m almost...
I’m cumming... I’m cumming already.
And so... he forced me to divorce him, and kicked me out of the apartment.
I have no job and no skills. Death was my only option.
Kill my deadbeat husband and...
Then you should just live in this house.
It’s rent-free.
And if you need a job, you could always work at my bar.
Yes, but...
I think it was no coincidence that you came here.
Well?
Yes!
Well then, I'll go get my belongings.
Yes, M-
Call me “Sayuri”.
Yes. Sayuri-san.
I’ll be right back, Akihiko-san.
Yes, Sayuri-san.
W-Well, then, I’ll be back.
Okay.
Onee-sama! What are you... Wow...
What’re you saying?
Listen, there's a rule for living in this house.
And it doesn’t seem like you don't like it.
Your panties are all wet.
No...
You’ve been lonely without your husband, right?
Yes... that’s true.
It’s been a long time, hasn’t it?
Yes, it has been!
So you’ve been consoling yourself this whole time.
Yes, I have.
Well? Doesn’t this feel good?
Yes. It does.
Onee-sama, you’re so... oh no!
Shizui-chan, your confused face is so cute.
Onee-sama... I... I...
Not yet. There’s more to come.
That reminds me... Auntie and that girl... I wonder how they’re doing?
Onee-sama, what are you...
I’m embarrassed.
Oh dear. Your panties are all wet.
Did you pee yourself?
N-No, it’s sweat!
That time your body convulsed – you were cumming, weren’t you.
Just be honest. Then I’ll make you feel even better.
More juice is coming out.
No, no...
It was pee.
No, it wasn’t pee. It was cum.
It was cum...
You’re so cute.
Your nipples are so hard too.
Oh no... not any more... no!
I’ll cum again!
You can’t cum just yet.
A penis feels much better than fingers, right?
Aki-kun, you’re out there, aren’t you?
Sorry.
I didn’t intend to eavesdrop.
Never mind that, just get my bag from the living room.
Ta-dah.
Isn’t it amazing, Shizue-chan?
Yes...
Onee-sama...
“Onee-sama”?
Ready, Shizue-chan?
I’m putting it in.
It’s going in!
Well? Doesn’t it feel like the real thing?
Yes.
It feels very good, but...
Why are you embarrassed?
Well...
If you live in this house, you need to please both me and Aki-kun.
Aki-kun, take off your underwear.
What?!
Never mind, just take them off.
Okay...
See? Aki-kun is also rock hard.
Well? How many years has it been since you’ve seen a naked dick?
Five years...
You may use this dick whenever you want if you live in this house.
But not yet. Not until I’ve had some fun.
Oh, yes! Onee-sama!
No!
This feels great!
No...
Wow! Oh no!
I... I... Oh...
You already came?
I guess it was only to be expected – seeing as how it’s been years since you’ve been plowed so deep in your uterus.
Well! Next up it’s a real penis.
Shizue-chan, lick it to get it wet.
Dick...
Okay.
Oh, my.
Sucking on a real dick is making lots of juices seep out of you.
Hey, don’t stop moving.
Stroke it and suck it good.
Oh no... I’m almost...
Don’t, Aki-kun.
Hang in there.
Cum inside Shizue-chan.
Now, show him your butt and beg Aki-kun.
Okay... Onee-sama...
Akihiko-kun? My pussy...
Fill it with semen – it’s been dry for five years.
Wow!
Your dick is so hard.
Yes! This feels great!
Yet!
Come in deeper.
All the way inside!
Oh no!
I’ll pee myself!
It’s all the way in my uterus!
Oh, yes!
I...
I... I’m almost...
I’m cumming again!
There’s more to come.
The night is long.
Let’s have much more fun.
My back hurts from too much fucking...
I’m so tired.
I’m home.
Huh?
Mom?
It’s Sayuri.
Sayuri-san... Why are the lights off?
Akihiko-san, we need to talk.
Huh?
That reminds me, where are my aunt and Shizue?
They’re both at work.
Oh, I see.
Do they really concern you so much?
You’re all I’ve got!
Akihiko-san, do you prefer Fujino-san over me?
That’s not exactly...
Sayuri-san!
Why’re you like...
Look, Akihiko-san.
I’m lonely.
The more you have sex with other women...
I belong to you, Akihiko-san.
I am your maid.
Your slave.
I will do anything you want.
So just look only at me.
Tease me plenty!
I’m begging you!
Please love me!
No!
What are you doing?
You said you’d do anything, right?
Y-Yes...
Sayuri-san, I want to fuck you up.
Okay. I’d love to.
Wow.
Your butthole is also visible.
No! Not there!
First, I’ll put one in the pussy.
Then one in the asshole.
How does it feel?
Double penetration.
A little strange.
This’s the first time I’ve used my butt.
No!
Yes!
Next the asshole.
My butthole!
No...
My butthole feels good too!
My pussy, oh!
Yes! This feels great!
Akihiko-san, how will you punish me next?
Yes, Akihiko-san, your dick, put it in my butthole and shove it in deep.
Wow!
It's a completely different ecstasy than from my pussy!
This feels so great.
Anal... I could get used to this.
Yes!
My pussy feels great too!
Rougher!
Get in me harder!
This feels great!
Akihiko-san, I love you!
Harder... Love me harder!
This is amazing!
What is this?
This is a first...
I’m... I’m cumming already!
I thought you looked strange this morning.
How dare you monopolize Aki-kun!
I’ll return that question to you.
I’m merely being a good aunt to my beloved nephew!
Akihiko-san is not a toy – not the way you treat him.
What would an old bat like you understand?
Even an old bat has a right to love!
Right, Akihiko-san?
Aki-kun?!
Umm...
Just cut it out already!
Akihiko-kun suffers the most when you fight!
Won’t you consider his feelings?
Girls... thanks.
I understand that you all care about me.
I’m very flattered.
But...
From this point on, the four of us are living here together.
So don’t fight and let’s all live happily together.
Right?
He’s right.
Then, everyone...
Belongs to Akihiko-san.
Yes!
Aki-kun.
Please do me.
Akihiko-san, your dick... give me your dick.
Fujino-san, you’re great!
This feels so good.
Akihiko-san, wow! You feel so good.
Come in deeper.
Oh, my pussy is falling apart!
Yes, right there. Shizue-chan, very nice.
This feels great!
Yes, there.
Deeper, Aki-kun. Yes!
Yes, Aki-kun. I’m cumming.
Yes... yes...
Onee-sama, you’re squishing my nipples.
My nipples will fall off.
Yes. This feels great.
My hips are moving.
Oh no. Not there.
Akihiko-san!
Oh, yes!
Onee-sama, yes!
More...
Harder.
Aki-kun, harder!
No! More...
I’m home!
I need you, Aki-kun!
Oh dear, Akane.
Why are you back now?
She’s right – you’re in the way.
We have no room for little bitches here.
And so... Akane, sorry.
Wait, wait!
What are you doing with my Aki-kun?
What are we doing? We’re fucking.
We’re in love.
He doesn’t belong to you anymore.
Akihiko’s dick belongs to all of us now.
What are you saying?!
Aki-kun, say something!
I’ve gotten spoiled with multiple flavors.