I'm sure you're tired, so please let
me service you on this occasion.
Have you gotten used to life in this castle already?
It seems that other maids have shown
their rudeness one way or another.
But please forgive them.
There are only very few males here.
Not only that, but you're even the hero
that saved our Royal Highness.
She may be acting like that,
but Mistress Reaina is actually very happy to
have had such a wonderful knight as you.
So hard, and hot.
How wonderful.
Also,
it's very cute.
Does it feel good?
Just let it out if you want, no need to hold it in.
How is this?
Does it feel good?
You seem to have cum a lot.
Please forgive me.
Looks like I'm the one who could no longer restrain herself.
It's still so hard.
Now I feel like servicing it more.
I'll be taking your first time... okay?
It's...
in.
It's so hot, and so hard.
My goodness.
Please go ahead, I don't mind.
Oh wow.
You're always fondling that spot.
Don't!
Yes.
It feels great.
So deep!
It's... reverberating in me.
It's reverberating deeply in me!
It's so intense.
I'm cumming, I'm about to cum again.
It's bulging inside me.
Please, just do it all the way.
Cum inside me!
There, that spot.
Just continue pushing it.
Keep it up!
I'm cumming!
I just.
I just came.
Lots came out, I see.
I feel like my soul is also about to fall for you now.
Please, try to get along well with Mistress
Reaina and the others from now on.
However,
the dissidents that tried to take down His Royal Highness,
have also tried to kidnap Mistress Reaina.
At this time, his knight arrived and went into the fray,
and protected her.
Thank goodness.
It seemed like you'd never wake up.
I was worried.
I-It's not that I.
I-It's but a normal thing for royalty
to be worried about their subjects.
Making me worried like this.
I want you to take care of yourself better.
I wholeheartedly agree.
She never once slept while watching over you.
Do you have any idea what Mistress Reaina has gone through?
Diana!
It was indeed my fault that you became injured.
I just had no choice but to look after you.
That's right, I had no choice.
Well then, I shall take my leave.
B-Be grateful to me.
For it is I who have personally nursed you!
That's... not really what I want to say.
Well... it's just that,
you went that far just for me.
Thank you.
Thank goodness.
I'm glad that you're fine.
You've led me up to this point only to grant me shame?
What I'm saying is that I'm alright with it!
It can be quite intense, I see.
A kiss, I mean.
But,
it doesn't particularly feel bad, at all.
It hurts a bit when you fondle that vigorously.
No, not there!
It's not like I'm feeling good with it.
What are you trying to do?
Don't, stop!
Please stop!
No, that spot is.
Do not... rub it too much.
This is.
S-Stop.
My goodness!
So this is.
It looks like I win.
It's inside me now.
It hurts.
I'm alright.
Please, do it gently.
So hot.
You're fondling my breasts... too much.
And it is always at that spot.
Please don't.
I'm... fine.
I'm not really.
Oh no, why?
That just now,
Just wait!
So intense.
No!
It is so deep!
If you keep pushing deep like that.
Oh no.
Very intense.
No, no.
You're pushing too hard!
No, don't.
Umm.
Well.
Please don't tease me.
Move... please.
This is too intense!
It is alright, it no longer feels.
Oh no, this is!
It is really pushing hard.
Oh no, oh no... don't!
It feels so tight.
Really tight.
You came a lot, I see.
I never thought it would feel this hot.
Wait.
No!
It feels even deeper than earlier!
You just came, and yet!
No, stop!
Oh no, I'm about to cum.
No!
For you to be this rough on me.
My goodness.
Please, protect me always.
For you're my knight.