You must surely be rather exhausted.
Please allow me to service you.
Have you become accustomed
to your new life here?
The other maids might have come to you one after
another and treated you like a rare creature,
but please forgive their rudeness.
You're one of the few males here,
but you are also the hero who saved the King.
His daughter, Princess Reiana,
may seem indifferent to your presence,
but she is actually very glad
to have you in her service as well.
It's so hard and hot...
It is truly wonderful.
And it is also really cute.
Does it feel good?
Please hold nothing back
and cum whenever you desire.
How am I doing?
Does this please you?
It seems that you were
able to let out a lot.
Tsundere Princess.
Please forgive me.
It appears that I am the one
who can no longer restrain herself.
I am impressed that it is still this hard.
You make me want to service you further.
I will be taking your first time.
It's all... inside...
It's so hot and so hard!
Please do as you will with me!
Right there!
Please do not touch me there so much!
So good! That feels so very good!
It's so deep!
I can feel it!
I can feel it shaking my very insides!
This is so rough!
I am cumming! I am cumming again!
Inside me, so deep...
You can cum inside me like this!
Wait... That's it! Right there!
Let it out right there!
Please cum inside me!
You're cumming so much!
I... came...
You came a lot, didn't you?
I feel like I'm going to fall for you,
both body and soul.
Please do your best to take care
of Princess Reaina and the King.
However,
in a nefarious plot aimed to harm the King,
group of scoundrels attempted
to abduct Princess Reiana.
But before they could even
so much as touch a strand of her hair,
her Knight showed up and drove them off.
Thank goodness.
You were not showing any signs of awakening,
so I was beginning to worry.
B-But that's only because I'm royalty.
I must always have an open heart
for those who serve me.
Do you understand how
worried you have made me?
I really wish you would be more responsible.
I could not agree more.
You have made Princess Reiana nurse you
without even so much as a wink of sleep.
Diana!
I-It was only natural for me to nurse you when
you risked your life to save mine. I had no choice.
Yes, I had no choice.
Well then, I will be excusing myself.
Y-You should be thankful
that I nursed you back to health.
That's not what I meant to say...
Um, for rushing in to save me
without a second thought, I...
Thank you very much.
I am relieved to know that you are fine.
A-Are you attempting to embarrass me further
by making me push myself more than I already have?
I am saying that you have my permission!
Kisses are quite intense, aren't they?
But...
it's hardly a bad feeling, is it?
It hurts if you are that rough.
No, not there!
No, it does not feel as bad as...
What are you doing?!
No, stop!
I order you to stop!
No, that's... Don't be so rough!
This is...
No, I order you to stop!
Sheesh.
So this is...
It seems that I have come out on top.
It is inside me...
It hurts...
Do not worry about me.
Please move as you desire.
It's so hot!
Don't play with my breasts so much...
You keep touching me in the same place... Stop it!
There is nothing wrong. I mean it...
No... Why?
I just...
W-Wait!
You're being too rough! No!
You're so deep!
You're going so deep inside me!
Oh no, this is so intense!
This is too intense!
Sto...
Um...
So...
Don't be so mean! Keep moving!
Oh... It's so rough!
It feels so good! Oh, no!
I'm so happy!
Oh no, something's... no, stop!
Something's coming! I am going to cum!
You certainly came a lot.
There is so much of it.
I cannot believe how hot it is.
Wait just a minu...
No! You're even deeper than before!
Even though you just came...
No, don't!
No! No!
No! It's so intense! I'm cumming!
I cannot believe you were so rough with me.
Please continue protecting me from now on.
You are my one and only Knight.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
editor: fyurie
quality check: hyakupercent