I won't forgive you. I definitely won't!
I won't forgive you! Don't mess with me!
Y-You see... That's...
S-Sorry! I have nothing else to say but sorry.
So... sorry!
Stop apologizing and explain yourself.
Umm... what I want to say is...
I-I'm a man too so I also have some
interest in these, or something like that...
This is the worst.
What the hell is this? Isn't this way too much?
How did it turn out like this?
F-Forgive me for having these when I
already have you as my girlfriend, Saki!
That's not what I'm talking about!
I'm asking why does it have to be
like this? What's with this genre?
It's called S&M.
They're S&M genre magazines
and DVDs. That's what they are.
Do you like stuffs like these?
When you do it with, we always do it normally.
Well that's, you see...
I am just curious about these stuffs, or like...
So the truth is, you want to do stuffs like these?
Th-That's not it, Saki. I'm always
satisfied whenever we do it.
But when it  to erotica hobbies,
it's a separate thing...
Separate?!
I'm sorry! Forgive me for looking
at lewd stuffs when I have a girlfriend!
I'm really sorry!
Y-You can use this, right?
J-Just so you know, I'm doing this
so you won't get pent up
and end up doing something
that will cause trouble.
So don't get any wrong idea!
Just do it already!
Didn't you want to do stuffs like this?
T-Tie me up with that towel.
Just so you know, it's not like
I wanted to do this, okay?
S-Saki, it's fine, right?
I'm really going to tie you up, okay?
It's fine! Th-This is embarrassing enough,
so don't humiliate me further!
O-Okay.
Wow... Saki, you're the best!
He's more excited that usual.
So he really like this kind of stuffs.
I-I'll play along with your kink for today.
That's why... D-Do it to me while I'm tied like this.
You're beautiful, Saki.
Quit staring so much.
Then, I'm gonna put it in like this.
Just tell me if it hurts on
your wrists or down there.
If it hurts, I'll bear with it.
Isn't it bigger than usual?
I-It's reaching so deep inside me, what's happening?
Wh-What's this, I'm more sensitive than usual...
It feels so good that it's driving me nuts!
W-Wait!
Wow!
I-It's going inside!
I-It's going so deep inside.
What's happening? This is not like the usual!
I-I became very sensitive!
Oh no, I'm coming! No, I'm coming already!
I'm coming soon, it feels good!
I'm gonna get torn apart down
there. It's hot like it's melting,
I never felt this before!
Something hot is flowing in me!
It's pouring into me!
I have only been tied up on
my wrists, but it drove me nuts.
All from just getting tied up a little...
S&M... Just getting tied up gave
such a different stimulus.
I still feel the heat diffusing off me...
Maybe S&M is actually something incredible.
Tsun M !
Tightly tie me up and coach me
(Tsundere Masochist)
Tsun M! Tightly tie me up and coach me.
Good morning, sensei.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Yeah, good morning.
Sensei, good morning.
My name is Koike Saki.
Good morning
And this one is a teacher, Hamaoka Takeshi.
Sensei and I have a student-teacher
relationship in the same school.
And he is also the coach of
the swimming club where I belong.
Of course, as a teacher and student in the school,
and as I am a club president of the
swimming club and he's our coach,
we get along just a bit well enough.
Or that's how we try to be like.
This is our relationship inside the campus.
But Takeshi is so lost without me.
I'm home!
Welcome home. Dinner will be ready soon.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
Your cooking is so good that you
can brag about it on everyone.
Alright, dig in.
I'll help myself with these!
But you don't have to bother doing this
every day. Isn't it a burden for you?
But sensei, you'll just eat bread
or cup noodles if I don't cook for you.
Jeez, you can't do anything by yourself.
What's with that?
Doesn't it look like you're the teacher, and then I'm the no-good student?
Thanks for the meal!
I'm glad that you liked it.
Sorry for making you clean up after me.
It's fine, don't you have work to do?
Hey, Saki.
What's the matter?
It's about yesterday.
Well... I was just thinking if it's okay for us
to go on a little further than
last time. What do you think?
You're talking about 'that'...
Do you want to do those stuffs that much?
Oh... umm... well... yeah...
If you don't want it, then...
I understand. If you really want to do it...
Alright then, right there... Sit on the bed.
O-Okay...
It's alright, just relax.
Wh-What are you going to teach me? Jeez...
Why are you acting like a teacher
only at times like these?
That's because I'm a real teacher, you see.
Wh-What are you doing?
Just calm down.
Huh, wh-what's this?
It's called a 'blindfold play'.
So, this is a 'blindfold play'...
S-Sensei?
I'm looking at you... I'm just
looking at you and I got hard!
Stop! Don't stare at me!
Hey... where are you now?
Sensei, how about answering back to me?
I'm right here, Saki.
See, I'm right here.
Wh-What are you doing?
You're adorable, Saki!
Is this considered S&M as well?
S-Stop!
How about this?
No!
Aren't your nipples already erect?
You're so sensitive, Saki.
S-Somehow I became more sensitive
on certain parts because I can't see them.
It seems that you liked it.
I-I'm a little scared because
I couldn't see anything.
This is also a S&M play, you know? Let's proceed.
What's the meaning of this?!
You see, I brought some work home.
Just sit down and wait there.
Why did I have to be like this?
This is also an S&M play, you see.
Being gagged and then tied down...
You look so lewd down there, Saki!
What are you doing?
Sensei, what's with this?
I'm in the middle of work. Sorry, I can
only accompany you with my foot.
Wait... I said wait...
It feels good... down there...
What's happening?
It's so hot... I can't do this anymore...
Sensei... please!
It can't be helped.
Can you do this instead?
Come on, Saki.
That's it.
I'll be done here soon.
I don't know what's going on anymore, sensei!
I'm coming!
I feel like choking... down my throat!
Swallow all of it, Saki.
Swallow? All of it?
Did we overdo it? Good job on bearing with it.
D-Dumbass! I was scared as hell!
I'm sorry. We'll properly do it now from here.
S-Sensei, are we going to do it like this?
That's right, I'll put it inside just like this.
You're already this wet so it should go in easily.
Don't put it so suddenly!
Even though you just came.
It's so hot! Something very hot
and hard is hitting inside me.
It's really hot! Both your thing
and me down there are so hot and twitching!
I can't get enough of you pounding me
down there! No, I'm coming! I'm coming!
It's coming... It's coming, it feels good!
It feels so good... I want him
to ram it even deeper into me!
I-I'm gonna come already...
Why am I coming this quick... I can't,
I'm on the verge of coming already...
Incredible! It just keeps on poking deep inside me!
It feels like I'm getting scraped inside!
Don't you want me to come, Saki?
I'll spray it on you with all my might,
so you should come! Make
yourself feel good as well!
Wow, I became very sensitive!
Is it because I'm tied down? Am I feeling
it more because I restrained?
I'm coming! Shoot it out, shoot it!
Pour it all out and make me come!
I'm coming!
S-Sensei, you also came, right?
It felt good for you too, right?
Of course I did.
I came, and it's better than anything else before.
Sensei...
I knew that I really love you.
Alright, do your warm-up exercises properly.
We can't have you getting
leg cramps and injuring yourselves.
Okay, we got it! Thanks for the concern as always.
Sensei, you're always passionate.
You're an amazing teacher.
Wh-What are you saying...
You're kind, young and cool as well!
Do you have a girlfriend? You have one, right?
Enough of that and go practicing now.
Ah, he dodged the question.
Oh, could it be that there's a girl
in this school that you like...
Hey there, the practice is starting.
S-Sorry!
See you later, sensei.
Here is today's training menu.
Oh, thank you—
What's wrong?
Nothing... Thank you.
There's a lot of issues like school responsibilities.
I can't just say something like
'My girlfriend is enrolled here.'
Saki!
What's up with that earlier?
You look so enticed and happy.
I bet you're cheating on me.
No... What do you mean 'cheating'?
How did you end up with that?
I was just talking to them like a teacher would.
Trying to make an excuse for
those flaring nostrils earlier?
Well, sorry for not being an honest and good girl.
Huh?!
I'm a bad student, right?
I do all sorts of things. May it be barging
in the male locker room or anything,
I can do all of those!
Saki, you're acting weird...
Saki, come here.
Huh? Wait... sensei?
I-It ended up to something like this, after all.
You have to tie me up like this...
There will be a public outrage
if we get caught with this.
News will spread about
a teacher raping his student.
Did you come here wanting to be raped?
Of course not!
Of course. But you want to be tied up, right?
You even brought something like this.
What are you talking about? Aren't
you the one who wants me tied up?
You always talk your way out towards
your own convenience, sensei.
Well then, just let me do as I please.
No!
Is your body feeling cold? Your
nipples are hiding underneath.
S-Sensei, not there!
S-Sensei...
Looks like you're getting in a good mood now.
D-Did you somehow become good at this?
Don't tell me that you're cheating on me!
That's not the case. I can do this
on nobody else but you, Saki.
You see, I've been studying ways to please you.
Wh-When you say it straightforward like that,
it's hard for me to feel flattered.
What's with that lewd reply?
Just stay still, I'll put it in just like this...
Eh... Eh, wait—
No... This is really bad, I can't stop my voice...
Wait! I said wait...
If we get caught, it will be the end for both of us!
Wh-What?
Since you took the effort to bring
this, I have to tie you up.
T-Tie me up... Does doing that
amount to something?
Is somebody there?
Ah... Sorry. It's me, Hamaoka.
I'm using the shower.
Oh... What's happening?
Oh, is that you, Hamaoka-sensei?
Sorry for disturbing you.
Nah... Same here, I just got it.
Is that so?
He grew even bigger!
I see. I wanted to ask you a favor.
Wait... Why are you moving?
I'll be taking a bit longer though.
I see...
Alright then.
Sensei, you idiot! My voice will leak out!
I'll just try to get someone else. Pardon my intrusion.
I-If you keep tightening up the rope...
I understand.
Take your time.
This is bad. It feels good when you thrust slowly like this.
Just let me know when you're done.
My voice will leak out!
Sorry, I'll try to get done here as soon as I can.
No! This is bad... Sensei...
It's coming in!
You're an idiot! Why did you do that?
If that teacher found us out, we won't
be able to go back in this school!
But it felt good, right?
What are you talking about?
Stop messing around.
There's no way I can hold myself
back from this anymore!
Then, let's stop holding ourselves back.
Let's both just do what we
want. That would be the best.
Alright, I get it already
so hurry up and give it to me!
Or else that teacher will
already be back here, so hurry!
I'm coming already. It feels good, I can't stop!
I'm getting stirred and it's like melting down there!
Oh no, I think I'm coming already!
If you squeeze me that tight down
there, I'm gonna come, Saki!
Shoot it all in, shoot it with all your might!
I'm coming... Make me come, sensei!
Come... Constrict me with all your strength!
I'm gonna come too, so shoot it in as well!
Ejaculate!
That felt good... even when it's painful... why?
...and it will be like this.
This will be in your exams.
Make sure to review these, understood?
I got home very late tonight.
I'm sure Saki is angry again.
S-Saki?!
Sensei... do it more... Tease me more!
It feels good!
More on my clitoris.
Sensei, more... Tighten it up even more!
Sensei... I'm already soaking wet!
I'm gonna come... It feels so good!
Sensei, sensei... More... more!
S-Since when did you—
Well... I was watching the whole time.
S-Sensei, this is... not like—
Does this feel good?
Saki!
More...
Do it harder...
Saki?
B-Being tied up might feel better...
What did you just say?!
I-Idiot! Don't make me say it again.
Thank you, Saki! Seems like
you turned over a new leaf.
It's your fault that I became a pervert.
Thank you for listening to me.
Enough of thanking me... Do it already.
I'm telling you to tie me up properly!
Idiot!
Well, it's your first time. I think having sex
while you're bound in your swimsuit is fine.
Idiot! Doing this naked is embarrassing!
This is amazing somehow. The rope
is digging into me so tightly.
It hurts a little, but I'm starting to feel hot.
You're gorgeous, Saki.
Sensei...
Try to put it in by yourself.
S-Sensei... I can't put it in
properly when I'm like this!
Come on, Saki!
Even if you say that...
Th-This is amazing, you're so tight inside!
No way! It's because I'm tied up
that my clitoris became so sensitive...
You just had it in a moment ago.
It's coming... I feels so good.
Something hot is coming in... and reverberating!
My clitoris feels so hot and it's
getting squeezed... It feels good!
Oh no, I'm coming! I'll end up sopping wet.
Sensei, the cord tightens down
there whenever you move!
I already came but I'm gonna come again!
When I'm thinking of you, I can come
no matter how many times!
Saki...
You're doing good down there too.
You're reaching so deep up to my womb!
I'm coming again. It feels good. I'm coming!
Come. We'll do it together this time, Saki!
Shoot it out! Shoot everything out!
I'm coming as well. My womb
can't take it anymore!
I can't stop myself too, Saki!
You're going deep inside me.
The pleasure won't stop!
Good... It felt good, sensei.
I knew that it feels so good
when you do this to me.
I want us to do it like this from now on!
Of course.
I'll do this to you from now on
even if you hated it, Saki.
Yeah... That's a promise, sensei.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization