Auditions for Confined and Tortured Females
This Week's Bargain Marina
Turn it off! Turn it off!
Someone! Someone!
Enjoy the rest after joining. Click
H-How did things end up like this?
What happened?
Professor.
M-Ms. Ozawa.
Professor, this is definitely Marina, right?
l'm pretty sure it's her. Marina has been acting kind of weird.
Weird? How?
l can tell something's wrong by looking at these pictures.
But hold on a minute.
l'm getting all confused now.
l first noticed there was something wrong with her about six months ago.
l believe it was during phys ed class...
What's wrong?
You know, you should shave your armpits.
Since you're beautiful, Marina.
What? Why?
Why?
Well, it's just...
Honestly, l didn't know what Marina was thinking.
lf Marina is the kind of girl who does indecent things...
She didn't even come to you.
But she's not that kind of girl.
You're right. Ms. Horiguchi wouldn't do such slutty things.
That's why l came to see you.
You're her and the handicraft club's advisor, so you know her well.
Now, about all this...
l won't tell anyone. l know.
l wonder what it is with that adult site...
l can't believe Marina Horiguchi is on that site...
Ms. Horiguchi.
Ms. Horiguchi?
Oh, Professor, what's up?
How are you doing?
Never mind that, do you know the latest rumor?
The urban-legend rumor of the Kyosai line.
Urban legend?
There's a dreadful pervert...
...on the sixth car of the 6:40 upbound Kyosai train.
A pervert?
The women who encountered the pervert have all disappeared.
Disappeared?
Well, where did they go?
l don't know.
After all, it's just talk.
Just talk...
Speaking of which, Ms. Horiguchi, you take the Kyosai line here, right?
Yes, l take it every day.
Do you see any perverts?
Perverts? l don't see any.
The people on that train are all good people.
How can you be so sure?
Say, Ms. Horiguchi, don't you need to answer your phone?
Ms. Horiguchi.
Professor, l have to go now.
What's the matter with her?
Where is she going?
This is a Kyosai-line station.
ls she waiting for someone?
Hey, look at that.
What's going on?
Who are those men?
That's good.
You want me to stick it inside?
No!
Stop!
Be sure to get her on video.
Be quiet!
Go! Go!
There...
There.
Yes!
She doesn't know how to control herself.
Here.
P-Please forgive me.
But l'll feel you up real good.
No more.
Forgive me!
How horrible!
Hey, you shouldn't interfere.
W-Who are you supposed to be?
l should be asking you the same thing.
l'm her professor. Ms. Horiguchi's advisor.
Oh, her professor. l see.
And what business do you have with her?
What business? My student is getting harassed by perverts.
l'm here to help her of course.
Well, it's not like that...
What's not?
Studio Z representative director...
What's this business card for?
Jeez...
To tell the truth, we're involved in guerilla shoots for adult videos...
...and we have many reasons for this. Can l ask you to forget this matter?
What are you talking about?
l can't just let this go. l'm taking back my student.
Well then, we have some tricks up our sleeves, you know.
Ms. Horiguchi, are you okay?
Professor...
You're all right now.
Professor, they did lots of dirty things to me...
Things can't go back to normal.
Don't worry. You'll be fine.
Professor, you're beautiful.
So what?
Professor, have you ever done it till you were about to die?
We're pros, you see.
We get women and make them feel good.
l guess you can say we're angels.
Who are you people?
What's the meaning of this?
l think you should let us make you feel comfortable.
Professor, run!
Please stop!
This was unexpected, but that's okay.
We have plenty of time.
l simply want a taste of her body.
Professor, Ranko is also known as a ladykiller.
Give her 30 minutes and she'll make any frigid woman feel good.
Well, we can't stay with you that long today, but...
...just enjoy the show.
Looks like you need to let it out.
She'll be feeling good in no time.
What's going on? Can l let this kind of thing happen?
Now, let's take a look at your private area.
Take a look at those bristles. lt's growing everywhere.
Professor, you should take good care of it.
Do you want us to take care of it for you?
Professor, there's no need to hold back.
l-l must be dreaming... l-l can't believe this is happening inside a train...
A shameful act like this...
We're getting a bit more serious now.
How about l peel this back and rub it directly?
There. l'm going to play with it.
lt's okay, Professor. You're feeling good, right?
No... Not there...
Now, let's do a little more, Marina.
No!
There!
lt's beautiful...
Professor, you must be feeling good.
So much white, sticky stuff came out.
N-Not here...
No, l'm coming... l'm going to climax!
Well, Professor, we're going to take good care of Marina.
Oh, why don't we take a commemorative photo?
Auditions for Confined and Tortured Females
This Week's Bargain Shiori
Would you like to ride the Kyosai line?