Sarah Scorpion. The infamous knight and leader
of the pirate crew known as the Scorpions.
Standing in her way is the knight Silver Sylia.
Sarah captures Syha and turns her over
to Duke Joachim of Blankenheim
in return for information about the
whereabouts of the Sword of Bernstein,
an artifact which is said to govern the fate of the galaxy.
Learning the sword is in the hands of Baron Gielen,
Sarah infiltrates his home on the planet Carib.
However, she soon finds herself in a trap concocted by the
Duke, who is secretly in league with the Gielen family.
Baron Gielen's knows that Sarah is the last of the Bernstein bloodline,
and that she is therefore the only person who can use the sword's power.
Overcome with fear, Sarah is swiftly subdued
and plunged into a world of humiliation.
Marking the beginning of what is to
become an ever more dire situation...
Good to see you again, Duke of Blankenheim.
Welcome to our abode.
I just came to check on the ripeness of the wine I left with you.
Not yet, I imagine. Good wine takes time.
Is there any danger of Sarah's crew breaking her out?
No danger. Her crewmen have gone far away.
Meanin ...?
Beyond the moon... Yup!
Good. Then we're ready.
Are you sure about Sylia?
Letting her walk freely around the castle. It seems unsafe.
Rest easy. It's all under control.
I can't say I'm happy to be seen like this.
Likewise. Fate has dealt us both a cruel hand.
Sylia, let's work together. We could escape.
I've been thinking about that. Together, we might stand a chance.
But...
Not again!
Sylia?
The Duke put this on me...
Every few minutes, it vibrates.
Sylia, your body...
Please, don't stare.
I'm no longer a normal woman.
Come on. Silver Sylia doesn't give up so easily!
I should rest. I need my strength for today's "taming".
Oh... All right.
"Taming"? What have they planned for us?
Space Pirates - Sara
Vol. 02 Masochist Prisoner Knights
You're getting lots of attention in that swimsuit.
This is no better than parading around naked. Worse, in fact.
Don't hide yourself. Show these fine folks what you've got.
Okay, okay...
What?
What? I'm just giving you some oil so you don't burn.
Oilr? Where do you think you're touching?
Cool, let me help.
S-Stop. Cut it out! No!
Get your filthy feet off me!
Time to entertain the tourists.
It's showtime!
Huh?
You're going to humiliate me in front of all these people?
Hey, everyone! This is Space Pirate Sarah!
Former noble turned marauder!
Why treat me like this? Why this mockery?
What's that? You want to suck a cock?
Come on! I said "mockery" not "cockery"!
These people are subjects of His Excellency the Baron.
You better not resist.
Got it, pirate bitch?
All right, whatever.
Huh? No, you have to ask for it nicely.
Please... Please use me as your cock polisher.
All right, then. Suck it up.
No biting!
Just get it over with...
I'll take some hand love while you're at it.
And I'll take some foot love.
Are you satisfied?
You're kidding, right? We're just getting started.
No way...
Titty fuck! Let me cum between those huge tits.
Oh, God... It's hot! Don't rub so hard!
How can this be? Even after cumming...
...their cocks just get harder and thicker...
Please, no more.
My face, my mouth, my tits... They're all so sticky!
Please, stop!
I can't take any more...
Huh?
Boss... Hey, Boss!
Hans? Is that you?
I'm contacting you directly through your brain waves.
Hans, where have you been?
Sorry for the delay. After your capture, we escaped through the sewer.
How did you get out?
They only wanted you, I guess. They didn't even chase us.
You weren't so lucky, apparently.
They're treating me like a walking sperm bank.
Boss, I'm sending you a video.
What's this?
Gielen's tower. I've located it.
The Sword of Bernstein's somewhere in there.
Wait! Don't, Hans!
What?
The security in that tower is tight. You shouldn't rush into anything.
Yeah, I know.
Find a safe place to hide for now.
What's your plan?
You have to gradually sabotage the tower's defenses,
a little each night They won't suspect a thing.
That will take time. Can you last long enough?
I'm the renowned leader of the Scorpions. I can last.
All right. I'll pull back. We'll start tomorrow night.
I have to cut this short. They might be listening in.
Roger that. Get it done, Hans.
Be strong, Boss.
Just you wait Karin and Cecil. This isn't over yet!
What? I'm supposed to fuck an iguana?
That lizard is going to throw her around like a ragdoll.
Don't worry. He never eats people. I trained him not to.
Oh, God!
Let me go! Let go of me right now!
No!
Sarah...
No... It's too big!
It'll never fit!
Stop! Stop!
Just like animals in a zoo. Fucking in front of everyone.
Careful, Mr. Lizard! Don't break your lizard girlfriend.
I'm... not a lizard!
He's pounding my uterus. I'm going to burst!
Looks like she's matching his rhythm. Dirty lizard whore!
Mr. Lizard's enjoying himself, I think.
Oh, no... He's going to cum... inside me?
God! It's so much!
He cums pretty hard.
Take it all in, Lizard Girl.
I can!t... I can't...
Blast off!
Sarah...
We've just begun. Mr. Lizard has more where that came from.
He's going to blast you with his cum all night long.
How long can this continue?
Don't you... ever... get tired?
The nobles... They enjoy watching this kind of abuse?
Oh... treating me nice now?
That's right. You're more humane than those nobles, aren't your?
Okay, I'll be your lizard woman.
Yes! Fuck me as hard as you like.
Now you're being greedy. Do you like it that much?
Go a little slower.
The lizard girl is enjoying herself again.
Go easy on my boobs!
Oh, God!
Good... I love your big, scaly cock.
What's the matter, Duke? Feeling inadequate?
Fucking lizard bitch!
Get an eyeful, Duke. Look how much fun we're having.
Good, good! Mate with me! Fuck me harder!
I've never had it so good. Lizard cock is the best!
You're so much better than the fat, old human watching us over there.
You aristocratic whore.
You're lower than a beast, Sarah!
Good! My pussy is all yours!
Let's cum together!
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
That was much better than the Duke's tiny dick could ever be.
Damn you, pirate. You'll pay for this outrage!
I won't forget about this.
He was pissed.
Very clever, Sarah-Oneesama. This isn't over though.
What do we do now?
We punish her for this farce.
Even in such humiliation, you somehow kept your pride.
Sarah, well done.
Boss?
Onee-sama? Sarah-Oneesama?
Sarah...
Sylia? Why...?
Sylia-Oneesama's hard prick needs your attention.
You're being punished for what you did to the Duke. Understand?
No, Sarah. You don't have to...
All right, I'll do it... if it'll mean ending this stupidity.
Please, don't stare.
It's so strange, isn't it? Having this thing on a woman's body.
So big and hard... You're naughty, Sylia.
I never thought another woman's breasts could feel so good.
Control yourself. A knight like you shouldn't
be turned on by such base temptations.
I know. I don't want to like it, but...
Don't... lick it!
Wow. Onee-sama seems to like sex a lot, huh?
Sylia-Oneesama looks happy, too.
"Happy"? Is that what you think?
You're getting even harder, Sylia.
Don't say that! It's embarrassing...
This needs a good polishing.
It's your precious cock after all.
What's gotten into you?
Do you like being ordered around by these brats?
Shut up and enjoy your blowjob.
Stop it!
Look, it's throbbing. You must be ready to cum.
Please, leave me alone. I'm going to... cum!
Fine. Go ahead. Let loose all your dirty semen.
What a smell! Stronger than a man's cum, even.
But wait, there's more!
Breasts, mouth... and now Sarah's vagina.
What is this?
It's a contest.
A contest?
The first to cum, loses.
Sounds fun, doesn't it?
Fun for who?
Sylia-Oneesama, you're getting erect again. I guess you're ready.
No, stop!
It's huge!
Sylia-Oneesama, try moving your hips.
So hot. This feeling... This is a woman's...
Don't Sylia. Don't give in to them!
Didn't you just cum? Why are you pushing so hard?
I'm sorry. It's just... I can't stop!
How's it feel to lose your virginity, Sylia-Oneesama?
Treat the rookie nice.
Shut up!
Sylia, slow down. Be gentle.
Is my pussy really so good?
It's so nice... Our bodies rubbing together.
No... if you keep fucking me... I'll...
Fuck... Sarah... Sarah!
Wait... Settle down!
Me? What about your?
You're getting wetter and wetter!
You're the one who was ready for round
two less than a minute after cumming!
God... Your pussy is so tight!
Well, they seem to be getting along now.
I guess they forgot about the competition, too.
It's time for punishment!
I have a good idea.
Oh... Fascinating.
Sarah-Oneesama, I'm putting this in your ass.
Wh-What!?
One for you too, Sylia-Oneesama.
My ass?
What was that?
It's an electric dildo.
It'll open your ass up permanently.
Just press the button, and...
I'm cumming!
My cum is gushing inside!
Look at them twitch! Science is fun!
Let's increase the voltage and really open them up.
Turn it off!
I'm... still... cumming!
What a sight. I can't help but laugh.
I can't take any more... please!
Now, full power! Your ass will be destroyed.
No, don't!
Oops. We messed them up pretty bad, I guess.
It's about time.
Wh-What?
Sarah!
Something's coming out of me!
No! Not Sarah, too!
What? What is this?
I have a cock!?
Oh, it's big. The experiment is a success!
How do you like it? Our gift to you!
No... No! This can't be!
No! No!
No!!