Shit, where is she?
Don't lose me, boys.
I'm quite a catch.
How did she...
Let's not cause a ruckus here in the city. It'd be rude.
What the...
Don't you fools know? Only a knight can beat a knight.
It's really her!
The knight among pirates... Sarah Scorpion!?
Thanks. You've saved me the trouble of introducing myself.
Finally, here comes a worthy challenger.
S-Sylia-sama!
Stand back. Your weapons won't hurt her.
Sylia Von Bernstein, AKA Silver Sylia.
You appear to be as strong as they say.
En garde!
You followed me here, didn't you!?
Tell me Sarah, what's your plan?
I came for you, Sylia.
What?
A battleship?
Always a step ahead.
That's how we pirates roll, tin woman.
A cannon!
Let's get outta here!
You fool.
If it fires in this direction,
the whole town will be destroyed!
That's right. Unless you want to do something about it.
Stop this!
You're quite the specimen, Silver Sylia.
Sarah, you coward!
Hang in there, or this town will have itself a new swimming pool.
Stupid Sylia. Why risk your own life like this?
Must... block the attack... and buy time for the people to escape.
Such foolishness. Your efforts are wasted.
That was reckless, boss. We don't need her dead.
Hans, any word on Sylia's soldiers?
They're long gone. The cowards ran away.
I see.
Space Pirates - Sara
Vol. 01 The Gielen Twins
What are you doing?
Well, look at that. In this light, she's almost sexy.
Let's get this outta the way.
Do you always do this with prisoners? At least act noble!
Aww, the knight is sad she lost to some pirates.
You sacrificed your own body to save the town.
Very heroic of you, Silver Sylia-sama.
I know we're enemies, but this is disgraceful.
Have you no shame?
Shut your mouth.
I heard she tried to stop the blast with
only an energy shield. What an idiot.
Well, nobody said knights were very smart.
Let's get this party under way. How much can you take?
I saved those people... and this is how I end up?
You don't get it. You're no longer a knight.
You're a slave... A plaything for our father and for us!
Slave? Plaything?
However your body's too nice just to play with...
That hurts!
What hurts?
My chest... My chest hurts!
Could you be more specific?
My nipple! You're hurting my nipple!
In that case...
Let me give you a massage.
What?
What is this?
Electro-massage.
Want some more?
What are you doing to me?
Oh no. My body's getting hot... with desire!
What? The knight likes being massaged?
That's...
But look how wet you are.
Get that out of my face!
Now, repeat after me.
What?
What is this?
These prods are capable of quite a zap.
Oh, God...
Come on, beg for us.
Say it already!
I'm... Sylia... the dirty slave knight.
I like the electro-massage. It makes my... pus...
Pussy!
...makes my pussy so wet!
A little more.
My tits, my ass, my pussy...
Use them as you like.
Please rape my naked body.
Very good.
Please... Please take the prods off me.
There's just one more thing we have to do.
Maximum power!
No woman's ever withstood so much.
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Stop it... You'll make... You'll make it come out!
Go ahead. Show us what you can do.
No!
Please look away!
It's coming! It's coming!
It's coming!
Well done, taking Silver Sylia alive.
I expected no less from Sarah Scorpion.
Thank you. Where is she now?
My sons are welcoming her right now.
"Welcome" might not be the right verb...
So, she's being drowned in cum, then?
What? Is there a problem?
No, sir. Now, about my reward...
Of course. The Sword of Bernstein, wasn't it?
Yes.
It would appear that Baron Von Gielen currently-has the Sword.
Baron Von Gielen? Why does he have it?
It's a thing of apparent importance to him.
He keeps it locked in a tower.
There's more information on this data unit.
Take it with you.
Thank you, sir.
Sir?
I hold your ability in the highest esteem.
Would you consider joining my command?
If it is your desire, I could even use my
authority to make you a noblewoman.
That's generous...
However if I were you, I'd keep my fat hands to myself.
What!?
Not another move.
What is this?
My apologies, sir. But I can't make any such commitment.
It's not my way.
Impudent pirate bitch!
That bitch!
We haven't seen her in years.
Ten years, maybe. She's grown.
- Several Weeks Later -
- Planet Carib -
Damn, I thought Carib was a resort planet.
This sewer ain't exactly the scenery I imagined.
Come on. Did you think the royals would just let us in?
Whatever. I'll deal with a little dankness
for the treasure we're gonna score.
So far, the intel from the Duke has been accurate.
It's quiet. Too quiet.
Now you're the one complaining.
Hans is itching for a fight. God help us.
Where are we?
Looks like the castle's central aqueduct.
Everyone, freeze!
Security droids!
An ambush?
Look sharp, guys!
Son of a bitch!
There's no end.
Too many... We're surrounded!
Most people would have entered through the front door.
Welcome to our castle.
Greetings!
Kids?
What? It can't be...
I'm Karin Gielen.
And I'm Cecil Gielen.
Gielen? So these kids are in charge~
Boss?
It's impossible. They haven't even aged since...
Goodness.
Sorry, Onee-sama.
It's been ten years. We have catching up to do.
All this fire... You really overdid it.
Even the cows, chickens and pigs... burnt to a crisp.
At least we got what we came for.
I'll never forget that sight.
They killed my family and stole the Sword of Bernstein.
It's definitely them.
Finally awake, Sarah-Oneesama?
We barely even zapped you, yet you fainted.
You two!
You don't scare us.
That's...
Without the sword, your skills as a knight are meaningless.
We've been searching for you, Sarah Scorpion.
Or should I call you Sarah Bernstein-Oneesama?
We didn't know the sword could only be
used by one of the Bernsteih bloodline.
S-Stop!
Did you know? Bernstein is the oldest noble bloodline in the galaxy.
He who holds that sword is destined for the Imperial Throne.
Her nipples are soft and spongy.
Don't...
We've found your sensitive spot.
Don't do that.
These are special nipples aren't they?
Indeed. So big, each one is almost like a penis.
Dammit! These brats are making my nipples erect.
You seem to be enjoying it. Pervert, have you no shame?
Who says. I... like it?
This planet is a vacation spot for lots of nobles.
A place where they can forget their worries,
so let's put our past behind us... and be friends.
But first, be nice to your crew.
You're all right?
What's wrong?
Boss, you've deceived us.
You've put us in danger to get the sword for yourself.
It's not like that.
And now we find out that you're a noble!
You've got some explaining to do.
Onee-sama, you lied to your friends?
This calls for some punishment.
Having your tits massaged while we do all the work!
We never thought we were working for some kind of whore.
What's the meaning of this?
Don't just rape her. Each of you must ejaculate three times.
Anyone who doesn't will die.
What!?
Please understand, boss.
Our lives depend on it.
No! No!
Let go! Let me go right now!
Don't resist.
Stop it!
Boss's bosoms! Unbelievable.
Open her legs.
Guys, please...
These are in the way.
Nice panties you're wearing, boss.
Please, don't...
Show me that pussy!
Her crew are a lively bunch.
Onee-sama's body might not survive this.
Look at her huge titties!
Her pussy is looking good, too.
Let me go, dammit!
Make me cum, boss.
Shame on you! Treating a woman like this!
Shut up.
Like you've said before, we don't tolerate traitors.
Here we go.
Ow! I'm not wet enough... Slow down!
Damn, she's nice.
Stop it! You're too rough!
Ain't that a sexy voice. Are you in heat?
No, that's...
But her pussy is getting wet. Dripping wet!
No, don't talk like that...
No!
If she enjoys it, it's not punishment.
True. Maybe we should say five times, instead of three.
Hurry up!
Just cum anywhere!
No, wait a minute!
No!
Don't worry, I'll be quick.
Wait not inside me. Anywhere but inside me! Please!
You did it! You actually came inside!
No!
Okay. I'm next.
Again?
What? Your nipples ain't gonna get any harder.
Stop!
Gotta speed this up. I'll take the mouth.
That's a good idea.
My body can't take this. They're going to make a mess of me!
Incredible. She's going to service them with her whole body.
It would seem the slut's enjoying her own rape.
She's running on fumes.
No surprise, I guess. We've been at it all afternoon.
No more, please...
We're not done yet.
Please, let me rest, just a little...
Look at that! Boss' jugs are leakin'!
Please, don't look.
Are you knocked up already?
It's just something that happens to me.
So sexual pleasure causes her to lactate.
What a dirty cow!
It's time to get some backdoor action.
No, leave the backdoor alone!
Quiet!
Nice and tight!
Is this really necessary?
I need to bust off one more.
It's rude to fuck someone in the ass without permission.
I think she likes to be abused.
She must be a real thrill seeker.
No... No... No more..
No! Stop, I don't wait any more!
Don't squeeze my breasts at a time like this!
Shit, this is good!
Same here!
Please stop! I don't want any more.
Gentlemen, fill her holes with your sperm.
Oh, God! My pussy! My ass!
Cover her from head to toe.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
Oh, God!
You think she'll be our friend now?
Not yet, Cecil. We have to play with her more first.
Oh, God...
We meet again, pirate wench.
You!
Hope I'm not too late to join the party.
Am I?