Our heroines, Sarah Scorpion and Silver Sylia
undergo continued sexual humiliation
as prisoners of the House of Gielen.
Sylia, with her body now perverted by the
Gielen twins' 'futanari conversion",
loses hope, and her pride, as she suffers constant indignity.
Sarah faces equally dire straits as she is gang-raped on a public beach
and then ravaged at length by a wild lizard man while a crowd looks on.
Adding to insult, Sarah's body is also given the futanari conversion.
In spite of all this, Sarah maintains a faint, hidden glimmer of hope...
Tihanks for the treasure. You've been ever so generous.
Somebody help!
Look at you... You're a pathetic excuse for a noble!
You look exhausted. We're just getting started, though.
Onee-sama's not looking so good.
She doesn't even look like a pirate.
Space Pirates - Sara
Vol. 03 Orgy of the Futanari Knights
No... Stop it, you two.
Don't worry.  It's your first time, so we'll gentle.
Wow, look how big it is.
She's well endowed. Both upstairs and downstairs.
Maybe there's a correlation.
Don't talk about me like that.
Sarah...
See that? It's throbbing. Begging to be touched.
No!
Embarrassed? We'll teach your cock a lesson in pleasure.
Don't bite!
Please, not there!
I can't believe how sensitive my penis is, it's unbearable!
Well? How's your first cross-gender experience?
You like it?
How can I possibly like...
You shouldn't lie.
It feels so good to have my huge dick stroked.
Being rubbed feels ecstatic, doesn't it?
I said no. Not with this fake dick.
She's stubborn.
Well then. Why don't we ask Sylia-Oneesama for some assistance?
I can't do this. Let me go!
Settle down. You've been on the receiving end.
Now it's your turn to fuck Sylia-Oneesama's pussy.
Wait... No!
Stop!
Sylia, I'm sorry.
Sylia... Sylia!
Sarah, that's.... too hard!
But it's... so good... I can't stop!
Your pussy feels so good!
Push against me, Sylia!
Sarah-Oneesama is finally enjoying herself.
Impressive hip action. You think Sylia-Oneesama will be okay?
So big... Sarah, your cock is going so deep!
It's a tight fit. My cock is a perfect fit for your pussy.
Sarah, I want you to cum inside me.
Your pussy is the greatest!
I'm sorry Sylia, I'm going to cum inside.
I'm going fill you with my sperm!
What a big load of semen.
You said it. Onee-sama's a mess.
Shall I help you undress?
What are you...?
I got a little excited watching you two go at it.
Yeah. This time, I think you'll go at it with us.
Are you implying that we're not finished?
I'm going to take it all in.
Stop this...
You're aggressive, fucking me from below like that.
I'm not... doing anything!
Onee-sama, your cock... It's getting bigger inside me.
But I'm not...
Your dick is big again, Onee-sama. So thick and manly!
Don't call me "manly".
NO? You're pounding my pussy though. Very manly indeed.
Stop! I refuse to enjoy this... this farce!
I feel something leaking out.
I see... You're getting ready to cum.
I'm not! I can't!
But, Onee-sama. This part of you says otherwise.
See?
Amazing!
Your cock is as hard as ever.
You're sopping wet.
Do you like my pussy that much?
I don't... I don't like...
Your hand?! No!
Stop it... You'll stretch me out!
Hey that's a good idea. I'll get my fingers wet, too.
My pussy... You're wrecking it!
I can feel it. Your dick is about to explode.
And when I put my fingers in you, your
pussy grips them as if they were a dick.
How's that? It's getting tighter and tighter.
Want to shoot a big, thick load?
I've had enough. My pussy is tired.
I can't possibly cum anymore!
Hey. Boss, can you hear me?
Hans? Where are you?
I've reached the fourth floor of the tower Just a bit further.
You sound out of breath. What happened?
Oh that? It's nothing major.
It was just the security surrounding the sword.
There was quite a welcoming party.
However I'm thirsty. All this ass-kicking is hard work.
When this is over and I'm the head of the Bernstein House, we'll drink.
It'll be my treat.
Hans?
Wait. Something's wrong.
Security droids?
No. Something else.
So the rumors are true.
What do you mean?
A machine with the fighting skills of a knight.
It's the result of a cutting-edge AI experiment.
You'd better fall back.
I've been waiting for this chance for a long time.
Since ten years ago, when I saved you from that fire.
I've been waiting for this chance...
to test my skills. Not as a pirate, but as a knight.
Sorry boss. Ending transmission.
No, Hans!
I'm always part of the clean-up crew...
Never the hero.
Now, however, I get to face a real opponent.
They call me Hans Biilow!
Prepare to die!
Hans!
What's wrong?
Who are you talking to? Are you hallucinating?
Sarah-Oneesama, I hope you're ready for work.
Work?
I can't believe they're all seeing me like this.
This is what you get for embarrassing
the Duke at his party the other day.
Now you'll both apologize with your bodies.
Oh, God...
Their dicks are at critical mass.
Perhaps they actually enjoy this performance.
Quit fooling around! Haven't you embarrassed us enough?
Cease this farce immediately!
All right if you're sure you're ready for the next stage.
This is...
What? What is this?
The spectacle begins.
Don't touch me like that in front of everyone!
Actually, this is a mere game.
If your dicks shoot enough cum, we'll reward you with treasure.
Ladies, have you no shame?
We're women, just like you!
How rude. You're nothing like us.
You're toys for the nobility.
Filthy pigs, nothing more.
No...
Please, stop. I can't take all of this stimulation!
I beg you, take the ring off my penis.
Please!
Stop complaining. You can hold it, can't you?
Please... I want to ejaculate!
This can't be good for my health.
What is it you want to "ejaculate", then?
Don't... Don't make me say it.
If you say it, I'll make you feel good.
I want to cum! I want to shoot lots of cock sauce!
Not yet. You need to save up for a chain orgasm.
Chain? Wait a minute!
Your pussy is so wet, it's drooling.
I can't take it! I'm gonna burst!
Let's give these big, stiff nipples a pinch.
Well? Will you beg us?
Let me cum... Please!
Nope. Hold it a little longer.
I can't stand it!
I need to let loose a huge load!
My cock... My cock is...
Me too! Please, let me cum. Let me cum!
Louder. Say it with a voice as big as your penis.
Oh God, my cock is going to explode!
I'm getting close! I want to cum so badly!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's coming out! It's spraying all over my own face...
It's hot...
So good...
Hot cum is all over my face!
But wait, there's more.
The party is just getting started.
No way... Wait! I can't...
Poor knights.
Our party friends are really getting into it.
S-Stop it! I need a break!
Chain orgasm!
I Rapid-fire cockwhore cumshots, huh?
I'm going to pump out every last drop.
There isn't any more.
Oh, but there is. Come on!
God, stop it!
Cumming!
No more!
Aww... Are they done already?
Cum some more, you twisted dickslut.
I don't have a single sperm cell left.
I think they've run out.
Then we'll have to see how many times their pussies can cum.
Are you serious?
We're still not done?
That's it, thrust your hips against me.
This is hot shit!
How many fucks is this now, Sylia?
I lost count after ten.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum again!
Sylia, again? You really like cock, don't your?
Speak for yourself, Sarah. Just look as your face.
Hey you're forgetting to jerk each other off. Get to it.
Yes... I'll jerk Sarah's stiff prick.
I'll jerk yours too, Sylia.
Like that!
You like this, don't you. Getting stroked
and pounded at the same time.
This pussy is amazing.
I can't believe how tight it is.
Incredible. Just the two of them, able to satisfy all these nobles.
As if we had a choice!
What a party, Cecil. Sarah and Sylia are having a ball.
I'm not having a... Oh God, not again!
Who'd have thought a pirate and a knight could
be such a couple of nymphomaniacs?
Oh, this feeling...
Both my cock and my pussy are going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Amazing... It's so good!
So good! Thank you!
Don't grab my tits!
Let me go! I don't want to cum again!
Please, let go of my breasts!
I'm surprised they can feel anything at this point.
Quite sordid, indeed.
Enough already! You're going to ruin my body!
Stop laughing! Stop laughing!
Sylia! Sylia! Sylia!
Sylia!
Sarah!
They've hit bottom.
Amen to that. Let's finish them off.
My... My uterus!
You filthy pigs will receive punishment from us.
Don't cum inside me! You'll make me cum again if you do!
Please, not that!
You're hitting the back of my womb!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! I'm...
Look at them. Cum-blasted and loving it.
I wish I could join the fun.
That's right. Next time we should take a turn jacking them off.
Another chain orgasm punishment for them both.