Space Pirate Sarah and Silver Sylia are captured by the Gielen twins
and subjected to much humiliation.
Sarah, now equipped with a penis, is forced by
the Gielen twins to use her new organ on Sylia.
The twins then ride both women's turgid members
to the point of absolute sexual exhaustion.
Meanwhile, Sarah's first mate Hans finds himself within
reach of their ultimate prize, the Sword of Bernstein.
Before he can liberate the sword from its tower, however,
Hans is distracted by a state-of the-art robotic knight.
Moments later, Sarah andSylia are humiliated
again as they are repeatedly brought to climax
and used for pleasure by aristocratic subjects of the Gielen House.
Determined to break their wills, the nobles ravage Sarah and Sylia...
...until both women lose consciousness.
So the rumors are true.
What do you mean?
A machine with the fighting skills of a knight.
It's the result of a cutting-edge AI experiment.
You'd better fall back.
I've been waiting for this chance for a long time.
Sorry, Boss. Ending transmission.
No, Hans!
I finally get to face a real opponent.
They call me Hans Btilow!
Prepare to die!
Hans!
Space Pirates - Sara
Vol. 04 Revenge of the Pirate Knight
Onee-sama.
Wake up, Onee-sama.
What the hell is this?
Sarah!
Sylia... You too?
What do you think? They're beautiful, aren't they?
I raised them well.
What are you up to this time?
More punishment. Because you tried to steal the sword.
Your friend tried really hard.
Hans? What's happened to him?
That robo-knight is state-of-the-art.
A washed-up fighter like your first mate wouldn't stand a chance.
Oh, no...
Oh, look! My pets...
They're getting frisky.
Let... Let me go!
That's my... urethra!
Good, I'm glad to see you're making friends.
Raping my pee hole... That's a first...
Bring it on. I've survived everything you've thrown at me so far.
Whatever you say, Onee-sama.
That was fast...
Cecil, let's commence phase two.
Roger-dodger!
Wh-What?
It's hitting my uterus...
We're going to push you to the limit.
What do you mean?
Your cervix is puckering up... Like a kiss, almost.
How would you know?
We can see it.
Wanna know why? Cause there's an eye at the end of that tentacle!
An eye?
An eye is looking at my insides?
Let's have a look... at your womb!
Stop it!
How humiliating... how completely shameful.
It went right for her ass.
My ass!
It's inside...
It's fucking my ass!
Look. Her anus is twitching.
I guess she likes it.
Stop it! Stop talking like that!
Look away. Don't look at me!
I've had enough!
Raping my uterus? You two are sick.
Let's shut that noisy mouth.
Onee-sama's womb is so red...
So slimy and trembling...
Please, no more. Stop looking!
Another one... Another eye is looking inside me.
It's getting crowded in there. Almost like you're pregnant.
Stop it.. Stop looking.
Imagine if we could get another cock inside you.
You'd cum in no time.
Your uterus is positively erotic.
No! No!
It's so embarrassing... I hate it!
Keep it up, Onee-sama.
Milk those tentacles with your womb and your mouth.
What?
Of course. They can ejaculate.
Ouch!
Look at her nose. Like a little piggy!
Stop this!
Just watching this is turning me on.
My pets are poking around all her dirty holes.
Stop looking! And stop getting turned on!
But your dick seems to agree with me.
Stop this...
No, if this keeps up...
Look, your cock looks so happy.
You're a hermaphrodite sex fiend.
No... No... I'm not a sex fiend!
You forget, I can feel what the tentacles are feeling.
I can tell your cock is about to explode.
That tentacle squeezed the cum right out of you.
Stop it! Please, leave my dick alone!
You're right. We should focus on this hole.
No... No... No!
Amazing. With all your sex organs, you can enjoy
yourself far more than a normal human.
You've already made my pussy and my cock into your playthings.
Stop this already!
I want to see more...
I want to see deeper inside you, Sarah-Oneesama. All the way inside.
It's so deep inside me... and it's going deeper...
H-Here too?
What?
My breasts... They're burning hot!
We're going to get more milk out of those big tits of yours.
Deep inside your womb...
There it is! Your oviduct!
No, don't!
Stop it!
Leave my tubes alone!
I can see, Onee-sama. I can see everything.
Don't look up my oviduct! Don't look!
Stop raping me!
Oh, that's what you say, but look at how big it's gotten.
Getting raped has made your nasty girl cock this big.
That hurts! Stop it...
My dick... You're gonna scar my dick!
So now your dick is important to you?
Not to worry. Your cock likes it rough.
That can't be...
It's fucking the inside of my cock!
That was sure quick.
You really like being catheterized by tentacles, don't you?
My insides...
The tentacles are having their way with my insides.
My pussy... My ass... My cock... They're all getting raped!
Don't look at me!
No more! Stop it!
No!
These two have been getting raped all day. They're tough, though.
Not to mention sticky.
What shall we do next?
Enemas are fun!
You two aren't tired of this yet?
No way.
Not until you submit to us and become our friends.
Is this...
Impossible. Tihe Sword?
How?
Did I come at a bad time?
Hans!
Sorry I'm late, Boss.
He beat the droid knight?
Unbelievable.
That's what happens when you underestimate your enemies.
Hans...
The Sword guided me here... To it's rightful master.
What!?
Some call this sword the Imperial Scorpion.
It holds the power of the ancient Galactic Emperor.
What happened? All of a sudden you're at a loss for words.
With this sword, my family will be avenged in full.
You really thought we didn't know
about your connection to the Sword?
We used it as bait.
Everything's gone as we had planned.
You've lost.
I regret to inform you both that you'll now perish.
Damn you!
You've got the Sword. Defeat us if you can.
I can.
Oh, I'm so scared.
You beat the droid knight. Not bad for an old man.
Roar!
Huh?
Sure, leave me to handle the one who fights dirty, Boss.
Don't give up, mister.
Tihey call me Hans Bulow!
Prepare to die!
Incredible.
With that sword, she actually stands a chance.
If I had known you'd be this much trouble,
I'd have killed you much earlier.
It's too late to worry about that now!
Three energy shields at once!?
Are you just going to swing it around, or actually use it?
What?
You still haven't begun to draw on the sword's true power.
True power?
Maybe you still need more of my "training"!
Sarah!
Shit she's strong!
If I had your body, I could make an even stronger droid knight.
I'd better kill you carefully.
You're the one who made that thing? You freak.
Hey, Onee-sama. The human brain is made of protein, is it not?
The brain, and therefore the soul, is nothing but meat.
It can be permanently damaged by extreme heat.
What are you talking about?
Your soul was burned, long ago in that fire. It's dead now.
What?
Scarred by flames, agony and fear... and irreparably so.
My... soul?
You heard me, Onee-sama!
Hans!
Snap out of it, Sarah!
So obstinate.
Hey, I was fighting the old guy. No fair.
That's all right. We can share, can't we?
We're gonna chop off your stupid heads.
The Sword...
Look out!
Let's end this. Your soul is done for!
Too close for comfort!
You missed, Onee-sama!
My soul... is still alive!
Cecil!
This is...
A scorpion?
Cecil...
It hurts! It hurts!
It's finally over... everyone.
Karin, I'm dying.
So this is what pain is like.
Don't die, Cecil.
My other self, Cecil... Cecil...
Security droids.
We're not outta this yet.
Sylia... did you...?
Forgive me. I should never have opposed the Emperor's daughter.
From now on, let's work together.
I'd be very encouraged to have you on my side, Sylia.
Thank you... Your Majesty.
Whoa, whoa. Just call me Sarah.
Can we do this later? All the castle's droids are headed this way.
Okay.
Look sharp, everybody.
We're getting out of here.
How many are there?
The Elfenbein!
Both of you, ready your energy shields.
Not again?
This is...
a bad idea, after all.
If we survive, promise me you'll never do this again, Boss.
Thus began the Era of the Scorpion, which would remembered
forever in history as a golden age of law and order.
In the blinding, all-engulfing blast of the
battleship's cannon, stood our new champion.
The pirate who became our Empress.
A year has passed.
Under my given name, Sarah Bernstein,
I have presided over the tumultuous galaxy.
I made Sylia my lieutenant and chose Planet Carib as my capital.
Duke Blankenheim's corrupt aristocracy has been wiped out.
Our vengeance is complete.
However, this is just the beginning.
Our fight has only just begun.