I just had sex with onii-chan.
He said that he likes me.
That means I'm his girlfriend, right?
Who is it?
Calling
Brother
Hello, onii-chan?
Nagisa?
Yeah.
Hey, if you're free tomorrow,
would you like to go out with me?
I'll be waiting in the school's music room.
Oh, okay. I understand.
Bye then.
Is this a date?
Uhou Renka
Slightly Endowed and Obedient - Nagisa
~ The Sadistic Mellow Love Recipe ~
Original Animation
Toyohira Household
Good morning, Ryouhei-san.
Oh?
He woke up early today.
O-Onii-chan...
Are we really going to do it here?
You don't want to?
I-It's not that.
It's just that this room is usually used.
It's somewhat...
That is exactly why.
I'll make you feel good.
I... see.
I'll release it for you.
Okay, I understand.
You're such a good girl, Nagisa.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan, it's embarrassing.
No...
Onii-chan...
I'm starting to feel numb.
I'll stop if you speak.
I'm getting teased by onii-chan...
This is...
Onii-chan...
This is... Wait...
Onii-chan, wait.
I think we'll be seen after all.
If we do it here...
Onii-chan, somebody might come.
There's no one here at this time.
Onii-chan's cock is entering inside me.
I told you already, right?
Y-Y-Your cock...
Your cock... is entering my pussy.
It feels embarrassing, so why do I...
Feel good?
It's good.
Onii-chan's cock feels good!
Onii-chan, this...
I'm going to cum!
I'm going to cum here!
No...!
Onii-chan, I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum!
That was great.
We're not finished yet.
Onii-chan!
No, onii-chan... I think I'm...
You need to feel it more.
Oh, no!
Onii-chan, no...
The sounds may be heard...
At this rate... I... No!
Your cock's thrusting into me.
Thrusting into my pussy!
– Onii-chan, I'm going to... going to cum again!
– Let's cum together.
Onii-chan...
Together...
Together with me...
Is this...
Sorry, I did it too intensely.
No, it's nothing like that.
I am happy that you don't hold yourself back with me.
Toyohira Household
Welcome home.
I'm home.
What's wrong?
So you don't care, huh?
How terrible.
Sorry, I was busy with a few things.
I don't want to hear those excuses.
I want you, Ryouhei-san.
Hey, do that after I take a bath...
It's been quite a long time already.
It's getting bigger.
Is... this okay?
So Ryouhei-san really is...
A lot came out.
Just keep your position like that, okay?
Ryouhei-san's cock is entering me.
Ryouhei-san's cock is now all the way inside.
It's good.
Ryouhei-san's cock is amazing.
Does it feel good, Ryouhei-san?
My insides feel so full now.
Ryouhei-sama, does it feel good?
Yeah.
Onii-chan...
H-Hey...
This is embarrassing...
– It feels good.
– Onii-chan's cock is getting into my pussy!
Ryouhei-san, it's okay.
Go deeper...
It feels good.
Ryouhei-san, I'm...
...going to cum.
I'm cumming!
This is amazing.
Thanks for helping me with my homework.
I did fine thanks to onii-chan.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Well, do you plan to stop by
somewhere else, onii-chan?
I think I will stay here a bit longer.
I'm looking for something...
I-I'm going to go out there for a bit.
I'll be back shortly.
Isn't it dangerous to go alone?
It won't be much longer, so wait a little further.
Umm, I'll be fine. I'll come back immediately.
I said no.
The world is much scarier than you think.
I'm really okay, so I'm going just a bit, okay?
I don't like girls that can't be reasoned with.
Onii-chan, umm...
What's wrong?
I want to go to the toilet...
What did you say?
To the toilet! I want to go to the toilet!
Oh, you're just going to the toilet, huh?
Then you just have let it out, right?
Here.
Okay, I got it.
O-Onii-chan, what are you saying?
You were kidding when you said to do it here, right?
I'm not kidding.
And also I want to see how you do it anyway.
O-Onii-chan, let go of my hand.
It's going to leak out already, onii-chan.
I want to see it.
Nagisa's embarrassing spot.
Th-That's not something you have to
say with that serious face, you know.
You're really...
I beg you...
Okay, I got it.
This is really embarrassing after all.
I'll wait until it comes out.
So there's no need to push yourself.
N-No way...
Onii-chan, I can't.
I'm already...
I'm peeing...
In front of onii-chan...
I'm peeing...!
Does it feel good?
Y-Yeah.
It's embarrassing,
but I think it feels quite good.
Onii-chan, it hurts.
Sorry, Nagisa.
Onii-chan...
Your cock is...
It hurts.
I can't...
It won't go in any further.
It's really hot.
Nagisa...
What is it, onii-chan?
Onii-chan, no!
We're doing this embarrassing thing again...
Hey...
No one else is looking.
It's going deep inside.
Onii-chan's cock...
It's going in.
It's getting filled with your cock.
A cock's inside my pussy.
It's moving so intensely.
It sounds really lewd every time
your thing thrusts inside me.
This is so intense.
It's amazing, onii-chan.
I'm going insane.
I'm feeling weird because of onii-chan.
I'm going to make you feel better.
To thrust your cock... that deep...
Onii-chan...
I'm already...
I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
This feels great...
Onii-chan's semen is going inside.
Whenever I meet with onii-chan, it's always about sex.
I want to go out sometime,
but even if I say it, there's only the sea.
I got it!
I just thought this would be fun.
Onii-chan, how about wearing a swimming attire, too?
Onii-chan,
what's wrong?
This kind of... You can't...!
Onii-chan...
You can't do this!
If we do it here...
Karen-san will...
Onii-chan...
I said we can't...
I said we can't do it here...!
Why are we doing it here?
I don't want this.
Now, let's go to this part.
Onii-chan, that is...
No...
You can also feel it here, you know.
No way...
I'm not that...
It's definitely not it...
No...
Onii-chan, that's really not it.
It's not it...
Are you starting to feel it?
Wh-What are you saying?
I said that's not it!
I'm telling you to stop!
I guess we'll have to try this one out.
What's this...?
This hole's seems good, too.
No, I don't want to!
This is wrong!
You're entering the wrong hole.
Are you feeling it already?
I'm not feeling it a single bit.
Don't say such weird things.
No...
Your cock's rubbing the insides of my butt.
It's the wrong hole, but your cock is still going inside.
No!
Don't do it so roughly.
My insides are getting stirred up.
Something really big is going inside me!
It's going deep inside. You're filling me up.
This feels great.
N-No...
This is weird. It's not even right.
Onii-chan, wait. If we continue this...
No...
No way...
What should I do?
I can't... hold it...
I'm cumming.
It's in a different place inside me.
I...
The semen is coming out from my butt...
O-Onii-chan, wait. This is too intense.
Wait a bit...
His cock is going inside me again.
Onii-chan, we can't.
Your cock... I said we can't...
This is intense...
Onii-chan, no...
I can't take your cock anymore.
Give me some rest.
It's so intense, I'm going to break.
If this continues...
It's cold!
What...? D-Didn't you go out somewhere?
When I thought that Nagisa-chan will be done with...
And to think that it was you who's doing it...
Why don't I join in to keep things enjoyable?
Karen-san?
It's okay, Nagisa-chan.
No...
What's this?
I can't... Stop this...
Don't lie to yourself.
This part beeps on saying that it wants more.
No...!
What's this?
My insides are getting tingly.
You were too careless.
And you kept doing it with her.
Onii-chan, you're still keeping it up with Karen-san?
It's not just me?
We're not lovers?
No, Nagisa, this is...
It's unfair of you to keep Nagisa-chan
all to yourself like that.
Let's do it at least every other day...
We'll share him even?
What are you saying?
Besides, I also like you Nagisa-chan.
I don't want to let you go.
Wait, Karen-san?
No, no...
What... Why...?
Karen-san and I...
It's not bad to have something like this, right?
Don't...
If you push it in... my pussy will...
Don't do that... so roughly...
I'm going to feel even weirder than before...
Let me join in, too.
No way...
Ryouhei-san's cock...
This is great...
Karen-san, wait...
You can't just have onii-chan's cock...
Nagisa-chan...
This feels good.
It's going in so deep.
Onii-chan, it's unfair to just keep on doing her.
Teach her, Karen.
No...
Karen-san...
I've started to move, too.
Amazing!
It's great.
To have it go in and out.
It feels really good.
Onii-chan, I want to get stirred up too.
That can't be.
Ryouhei-san's cock hasn't released yet inside me.
It's stirring me.
Your cock and my pussy are rubbing
against each other so intensely.
My pussy...
It's not even a cock and it still stirs me up.
I'm going to melt.
This is really good.
No, I can't take it anymore.
My pussy is really dripping wet.
No.
I'm already...
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming!
Onii-chan, I'm cumming, too.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
This is... This is...
It is weird, but it's so good...
Karen-san, you shouldn't have
sex with onii-chan anymore.
I don't think I can promise you that.
I guess Nagisa-chan won't come around this early.
Huh!?
Onii-chan's cock is mine.