I did it with brother!
Even told him that I liked him!
This means we're lovers, right?
Who's that?!
Hello, Brother?
Nagisa?
Yeah.
Hey, if you're free tomorrow, how about going out with me for a while?
Eh?
I'll be waiting on the music room at school.
Okay, got it.
Bye then.
Does that mean it's a date?
Good morning, Ryouhei.
Eh?
He's early today?
B-Brother...
Are we really doing it here?
You don't want to?
That's not what I meant.
It's just that, the school's a place we're always using...
It somehow feels a bit...
So?
Eh?!
I'll make you feel good.
I see.
I'll lead.
Got it.
You sure are a good girl, Nagisa.
Brother...
Brother.
That's so embarrassing, Brother.
No, Brother!
I can't muster any strength.
If  you want me to, I'll stop.
Don't!
Brother's teasing me.
This is...
Brother, why do it like this?
Brother, wait!
If we do it here,
they're really gonna find us!
Brother, someone's greally gonna come!
There's nobody here at this time of day.
Brother's thing is penetrating me deep inside.
Didn't I tell you something?
Your dick, it's penetrating my pussy.
It's so embarrassing, but...
Does it feel good?
It does.
Your dick feels so good.
Brother, sorry.
I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum from this.
No!
Brother, cumming, I'm gonna cum!
A-Amazing!
We're just getting started!
Ah, Brother!
Don't, Bro! I'm still sensitive.
Feel it more!
No, don't!
Brother, stop!
It's making sounds!
I can't take any more of this.
Your dick's penetrating my pussy!
Brother, I'm gonna cum again!
Let's do it together, right?
Brother, together, cum together with me!
So much...
Sorry for doing it so hard.
That's not the case at all.
It made me happy to see you lust after me.
Welcome back.
I'm back.
What happened?
So you aren't concerned after all?
How awful.
Sorry.
A lot of things came up and...
I don't want to hear excuses like that.
I want your thing, Ryouhei.
Hey!
I still haven't taken a bath yet.
It's been a while, huh?
It got hard.
Does this feel good?
Ryouhei, so you really...
A lot came out, eh?
Just stay like that, Ryouhei.
It's e-entering me, your dick!
Ryouhei's dick entered me!
So good!
Your dick is amazing!
Does it feel good, Ryouhei?
My insides are filled with you.
Yeah.
Brother, don't, this is so embarrassing!
Your dick is penetrating my pussy, Brother!
Ryouhei, it's so good.
Penetrate me more, it feels so good!
Ryouhei, I'm gonna... cum already!
I'm gonna cum!
This is amazing.
Thanks for helping with my homework, Brother!
That helped me big time.
Sure.
What's up?
Eh? No, it's nothing.
Shall we go somewhere then, Brother?
How about staying here for a little while longer?
I'm looking for something...
Wait, no need to go that far, I'll be back soon!
It's dangerous alone, right?
It's just a little bit more, so hold up for a minute.
Uhm, it'll be fine, I'll make sure to return soon.
As I keep saying, no.
The times aren't quite as easy as you'd hoped.
I-It'll be fine, I'll only be gone for a moment, okay?
I don't like disobedient girls.
Uhm, Brother, well...
What was that?
-to go to the toilet!
Huh, what was that?
The toilet, I need to go to the toilet!
Oh, it's just that?
Can't you just do it right here?
Okay, got i-wait what?!
Brother, what are you saying?
Do it right here, that can't be right, can it?
I'm being serious here.
Besides, I want to see you pee as well.
Brother, let me go.
It's gonna leak, Brother.
I want to see it, your embarrassing place.
That's not something you should be saying with such a serious face, no?
Geez.
I'm begging you, please.
O-Okay, got it.
This is so embarrassing after all.
I'll wait till it happens, no need to push yourself.
You can't be serious...
Brother, no!
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm peeing while Brother's watching me.
Does that feel good?
It's so embarrassing, but it feels good too.
Brother, I can't breathe.
Sorry, Nagisa.
B-Brother.
Your dick's so big.
It's good.
No, don't!
It's so big that it won't fit!
It's so hot.
Nagisa!
Brother, what is it?
Brother?!
Don't do something this embarrassing again, hey?
There's nobody looking.
Your thing's penetrating me so deep, Brother!
Your dick's entering me.
You're thrusting so deep with it inside me!
My pussy's going numb.
Your dick's so rough.
Producing so many perverted sounds,
Your thing's entering me!
You're so rough!
This is amazing, Brother!
I'm gonna go crazy!
You're gonna make me go crazy, Brother!
I'll make you even crazier!
Your dick's suddenly pounding my deepest parts again!
Brother, I can't anymore!
Bro!
I'm gonna cum, cumming!
This is amazing!
Your semen's flooding into me.
All we ever do when out is have sex, eh?
I wouldn't mind taking a walk normally sometime either.
Though, there's nowhere else but the sea to go.
Ah, that's right!
I figured that things like these are okay too.
How about joining me in your swimsuit, Bro?
Brother, what happened?
Wait, no, don't!
Brother, don't!
Karen's gonna see us here!
Brother, I keep telling you, don't.
Don't...
Why are you doing this to me even at a place like this?
No...
I guess it's about time for this hole too.
Brother, that's my...
That's the wrong place, don't!
You can feel it from here too, you know.
That can't be!
It's not like that, it can't... be like that!
No!
That's not the right hole, Brother!
Are you feeling it?
It's not like that.
I'm telling you to stop!
We need to give it a try, I guess.
What's this?
This holes looks okay too.
It's not meant to be like that.
You're mixing them up!
Are you feeling it already?
That's not it.
Don't say weird things.
Don't!
Your dick's messaging my insides!
It's wrong, but Brother's dick is penetrating me!
No, don't do it so hard.
My insides are becoming restless, something amazing is penetrating me!
It's reaching my deepest, deepest parts!
That's the way it should be!
This is supposed to be weird, and abnormal...
Don't!
Brother, wait!
Don't do it any more than this!
Don't, what should I do?
I can't hold back!
I'm gonna cum.
Cumming.
I ended up cumming from a weird place...
My insides are flooded with semen.
Brother, wait, you're too rough!
Your dick's penetrating me again!
Brother, don't!
You're being so rough!
Brother, this isn't right!
I can't deal with your cock anymore.
I need some rest.
It's so rough, I'm gonna break!
So cold!
What's that?
Weren't you supposed to be out on a walk?
I was wondering if you were gonna do it with Nagisa again, but...
Ryouhei, how about including me on the fun as well?
Eh? Karen?
It's fine, Nagisa.
Karen, what's that?
No, don't.
Lying is bad, mmkay?
You should be screaming that you want it more.
The hell this?
My insides are coiling up.
Wasn't that just selfish?
Doing it with Nagisa only...
Eh?! You guys didn't break everything off?
It wasn't just me?
I'm not your lover?
Well, Nagias, you see...
You too, Nagisa.
Hogging him all to yourself is unfair.
At least share him.
By that, you mean pushing him?
What are you saying, Karen?
Besides, I like you too, Nagisa.
I don't want to be separated.
Wait, Karen!
No, what is this?!
Why am I with Karen?
This feels good too, right?
No, don't!
That place is... so rough, don't!
Add me in that too!
Ryouhei's cock is so amazing!
Karen, hey!
Brother's cock is so amazing.
Nagisa!
You're reaching my deepest spots, it feels so good!
Brother, it's unfair just to do Karen!
I'll teach you, Karen.
No...
If you move that thing like that...
So amazing!
It's going in and out of me, so good!
Brother's supposed to be mine,
I want him to do that to me.
You can't!
He hasn't ejacualted yet!
It's mixing me up!
It's so stiff inside my pussy!
That's not even a real dick inside me, but it's so wet!
Melting, my hips are gonna melt!
It feels so good!
Don't, I can't take it anymore!
My pussy's gonna flood!
I can't anymore either!
I'm gonna cum, cumming!
Brother, I'm gonna cum too!
Cumming!
This is weird, but...
Karen, you can't do it with Brother anymore.
I don't think I can promise that.
Nagisa shouldn't be around since it's so early.
Brother's cock is my property!