That's enough for a day.
What was I expecting?
Welcome.
Don't startle us, Karen.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Kanou Karen, daughter here at the Toyohira inn.
Welcome.
I already know Uezato.
Your room has been prepared.
Thanks, Kanou.
Oh, call me Karen.
This way, please.
So hot...
It's hitting against it...
We're making weird noises when you pull out and thrust in...
Don't, Ryouhei...
I...
What's wrong with it?
My pussy feels weird...
So good...
So much...
Ryouhei...
When this happens...
I can't breathe...
You smell nice.
You did it.
Isn't this your fault?
And...
so are the clothes...
What the kimono?
You're the lady of the house.
So I have to wear a kimono?
It's a pretty cheap one.
Taking it off is the part that's fun.
Wait.
What are you doing?
You're squeezing...
my breasts...
Am I in?
Yes.
Ryouhei, you're—
They're out.
Good.
Your cock...
It's in...
Your cock is so hard.
It tickles...
It's turning me inside out.
It's going to hit my womb.
It's good.
Your cock...
Yes! It feels so good!
Come inside.
More.
It's so good.
It feels so good.
Your cock...
It's making me come.
I'm coming.
I'm coming!
The Smell of Rain
A Love Song
Karen!
You got this hard even in your sleep.
Why?
I was looking at your sleeping face when I came in.
I saw you'd gotten hard.
You like this, huh?
Your penis changed me.
Yes, it's been different since that time.
Why are you naked?
I wanted to feel like a slut, even if only a little.
Don't, Ryouhei.
You've done it yourself, haven't you?
I...
You have.
Yes.
Yes... I have.
When I was alone.
Wait.
Don't.
Want to do it yourself?
I...
No...
Don't...
Wow...
He's going to do me.
He's going to put his cock in.
It's so big...
It's going to go inside me...
Do it.
Is it your first time?
Yes.
It hurts.
I'm having sex.
I'm having sex in a place like this.
What is this feeling?
I...
Does it still hurt?
There's a tingling...
It's mostly gone away, though.
That's all?
It feels good.
You're a little slut.
Don't say things like that.
That's too sudden!
Come inside!
It's my first time, but this is so good.
It's so different.
What is this?
You can feel it, can't you?
I never thought cocks would be so good.
I'm coming.
We did it.
That was great.
This is good.
Some is still inside.
That stuff, I mean...
That's another experience for me.
I was a little afraid of this and wondered when it would happen...
Are you okay that it was me?
Yes.
Since it was you... because of that...
Have you liked me since we met?
Don't ask that out of the blue.
It's so amazing it can get so big...
This feels too good.
You little slut.
Don't...
Don't say that...
If you come inside me.
It's gonna leak out.
It feels weird.
Don't.
Sex feels so good.
There's no going back now.
Move more.
I can't.
It's inside.
Don't.
Not inside.
There's a wall there.
I'll break through.
I feel like I'm boiling.
It feels really slutty.
You are hitting my insides really hard.
I can't let go.
It's so good.
This little manwhore thing turned me into a slut.
I love cocks now.
Why?
Hold it between your tits.
Like this?
It's so hard.
Why with my tits?
I...
Wow.
This is too amazing so early.
We should get going.
You're right! I'll be late!
I might just make it!
Goodbye!
Be careful!
Do you remember the likelihood?
Mathematically speaking, probablity is anything influenced by random chance.
Brother...
Consequently, the likelihood of an occurence increases with its relative frequency.
When we think of the relative frequency as the probability, using it...
I think...
Ryouhei...
They can see us.
Only if you act unusually.
I can't help it.
The neighbors are there.
Hello.
It's hot, isn't it?
No...
Oh, Karen.
Have you seen my brother?
No...
I can't take it.
Ryouhei...
This...
Don't...
Hey, Tsukayama.
Tsukayama.
Hey, Earth to Tsukayama.
You manwhore!
Uh?
Hey, that was rude.
I'm a real gentleman.
Only in your classes.
Of course.
That's harsh.
Oh, no. What am I doing.
I'm at school. What am I doing?
Slut.
Don't say that. It's really embarrassing.
We can't be seen.
You wanted it yourself.
We've gone overboard.
You did it yourself, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
Well, I...
A little...
Not now!
You're supposed to meet Nagisa today.
I have to go out for a meeting too.
Karen.
Yeah?
You're teasing me now.
Did you forget something?
Why are we he—
Since when are you with her?
Since when are you and Karen lovers?
When did it start?
Did you hide it from me?
Did you meet her and come back home to me?
Um, well.
She's my sister and all.
Nagisa, wait.
But, but.
But I...
I've always loved you!
Do what you've done with Karen!
Do it with me!
Nagisa...
I love you.
I can't stop.
I won't stop if you say no.
That's fine.
You're...
No.
Brother...
No!
Don't!
That's dirty!
I have no strength...
No.
No!
If you touch my breasts...
This is your...
It'll hurt. Try to bear with it.
Do it.
Don't worry about me.
Your...
I can feel you inside.
It's your first time.
You can have my first time.
It hurts, but try to bear it.
I'm fine.
The pain will be precious to me too.
Okay.
But tell me if it hurts too much.
Do it.
Brother!
I'm so happy.
This was my dream.
I'm so glad.
Nagisa...
Thanks...
Brother...
This is embarrassing...
I'm feeling light...
Just a little bit.
What?
What is it?
What's going to happen?
This feels weird.
You'll like it.
Like what?
You're tightening up.
No.
This is embarrassing.
Don't do that.
Pull out
Don't do it inside.
Don't, Brother.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Don't.
At this rate...
I'm going to come.
I'm gonna come.
I'm coming!
This is so embarrassing.
There's so much inside.
She's always loved him, hasn't she?
My brother is coming back.
I didn't know you had a brother.
He's not my real brother.
He was my sister's classmate.
He was her boyfriend too.
Okay, so you called him 'Brother'.
Yep. He's kind and really cool.
Oh, my. Was he your first love?
I see.
I wonder if he'll remember me.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I've changed a lot.
What matters is that you've gotten really cute.
I bet they're doing things I don't know.
Sorry, Brother.
Maybe I was hard on you too. It was your first time.
I'm fine.
Does it hurt?
It tickles.
It's like you're still inside me.
This is it for today.
For today, eh.
All right.
Hey.
Took you.
Hey!
This is Nagisa's blood.
Been a bad teacher, haven't we.
Hey, Karen.
You just want to ram it in, right?
Like you did with me.
I kept remembering how it was there.
She might become the same.
Hey...
Brother...