I guess I'll stop here for today.
What was I looking forward to anyway?
Sign: Toyohira-ya
Welcome!
Geez, Karen-san, don't surprise us.
Hi. I'm the heiress to Toyohira-ya, Kanao Karen.
Nice to meet you!
I've heard about you, Uezato-san.
I've got your room ready.
Thank you, Kanao-san.
Oh, you can call me Karen.
Come this way.
Ryouhei-san...
Th-This...
It’s in so deep and... makes erotic noises...
It goes in and out...
No, you can't, Ryouhei-san!
I...
Is it okay?
Well, I...
My pussy is getting rubbed...
Amazing... so good...
Ryouhei-san...
You're hard again...
It’s going to spill!
What a perverted young lady...
You made me this way.
It's your fault!
And you... made me wear this too.
Why do I have to wear a kimono?
It’s because you're the owner of the inn.
Because I'm the owner? You're too old fashioned.
But it’s more fun to take it off.
Wait... W-What are you...?
No! You're pinching... my boobs...
Aren't you wearing any?
N-No I'm not...
You're amazing!
It’s all out!
Yes! Your dick feels so good!
It’s in so deep!
Your dick is so hard!
My pussy is getting scraped!
It’s entering the place where babies are made!
Dick...
Yes! It feels so good!
My pussy is so full!
Your dick is so good!
It feels so good!
Your dick is going to make me cum!
I'm cumming!
W
Original Animation
Uhou
Renka
Blushing, Sexy Tits, Summer love
~Perverted Midsummer Truth~
Karen!
It’s so big... even though you were asleep.
Why are you...?
Well, I was watching, and...
I was watching your sleeping face and I caught a glimpse of it.
Your hard dick.
You sure like it.
It was this little guy that made me perverted.
Yes, I changed after that incident.
Why were you walking around naked?
Well... I wanted a...
Small stimulus, so...
No, you can't, Ryouhei-san!
Were you masturbating?
I’d... never...
So you were masturbating.
Yes... well...
To tell you the truth... I was doing it... by myself...
Wait!
No!
I don't want to!
Are you moving by yourself?
No... I-I wasn't...
No...
Amazing!
He’s going to do me...
He's going to put his dick in me...
It’s so big...
That's going to go inside me.
Come in...
Was it your first time?
Yes.
It hurts so much!
I'm doing it! I'm having sex! I'm having sex in this kind of place!
This...  what is this... am I...?
Does it still hurt?
It tingles, but it doesn't hurt anymore...
Is that it?
Also, I think I feel a bit better now.
So you're a pervert.
Don't say that kind of thing!
Don't do it so hard all of a sudden!
So much inside...
Even though it’s my first time, it feels so good.
What's this?
You’re turned on, aren't you?
I didn't think... a dick would feel this good.
I'm cumming!
I-I'm cumming!
We did it and it felt great.
So it feels this good...
It feels like it’s still inside.
Your dick...
I finally got to feel what it’s like...
I always thought I would get seduced one day because of what I was doing.
Was it okay to be me?
Yes...
Yes.. well, if it was you, then...
Since we met?
Sheesh... don't ask weird things.
So it gets that big...
Even though it’s small now.
It feels too good!
You're such a pervert.
No... don't... say that!
So much... in me!
Isn't it too much?
No.. I’m gonna go crazy...
I'm going to go crazy...
No way! It’s going crazy inside...!
Once I taste true pleasure like this, there’s no turning back!
Loosen up a bit.
I can't do it...
It’s in so deep...
Don't put it in so deep!
You can’t go further than that!
I’ll just dig in more.
It’s poking... my stomach...
You’re going to imprint your perverted shape in my body
I can't get away from it now...
Not again... yes... yes!
I was turned into a pervert by this erotic thing...
The reborn me loves dick so much that I can't help myself!
What is it?
Put it between your tits.
Like this, with my boobs?
You've gotten hard.
Does it feel good?
You can go any time...
Wow... you're so good even in the morning...
Uh... it’s getting late, isn’t it?
Oh my! I'm going to be late!
I'll barely make it.
Have a safe journey and be careful.
Do you know the probability?
The mathematical probability of something happening by chance is...
Sometimes irrelevant when you bring in the idea of coincidence.
Onii-chan
However, usually the way it works is that the more often something is attempted, the higher the probability that it will succeed,
This release was done by SubDESU-H, go to our website www.subdesu-h.net for official releases.
So if we look at this "getting closer to something happening" as a percentage probability, we can then calculate...
That...
Ryouhei-san.. everyone can see it.. Ryouhei-san...
Just act natural...
I can't do that!
Ah, that’s the neighbor...
Good evening... it sure is hot...
No...
Ah, Karen-san, so Onii-chan is back too.
No! I can’t hold on much longer!
Ryouhei-san.
This is bad...
Hey, Tsukayama!
Tsukayama... Tsukayama!
Hey, can you hear my voice?
O-Onii-chan, you pervert!
Huh?
Well, that's rude - I'm a gentleman.
But if you have Sensei’s face in front of you...
Yeah, I would too
You're mean...
Oh no, what am I doing?
What am I thinking while at school?
You're a pervert.
Don't... it’s so embarrassing, so don't look.
Even though you usually lecture me about it.
D-Don’t look at me with those perverted eyes.
You were masturbating, weren't you?
W-What are you saying?! I wasn’t... well, I...
Just a little...
N-No, you can't!
Nagisa-chan needs my help today.
I have to go out as well.
Yeah... Karen...
Yes?
You're such a meanie.
Forgot something?
Why are you...?
Since when did you start going out?
Eh?
Since when did you start going out with Karen-san?
How long have you known her?
Were you hiding it from me?
Did you come to meet her and went back?
Ah... um, well...
I thought it couldn’t be helped, because of my big sister...
Nagisa-san, wait!
But, but...!
I also want... you...
I've always loved you!
Please, do what you did to her! Do it to me, please!
Nagisa...
I love you!
I love you, Onii-chan.
I’m not stopping.
I won’t let you go, even if you change your mind.
Please, do it Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, you’re breathing on... mm...
No...!
Onii-chan!
N-No!
No... Onii-chan, it’s dirty there...
Can't summon any strength...
Yes!
Onii-chan is touching my boobs!
T-This is Onii-chan's...
It’s gonna hurt, but bear with it...
Put it in!
I don't care if it hurts me!
I want you and your dick...
I can tell that you're inside m...
Is it your first time?
You're my first, Onii-chan.
It must hurt, but please bear with it.
I'm fine...
I’ll remember it more if it hurts.
Fine.
But tell me if it hurts too much.
Ok... Onii-chan, move!
Onii-chan, I'm so happy! So happy! I... I...
It’s a dream come true to have sex with you, Onii-chan!
Nagisa...
Thank you, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, I'm embarrassed!
Onii-chan...
What... so deep...
Just a little bit.
What is it, Onii-chan?
No... it feels like it's expanding... it feels weird...
You're getting sensitive.
Eh? Sensitive?
Eh?
You're tensing up.
Don’t say something so embarrassing, Onii-chan.
So this is sex... Yes, Onii-chan, deeper!
Oh no, I can't stop shaking my hips, Onii-chan!
Onii-chan, more...
No... I'm going to...
Onii-chan I'm going to cum! I'm cumming... no, I can't hold on, I... cumming... cumming!
So embarrassing...
So much of you inside me...
She always liked him...
Onii-chan is coming back.
You have a brother?
We aren't blood related, but...
He's the same age as my sister.
He was my sister’s ex... so...
Ah, I see, so that’s why you call him Onii-chan.
Yes! He's cool and so gentle.
Oh? Maybe he's your first love?
I see...
Do you think Onii-chan will still remember me?
I don't know...
Yes, you're right... I've changed a lot since then...
Well, we can say one thing for sure - you've become really pretty.
She knows everything I don't know about him...
I'm so sorry.
Me too, I think I went a little bit too far on your first time.
No worries... I'm fine.
Does it hurt?
No, it tingles a bit.
It still feels like I've got yours in me.
We're all done for the day.
"For the day". Okay, I understand.
H-Hey!
Aren't you late?
Hey!
This is Nagisa-chan’s blood.
Aren't you a bad little teacher?
Hey, Karen!
Look at you, all sticky!
I bet you were rough with her like you were with me.
She was fucked hard for her first time...
She might turn out just like me.
H-Hey!
Onii-chan.