After becoming stranded on this desolate island,
the girls in my class contracted a terrible virus.
A virus that keeps them in a constant state of arousal.
A doctor named Ichijou-san was stranded here
as well, and according to her analysis,
you die when the symptoms reach their peak.
The only way to treat the symptoms,
is to take in a man's semen.
On this accursed island, men are their only salvation.
In other words,
my cum is the only cure.
Alter - Impregnation Island.
Go ahead. I want the creep's dick.
My mind's going blank.
Your giant dick is amazing.
Getting fucked from behind is even better!
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
It's pumping into me.
I never thought that I'd be fucked like this by such a creep.
Though, now I'm addicted to your cum.
Hey, since it felt this good,
let's make the best of this while the getting's good.
Come on, fuck me more!
Yes, this is it!
I can feel it penetrating me so deeply!
Come on, come on!
Cum inside me again!
I want you to impregnate me.
Impregnate me with your child, creep!
Get ready, I'm about to shoot my load deep inside.
Just cum!
Cum it all.
Creep, that was the best.
Ai-chan, good morning.
Well? Does this feel good, Shouta-kun?
Your dick's gotten hard.
I'll do my best, so please cum lots for me, okay?
This big and hot thing is clinging to my breasts.
My body's scorching hot, too.
I'm about to...!
I want your cum, Shouta-kun.
Let it out. Come on, squirt it all out!
That's so much cum. I'm so happy!
Up next is...
I want you to impregnate me.
You have to get impregnated soon, Ai-chan.
I want to become his number one.
Come on, hurry.
His cum will get cold.
Oh wow...
Take a look at this, Ai-chan.
Cum's pouring into me, and it feels amazing.
My head's feeling fuzzy.
I think it's trying to fertilize me.
Shouta-kun and I are making babies first,
so you can't take him away and be first!
The girl that tried to take over for me,
should just lie there and watch us make lots of babies, okay?
Shouta-kun, your dick is going wild inside me.
I'm going to cum with this messed up
and already impregnated pussy!
I'm cumming while being fucked hard.
I'm cumming while being impregnated!
I'm giving your pussy a bit extra, okay, Ai-chan?
This isn't gonna work.
My body won't cool down.
I guess, I'll have to ask him again.
Now you understand that water doesn't work.
No need to be alarmed.
I just thought I'd help since you looked like you need a dose.
Th-That's not it.
I'm willing to save you, since you'll die if you don't take my semen.
That's not it.
You just need to drink the right amount.
Stop sticking it between my ass.
You start feeling at ease once I start caressing you like this, right?
It doesn't feel that...!
No, stop this.
It's starting to feel weird.
Why would you squirt your cum on my back...?
Sorry about that.
I'll let you drink the rest.
I can't...
I can't, breathe...!
Toume-san, you have no other choice.
I can still give you some, you know.
What are you going to do?
All right.
I'll let you have your way.
Just do it. Try fucking me then.
You're not being honest, eh.
Not my problem, though.
It's pushing into me.
It's penetrating and spreading me apart.
My insides are getting churned up.
This is my first time, and yet,
I think I'm about to cum.
Your tan lines are arousing me.
I want you to wear your swimsuit when I fuck you next time.
That's dirty...!
No need to feel embarrassed, your heat virus will bare it all.
Just wait!
Oh no... I can't restrain myself anymore!
Just cum, then!
And lay there as I cum in you!
Oh no, I'm cumming. I'm cumming!
It's pumping into me.
It's still flowing in.
It's my first time feeling such a sensation.
But this is the last time.
This is gonna be my last semen dosage.
Don't worry. I'm cumming inside.
Then cum!
Your white thing is seeping through
me, making my mind blank as well.
Oh no, here it comes... you're about to cum.
Here it comes!
It's coming out.
I shouldn't do this, and yet...
I'm gonna get pregnant.
Huh?
That's...
Ichijou-san?
Sorry for the wait, Ichijou-san.
A month has passed, and it already feels like paradise.
All thanks to the virus that you created.
What are you trying to do by...
A secret room below the cliff where the house sits.
I found the place,
along with all of the sex reports, and your infection targets.
I even stumbled upon the vaccine that you created.
Now, confess.
Tell me how you hid vaccine.
Also, I can't believe Kisaragi, class prez,
and sensei were actually here all this time.
All that was left was for you to find a way out of here.
I wanted you to be my guinea pig for a little longer.
Please,
I'll pleasure you all you want.
Just let me go.
The one that wants pleasure,
is your depraved self!
I'll fuck, but no cum for you until you finally tell me.
That can't be. If I don't take my proper dosage now,
the virus will...!
Oh no. I won't be able to endure.
I'm gonna lose it!
Please, stop it already.
I'll just keep cumming!
Do you feel like telling me now?
Okay, okay! I'll tell you!
Just cum already, please!
I hid a vehicle somewhere in the waste area.
There, you're satisfied, right?
Hurry!
I'll go crazy if this goes on!
I won't be able to survive. I'm going to die!
So you finally spilled your guts.
In that case, here's the last dosage of cum you'll ever get!
Please cum!
I beg of you. Cum. Cum it inside me!
Let me cum while being impregnated!
Wow.
So much hot stuff is filling me up.
I've definitely been impregnated.
You are expendable now.
It's been a while since a shipwreck has entered the public eye.
Now that we've all escaped from that island,
we've returned to our normal lives.
If there's one thing that changed,
it would be that I'm no longer being bullied.
Also...
Akira, your tummy's a bit swollen.
Yeah.
I want to see our baby already.
That means, our surreal relationship from before,
is real... and has reached the next level.
You're drilling so deep inside!
I promised you back on the island, right?
I became your dick's slave at that moment.
Here it comes.
My womb and the baby are receiving your cum.
I think they're about to find out about your tummy, Yumi.
I guess.
I don't care if they do, as long as you're by my side.
Then why don't we both leave this place
and find us a quiet place like that island?
Yes. I'd love to.
I want to be with you forever.
My womb is being filled with your milk!
I'm home, everyone.
Welcome home, darling.
My baby is happy that you're fucking me, darling.
Please cum.
Give my pussy your homecoming cum!
Today is Akira's turn, eh.
I'm a prince, both on that island, and back home.
Welcome home.