After drifting onto this uninhabited island,
my female classmates got infected by a mysterious virus
that makes them sexually aroused beyond control.
According to the analysis of Ichijou,
the doctor that also drifted here by chance,
The women will end up dying after
suffering long enough from the disease.
The only specific drug that will alleviate their symptoms
is semen from a man.
Their only salvation is a man that is in this island.
In short, it's nothing else but my semen.
Jutaijima
- Fertilization Island -
Ura • Jutaijima
- (The Other Side) Fertilization Island -
Ura Jutaijima.
Don't pull out until I'm knocked up...
It feels good! Creep-o's cock!
I'm losing my head!
Your huge cock is incredible!
Getting fucked from behind is really incredible!
Coming... I'm coming!
It's pouring in deep inside me!
I never ever thought that I'm gonna
be fucked by a Creep-o like you!
It feels like you already impregnated
me after giving me a creampie!
Well, it felt good, and I don't want
to die yet so it can't be helped.
Here, give me more!
That's it, right there, you're
digging me inside like crazy!
Hey, come on!
Come and give me more of it inside!
I-I want you to knock me up!
Make me pregnant with your baby, Creep-o!
I'm gonna come in your deepest parts!
Give it to me!
Shoot your semen!
Creep-o... You're the best...
Good morning, Ai-chan!
How is it? Does it feel good, Shouta-kun?
Your dick got hard!
I'll do my best on servicing you
so give me a lot of semen, okay?
Your hot and huge thing is sliding in between my tits!
I think my body is getting hot as well!
I want your semen, Shouta-kun!
Thrust it in! I'll take it in so thrust it in!
That's a lot of semen, I'm glad!
And then next, you see...
I want you to make me pregnant!
Hurry up and knock me up before Ai-chan.
I want to become your number one girl!
Hurry up! Your semen will get cold.
This is amazing!
Look over here, Ai-chan!
The semen is pouring into my pussy, wow—!
It's flowing deep inside me!
I wonder if I'll get pregnant with this.
I'm going to be the first one to have Shouta-kun's baby,
so you can't just be indulging yourself!
For someone with sticky fingers like you, Ai-chan,
you'll have to watch how we make a baby, okay?
Shouta-kun's dick is running wild in my belly!
Your semen is getting stirred up in my slutty pussy!
Coming... I'm coming!
Your semen is splashing around in my pussy!
I'm coming! I'm coming from your dick!
I'll share my own blend of secondhand
semen to your pussy, Ai-chan.
I knew it, this won't be enough.
My body won't settle down!
Somehow, the idea of...
asking him a favor is...
You already know that soaking your
body in water won't help, right?
You don't have to be stubborn.
It looks like you're suffering so
I just thought that I should help.
Y-You're wrong!
You'll die if you don't drink semen,
so you should just let me help.
It's not about that...
Just like usual, you should just drink it.
It's rubbing on my butt!
You know that if we do this to feel good,
your body's arousal will settle down, right?
I'm saying that I don't really want to feel good...
Stop this... I'll end up feeling strange!
You sprayed your semen on my back...
My bad, my bad.
I'll make you drink my remaining semen.
I can't breathe... I can't breathe!
Toume-san, this is something inevitable.
I still can come though...
What should we do?
I understand.
I'll let you have it your way.
How about you put that thing
inside me however you want.
You're not being honest. Oh well, I'm fine with it.
It's going in!
It's stretching me wide, it's pushing deep inside!
You're stirring me inside!
Even though it's my first time...
...I-I'm already on the verge of coming!
I love your tanlines! I'd love to fuck
you in a swimsuit next time.
No—!
What are you saying?!
It's the virus's fault that you're in heat,
so don't feel ashamed even if you come!
Wait... No, seriously... I can't already!
Come! I'll shoot it inside you!
No way! I'm coming... I'm coming!
It's pouring in...
It's still pouring more in...
You took away my first...
But this is a one-time thing! Just so I can
get your semen... Only this one time!
Inside... I'm going to shoot it inside you, okay?
Pull it out! My mind is going blank.
My head feels like getting zapped, I'm going crazy!
Stop, you should stop... Ah, stop!
It's coming inside!
Even though we shouldn't...
I'm gonna have a baby...
Isn't that...
Ichijou-san?
Sorry for the wait, Ichijou-san.
It's been a month since we came to
this island and it's been a heaven for me!
It's all thanks to that virus you made.
D-Do you think you can—
I found out about everything
in the basement hidden in the cave.
The fact that you infected yourself with
the virus written in your crazy report
and that you already made a vaccine for it as well.
So hurry up and tell me where the vaccine is.
And I'm surprised that you even hid Kisaragi-san,
the class rep and the teacher in here!
And tell me about your way
to escape from this island too.
I want you to cooperate with my
experiment for just a little more.
Won't you, please? I'll make sure
that you'll feel good a lot,
so I want you to untie me.
Isn't this the one you want instead?!
I won't come inside until you
tell me what I want to know!
No way! If you won't hurry up and give me semen, the virus will...
No! This is really bad, I'm losing my mind!
I'm serious! Stop this already,
or I won't stop coming!
Isn't it about time that you feel like talking?
I understand... I-I'll tell you,
so hurry up and come in me!
I hid a motorboat somewhere inside the sea cave!
Hey, I already told you what you want. Hurry up!
I'll go crazy if you don't! I'll come
myself so much to death!
You spill the beans so easily. Alright then!
Please have a good taste of your last semen!
Give it to me inside! Come!
I'm begging you... Semen... Give me your semen!
Make me pregnant!
So hot! Amazing! Your hot
stuff is flowing deep into me!
I'm definitely pregnant now...
And with this, you're now intoxicated.
It will still need some time before we can take
our minds off the recent shipwreck tragedy.
After escaping from the island,
we all went back with our everyday lives.
But there's a big difference from before then.
It's the fact that I'm not getting bullied anymore.
And also...
Your belly is starting to be noticeably big too, Akira.
Yeah, that's right.
I want to see our baby's face already.
Our relationship that's far
removed from reality continues.
Jeez... You're penetrating me so deeply!
Didn't we promise to do this on the island?
Since that day, I've become a cock slave only for you!
It's flowing in! A creampie into my baby room!
Yumi, won't it be long til everyone
finds out about your belly too?
You're right. Even if they all find out about this,
I'll be fine as long as I'm with you, Shouta-kun.
Then how about we get away from here and
live together just like back then in the island?
Yes, I'm happy!
I want to be together with you forever!
The semen that your poured
in my baby room is spilling out!
I'm back, everyone!
Welcome home, darling!
Darling, your cock is right next to the baby!
Shoot it out! Pour your thick semen in my pussy!
Is it Akira's turn today?
Whether it's on the island or back to our real lives,
I became a king.
Welcome home.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization