Ever since we washed up on this island, the girls
in my class were infected by an unknown virus.
They were always in heat, constantly aroused.
Fortunately, a doctor happened
to wash up on shore with us,
and she found that those who did
not regularly ingest semen would die.
Thus, the only way to avoid certain
death was to consume sperm.
As the only man on the island,
I'm the only one who can save them.
In other words, the only thing standing
between life and death for them is my dick.
Island of Conception
Hidden Island of Conception.
#2 Don't take it out until we make a baby...
It's so good! Your dick is so good!
My mind's going crazy!
Your dick is too good!
Getting rammed from behind is the best!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
It's coming! It's coming deep inside me!
I can't believe I'm doing it with a creep like you!
But my pussy's completely addicted to your dick now!
I guess that makes sense since it feels good,
and I don't wanna die.
C'mon, do me more!
Yeah, just like that!
It's digging so deep into me!
C'mon! Cum inside me again!
Get me pregnant! Knock me up!
Make me bear your creepy baby!
I'm cumming! In your deepest parts!
Do it!
Shoot out your semen!
So good... This is the best!
Good morning, Ai.
Does it feel good, Shouta?
Your dick's getting harder.
I'll do my best to make you feel good,
so give me lots of your semen, okay?
Your big, hot thing is getting wet
and slippery between my boobs!
I'm getting really hot too.
I want your semen so bad, Shouta!
Shove it in! Shove it in deeper!
You gave me so much! I'm so happy!
What shall we do next?
I want you to get me pregnant!
I wanna get pregnant before Ai
and become your number one girl!
Hurry! Hurry!
The semen's gonna get cold!
It's so good!
Look, Ai!
The semen's going into my pussy...
It's filling me to the brim!
I wonder if this'll get me pregnant.
I'm going to get pregnant first.
You can't jump in front of me!
As punishment for trying to cut the line,
I'm going to have you watch us make a baby.
Shouta's dick is going wild inside me!
It's stirring up the cum inside my pregnant pussy!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum from him ramming his cum inside me!
I'll share a little bit of the cum
I got with your poor pussy, Ai.
This... really isn't enough.
My body won't calm down!
I guess I'll have to ask him again.
You should know by now that
cold water doesn't do anything.
Don't be like that. I'm here because
you look like you're in so much pain.
I-I'm not!
You'll die if you don't ingest semen. Let me save your life.
That's not what this is...
You're good with just drinking it, right?
Don't rub it against my butt.
But you know that your cravings will
go away if you feel good, don't you?
I told you, it doesn't feel good...
N-No... This is making me feel weird!
Why did you cum on my back?
Oops. My bad.
I'll make sure you get your fill!
I can't... I can't breathe!
We can stop if you'd like, but I can keep going.
What's it gonna be?
Fine.
Have it your way.
Just put it wherever you'd like.
You're not very honest with yourself.
But, I don't mind.
It's... coming inside!
It's spreading me out! It's stabbing inside me!
You're twirling around my insides!
This is my first time!
But I already feel like I'm going to cum!
I love these tan lines!
Let's do it with your swimsuit on next time.
Don't touch...
You don't have to hold back. Blame it on the virus!
Wait! Stop, I'm really gonna...
I'm gonna cum inside you!
No! I-I'm cumming!
It's coming out!
It's pouring inside me!
You stole my first time...
This is the last time I'll let you cum inside me, okay?
In that case, I'll release inside you again.
No! My head's still spinning from last time!
No! Don't cum inside me!
It's coming out!
Even though I told you not to...
I'm gonna get pregnant!
Isn't that...
Dr. Ichijo?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Dr. Ichijo.
This last month has been heaven for me.
And it's all thanks to that virus you made.
Y-You think you can get away...
I found it all in that hidden laboratory.
I found that disgusting sexual report
that you wrote up about the virus
and the vaccine that you already have prepared.
So tell me, where's the vaccine?
I honestly can't believe that you had Kisaragi, our class
president, and even our teacher hidden down here.
The only thing left is you telling
me how to get off this island.
I'd like you to participate in this
experiment for a little longer.
How does that sound? I'll make you feel
more pleasure than you've ever felt before.
You're the one who wants to feel more pleasure, aren't you?!
I'm not gonna cum inside you until you tell me!
If you don't give me semen soon, the virus is gonna...
No! Seriously, please!
P-Please, I'm seriously at my limit!
I'll tell you!
Finally in a talkative mood?
Y-Yes! I-I'll tell you!
So please, cum!
I have another vial hidden deep in the lab.
That's good enough, isn't it? Hurry!
I'm going to lose it!
I've cum too much! I'm gonna die!
That wasn't so hard, was it? Then let's have
you savor this last bit of cum from me!
Cum! Please!
Semen! Give me your semen!
Make me pregnant!
Amazing! Your hot stuff is filling up my insides!
I'm definitely pregnant...
I have no more use for you.
The shipwreck incident is still fresh in our
minds even though it's been quite some time.
After getting off of that island,
life went back to normal.
Well, not exactly "normal".
I wasn't being bullied anymore.
Also...
Your stomach's gotten pretty big, Akira.
I hope our baby is born soon.
I want to see our baby!
Our almost unbelievable relationships still continued.
It's going deep inside me again!
I promised you on the island, didn't I?
Yeah, it was after that day that I
became a slave to your dick, Shouta.
It's coming! Your cum's hitting my baby room!
People might start noticing your stomach, Yumi.
Maybe. But even if they do,
I'm fine as long as I have you, Shouta!
Then how about we just start living
together like we did on the island?
Yeah! That'd make me happy!
I want to be with you forever!
Your milk's being poured into my baby room again!
Hey everyone, I'm home!
Welcome back, Dear.
Your dick's gonna make me give birth, darling!
Cum! Give me your first load from coming back home!
Oh, is today your turn, Akira?
I've returned home from the island as a king!
Welcome home!
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: ragingheartsexcelion
quality control: ragingheartsexcelion
softsub: торрент иваниваныч