You remember how tough the effects were?
It's already been a month since then.
These women were infected with
a virus that amplifies their sex drive.
Hey... Use my mouth too!
You can use it like a pussy if you want!
Shouta...
I'm coming!
You can still come this much?
It's pouring inside me!
Hey, Shouta-kun. You'll do me next, right?
Isn't this in "oldest first" order?
Hey, watch me!
Y-You suddenly came!
Afterwards, I'm now treated like this
on the uninhabited island.
This virus which will kill them unless they receive semen
twisted the common sense we all had.
Why does semen taste this good?
Jutaijima
- Fertilization Island -
Ura Jutaijima.
Ura • Jutaijima
- (The Other Side) Fertilization Island -
Why Does... Semen Taste... This Good...
The ship that we rode for
a school trip got wrecked in a storm.
Our lifeboats capsized as well.
We somehow miraculously drifted onto this island.
A-A corpse?
What's up with this place?!
Ichijou-san, the doctor supposedly from the same ship
informed us with the shocking truth of our situation.
This is...
Ai-chan!
If we won't receive our required semen intake,
the virus will proliferate and result in our death.
What are you doing at a time like this?
Didn't I tell this to everyone
many times already, Himura-san?
High fever, increased body temperature and intense palpitation...
Everyone here that caught
the virus had those symptoms.
Huh? What are you saying?
It's also accompanied by
an abnormally high sex drive.
Have you not realized it
within your own body yet?
According to the research data we got
from the corpse of that scientist,
the symptoms will show up when
our ovulation day draws near.
And then we will end up dying.
Th-That's... I don't want any of these!
What the hell is that?
What I'm saying is, why do we have to do that?
I'm afraid to say that there isn't any vaccine for it.
Haven't I we already found the
method to cure this infection?
We already confirmed that Shouta-san
is the only male in this island.
If you won't hurry, you might end up
not getting your own share.
No way... I'm fine if it's with my boyfriend,
but I'd never ever do it with Creep-o!
I... I don't want to die!
G-Give me your semen too... Please!
Huh?! A-Are you serious, Yumi?
These girls have been bullying me up until now!
And now their lives depend on my semen!
I don't like this, but its for my own survival...
...so I'll be able to return home!
It's disgusting!
No way!
This is making me dizzy!
Uhh-ahh... After I've had the trouble coming for you...
Let's just do this another time if you don't want it.
I-I want it! I'll do it properly!
I'm getting tired of this now. What should I do?
I'm begging you! Please give
me your semen! Please!
If that's so...
A-Am I doing it right?
Th-This is for my own survival...
For my own survival—
It hurts!
With this... I'm already—!
W-Wait a second!
Something hot is shooting into me!
What am I gonna do about this...
Even though I might have a baby from this!
Yumi...
I am a doctor, so I can help anyone on many
ways in case that they get pregnant.
So you don't have to hold back
and take his semen, okay?
I-I understand. I'll be fine to do this
with peace of mind, right?
No! This is... Ah!
Your semen is getting stirred inside me!
You're making a soppy mess of me!
I need you and the others too, Yumi-chan!
I will come as much as needed
for the sake of your survival, okay?
R-Really?
I-I'm afraid of getting pregnant,
but I want you to fill me inside
with your semen, Shouta-kun!
Please ejaculate!
There's so much of semen pouring inside!
He came a lot inside me, Ai-chan
I just have to stimulate this, right?
Uhm... Toume-san?
What? I'm gonna drink it because
I'm told that I'll die otherwise.
In regards of sex appeal, this isn't stimulating...
Compared to others, it's like
you're not showing sincerity...
Whatever, just shoot your semen out.
What's with this? It's disgusting.
It's slimy and it's sticks in my throat.
It feels like my body is heating up.
Getting off from a footjob...
Seems that you're a real pervert.
Yeah, my cock feels amazing!
You don't have to say it!
I'm already—!
Jeez... If you're gonna come, do it in my mouth!
My bad, my bad. I'll do it properly this time.
I just played with it using my feet...
Can you see it rubbing between my tits?
Compared to others, I'm told that for Toume-san,
taking my semen into her
stomach is more effective.
It seems that it was indeed true.
Semen... It's so much...
Shouta-kun, more... Pound me more!
You're too loud...
Woah... Yumi?!
It's rubbing all over inside my pussy!
Stop that, Yumi! You're not that kind of girl!
You look miserable, Ai-chan!
Huh?!
You were always bragging about your sexual
escapades, yet you couldn't do it with Shouta-kun.
Could you actually be that inept?
Huh?!
Shouta-kun's dick is huge and hard,
and it feels amazing too!
Whenever he comes inside, I feel like light-headed and fainting!
It makes me lose my mind!
Not inside, I'll get pregnant—!
The semen is gushing into me!
Here, have a look!
Shouta-kun poured his semen inside my pussy!
Yumi, you did it with that creepy guy...
If you want to survive in this island, you need to
rid yourself of that pride and do this!
Shouta-kun, let's show Ai-chan
how I hog all of your sperm!
S-Semen...
I wonder if I already got pregnant?
Yumi... It's is because you
showed me something like that...
I won't be able to get off just
with masturbating like this!
Isn't that right?
Only this one can satisfy you, right?
C-Creep-o?!
I can lend this to you if you want to, Himura-san.
I really don't want to do it with you,
but my body won't listen! Do something about it!
This thing is nothing like my boyfriend's... It's huge!
It's still getting bigger? He's way beyond
what I thought, even when he's just a Creep-o!
Just how big can he get?
That feels good, Himura-san!
Get satisfied already, is he still not coming?
If I don't hurry up, I'm going to die!
Wh-What's happening?
Just from gulping Creep-o's juice...
It's just like Yumi said!
Our lives depend on this, so we have no choice!
Creep-o's cock is going deep inside me!
Your hot and stiff cock is
hitting my deepest parts!
I never had something this deep in me before!
Seriously, this is awesome!
It's way better that my boyfriend's!
I'm coming already... I'm coming, I'm coming!
I-If you squeeze me that tightly—!
Something hot is pouring in me!
This is bad, you'll get me pregnant!
I-I might get pregnant, I should stop it here...
But I can't hold myself back!
I'm using the technique I learned
for my boyfriend to you instead!
It's because I need your semen!
I'm working this hard for you!
Hurry... Shoot your semen out, shoot it all out!
You're just a Creep-o, yet you're amazing!
That's everyone... who took in my semen.
Isn't that great? You're saving people's lives.
You should also help other girls if possible.
Okay!
Good answer. I'm grateful that
you're cooperating in my research.
I wonder if anal sex will have an effect
on the advancement of symptoms as well?
You ejaculated an amazing amount as always.
When a woman is infected by the virus,
she won't be able to resist
craving to drink your semen.
Even if she doesn't want to at first,
it won't be long before she changes her mind.
All of the women in this island
are all yours to be raped anytime in any way you want.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization