This is driving me crazy!
It's been one month.
These three girls have had their libido subjugated by the virus.
Hey, please use my mouth, too!
Just use it like a pussy!
Shouta.
You can still shoot out this much cum?
It's coming. It's coming out!
Hey, Shouta-kun.
You're going to do me next, right?
I'm up next, you know.
Hey, look at me properly.
It suddenly squirted out!
Soon, this uninhabited island will gain a new name.
This virus forces them to take in my semen, or else they'll die.
Some of them have lost their mind over time.
Hey, why does cum taste so good?
Alter - Impregnation Island.
The ship we took for our elective classes went off course here.
None of the lifeboats made it, either.
By some miracle, all of the survivors
managed to wash up on this island.
A-A corpse?
What the hell is this place?
Ichijou-san, the doctor who happened to be aboard the ship,
enlightened us on the shocking situation.
This is...
Ai-chan!
A virus that kills those who don't take in semen,
has spread all over the island?
What are you trying to do at this time?
I've told you countless times, Himura-san.
It's a fever so hot that it burns the body,
and causes severe palpitations.
All of these are symptoms caused by the virus on this island.
Wait... what?
An extreme form of sexual arousal.
Are you starting to follow along?
According to the documents we found on
that abandoned facility beside the corpse,
the symptoms worsen at the peak of our ovulation cycle.
Death is certain if it's not treated.
Th-That can't be.
I don't want this.
What the heck is that?
That doesn't mean we have to do something depraved.
I'm sorry, but there wasn't any information about
a vaccine hidden in the papers we found.
Shouta-san is the only male on this desolate island.
If you don't hurry,
he'll run out of cum to share.
See?
If it was my boyfriend, I would have done it already.
This creepy freak is out of the question, though.
I... I don't want to die.
Please... give me your cum, as well!
What?
Yu-Yumi, are you serious?
These girls who bullied me for so long,
now depend on my cum to survive.
I don't like this.
But if it means surviving and heading back home...
So gross.
Give it to me.
Man, I unleashed that load just for you.
If you don't want to,
then we'll continue next time.
I-I want to!
I'll do it properly!
I've gotten sick of you, anyway.
I wonder what I should I do.
I beg of you!
Give me your cum.
Please!
In that case...
Is... is this okay?
It's so I can survive, it's so I can survive...
It hurts!
This is already...!
Just wait...!
It's pumping straight into me.
What should I do with this?
I'm pregnant now.
Yumi.
I'm a doctor, so I can assist anyone that's impregnated.
So please, don't hesitate to take your dose of cum.
I understand.
So I don't have to worry, right?
No, this is...!
Your cum is sloshing around inside.
My insides are getting messed up.
I need everyone too, including you, Yumi.
I'm prepared to cum as much as I can to help you girls live.
Really?
I don't want to be impregnated,
but please, I want lots of your cum inside me.
Pump your load into me.
There's so much cum!
Ai-chan, he came so much inside me.
I just need to stimulate this thing, right?
Umm... Toume-san?
What?
I called you out here because she said I'd die if I don't drink cum.
I just want to say that it's rather, lacking...
Even though you've fallen behind the others.
I don't care.
Just cum already.
What's this?
It feels gross.
It's dinging to my throat.
My body is heating up inside.
You're such a pervert requesting me to caress it with my feet.
My dick feels so good.
You don't have to say it out loud.
I'm going to...!
Hey, you need to tell me when you're about to cum.
Sorry about that.
I'll do better next time.
It just stained my crotch, and it already...
This is making me look like the pervert.
It seems that the rumor that you're
smitten with this situation is true.
I never knew cum could be this...
Shouta-kun!
More, please fuck me more!
Geez, shut up already...
Yumi?
My insides are being churned up.
You can't do this! This isn't like you!
Ai-chan, how pathetic.
What?
You're the one who's always bragging about sex,
and yet you haven't fucked Shouta-kun yet.
Could it be you're actually shy?
His dick is so big and thick. It feels so good, you know.
My mind just goes blank whenever he cums inside me.
I don't know what's going on anymore.
Stop, don't! You'll get pregnant!
In goes the thick cum!
Here, look.
He came lots inside for me.
Yumi, this creepy guy is just...
To survive on this island,
you have to throw away your useless
pride, and fuck without restraint.
Shouta-kun, show me how I hog your cum.
C-Cum...
I wonder if I'm pregnant now.
That Yumi, showing off everything...
Masturbating isn't satisfying at all.
I can't quell the symptoms this way.
I know, right?
It's not satisfying unless you get fucked by this, right?
S-So gross!
So long as you consent, Himura-san,
I'll be willing to lend this to you.
I hated the thought of fucking you,
but please quell my body's urges!
This... puts my boyfriend's penis to shame!
It's getting even bigger?
You've got quite the package despite being a creep.
Just how big can this thing get?
Himura-san, it feels amazing.
He's not gonna climax even though he's so aroused?
I'm going to die if he doesn't cum soon.
Wh-What the hell is this?
I just got a good whiff of it, and I'm already...
See? What did I tell you?
Logic goes out the window when your life's on the line!
Your gross thing is slowly penetrating me.
Your hot and stiff thing is rubbing my insides.
This is the first time I've ever been penetrated so deep.
This is something else.
My boyfriend's penis can't hold a candle to this.
I'm going to cum soon.
I'm cumming, I'm cumming!
If you keep clamping down on me like that...!
Your filthy cum is filling me up.
Oh crap, I'll surely be impregnated.
Though, I can't go back even if I do become pregnant.
I'm now pleasuring this creep with the
techniques I used on my boyfriend.
I'm letting your cum reach my womb,
so you've got to let me bask in the pleasure.
Come, cum already.
Cum, squirt it all!
You're marvelous, despite being a creep.
That's all.
Those are all the girls that I've cummed inside.
This is incredible.
You just saved their lives, you know.
Don't forget to help whoever you come across, okay?
Yes.
Good answer.
Let me thank you for all your hard work.
I wonder if the symptoms will be treated through anal sex.
You came so much as usual.
As the virus ravages the body,
women get the urge to drink your cum.
They may resist at first,
but sooner or later, they'll crave it.
All the women on this island must adhere to this rule.
So just rape them to your heart's content.