This is seriously good! Holy shit!
It's been a month since that day.
Since they were infected by a virus
that amplified their sexual desires.
Hey, use my mouth too!
You can use it like you'd use my pussy!
Shouta...
I'm cumming!
You still have that much cum left in you?
It's coming! It's filling me up!
Hey, Shouta-kun, you're going to do me next, right?
This isn't in order of age, you know?
Hey, focus on me!
Y-You came without warning!
There's a reason why this is an uninhabited island.
The virus requires you to consume a large
amount of cum, or else you die.
It throws all our common sense out the window!
Why does cum taste this good?
Island of Conception
Hidden Conception Island.
#1 Why does cum taste this good...?
The boat we were on for a field
trip was caught up in a storm.
We were able to escape on lifeboats, and as if
by a miracle, we safely washed up on this island.
A-A dead body?!
What is this place?!
Ichijou-san announced the shocking truth
about what we were getting into, marooned here.
What is this?
Ai-chan!
This island is plagued by a virus that kills
the infected if they don't consume semen?
Hey, what are you doing?!
Himura-san, I've told you already, haven't I?
The fever, your body's raised temperature, your elevated
pulse... they're all because of the virus on this island.
Huh?! What are you talking ab...
Don't you feel an increased urge
to engage in sexual activities?
According to the research materials I found on that body,
we've been infected and will soon
be exhibiting the symptoms.
And we will die.
That can't be true! I don't want to die!
That makes no sense!
Why do we have to do what you're doing?
Unfortunately, there were no signs
of any vaccines or treatment.
The only male we found on this island was Shouta-san.
If you don't hurry, there might not be enough left for you.
Right?
I'd do it if he was my boyfriend,
but I don't want to do it with him!
I... I don't want to die!
Please give it to me...
Give me your semen!
Huh?!
Y-Yumi?! Are you serious?!
These girls have done nothing but push me around!
And now they can't live without my semen?!
I don't want to do this, but I don't want to die!
This is all so I can go home again!
It's so gross!
No... It's swelling up!
Oh, that sucks. You wasted my cum.
If you don't want to do it,
we can save this for another time...
No, I want to!
I'll do it right this time!
I'm kind of bored now, though.
What should I do?
P-Please! Give me your semen!
I beg you!
If you want it, then...
Like this?
I need to survive!
I absolutely have to survive!
It hurts!
This is gonna make me...
W-Wait!
Your hot stuff is flooding out inside me!
What should I do about all that?!
It's gonna get me pregnant!
Y-Yumi...
If you get pregnant, I'll help you out. I'm a doctor.
So just take in as much semen
as you want without worrying.
Okay, so I don't have to worry about anything, right?
N-No... This...
You're churning the cum around inside me!
It's mixing in with my liquids
and turning into a huge mess!
I need you all as much as you need me.
I'll cum as much as I need to, to keep you all alive.
R-Really?
I-I'm scared of getting pregnant,
but please fill me up with your semen, Shouta-kun!
Blow your load inside me!
There's so much semen inside me!
Ai-chan, he gave me so much!
I just need to stimulate this, right?
Um, Toume-san?
What?
I was told that I'd die if I didn't drink it. That's why I'm here.
I know you're not as slutty, and are usually more reserved,
but to do this just because the others got a head-start...
Whatever. Just cum already.
What is this? It's so gross.
It's sticking to my throat.
I think my body's heating up!
You really want me to do it with my feet? You pervert.
My dick feels so good!
Keep that to yourself!
I'm...
If you're going to cum, do it in my mouth.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'll do it right next time.
Even the slightest touch is making me...
My boobs feel so good!
It looks like what I heard about Toume-san
being more sensitive to touch was true.
There's so much semen...
Shouta-kun! More! Shove it deeper in me!
Keep it down a little...
Y-Yumi?!
It's rubbing against my pussy so hard!
What are you doing, Yumi?! You're not that kind of girl!
Ai-chan, you're so pathetic!
Huh?!
You always bragged about how much sex you've had,
but you haven't even touched Shouta-san once.
Maybe you were just lying?
Huh?!
Shouta-kun's dick is really big and hard...
it feels really good!
And when he cums inside me,
I feel so warm and fuzzy!
I can't even think straight!
It's no use! I'm gonna get pregnant!
His semen's pumping out inside me!
Come on, look!
Shouta-kun gave me this much cum!
Yumi... you really did it with that lecher?
Throwing away your pride to live is
the best thing you can do on this island!
Shouta-kun, show Ai-chan how I take in your semen!
S-Semen...
I wonder if I'm pregnant now.
Yumi... She just had to show me all that.
Now masturbating isn't enough!
I can't calm down!
Of course you can't.
You can't satisfy yourself without this, can you?
Y-You creep!
I'd give this to you if you asked me to.
I never, in a million years, want to do anything
like this with you, but please save me!
It's so much bigger than my boyfriend's...
It's getting bigger?!
How does this creep have such a huge package?!
How is it so big?
Himura-san, that feels really good!
I hate this so much! Can't you cum already?!
I'm going to die if you don't hurry up!
Wh-What's going on?
I'm getting really turned on just from the smell.
Yumi was right. Our lives are at stake.
I don't have a choice, right?
Your filthy dick is coming so deep inside me!
Your hot, hard thing is reaching my womb!
I've never had it so deep before!
This is seriously too good!
My boyfriend's nothing compared to this!
I'm gonna cum already!
I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum!
I-If you tighten around me that much...
Your hot stuff's shooting out inside me!
Holy crap, you're gonna get me pregnant!
I don't think I can stop, even if I'm pregnant now.
I'm using all the techniques I learned
to please my boyfriend on this creep!
You can cum whenever you want!
Just give it to me!
Hurry up and cum! Give me your cum!
You might be a creep, but you're good at this.
And those are all the people I gave my semen to.
Good job!
You're saving lives here.
Be sure to give everyone as much of your semen as possible.
Understood!
Good answer.
Thank you for helping me with my research!
I wonder if the same symptoms
will present, even with anal sex?
The amount you cum never ceases to amaze me.
When the effects of the virus get too strong,
the infected will crave your semen immensely.
They might not want to at first,
but they'll come around eventually.
You can fuck the women on this island
whenever and wherever you want.
translator: hikarucon
timing: mr.mew
typesetting: bl4cc4t
edit: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч