Where always there is a God...
there is also a devil.
Where always "Chojin" is...
is also "Kyo-O" not far.
What came about up to now...
An old legend says
that every 3000 years...
a being manifests
that unites all three worlds and...
creates a powerful empire.
This being, called Chojin,
is the destination of Amanos search.
In Nagumo an inconspicuous boy...
he believes to have found the Chojin.
I can't control myself again...
3000 years sleep...
However, now I have returned!
Master! I have seen him!
No doubt, Nagumo is Chojin!
What did u say?!
Amano becomes witness of
Chojin's incredible strengths.
Akemi, I will always be with you.
Chojin's power inside him
Nagumo's fate takes it's way.
The love to his girlfriend Akemi
develops stormily...
Nevertheless evil's dark shadows
pursue him.
Soon after a second creature appears...
which is obsessed with destroying Chojin.
Suikakuju! You're still alive?
Chojin is not
what you think of him!
What did you say?!
Niki who becomes a monster himself
through a pact with the evil...
Yet also from other sides threats lurk...
The Mage Faust Münchhausen II
works on...
resurrecting Kyo-O,
who is Chojin's opposite existence.
Mom! Dad!
For this intention he has chosen Takeaki,
Nagumo's cousin.
Yet before the summoning ritual is ended
Amano intervenes.
Takeaki...!
Takeaki...
Nagumo...
Then at last when Nagumo
and Akemi find together...
Nagumo's power shows itself...
and brings the apocalypse to all three worlds.
Die drei Welten werden zerstört!
Choro!
Nagumo continues his crusade of the annihilation.
Then you are...
I'm the child of
Nagumo and Akemi.
I'm the one you're looking for
the true Chojin.
Finally Amano finds out the truth...
about the legend of Chojin.
Yet he isn't born...
Akemi still carries Chojin in her.
He is the one who let me return.
He destroys the three worlds
for my return.
He is a demon of annihilation.
You can't do anything
to stop him, Amano.
Akemi can't die before I was born.
Also Nagumo has no choice
as to fulfill his mission.
Stop it! Let both become
human beings again.
End the horro... Chojin!
Amano there is nothing
that should worry you.
Very soon I will have created new world
in which my parents will live
as humans again.
Really?
Will it be like that?
Of course.
In this new world finally
their love will be fulfilled.
Destruction always comes with new life.
This is only the beginning.
Will you sustain the time
of annihilation, Amano?
If it's followed by blossom I will sustain.
Even if it takes hundreds
or thousends of years.
I will be witness of your future
and that of Nagumo and Akemi.
Up to this day I will hold out!
Then the destruction began.
Two weeks later...
Current coordinates: 7-12.
Recording runs...
Destination was destroyed
no survivors.
It is time, Sir.
The hotline...
Indeed!
Hello?
Mr. Präsident...
The rest of our wing arrived
in the target area.
We are ready for the attack.
Which Destination?
Osaka, Japan.
Osaka... Japan?
There we located the infernos' origin.
As you command, Sir. Destination: Osaka, Japan.
Good luck.
My mission is completed.
John, what the...
There is not any back anymore.
He rose and will destroy everything.
Let's do it... a last time!
Destination: Osaka. Program
all rockets on the destination.
Do we really save mankind with this...?
Captain!
A not identified object approaches!
Speed... 250 Knots!
What?!
It disappeared...
What happened?
It's HE, Nagumo!
To hell with him!
Urotsukidoji
Die Rückkehr!
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 1 Part 1
20 years after the destruction a new
order forms out of the ruins.
The apocalypse produced a new race.
Neither human nor animal nor demon...
They are called Makemonos and
are disfigured by the inferno.
What's wrong boy?
Your time hasn't come yet.
I come... Mom,
I don't want wait any longer.
Chojin...
The Chojin! It's the birth of Chojin!
What...?
Amano, what happened?
Why now already...	?
What's the meaning of this?!
What the...! Akemi...?
What happened Akemi?
I have waited for you, Amano.
Are you... Chojin?
How did you do, Amano?
I dreamed of you...
I know.
Why now? Prophecy says
you should be born in 100 years.
Was it a lie? What happened?
That, what had to happen.
In the east the evil was born
It will try to kill me.
Why does it want to kill you?
Aren't you immortal...?
Everyone can die... I'm not an exception...
Currently my enemies are very strong...
Maybe there can't arise
a better world in this generation.
Amano! You must protect
me from the evil!
I beg you, Amano!
But... how do I recognize the evil?
Chojin!
Brother!
Seems a Bastard hunts the Chojin...
The Chojin...?
Where always there is a God...
there is also a devil.
Where always "Chojin" is...
is also "Kyo-O" not far.
Where am I supposed to search for the evil...
I will try it in the east...
There it will have to meet me...
and then I will destroy it...!
Human women have a deliciously tender skin...
That feels in a really heavenly way...
Now you will pay for
your superciliousness...!
Buju...! That is our booty...!
In this realm all
women belong to me.
Evil of the east!
Disappear!
It has been a long time since
I fucked a human woman...
We will have much fun together!
I can hardly await it.
No! Stop it!
Already again... what the hell
is the meaning of this...?
Caesar's troops!
Caesar! Caesar!
Finally I found you, Kyo-O.
Now you are mine.
Don't let him flee or you will
pay for it with your lives.
Catch him!
Please take me with you!
Am I your nurse?
Watch how you can manage it.
Caesar's troops aren't a joke.
Take me to Kyo-O...
I want to use his magic power
for myself. I implore Kyo-O!
Where is he? Take me to his trace!
Here you are, Faust.
Caesar, my Lord.
He escaped again...!
My Lord, I have an idea.
Soon Kyo-O will be your prisoner.
Fine. I can hardly await it.
Chojin in Osaka is the only one
who can endanger our plan.
However if we gain the power
to destroy him...
nothing can stop us.
Yes, Caesar, we will conquer Chojin
and will rule the world.
By the way, is our small one
ready for his mission?
Don't worry...
Everything develops as planned.
The heart, which was teared
out of Nagumo's body,..
is fed with hatred of thousends
of murdered kins...
But it takes still some time
till he is complete.
Stay up! Pull yourself togther!
Pal... give me some water...
That guy is almost dead.
Out of the way with you!
Grace... please grace...
Damn...
Dumbass do you want to die
aswell?! We must survive.
Listens to me, Unworthy!
If you want to live keep on working.
Work for Caesar!
Move! Work!
Makemonos... poor creatures.
Born while the three worlds died.
Why only my father hate
them that much?
Alector... something you do here
in the darkening, darling?
Father!
Do you again observe the underworld?
When finally will you show me this world?
That's nothing for you...
The beauty of your skin would
suffer from the air there.
You shouldn't get in touch with the scum there.
You are my only daughter and I want you...
to stay with me forever.
You shouldn't go away from me...
You shouldn't meet anyone...
You are my single, beloved daughter...
Do you understand me, Alector?
Yes... father!
I will always be your obedient daughter...
Alector, my sweet child.
Bastard!
Is there another one disturbed
by my manners?!
Please... leave my pub.
This depends on you.
Seems today is my lucky day...
Could this freak be Kyo-O?
He doesn't seem to be a more
equal opponent for Chojin.
Still there is something about him...
But I don't know what...
Buju... we searched for you.
Who on earth are you?
I don't know you.
We are the servants of
the priest of Kyoto.
We are supposed to send you an embassy of the Gods.
You are a chosen one, Buju.
Me, a chosen one?
Yes, Buju.
At full moon, in the valley of the
eagle, the prophecy will fill.
What was that...? Come now...!
Yes...!
Chosen by the Gods? Seems
in the end it's worth...
to observe this guy.
But who is the priest of Kyoto?
Amano!
Mimi!
How did you find me?
The lust guided me!
You already need it again?
Yes and this time you won't get away!
Well these two have their fun.
Why shouldn't we?
Stop talking and give it to me!
Come on I need it!
You are already wet...
I want too...
Hard...
Suck hard, Babe...
And now the main attraction...
Harder...
That's it...
I'm coming...!
You were great, Buju...
Who are you...?!
What do you want, witch?
Shut up! I have still a suprise for you.
Faust, my Lord! We have something to enjoy!
Hold it, wait!
What the hell is going on here?
Amano!
You know my name, bitch?!
Out of my way!
Why? Do I disturb you?
Have fun, small one...
Amano, are you ok?
Why didn't you finish her?
She suprised me...
Wanna fuck, Amano?
Seems someone else also search for Kyo-O...
I wonder, who...
What...? He isn't Kyo-O?!
No, Caesar. This Makemono isn't Kyo-O.
Indeed folks call him "The evil of the east" but he...
isn't the one we search for.
If I shall die then kill me fast...
A Makemono isn't worth such an effort...
Interesting...
He isn't Kyo-O yet a special power comes from him...
We can find Kyo-O with his help...
Really...?
Buju... You sure will help us to find Kyo-O, won't you?
I never heard of this before.
Even if I knew about Kyo-O I wouldn't tell you.
You will help us trust me...
You will die if you oppose...
Ok ok! You win...
Nothing can stop us now...
What? Amano?
Yes!
So he is involved too...
Take the rat in it's hole.
It looks like my life ends here. In this darken cell,..
I will die as Caesars slave.
Are you a Makemono?
What...?
Who dares...?! Show you!
Poor creature...
What does she do here...?
What do you want?
You bleed...
I know but I'm still strong.
Therefore pay attention!
Yes, King Buju.
King Buju?!
King Buju, I have a request. Please show me the underworld!
The underworld? My home?
Yes!
The price is my freedom and your virginity.
Hold on!
I can hardly await it!
I will fuck Caesar's daughter...!
An adequate price...
for that I show her the dark and dirty underworld.
What?! Buju escaped?!
Yes, my Lord.
Still more bad news?
I can't find your daughter anywhere...
What?! Alector?!
Take a closer look...
That's the underworld.
Even animals deserve a better treatment.
The ruin us pitiful...
What do you think, why are we treated so bad...?
Caesors troops would like to as strong and potent as me...
They just have a lack of courage in their bones and dicks...!
Who is once here won't escape slightly anymore.
Fate played a stupid joke with us...
How could that happen?
The Princess and Buju escaped together...!
But we will find them.
I know their aim...
Alector!
Anyone here?
No one?
All this was constructed by imbecile believers.
But God... is dead!
However now to you.
It's time to keep your promise.
Sit down.
Spread your legs...
Wide from each other, further!
Very good, princess... and now
move your butt, Most Merciful...
Still a lilte more...
Only human women can move so randily...
Tears come to me from joy.
Buju... may we do this anyway?
You do that very skillful...
I have never had such a small obsequious catkin yet.
Show me more, Buju...
Wait, sweety... You will get what you desire.
Yes, there... great!
Buju... Buju!