Where always there is a God
there is also a devil.
Where always "Chojin" is...
is also "Kyo-O" not far.
What came about up to now...
An old legend says
that every 3000 years...
a being manifests
that unites all three worlds and...
creates a powerful empire.
This being, called Chojin,
is the destination of Amanos search.
In Nagumo an inconspicuous boy...
he believes to have found the Chojin.
I can't control myself again...
3000 years sleep...
However, now I have returned!
Master! I have seen him!
No doubt, Nagumo is Chojin!
What did u say?!
Amano becomes witness of
Chojin's incredible strengths.
Akemi, I will always be with you.
Chojin's power inside him
Nagumo's fate takes it's way.
The love to his girlfriend Akemi
develops stormily...
Nevertheless evil's dark shadows
pursue him.
Soon after a second creature appears...
which is obsessed with destroying Chojin.
Suikakuju! You're still alive?
Chojin is not
what you think of him!
What did you say?!
Niki who becomes a monster himself
through a pact with the evil...
Yet also from other sides threats lurk...
The Mage Faust Munchhausen II
works on...
resurrecting Kyo-O,
who is Chojin's opposite existence.
Mom! Dad!
For this intention he has chosen Takeaki,
Nagumo's cousin.
Yet before the summoning ritual is ended
Amano intervenes.
Takeaki...!
Takeaki...
Nagumo...
Then at last when Nagumo
and Akemi find together...
Nagumo's power shows itself...
and brings the apocalypse to all three worlds.
Die drei Welten werden zerstort!
Choro!
Nagumo continues his crusade of the annihilation.
Then you are...
I'm the child of
Nagumo and Akemi.
I'm the one you're looking for
the true Chojin.
Finally Amano finds out the truth...
about the legend of Chojin.
Yet he isn't born...
Akemi still carries Chojin in her.
He is the one who let me return.
He destroys the three worlds
for my return.
He is a demon of annihilation.
You can't do anything
to stop him, Amano.
Akemi can't die before I was born.
Also Nagumo has no choice
as to fulfill his mission.
Stop it! Let both become
human beings again.
End the horro... Chojin!
Amano there is nothing
that should worry you.
Very soon I will have created new world
in which my parents will live
as humans again.
Really?
Will it be like that?
Of course.
In this new world finally
their love will be fulfilled.
Destruction always comes with new life.
This is only the beginning.
Will you sustain the time
of annihilation, Amano?
If it's followed by blossom I will sustain.
Even if it takes hundreds
or thousends of years.
I will be witness of your future
and that of Nagumo and Akemi.
Up to this day I will hold out!
Then the destruction began.
Two weeks later...
Current coordinates: 7-12.
Recording runs...
Destination was destroyed
no survivors.
It is time, Sir.
The hotline...
Indeed!
Hello?
Mr. Prasident...
The rest of our wing arrived
in the target area.
We are ready for the attack.
Which Destination?
Osaka, Japan.
Osaka... Japan?
There we located the infernos' origin.
As you command, Sir. Destination: Osaka, Japan.
Good luck.
My mission is completed.
John, what the...
There is not any back anymore.
He rose and will destroy everything.
Let's do it... a last time!
Destination: Osaka. Program
all rockets on the destination.
Do we really save mankind with this...?
Captain!
A not identified object approaches!
Speed... 250 Knots!
What?!
It disappeared...
What happened?
It's HE, Nagumo!
To hell with him!
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 1
20 years after the destruction a new
order forms out of the ruins.
The apocalypse produced a new race.
Neither human nor animal nor demon...
They are called Makemonos and
are disfigured by the inferno.
What's wrong boy?
Your time hasn't come yet.
I come... Mom,
I don't want wait any longer.
Chojin...
The Chojin! It's the birth of Chojin!
What...?
Amano, what happened?
Why now already...	?
What's the meaning of this?!
What the...! Akemi...?
What happened Akemi?
I have waited for you, Amano.
Are you... Chojin?
How did you do, Amano?
I dreamed of you...
I know.
Why now? Prophecy says
you should be born in 100 years.
Was it a lie? What happened?
That, what had to happen.
In the east the evil was born
It will try to kill me.
Why does it want to kill you?
Aren't you immortal...?
Everyone can die... I'm not an exception...
Currently my enemies are very strong...
Maybe there can't arise
a better world in this generation.
Amano! You must protect
me from the evil!
I beg you, Amano!
But... how do I recognize the evil?
Chojin!
Brother!
Seems a Bastard hunts the Chojin...
The Chojin...?
Where always there is a God...
there is also a devil.
Where always "Chojin" is...
is also "Kyo-O" not far.
Where am I supposed to search for the evil...
I will try it in the east...
There it will have to meet me...
and then I will destroy it...!
Human women have a deliciously tender skin...
That feels in a really heavenly way...
Now you will pay for
your superciliousness...!
Buju...! That is our booty...!
In this realm all
women belong to me.
Evil of the east!
Disappear!
It has been a long time since
I fucked a human woman...
We will have much fun together!
I can hardly await it.
No! Stop it!
Already again... what the hell
is the meaning of this...?
Caesar's troops!
Caesar! Caesar!
Finally I found you, Kyo-O.
Now you are mine.
Don't let him flee or you will
pay for it with your lives.
Catch him!
Please take me with you!
Am I your nurse?
Watch how you can manage it.
Caesar's troops aren't a joke.
Take me to Kyo-O...
I want to use his magic power
for myself. I implore Kyo-O!
Where is he? Take me to his trace!
Here you are, Faust.
Caesar, my Lord.
He escaped again...!
My Lord, I have an idea.
Soon Kyo-O will be your prisoner.
Fine. I can hardly await it.
Chojin in Osaka is the only one
who can endanger our plan.
However if we gain the power
to destroy him...
nothing can stop us.
Yes, Caesar, we will conquer Chojin
and will rule the world.
By the way, is our small one
ready for his mission?
Don't worry...
Everything develops as planned.
The heart, which was teared
out of Nagumo's body,..
is fed with hatred of thousends
of murdered kins...
But it takes still some time
till he is complete.
Stay up! Pull yourself togther!
Pal... give me some water...
That guy is almost dead.
Out of the way with you!
Grace... please grace...
Damn...
Dumbass do you want to die
aswell?! We must survive.
Listens to me, Unworthy!
If you want to live keep on working.
Work for Caesar!
Move! Work!
Makemonos... poor creatures.
Born while the three worlds died.
Why only my father hate
them that much?
Alector... something you do here
in the darkening, darling?
Father!
Do you again observe the underworld?
When finally will you show me this world?
That's nothing for you...
The beauty of your skin would
suffer from the air there.
You shouldn't get in touch with the scum there.
You are my only daughter and I want you...
to stay with me forever.
You shouldn't go away from me...
You shouldn't meet anyone...
You are my single, beloved daughter...
Do you understand me, Alector?
Yes... father!
I will always be your obedient daughter...
Alector, my sweet child.
Bastard!
Is there another one disturbed
by my manners?!
Please... leave my pub.
This depends on you.
Seems today is my lucky day...
Could this freak be Kyo-O?
He doesn't seem to be a more
equal opponent for Chojin.
Still there is something about him...
But I don't know what...
Buju... we searched for you.
Who on earth are you?
I don't know you.
We are the servants of
the priest of Kyoto.
We are supposed to send you an embassy of the Gods.
You are a chosen one, Buju.
Me, a chosen one?
Yes, Buju.
At full moon, in the valley of the
eagle, the prophecy will fill.
What was that...? Come now...!
Yes...!
Chosen by the Gods? Seems
in the end it's worth...
to observe this guy.
But who is the priest of Kyoto?
Amano!
Mimi!
How did you find me?
The lust guided me!
You already need it again?
Yes and this time you won't get away!
Well these two have their fun.
Why shouldn't we?
Stop talking and give it to me!
Come on I need it!
You are already wet...
I want too...
Hard...
Suck hard, Babe...
And now the main attraction...
Harder...
That's it...
I'm coming...!
You were great, Buju...
Who are you...?!
What do you want, witch?
Shut up! I have still a suprise for you.
Faust, my Lord! We have something to enjoy!
Hold it, wait!
What the hell is going on here?
Amano!
You know my name, bitch?!
Out of my way!
Why? Do I disturb you?
Have fun, small one...
Amano, are you ok?
Why didn't you finish her?
She suprised me...
Wanna fuck, Amano?
Seems someone else also search for Kyo-O...
I wonder, who...
What...? He isn't Kyo-O?!
No, Caesar. This Makemono isn't Kyo-O.
Indeed folks call him "The evil of the east" but he...
isn't the one we search for.
If I shall die then kill me fast...
A Makemono isn't worth such an effort...
Interesting...
He isn't Kyo-O yet a special power comes from him...
We can find Kyo-O with his help...
Really...?
Buju... You sure will help us to find Kyo-O, won't you?
I never heard of this before.
Even if I knew about Kyo-O I wouldn't tell you.
You will help us trust me...
You will die if you oppose...
Ok ok! You win...
Nothing can stop us now...
What? Amano?
Yes!
So he is involved too...
Take the rat in it's hole.
It looks like my life ends here. In this darken cell,..
I will die as Caesars slave.
Are you a Makemono?
What...?
Who dares...?! Show you!
Poor creature...
What does she do here...?
What do you want?
You bleed...
I know but I'm still strong.
Therefore pay attention!
Yes, King Buju.
King Buju?!
King Buju, I have a request. Please show me the underworld!
The underworld? My home?
Yes!
The price is my freedom and your virginity.
Hold on!
I can hardly await it!
I will fuck Caesar's daughter...!
An adequate price...
for that I show her the dark and dirty underworld.
What?! Buju escaped?!
Yes, my Lord.
Still more bad news?
I can't find your daughter anywhere...
What?! Alector?!
Take a closer look...
That's the underworld.
Even animals deserve a better treatment.
The ruin us pitiful...
What do you think, why are we treated so bad...?
Caesors troops would like to as strong and potent as me...
They just have a lack of courage in their bones and dicks...!
Who is once here won't escape slightly anymore.
Fate played a stupid joke with us...
How could that happen?
The Princess and Buju escaped together...!
But we will find them.
I know their aim...
Alector!
Anyone here?
No one?
All this was constructed by imbecile believers.
But God... is dead!
However now to you.
It's time to keep your promise.
Sit down.
Spread your legs...
Wide from each other, further!
Very good, princess... and now
move your butt, Most Merciful...
Still a lilte more...
Only human women can move so randily...
Tears come to me from joy.
Buju... may we do this anyway?
You do that very skillful...
I have never had such a small obsequious catkin yet.
Show me more, Buju...
Wait, sweety... You will get what you desire.
Yes, there... great!
Buju... Buju!
An always horny bastard, this Buju.
What was that?
Buju, what's wrong?
Crying skin! I send you to hell!
Please! Don't hurt him!
Don't do it!
You mustn't kill Himi!
Who are you?
You are in my way!
I will end that pitiful yelling.
Don't!
Himi... Himi...
Buju...
It laughs. It laughs when I touch it.
Oh, how sweet!
Caesar, we found them. Trey are in the eagle's valley.
Bring Alector back to me, in an unscathed way!
Buju is alike to me.
Take care of my daughter.
Buju, the temple is surrounded.
Release Alector!
First this skin and now Caesar's troops...
Not a good day for Buju.
Buju, if you release Alector we will spare your life.
Let Alector go... now!
That many asses... and only because of me.
Buju!
He will kill you! He kills everyone who crosses his way.
Let's flee together! We will be save in your world!
They won't kill me.
They want to use my powers to find Kyo-O...
I love you, Buju! I want to stay with you forever.
You want to stay with Makemono like me?
Really...?
Stop it!
Don't shoot!
Alector...
Please, spare Buju! Please... father...
Please, I beg you...
Buju...! What did you do to Alector?
Buju!
You mustn't die...
Oh no! You are...?!
Buju...
Alector, I will never forget you...
Alector, I created you...
We don't need Kyo-O anymore...
because our creature will be soon ready.
Save Alector's body, Faust.
Yes. And Buju?
Kill him!
Thanks...
Why only must I die for a skin like you...
After you got Alector we will withdraw.
Something is wrong here. Who is that baby?
What's going on here...?
Something comes up...
It's Nagumo! Why does he return?
He wants that child! Then this baby must be...
Kyo-O!
Mother... He awoke. I will have to combat him.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Nagumo!
I thought, he was dead...
Faust!
Finally I found you, Kyo-O!
Your powers will serve me well.
What is this? What happened?
What is this?!
That's our chance to escape!
What are you doing?
I asked you what you were doing!
Long time no see, Amano.
Muenchhausen...!
Now you become witness of my power!
What?
You will see it...
Finally it's time!
Nagumo, try it! Try to kill that baby!
You know that it's your enemy...
No!
Kyo-O, what do you want to do now?
Great...
Remain here...
No... please...
Afraid...?
Almost half of my body is metal.
The body is only the wrapper of the soul.
Such a sensitive body!
Soon intelligent machines will rule the world.
Come here...
It's your turn.
I give you an ecstasy of pain...
No...!
Now Tagushi, how do you feel as a Japanese prime minister?
Fine, thanks... without your help I
would never have reached this goal...
I owe you a lot...
You moved any of my opponents
out of the way without hesitation.
This was only the beginning. Soon
I will control the whole world.
I will succeed with what failed to Hitler once.
What?
Hitler's obsession became his doom. Yet I'm realist.
I studied history of mankind.
My researchs took me here to Tokyo.
I'm sure that civilisation has it's origin here.
At no other place of the world you are closer to the Gods.
The ruins, I found, are the key...
to domination of the whole world!
8th FEBRUARY 1982
HOTEL AKASAKA, TOKYO.
It's a great honor to us to be allowed to greet you.
Father!
Alector, my daughter, are you alright?
Yes of course, father. Do we dinner together today father?
I'm afraid not. I still have much work
to do. You will have to eat alone.
Alector, your father is a very busy man.
You must understand that.
I'm sorry, Alector. But tomorrow I'm only for you I promise.
Oh father...!
How tall she became...
Unfortunately I have only too few...
time for her since her mother died...
This is the most important excavation place of the world.
It's as old as mankind itself.
These hieroglyphs tell the history of mankind.
They tell about emergence, past, presence...
and even about future of the world!
The future?
Yes it sounds unbelievable but everything fits.
According to the records our end awaits shortly.
It's said that besides our world
two other parallel worlds exist,..
one of the Demons and one of the Human-Beasts.
Every 3000 years...
a being called Chojin unites the three worlds.
More can not be made out. From
I here the boards are damaged.
It doesn't matter I will continue
history from here myself anyway.
I will summon Chojin and then I will kill him.
Then I will rule as God.
I will determine the future...
Caesar, we made it. We have a direct access...
to NASA's computer system.
Now finally we will receive the last answers.
Which time do these ruins come from?
17.000 before Christ...
+/- 2000 years.
How reliable is this answer?
80%. Max. deviation +/- 5%.
What does this information base on?
On all entered information.
With who is Chojin to be equated?
With God... God... God...
Why did Chojin appear on earth 17000 years before Christ?
In order to release the earth and to unite the worlds.
Was the old God MU involved?
No, Chojin and MU are not like-minded
They used their powers against each other.
Can you summon Chojin?
Only if I manage getting into contact with him.
Reunion of all capacities...
Establishing of contact runs.
Are you the one who called me?
Are you Chojin?
I am called like this.
Then die!
Now I will unite the three worlds!
Never underestimate the power of a God!
Father!
Alector!
Run away, fast!
You won't be able to stop the apocalypse.
Alector! Alector!
Chojin! Who ever you are you will pay for that.
Alector!
Alector, come back to me...
I miss your laughter...
Alector!
What? That baby?!
Yes, Himi was kidnapped by Faust.
Before however he still managed reviving you.
Nonsense!
Only Chojin has power to revive dead.
Maybe Himi has the power to kill Chojin.
So what?
That isn't a reason for me to free the baby.
Nevertheless there must be a reason why it revived you.
I guess it chose you to protect it.
That's your fate.
Fate...
Alike as insignificant, every being has its fate.
If insect, half-human, demon or human...
everyone has a fate which he can't escape.
On my search for Chojin I became
acquainted with many people...
They all were guided by strengths also
against the power of their love...
They all couldn't escape their fate exactly as you and I.
I don't know what expects us...
however, I know that my fate will fill...
alike, what happens.
Don't you think the same... Buji?
In fact I came here in order to annihilate Kyo-O, the evil.
However now I know that Himi, the baby, is Kyo-O.
No!
You mustn't kill Himi!
Sorry but I can't promise that.
Yet I don't see any danger which
starts from Himi at the moment.
And you, Buju? Which role will you play?
Which role...?
Caesar plans something with Kyo-O.
As I know him he will try to kill Chojin.
However I will not allow that.
I will annihilate Caesar and if necessary also Kyo-O.
Unless...
somebody would destroy Caesar's plan
and free Himi. You for example...
That's none of my business...
Think of that it's a question of Himi.
I go now to Caesar.
Think still once about everything, Buju!
Amano! Don't hurt Himi!
Forget Alector, Buju. You must be strong now.
What?!
Just shut up!
Let's see what Caesar and Muenchhausen plan to do...
Are those ones all?
Yes. I did my Best in order to bring some people.
Doesn't matter. Perhaps there will come some more.
Now to our plan...
We are at this place.
Here is Caesar's palace.
And here is the mine in which we had to work.
Some of us couldn't escape and are caught here.
We have no information about the black monster.
Nevertheless I fear what a lot of us were hurt.
Therefore we should act as fast as possible.
Ruddle, do we really do the right thing?
We can't go back now.
And we don't want it either. We
have to pay back much to Caesar.
It won't be easy.
I feel something...
Evil powers conentrate around Caesar's palace.
Something incredible will come up.
We must save our friends fast.
God gave every Makemono specific abilities and strengths.
Now it's time to use them.
Yeah, let's do it!
We will creep tomorrow morning into Caesar's palace.
You know what to do when we give you the sign.
Yes!
Caesar, all preparations are done.
We wait only for the awakening of Kyo-O.
Faust, I'm worried.
All events arrive as prophesied by the hieroglyphs.
I ask myself if we really can change history...
No worry, Caesar.
We have Kyo-O, the key to ultimative power.
When Kyo-O awakes and combines himself with Faburil...
even Chojin himself can't stop us.
Faburil? I thought he was destroyed by Nagumo?!
No, only a part of him.
However he regenerated.
He is now even more powerful and he wants revenge.
Tomorrow morning the union with Kyo-O will occur.
Actual?
Caesar!
What?
The restoration of princess Alector is completed.
Ah, finally!
Alector!
Oh, Alector...!
Show me your face, daugther!
What's wrong Alector?
Where is Buju?
He isn't here.
He is dead.
Father!
Have you killed him, father! Did you do it?!
No!
Alector...
Buju...
Alector... why...?
What happened to you...?
Father, do we eat this evening together?
Alector, I will revenge your death...
Kyo-O, Faburil,..
the nuclear missiles... Chojin will soon be dead.
Alector, I will create a new world only for you.
Caesar, we register changes on the psychowave monitor.
Faburil reacts to the power of Kyo-O!
What?!
Who are you? Why were you born?
If you oppose me I must annihilate you!
So you are nevertheless my enemy?
So it starts! Very good, Faust!
You are supposed to suffer, Kyo-O! That
is the key to the union with Faburil.
Faburil approaches to the palace, Caesar.
He claims many sacrifices also among our people.
Don't see to that.
Caesar... the nuclear missiles are ready.
Destination: Osaka.
The shooting occurs tomorrow morning. Start the countdown.
Start of the countdown.
Watch, there below!
What's that? What's going on here?!
Nothing good I fear. Come, run away from here!
Why does this monster appear here?
The disaster breaks about us.
Father, I have a good news. Soon your Project finishs...
and our family will control the whole world.
Alector, forgive me.
I just wanted you back.
Soon you could be the ruler of the new world.
Everyone would obey you.
Please, Alector, laugh again...
What, Kyo-O?! You refuse Faburil?!
What are you afraid of?
You are still a baby. You can't already know...
what power you have.
Open yourself and allow Faburil to enter!
That's enough, Faust! Leave the baby alone!
Too late, Amano! Kyo-O is already under my spell.
To release Kyo-O you have to kill me!
Are you able to kill me?
Wait for it!
Hold, wait, Muenchhausen!
Oh, Faust...!
You don't want to kill Faust, do you?
You again! We have still a fight open!
I'm ready!
Damn!
Buju... Buju...
Himi...
Buju, Help! Help me!
Are... Are you Himi?
You are very beautiful...
Buju...!
How warm you are...
What the hell...
Himi!
No fear!
What a sword!
Caesar...!
Caesar, Kyo-O was kidnapped by Buju!
What?!
They just escape from the palace!
Catch him! He mustn't escape!
Kill them!
Yes!
This dirty bastard! So he is still alive!
Is Kyo-O responsible for that...?
Buju is alive?!
Buju!
Alector!
No, please! No father, no!
You aren't my daugther...
Just an useless android!
You are mine!
No!
That hurts!
Forgive me, father!
No father, please!
Buju...
You will forget him now.
No!
How do you like that, Alector?
Do I give it to you better than this Makemono, don't I?
I take you to ecstasy...
An idea comes to me!
You want to see Buju, don't you? I
show him to you... for a last time.
I will tear him apart in front of your eyes!
Caution... Caution. Only 300 seconds till the shooting.
All employees into the safety zones.
I should have take insect spray with me!
That was only a small taste, small one!
Go to hell, bitch!
Somehow it gets uncongenially here!
Caesar, you bastard show yourself!
Alector!
So we meet again, Buju...
for the last time!
Alector, say goodbye to your lover!
It's your last chance!
Buju...!
Buju...
You can't kill me...!
Sorry but you can't help me.
I can't move.
Buju...
No...!
Makemono... Faburil will engulf you together with Kyo-O!
Buju!
Alector! Alector!
Alector...
Only 30 seconds till the shooting!
Muenchhausen! I will destroy you!
Too late!
Amano, you lost!
Hold, wait.