Where always there is a God there is also a devil...
Where always "Chojin" is there is also Kyo-O not far.
The destroyer Nagumo visited the world...
with rage if annihilation.
What came about up to now...
20 years later as already hew power
structures had formed themselves...
Chojin awoke from his sleep...
100 years before the prophesied time.
Chojin had awoke because in the
east Kyo-O, the evil, was born.
Why now? According to prophecy you
should not be born before in 100 years.
Did you lie to me?
What happened?
That what needed to happen.
In the east the evil was born.
It will try to kill me.
Ordered by Chojin, Amano went to east.
There the apocalypse has created a new race...
neither human nor animal nor demon.
They are called Makemonos and are
misfigured creatures of the inferno.
Beyond them was a scruple-free and merciless chief.
They called him Buju.
In this realm all women belong to me.
The evil of the east!
I know but I'm still strong! So pay attention!
Yes, King Buju.
King Buju?!
Buju... Buju!
It laughs. It laughs when I touch it!
How sweet!
Caesar we found them they are in the eagle's valley.
Bring me Alector back, in am unscathed way.
Buju is alike to me.
Please spare Buju.
Please... Father...!
Buju!
You mustn't die...
Amano ordered by Chojin to find and kill Kyo-O thought...
that Buju is his enemy.
Yet Amano wandered - Buju and
Alector, Caesar's daughter,..
escaped from Caesar's palace...
and had to pay their love with their lifes.
But then...
What's going on here?
Something bad is gonna happen...
It's Nagumo!
Why does he return?
What does he plan?
The child...
He wants that child!
Damn...
Then this baby must be...
Kyo-O!
Meanwhile the event is pursued by an opponent of Chojin...
the mage Faust Muenchhausen.
Now as we have Kyo-O it's the end of Chojin...
What? This baby!?
Yes Himi was kidnapped by Faust.
However before he still managed reviving you.
Nonsense!
Only Chojins has the power to revive dead.
Himi has maybe the power to kill Chojin.
So what...?
That isn't a reason for me to release the baby.
Yet there must be a reason why it revived you.
I guess that it chose you to protect it.
That's your fate.
Fate...
Meanwhile Caesar, the arch-enemy of Chojin, prepares...
a missile attack on Chojin's whereabout in Osaka.
Faburil and Kyo-O are supposed
to form a devastating alliance.
Suffer Ko-O! Pain is fhe key to the union with Faburil.
While Chojin in Osaka is in big danger...
Amano tries to release Kyo-O in Caesar's palace.
That's enough Faust! Leave this baby alone!
Too late, Amano. Kyo-O is already under my spell.
To free it you have to kill me!
Can you kill me?
Wait for it!
Hold, wait Muenchhausen!
Oh, Faust...
You don't want to kill Faust, do you...?
You again! We have a fight open!
I'm ready!
Damn!
Only 30 seconds till the shooting!
Muenchhausen! I will destroy you!
Too late!
Amano, you lost!
Hold, wait!
Urotsukidoji
Die Rückkehr!
- Part 2 -
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 2 Part 1
What the hell is this?
It looks like a gigantic cocoon.
Is Kyo-O for instance in there...?
The missiles... they fly to Osaka direction!
Finally the day of pay back has come...
Wait only, Chojin!
You sick bastard!
These missiles will never reach their destination!
Cursed scum! I don't have the time...
to see to you!
Help!
Caesar's palace! Storm Caesar's palace!
Finally the hour of the Makemonos
has come! Down with Caesar!
Let the world know that a new age began!
They reached the palace!
Caesar is still busy with his missiles...
But what if he notes the attack?
Will we still have a chance then?
We can think about that later!
Do you hear that?
The baby cries for help.
However how did it come into there?
We can clarify that later...
Go go, we have to conquer the palace.
If we don't overturn Caesar he will revenge terribly.
What?!
What should we do?
Just now!
These bastards!
Caesar, the Makemonos revolt.
They already have the prisoner camp under their control.
Doesn't matter we have more important things to do!
But Sir!
Shut up! Pedro, finish that.
Yes!
Situation report!
What is with Faust and the missiles?
Everything runs to plan.
They reach in a minute and 35 seconds the Fuji-sound.
Our fleet is 100 miles before the Ise-Bucht, course on Osaka.
The air wing is ready.
Fine... there should be nothing left of Osaka.
And now, Faburil... your time has come.
Do you still think that you can save Chojin?
Muenchhausen! What do you plan?
Now you will find out the power of evil!
It's stronger than all your powers.
Missile number 1 got off the course! It loses to height...
What?!
With best greetings!
Brother!
Damn...!
My brother is in danger!
Akemi...? Chojin!
What... What happens to me?
It's getting hot in me...
I burn!
The situation demands that I use also your powers...
Aren't you Amano's sister, are you?
I... how can I help you...?
My powers...?
You are so powerful...
Give it to me, please! I can't stand it! I need it...
Fuck me... fuck me! Please do it!
I'm coming! Oh, I'm coming...!
I'm coming...!
I'm still hot...
Fuck me... now fuck me!
So it be...
I will raise your Chojin-powers!
No! No, please... no!
Finally! He is born!
Where you hide yourself, Faust?
Fool!
I don't fall in on the same trick twice.
Give up, Amano!
Death waits for your Chojin!
What do you want to do against that?
Don't you prefer to serve me?
You would like that, don't you? You bastard!
What...?!
Another missile descended! Another missile descended!
What!? What does Faust there in fact?
Muenchhausen! You will never be able to realize your plan!
There are only 4 missiles left! And I will get them too!
Didn't you forget something, Amano?
What...?
The time of truth has come! Now
you can prove your strengths!
Damn! This monster is really giant!
Muenchhausen! That is only the beginning!
What the hell does he do there?!
Shit! A dead-end street again!
The sectors A4, B3 and C5 are again under control.
Good! No one mustn't reach Caesar's palace.
Shit!
You poor devils...! I will revenge you!
Enko! If it goes on like that we are lost!
What should we do now? And there is Ruddle with his people?!
What happened?
Energy fall in turbine 2...
Did it!
That wasn't hard...
What the... What's going on here?
Malfunction in reactor room 3. Turbine
2 destroyed no control anymore!
What?!
The Makemonos must have penetrated there!
Energy fall in turbine 1 and 3.
In this state we can't hold the balance anymore.
The palace slopes!
Therefore increase the energy in turbine 1 and 3!
The Makemonos keep on penetrating.
They come more and more closer...
Intruders in sector A4 and B5.
They move onto the palace!
Now do something about that! Am I only surrounded by idiots?!
The palace! They storm the palace!
Don't panic!
Attack! Don't show any mercy! Our time has come!
You are still alive?!
How you see!
You worm!
What?!
Now only one is left!
We lost contact with the fleet!
What?! To hell with that! What's with the missiles?
Four are destroyed, one holds still the course.
What about Faburil?
We still get his signal but it's very weak.
Caesar, the signal gets better again!
I knew it... this creature is unbeatable!
I... I'm coming! I'm coming...!
I'm coming...
Now my power will show itself...
Muenchhausen, admit your defeat! You lost! Give up!
Amano! Do you still think you can defeat me?
This beast is still alive...?
Faburil is the personified hatred! Try to destroy him...
and you create even more hate!
Brother...!
Megumi...
Last missile destroyed!
Faburil changed his direction!
That is all done by Chojin! We are lost!
Even Faburil and Kyo-O together aren't strong enough...
to defeat him.
The palace's balance is reconstructed to 89%.
Status is held. State of the supporting-system is still critical.
Find Caesar! Destroy him!
They are in the palace! They move onto the headquarters.
Caesar! Caesar!
Caesar, where are you?
Show you, Kyo-O!
Kyo-O, who gave you your power?
I can't remember to have testified you.
What...?!
No... that can't be...!
It's like this...! I wait for you in Osaka!
Stop it... Stop it...
Stop it!
We don't obtain a signal of Faburil anymore!
Part of the palace assails!
Withdraw!
Where are you, Caesar? Show you!
Alector... Farewell!
Alector!
Forgive me!
I couldn't revenge you...
It seems I lost everything although
everything worked very well...
Till this bastard appeared!
These cursed Makemonos should pay for that!
I congratulate you, Caesar.
Don't be disappointed like that...
Since finally you managed creating a new world.
Over 20 years passed since the great destruction...
and a new being arose like you wanted it.
What do you mean with that?!
The Alector-module which you
constructed was an perfect Androide.
It's impossible to distinguish her from a human being.
That's right! Das stimmt! But I still broke down!
Tell me, how will Chojin's realm look like?
What will happen to the world as we know it?
Caesar, in your task I have analyzed.
to 100 percent these ruins created by Chojin.
But about the Makemonos and the Alector-modul...
was nothing recorded here.
The world moves in a direction...
which even Chojin couldn't predict.
And more strange is that the Alector-modul carries...
new life in it.
The Makemonos and this new life...
will determine the fate of the mankind...
because they outdo Chojin's imagination.
And because it is Kyo-O who will lead them.
When Chojin and Kyo-O will meet each other in Osaka...
then there will be the answer for everything.
However I won't have this concurrence anymore.
The Makemonos have already made too much damage.
This also is fate...
Farewell... Caesar...
Fresh meat!
Buju! Buju!
Buju!
Hey! That bitch is Caesar's daugther!
The small one makes us to heros among the Makemonos!
Catch her!
Alector!
Himi! Himi!
What happened? What's wrong?
Buju!
What the hell...?
Damn Makemonos! I will never forgive them!
Anything might happen but I take them with me into hell!
No...!
Caesar, do you hear me?
No... please, stop it...!
Come out and show!
Show or we kill her!
But first we will have a bit fun with your daugther...!
Father, don't come! They will kill you!
It doesn't matter what they do to
me but stay where you are father!
Alector, are you ok?
Daddy's small daugther, eh?
No! Please...!
Stop...! Stop it... please!
She hardly awaits it...!
Ouch! No, no! Please don't...!
Where are you, Caesar?! Your small bitch is afraid!
Stop!
We still want to have fun till Caesar appears...
Do you like that?
An iron-hard steel penis, just for you!
When he starts you will be just dead meat!
But we won't kill you yet.
Say that you need it!
I need it...
You need it? You really need it...?
We help you!
Then go...
I want it...
Look at that!
That bitch is already as wet as a whole lake!
Come on let's give it to her!
I... I do everything you want. Everything...
That sounds well!
Then let's take a look on your juicy arid randy pussy!
Come on spread your legs!
Very good...
Hey, what's this?!
Spread your legs if you want to live on!
Yes...!
Hey, she is already very horny!
Hold, stop it you hurt me!
Me first! Yes... this is good!
Spred your legs more!
And how does my cock feel like?
Do you like it?
Oh... she is so warm... so wet...!
I'm coming...!
Yeah the perfect cock massage!
I want next!
No me!
Ouch no! Stop, it hurts!
That hurts... it hurts...!
Stop it!
Caesar!
Too late Caesar! Your daugther is already sucking our cocks!
Alector...!
To hell with you!
Father...
We got him!
We killed Caesar!
Alector was everything what I ever had!
For that I will tear your heads apart!