USAF 13th Bomber Wing
1944. The outskirts of Berlin.
Headquarters of the Vrill Association.
What is it? My God!
Now, let my god Astara Odin
be brought forth!
Are the gates of hell beyond
even your abilities?! Munhi Hausen!
Cowards... Don't they realize
that only HE can give...
...the Third Reich dominion
over the 3 realms?
Now! Begin the process!
What are you doing?
Papa! It's overloading!
- Something's wrong...!
- Impossible!
My Lord of Chaos comes!
Mein Fuhrer!
Munhi Hausen!
What's gone wrong?!
My Lord of Chaos...
Your failure to the Fuhrer
will not be tolerated!
What is this...?
TOKYO 199X
You called,
Munhi Hausen?
You wasted
no time, Kohoki.
You're the only human who
never runs from me.
So?
What is it this time?
Do you wish
to kill the Overfiend?
THE OVERFIEND?!
Sure, I'd love to.
But I'm not crazy enough
to actually try!
Whoever kills the Overfiend
will control the 3 realms.
No thanks.
Unlike certain humans I know,
I rather prefer staying alive!
Do you wish
to return to Hell?
W-wait! All right!
I'll help you!
I'll help you...
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Demon Womb
"A Prayer for the Resurrection
of the Lord of Chaos"
Trouble!
We've got major trouble!
Hold on!
Who do you think I am?!
FRONTIER OF PRISON'S GATE
I hate this stupid place!
Where're you taking me?!
Hey! HEY!!!
Where can he be?
He's gonna be too late!
I won't let you take
another step in here!
Why do you
defile this place?!
What's keeping him?
And he has the nerve to say
what a high and mighty...
Boss! Where were you?
I've been waiting!
What is it?
What happened?
That did it?
No?
Human...
A human did this?!
A human who controls
a demon? But why?
Overfiend's...
natural enemy.
Natural enemy?
Beware, Amano Jyaku...
Boss, look at this!
It's the guardian
deity of my people!
So you guys have
someone you worship?
Actually, my grandpa says
these ruins are 4000 years old.
What?! 4000 years old?
That's impossible.
They'd be older than the
legend of the Overfiend!
And nothing's
older than that...
Something's up, outside.
Come on, Kuroko!
Yessir!
What's going on?
Amano Jyaku...
It's Mimi!
Lady Mimi!
You alone? Why're you out
here at Prison's Gate?
I thought we could do it here,
without Grandpa to stop us.
Okay, I getcha.
A quickie?
More than that!
Boss, wait!
If the Elder finds out you're
with his granddaughter...
Oh, you're so good,
Amano Jyaku...
You're just gonna do it
out here, you... ANIMAL!
Shut up and go help Megumi
keep an eye on Nagumo!
Yes, sir...
We watch him all the time,
and nothing ever happens!
Don't talk like that!
It's the Boss's orders.
Boy, you're all smiles.
Are you really that happy?
Of course! I haven't seen
my cousin in 10 years.
I wonder what
Takeaki's like now.
You're that close...
I think I'm jealous!
You two were
like brothers.
Oh yes! Maybe even closer,
don't you think, dear?
Oh yes. Tatsuo must be
quite the young man, now.
You'll have fun with him,
like when you were children.
- They're not kids anymore!
- Yes, you're right!
Is that it?
Yeah!
That's the plane!
Captain! We've got a
problem in the #4 engine.
Captain? Captain!
What the hell?!
Mom!
Mom! Dad!
Takeaki...
- Takeaki!
- Nagumo!
Demons, I'll bet...
But why?!
Hold off on that side!
Careful, now!
Over here! Hurry!
I think he's still alive!
Takeaki... Takeaki...
He's gotta be okay...
Takeaki...
He needs blood
immediately! Hurry now!
TAKEAKI!!!
No!
You can't go in there!
- Lemme go!
- Hey...!
Takeaki!
TAKEAKI!
Doctor, you gotta help him.
He's my cousin!
My blood... Give him my blood!
We're both type O!
Doctor, please!
Come with us.
Megumi, a transfusion
from Nagumo...?
And so Takeaki Kiryu,
the lone survivor of...
...the airline crash 4 days ago
is set to be released tomorrow.
Congratulations! Let's hope he
gets over this tragedy soon.
And on that note, next up
is the Mu Orchestra...
...with "Sole Survivor".
Enjoy!
Yeah...
Like that... Yes!
Oh yes...
Can't believe how
horny she is... Oh well!
Perfect!
Yeah, just try and
catch up with me!
Pretty fast.
What's he driving?
Did you hear
news this morning?
Yeah. On the the highway.
What's happening to this city?!
I'm scared...
Don't be! I'm always with you,
and I'll always protect you!
- You mean it?
- Sure.
Same old,
same old...
So, Megumi, do you think the
Demons caused the latest murder?
Nope...
We've lost Nagumo!
Forget him. I'm waiting
for someone else.
Megumi-i-i-i!
She's always here.
Hurry up and find her!
Megumi?
Are you here?
Where are you,
Megumi?
What do you
want this early?
Megumi!
Please have some! I hope you
like this batch, too!
Again?
Oh well...
- Captain!
- Captain, snap out of it!
Still...?
Yeah...
I want him! If we had
him on the team...
Hold it!
Try me!
You're strong, but I don't
think you can beat me.
It's him...!
I don't fight girls.
You win!
Megumi!
Sorry. I guess I went
a little crazy just now.
By the way, you really should
wear something under that.
My name's
Takeaki Kiryu.
Sorry I acted like that.
I'm pleased to know you!
Not half as pleased as me!
We need a guy like you!
You're incredible!
Same 'ol Tatsuo.
I guess... But when did you
get so good at fighting?
The whole school's
talking about you!
I got good at it in school
when I was in London.
Man! And you were such a
crybaby when we were kids!
You only just got out of
the hospital yesterday.
Don't push yourself!
Thanks for worrying
about me, Akemi.
I was worried, too!
Megumi...!
I'm Megumi Amano.
How do you do?
H-hi...
You were great.
A real champion!
Strong men make
me weak in the knees.
You're a cheerful
one, aren't you?
But!
Next time, don't hold
back when fighting me.
You won't lose, then.
S-sure...
You fought Megumi?!
The secret's out!
So, tell me about yourself.
Gotta girlfriend?
Oh no you don't, Megumi!
You're not corrupting HIM!
Oh, too bad.
There's the bell.
Guess we'll have to continue
this after school. Let's go!
Jerk!
I suck at Math and Chem...
They're just too boring.
Takeaki!
See ya later!
Megumi... huh?
Hey Takeaki!
We gotta go!
Almost had him...
Megumi, shouldn't we
tell the Boss about this?
Megumi?
Huh?
What's with you?!
- Really?
- That's right.
I can't believe you were
released only 3 days ago!
Yeah...
I'd really like to thank you
for everything you've done...
Especially finding that
apartment for me...
What're you talking about?!
We're family, right Mom?
Exactly.
And if there's any problem there,
be sure and ask us for help.
Or if you need
anything to fix it up.
S-sure...
It's a shame
about your parents...
But you survived, and that's
something to be thankful for.
I wish we could've done more
for the funeral service, though...
Would you two cut it out?
He's just gotten over it...
Forget it, Tatsuo. You've all
been so great to me.
Sorry I brought it up.
Forgive us.
Oh Dad, you should get Takeaki
some sportswear next time.
He's turned into a real jock
since we were kids!
Yes, I can see that.
He's looking great!
A real man, now.
- Yes, a fine young man...
- Very fine...
You'll have fun with him,
like when you were children.
- They're not kids anymore!
- Yes, you're right!
Not again...!
- What's wrong?
- Are you alright, son?
I'm fine.
Just a little dizzy.
Maybe you have
been overdoing it.
Yes, I think you should go
home and get some rest.
Oh man, it's just
like with Ozaki!
Takeaki!
Need some help?
I'm fine, really!
I'll take you someplace
really great tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Tatsuo.
I hope he's all right...
I guess he's going
home alone... Huh...?
Where'd you go?
Megumi?
In other news, a man's
body was discovered...
...in Nishiguchi Park
early this morning.
The man, identified as
Mr. Masahiko Aida of...
...Nerima District, is believed
to be the latest victim...
...of the so-called
"Night Stalker".
The discovery of a lady's handbag
on the scene supports this theory.
No... I don't know
anything about it!
I don't know...
No! It isn't me!
Dad, Mom... Help me...
He's fighting
the blood inside him...
Damn!
Where'd he go?!
It's ready.
Looks good.
I try my best!
Shall I open the wine?
Sure. I'd love some.
There you go.
Thanks, dear.
Oh, Takeaki,
you're home!
Come in. I'll let
you drink with me.
Dad... Mom!
What's wrong, son?
Come in already!
Awaken, Takeaki.
Awaken...
I've been waiting.
Who...
Who are you?
My name is Munhi Hausen.
And I am here to lead
you to your final form.
Final form...?
This form you now take
is merely temporary.
Takeaki Kiryu died
in that plane crash.
I have caused
you to be reborn.
So that we may
carry out our destiny.
No! My parents died in
the crash, but I'm still alive!
And my cousin's family
has been so kind to me...
I owe them so much!
Kind to you?
You really believe
their hypocrisy?
Human kindness
is merely a sham.
Humans always feel superior
to those they see in need.
They are kind only to absolve
themselves of the guilt they feel.
That is the essence of
"good will towards others".
Let me show you the true
nature of the human heart!
I'd really like to thank you
for everything you've done...
Especially finding that
apartment for me...
You'd better be!
It costs a bundle!
As if the funeral
didn't cost enough!
My goddam brother dies and
leaves me his kid to pay for...!
Do you realize how much
trouble you're causing us?!
What are you up to?!
You must be the
Beast-Girl, Megumi.
And you're no
ordinary human!
We will meet again.
In good time...
Who the hell was he?
And what does
he want with Takeaki?
He's gone!
Relax, it was
just a dream.
But...
I said I'd take you
to a great place, right?
Here it is!
THIS is it?!
I'm outta here...
Wha- Takeaki,
hold on a sec!
I'm blowing my whole
allowance on you, man!
Cut it out! Tatsuo, l...
Leggo...!
Well?
Pretty cool, huh?
Tatsuo... Do you come
here all the time?
Loosen up, man!
I'm going next door.
I can't handle this...
Oh man...
Hand job, sir?
Only 3000 yen.
It's just too much...
Hand job, mister?
Only 3000 yen.
A h-h-hand j-j...!
No thanks! I'm fine!
Megumi! What are
you doing here?!
I followed you!
Come on, Takeaki. I'll make
you feel REAL good...
No...! Cut it out! I can't
believe you're doing this!
Cut it out...
First time?
That's so cute!
Hey, for another 5000 yen,
I'll let you suck them.
Huh? What's going on?
I feel so strange.
I feel like they're being sucked,
but there's nothing there!
Kuroko, you little...!
What're you...?!
Megumi, please...!
Hey! What do you
think you're doing?!
Let's book.
Hold it! Someone's
gotta pay for this!
Come on!
There's no more...
What the...?!
Megumi,
how are you...?
I'm not human.
Surprised?
You're not quite
human either, now.
Relax, it's okay. I know
what's been happening to you.
You may
not believe it...
But not all the people in
this world are human.
There are Demons and
Man-Beasts here, too...
So Tatsuo is this...
this "Overfiend?"
Yes...
That blood transfusion made
you a "quasi" Overfiend...
That's what's causing the
changes in your body.
So that's it...
I'm sorry if this
is all such a shock.
Maybe I shouldn't
have told you.
That's okay. But can you
tell me one more thing?
What?
What's going
to happen to me?
I don't know...
But I had no idea Tatsuo has
such an important destiny...
It sort of makes my
destiny look unimportant.
He'll have his powers
manifest someday...
I can't do anything
about that.
But I'm going to fight it!
This blood inside of me.
Yeah! I know you
can do it, Takeaki...
Oh yeah...
Here. The King of my
realm gave it to me.
Take it, for good luck.
Thanks, Megumi...
Yokohama!
- Beautiful...
- Isn't it?
I mean you.
Oh for Pete's...
Don't say that! Come on!
What's wrong? Something's
draining my powers.
Megumi!
A demon!
Let's go!
That creature...
Takeaki!
Megumi!
Who are you?!
Lemme go!
It's only been 100 years.
Have you forgotten my name?
I'll help you
to remember!
What are you
doing here, Kohoki?!
Don't be so cold.
I came to the human realm
so that I could win you back.
That's one way to put it!
Take over my mind, more likely!
You still really believe you
can take me as your wife?!
I fell in love with you.
100 years ago.
When my queen found out,
I was cast into Hell for all eternity.
It just made you all
the more desirable.
So you broke
out of Hell, huh?
I broke out so I can
have your lovely body!
I thought Takeaki was
causing all those murders...
But there's more, isn't there?
Kohoki, are you in on that?!
That's my secret.
Just take my word:
Stay away from that kid,
for your own good!
So there
is a connection!
And that human's
behind this, too!
What do you
two want?
All I want
is your BODY!
What's wrong, Megumi?
Quick today?
We'll be joined together
in a grand, eternal climax!
I can't fight it.
Help me, Big Brother...
Help me...
TAKEAKI!
Yes...
He awakens.
With this,
the 3 realms are mine!
As there is God,
so too must there be the Devil.
When the Overfiend comes,
the Lord of Chaos will arise.
1944. The outskirts of Berlin.
Headquarters of the Vrill Association.
1944. The tide of the war had
turned against Nazi Germany.
Adolf Hitler, long a believer
in the occult, ordered a...
...secret ceremony performed to
resurrect the demon "Lord of Chaos..."
...so that Germany might
regain the upper hand.
The ceremony failed, as the
timing was still premature.
Dr. Munhi Hausen was
executed for his failure.
Tokyo, 199X
And now, in the present day,
Munhi Hausen the second...
...with the help
of the demon Kohoki...
...wishes to fulfill his father's desire
to resurrect the Lord of Chaos.
Together, they raid the ruins of
Prison's Gate in the beast realm.
The ruins hold the key to
reviving the Lord of Chaos...
...and are apparently 4000 years old,
pre-dating the Overfiend legend.
Actually, my grandpa says
these ruins are 4000 years old.
What?! 4000 years old?
That's impossible.
They'd be older than the
legend of the Overfiend!
Takeaki Kiryu, Nagumo's cousin,
is Munhi Hausen's next target...
...and the plane he is aboard
is caused to crash.
His objective: To transfuse Nagumo's
Overfiend blood into Takeaki.
My blood... Give him my blood!
We're both type O!
Doctor, please!
Come with us.
Megumi, a transfusion
from Nagumo...?
With the Overfiend's blood,
Takeaki recovers in only 3 days.
You win!
I'm Megumi Amano.
How do you do?
Suspecting demon involvement
with the plane crash...
...Megumi approached
Takeaki to investigate.
You're a cheerful one,
aren't you?
But!
Next time, don't hold
back when fighting me.
You won't lose, then.
Awaken, Takeaki...
Awaken!
Munhi Hausen's incantations
cause Takeaki's body to transform.
As her investigations continue,
Megumi begins to fall in love...
...with Takeaki, and decides to
reveal what's happened to him.
But I'm going to fight it!
This blood inside of me.
Yeah! I know you can
do it, Takeaki...
Oh yeah...
Here. The king of my
realm gave it to me.
Take it, for good luck.
Thanks, Megumi...
And just as Takeaki decides to
fight the blood's effects...
...they are attacked by
Munhi Hausen and Kohoki.
Who are you?!
Lemme go!
It's only been 100 years.
Have you forgotten my name?
I'll help you to remember!
All I want
is your BODY!
What's wrong, Megumi?
Quick today?
We'll be joined together
in a grand, eternal climax!
I can't fight it.
Help me, big brother...
Help me...
TAKEAKI!
Yes...
He awakens.
What the...
Wha...?!
That son of a...!
You're no
match for him.
His opponent shall
be the Overfiend.
What?
He's the Lord of Chaos?!
The preparations for the
ceremony are nearly complete.
Once I've unlocked
his true viciousness...
...the 3 realms will be mine!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Demon Womb
"Battle at Shinjuku Skyscrapers"
Megumi...
Megumi.
Megumi!
Takeaki!
- Where is he?
- He just went home.
You're okay!
What a relief!
Did Takeaki
bring me here?
I see...
Oh yeah! He left a
message for you. Uhh...
"Your charm worked.
Now I know I won't lose."
What's it mean...?
Takeaki...
Now, what I
want to know...
You were both soaking wet.
And YOU'RE practically naked.
What were
you two up to?
Megumi!
Megumi, wait!
Uh, hold on...
Where are you going?
Megumi,
what's wrong?
It's all his fault poor
Takeaki's going through this...
...and he doesn't realize it at all!
He's such a total moron!
But it looks like I won't be
able to help him by myself.
Oh well, better go
see big brother!
Wait up!
Megumi!
Thanks, Megumi...
Megumi...
Dad! Mom!
Is it painful, Takeaki?
Only I can take
the pain away!
Takeaki...
Do it to me!
Take me now!
Takeaki!
Need some help?
I'm fine, really!
See you tomorrow!
How do you like that?
After all we've
been doing for him.
What an asshole...
That's the way,
Takeaki.
Abandon your conscience.
Let the evil awaken within.
You must kill Nagumo...
Kill the Overfiend.
Only then will
the pain go away!
Sounds hopeless. I sure
can't do anything for him.
You can't?
Takeaki probably is that
killer they're after.
The demons must
be up to something.
They always try to exploit
human weaknesses.
So what do I do?
What's with you?
In love with him?
No way!
The simplest way
would be to kill him.
We can't risk everything
for one human.
You gotta see the
big picture, Megumi...
Oh man... She's really
busted up about this guy.
Come on,
make me come...
Show me, Mimi. Show me
what the ruins are hiding...
Who the hell...?
Cut it out!
- Come on...
- Nagumo...!
- Not here! Please!
- Come on...
You have such cute
little panties, Akemi.
This is embarrassing!
Nagumo,
you're such a pervo...
Kill him!
Kill Nagumo!
Tatsuo,
may I come in?
Uhh... Hold on!
So? Studying hard?
Yeah...
Takeaki hasn't
shown up, yet?
No... He's so late,
I don't think he's coming.
Mom, why don't we take Takeaki
on vacation with us?
Yeah, we can go camping!
And go fishing like we used to.
We'll see who can
catch the biggest one.
Oh Tatsuo, you're so
concerned for him?
Of course! He's my
only cousin, like a brother!
And we're
all he's got, now.
I want him to be happy
again, like he used to be.
Kill!
KILL!
You hear? The Stalker got someone
outside Nagumo's place last night!
That's 12 so far!
- It's so scary!
- Who is this guy?!
I hear they still haven't
found the women, yet...
Takeaki! Wait up!
Come on, wait up, Takeaki!
Jeez, what's eating
you today?
It's... It's nothing.
I think I want
to be alone, today.
Takeaki...
Nagumo...?
What's wrong with him?
Megumi?
What's with you, lately?
MEGUMI!
SHUT UP ALREADY!
She's really got it
bad for him...
But a beast and a human...
It just can't work...
Why couldn't you kill
Nagumo, Takeaki?
You have nothing,
and he has so much!
Is that right, Takeaki?!
Takeaki, please!
Kill him!
TAKEAKI!
Mom...
Takeaki, you in there?
Why're the lights off?
Wanna shoot off some fireworks?
It might cheer you up.
Come on!
Takeaki, don't!
Stop it!
Please, don't kill him!
Takeaki!
Takeaki...
Can't see.
Damn it! It's like...
Someone's in my head...
I won't let him...
Control me like this!
DON'T!
Stay back...
It's okay, Takeaki.
I'll help you, somehow...
- Come on...
- No! Please...
Just stay away from me!
There she is.
Butting in, as usual...
It's alright.
Don't be afraid.
Stay back!
You?!
Megumi!
What are you
doing with her?!
Nagumo, wake up!
Nagumo!
Takeaki!
Where is he?!
No...
Why...?
What happened to him?
Who made
him into that...?!
You did.
You gave
him your blood.
That transfusion
did this to him.
My blood...?
If you let him go,
he'll try and kill you again.
And he won't
stop there.
Not 'til the whole
human realm is destroyed.
We can't change him back?!
Not without killing him.
No...
You can kill him.
Kill him as the Overfiend!
It would be the kindest
thing you can do.
Well? Gonna try?
Wait up, Tatsuo!
Same 'ol, Tatsuo...
I'd really like to thank you
for everything you've done...
Especially finding that
apartment for me...
What're you talking about?!
We're family, right?
Tatsuo... Help me.
HELP ME!
I will.
But I won't kill him.
Not as that monster...
But Nagumo...
It's alright.
He's my only brother...
Down to our blood!
Amano, I'll show you.
He's a friend of yours?
That's different then...
Boss!
Kuroko?!
Boss...
Who...
who did this to you?!
Megumi's...
Megumi?!
Once, on Hitler's orders,
my father summoned...
...the devil himself
to that basement lab.
THE SHINTOCHO BUILDING.
A RECENTLY BUILT APARTMENT TOWER.
He broke that seal
by his own hand...
...and set loose an evil beyond
even his own comprehension.
But I do not curse him.
Rather, I salute him!
He gave me the power
to set loose an evil...
...far beyond anything
Hitler could ever be!
A glorious night...
A night for culmination of
my family's dreams...
For the coming of the
destroyer of the 3 realms...
A perfect night for the resurrection
of the Lord of Chaos!!
Megumi!
I don't remember
taking a beast woman!
A beast woman...
The perfect catch...
To kill the Overfiend?
Yes...
To kill the Overfiend.
And here's the
star of our drama...
Takeaki.
Kill her!
You want her,
you long for her!
Kill her, and the last remnants
of your conscience will die.
You can kill your closest
friend after that.
Do it...
Takeaki, no!
Turn back to normal...
Takeaki!
Takeaki, no!
No! NO!
M- Megumi!
Stop it! Stop!
Takeaki, change back!
Takeaki!
Takeaki...
Stop this madness
at once!
How can this possibly
kill the Overfiend?!
Call him off!
Takeaki...
Megumi!
MEGUMI!
What the...?!
God dammit!
Him! If I can kill him...
Go!
Hold on, Megumi!
I'll save you!
Get lost!
You bastard! You're the human
who was at Prison's Gate!
Listen well. My name is
Munhi Hausen the second.
You must be the
infamous Amano Jyaku.
How dare you use my
sister in this farce!
It is a sacred ceremony!
But he's just a human...!
Learn your lesson,
Amano Jyaku!
I will not let you
disrupt this ceremony!
Takeaki!
N- Nagumo...
Keep away...
Takeaki?
Takeaki, what's wrong?
It's me, Tatsuo.
You've come at last,
Overfiend.
Now, crush the
life from him!
You've killed
12 men already.
There is your last victim...
Nagumo!
Takeaki...
Takeaki... I'd know you no
matter what you look like.
Takeaki, enough of this...
Stop it.
Takeaki...
Good 'ol Takeaki...
Takeaki, no!
You're killing Nagumo!
Damn you...
What the hell you doing?
My family has studied
the beast and...
...demon realms
for a long time.
So that we might take
control of this world.
And then we learned of him...
The god above all others!
What're you talking about?
That's the Overfiend!
You misunderstand
the Overfiend.
At Prison's Gate, it is
written on the ruins:
"As there is God,
so too must there be the Devil."
"When the Overfiend comes,
the Lord of Chaos will arise!"
Lord of Chaos?
Keep your "Overfiend."
I have larger plans.
Tonight the Lord of Chaos
is reborn!
He shall rule the 3 realms
in the Overfiend's stead!
You son of a bitch... And use him
to become dictator of all 3 worlds?!
Cut it out! No one
messes with me!
You'll resurrect your demon
over my dead body!
A foolish gesture...
Megumi...
We're both pretty
beat up, aren't we?
I told you to stay
away from him...
Kohoki, you...
And I really wanted to get...
one more... shot at you...
Big brother!
Megumi... You okay?
Lmpressive, Overfiend.
I salute you.
Kill him! He can't revive again!
Tear him apart!
Takeaki, no!
Takeaki!
Megumi, don't interfere!
It has to be decided this way!
But Takeaki... Takeaki...!
No... It's too risky!
This place is full
of negative energy.
Takeaki may have
the advantage. But HIM...
Takeaki, no!
Megumi! You hear me?
Stay out of it!
But... but...
Promise me!
You bastard... You bastard...!
I won't let you!!
Pathetic...
Dammit...
I can't use my power
anywhere near him.
What do I do?
No more, Takeaki...
Finish him.
He's helpless!
Do not hesitate!
Fulfil your urge to kill!
Takeaki... Come back with me.
Back to our home...
Takeaki, enough!
Finish him!
Takeaki...
Takeaki!
I'm going to fight it...
Fight this blood in me...
He's still fighting it,
to the very end...
Damn his will...
The brainwashing failed!
Let's see your
hocus-pocus beat this!
You little...!
Takeaki!
Takeaki...
Don't die... Takeaki...
TAKEAKI!!!
Why did you...?
Guess it was too
much for even you.
Hope this doesn't
mess him up too bad.
"As there is God,
so too must there be the Devil."
"When the Overfiend comes,
the Lord of Chaos will arise..."
Great... I can't wait to
see how this turns out.
I look forward to it!
You hear that, Munhi Hausen?!
What am I
doing out here...?
And soon, my time begins...