Urotsukidoji
Die Rückkehr!
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 1 Part 2
An always horny bastard, this Buju.
What was that?
Buju, what's wrong?
Crying skin! I send you to hell!
Please! Don't hurt him!
Don't do it!
You mustn't kill Himi!
Who are you?
You are in my way!
I will end that pitiful yelling.
Don't!
Himi... Himi...
Buju...
It laughs. It laughs when I touch it.
Oh, how sweet!
Caesar, we found them. Trey are in the eagle's valley.
Bring Alector back to me, in an unscathed way!
Buju is alike to me.
Take care of my daughter.
Buju, the temple is surrounded.
Release Alector!
First this skin and now Caesar's troops...
Not a good day for Buju.
Buju, if you release Alector we will spare your life.
Let Alector go... now!
That many asses... and only because of me.
Buju!
He will kill you! He kills everyone who crosses his way.
Let's flee together! We will be save in your world!
They won't kill me.
They want to use my powers to find Kyo-O...
I love you, Buju! I want to stay with you forever.
You want to stay with Makemono like me?
Really...?
Stop it!
Don't shoot!
Alector...
Please, spare Buju! Please... father...
Please, I beg you...
Buju...! What did you do to Alector?
Buju!
You mustn't die...
Oh no! You are...?!
Buju...
Alector, I will never forget you...
Alector, I created you...
We don't need Kyo-O anymore...
because our creature will be soon ready.
Save Alector's body, Faust.
Yes. And Buju?
Kill him!
Thanks...
Why only must I die for a skin like you...
After you got Alector we will withdraw.
Something is wrong here. Who is that baby?
What's going on here...?
Something comes up...
It's Nagumo! Why does he return?
He wants that child! Then this baby must be...
Kyo-O!
Mother... He awoke. I will have to combat him.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Nagumo!
I thought, he was dead...
Faust!
Finally I found you, Kyo-O!
Your powers will serve me well.
What is this? What happened?
What is this?!
That's our chance to escape!
What are you doing?
I asked you what you were doing!
Long time no see, Amano.
Muenchhausen...!
Now you become witness of my power!
What?
You will see it...
Finally it's time!
Nagumo, try it! Try to kill that baby!
You know that it's your enemy...
No!
Kyo-O, what do you want to do now?
Great...
Remain here...
No... please...
Afraid...?
Almost half of my body is metal.
The body is only the wrapper of the soul.
Such a sensitive body!
Soon intelligent machines will rule the world.
Come here...
It's your turn.
I give you an ecstasy of pain...
No...!
Now Tagushi, how do you feel as a Japanese prime minister?
Fine, thanks... without your help I
would never have reached this goal...
I owe you a lot...
You moved any of my opponents
out of the way without hesitation.
This was only the beginning. Soon
I will control the whole world.
I will succeed with what failed to Hitler once.
What?
Hitler's obsession became his doom. Yet I'm realist.
I studied history of mankind.
My researchs took me here to Tokyo.
I'm sure that civilisation has it's origin here.
At no other place of the world you are closer to the Gods.
The ruins, I found, are the key...
to domination of the whole world!
8th FEBRUARY 1982
HOTEL AKASAKA, TOKYO.
It's a great honor to us to be allowed to greet you.
Father!
Alector, my daughter, are you alright?
Yes of course, father. Do we dinner together today father?
I'm afraid not. I still have much work
to do. You will have to eat alone.
Alector, your father is a very busy man.
You must understand that.
I'm sorry, Alector. But tomorrow I'm only for you I promise.
Oh father...!
How tall she became...
Unfortunately I have only too few...
time for her since her mother died...
This is the most important excavation place of the world.
It's as old as mankind itself.
These hieroglyphs tell the history of mankind.
They tell about emergence, past, presence...
and even about future of the world!
The future?
Yes it sounds unbelievable but everything fits.
According to the records our end awaits shortly.
It's said that besides our world
two other parallel worlds exist,..
one of the Demons and one of the Human-Beasts.
Every 3000 years...
a being called Chojin unites the three worlds.
More can not be made out. From
I here the boards are damaged.
It doesn't matter I will continue
history from here myself anyway.
I will summon Chojin and then I will kill him.
Then I will rule as God.
I will determine the future...
Caesar, we made it. We have a direct access...
to NASA's computer system.
Now finally we will receive the last answers.
Which time do these ruins come from?
17.000 before Christ...
+/- 2000 years.
How reliable is this answer?
80%. Max. deviation +/- 5%.
What does this information base on?
On all entered information.
With who is Chojin to be equated?
With God... God... God...
Why did Chojin appear on earth 17000 years before Christ?
In order to release the earth and to unite the worlds.
Was the old God MU involved?
No, Chojin and MU are not like-minded
They used their powers against each other.
Can you summon Chojin?
Only if I manage getting into contact with him.
Reunion of all capacities...
Establishing of contact runs.
Are you the one who called me?
Are you Chojin?
I am called like this.
Then die!
Now I will unite the three worlds!
Never underestimate the power of a God!
Father!
Alector!
Run away, fast!
You won't be able to stop the apocalypse.
Alector! Alector!
Chojin! Who ever you are you will pay for that.
Alector!
Alector, come back to me...
I miss your laughter...
Alector!
What? That baby?!
Yes, Himi was kidnapped by Faust.
Before however he still managed reviving you.
Nonsense!
Only Chojin has power to revive dead.
Maybe Himi has the power to kill Chojin.
So what?
That isn't a reason for me to free the baby.
Nevertheless there must be a reason why it revived you.
I guess it chose you to protect it.
That's your fate.
Fate...
Alike as insignificant, every being has its fate.
If insect, half-human, demon or human...
everyone has a fate which he can't escape.
On my search for Chojin I became
acquainted with many people...
They all were guided by strengths also
against the power of their love...
They all couldn't escape their fate exactly as you and I.
I don't know what expects us...
however, I know that my fate will fill...
alike, what happens.
Don't you think the same... Buji?
In fact I came here in order to annihilate Kyo-O, the evil.
However now I know that Himi, the baby, is Kyo-O.
No!
You mustn't kill Himi!
Sorry but I can't promise that.
Yet I don't see any danger which
starts from Himi at the moment.
And you, Buju? Which role will you play?
Which role...?
Caesar plans something with Kyo-O.
As I know him he will try to kill Chojin.
However I will not allow that.
I will annihilate Caesar and if necessary also Kyo-O.
Unless...
somebody would destroy Caesar's plan
and free Himi. You for example...
That's none of my business...
Think of that it's a question of Himi.
I go now to Caesar.
Think still once about everything, Buju!
Amano! Don't hurt Himi!
Forget Alector, Buju. You must be strong now.
What?!
Just shut up!
Let's see what Caesar and Muenchhausen plan to do...
Are those ones all?
Yes. I did my Best in order to bring some people.
Doesn't matter. Perhaps there will come some more.
Now to our plan...
We are at this place.
Here is Caesar's palace.
And here is the mine in which we had to work.
Some of us couldn't escape and are caught here.
We have no information about the black monster.
Nevertheless I fear what a lot of us were hurt.
Therefore we should act as fast as possible.
Ruddle, do we really do the right thing?
We can't go back now.
And we don't want it either. We
have to pay back much to Caesar.
It won't be easy.
I feel something...
Evil powers conentrate around Caesar's palace.
Something incredible will come up.
We must save our friends fast.
God gave every Makemono specific abilities and strengths.
Now it's time to use them.
Yeah, let's do it!
We will creep tomorrow morning into Caesar's palace.
You know what to do when we give you the sign.
Yes!
Caesar, all preparations are done.
We wait only for the awakening of Kyo-O.
Faust, I'm worried.
All events arrive as prophesied by the hieroglyphs.
I ask myself if we really can change history...
No worry, Caesar.
We have Kyo-O, the key to ultimative power.
When Kyo-O awakes and combines himself with Faburil...
even Chojin himself can't stop us.
Faburil? I thought he was destroyed by Nagumo?!
No, only a part of him.
However he regenerated.
He is now even more powerful and he wants revenge.
Tomorrow morning the union with Kyo-O will occur.
Actual?
Caesar!
What?
The restoration of princess Alector is completed.
Ah, finally!
Alector!
Oh, Alector...!
Show me your face, daugther!
What's wrong Alector?
Where is Buju?
He isn't here.
He is dead.
Father!
Have you killed him, father! Did you do it?!
No!
Alector...
Buju...
Alector... why...?
What happened to you...?
Father, do we eat this evening together?
Alector, I will revenge your death...
Kyo-O, Faburil,..
the nuclear missiles... Chojin will soon be dead.
Alector, I will create a new world only for you.
Caesar, we register changes on the psychowave monitor.
Faburil reacts to the power of Kyo-O!
What?!
Who are you? Why were you born?
If you oppose me I must annihilate you!
So you are nevertheless my enemy?
So it starts! Very good, Faust!
You are supposed to suffer, Kyo-O! That
is the key to the union with Faburil.
Faburil approaches to the palace, Caesar.
He claims many sacrifices also among our people.
Don't see to that.
Caesar... the nuclear missiles are ready.
Destination: Osaka.
The shooting occurs tomorrow morning. Start the countdown.
Start of the countdown.
Watch, there below!
What's that? What's going on here?!
Nothing good I fear. Come, run away from here!
Why does this monster appear here?
The disaster breaks about us.
Father, I have a good news. Soon your Project finishs...
and our family will control the whole world.
Alector, forgive me.
I just wanted you back.
Soon you could be the ruler of the new world.
Everyone would obey you.
Please, Alector, laugh again...
What, Kyo-O?! You refuse Faburil?!
What are you afraid of?
You are still a baby. You can't already know...
what power you have.
Open yourself and allow Faburil to enter!
That's enough, Faust! Leave the baby alone!
Too late, Amano! Kyo-O is already under my spell.
To release Kyo-O you have to kill me!
Are you able to kill me?
Wait for it!
Hold, wait, Muenchhausen!
Oh, Faust...!
You don't want to kill Faust, do you?
You again! We have still a fight open!
I'm ready!
Damn!
Buju... Buju...
Himi...
Buju, Help! Help me!
Are... Are you Himi?
You are very beautiful...
Buju...!
How warm you are...
What the hell...
Himi!
No fear!
What a sword!
Caesar...!
Caesar, Kyo-O was kidnapped by Buju!
What?!
They just escape from the palace!
Catch him! He mustn't escape!
Kill them!
Yes!
This dirty bastard! So he is still alive!
Is Kyo-O responsible for that...?
Buju is alive?!
Buju!
Alector!
No, please! No father, no!
You aren't my daugther...
Just an useless android!
You are mine!
No!
That hurts!
Forgive me, father!
No father, please!
Buju...
You will forget him now.
No!
How do you like that, Alector?
Do I give it to you better than this Makemono, don't I?
I take you to ecstasy...
An idea comes to me!
You want to see Buju, don't you? I
show him to you... for a last time.
I will tear him apart in front of your eyes!
Caution... Caution. Only 300 seconds till the shooting.
All employees into the safety zones.
I should have take insect spray with me!
That was only a small taste, small one!
Go to hell, bitch!
Somehow it gets uncongenially here!
Caesar, you bastard show yourself!
Alector!
So we meet again, Buju...
for the last time!
Alector, say goodbye to your lover!
It's your last chance!
Buju...!
Buju...
You can't kill me...!
Sorry but you can't help me.
I can't move.
Buju...
No...!
Makemono... Faburil will engulf you together with Kyo-O!
Buju!
Alector! Alector!
Alector...
Only 30 seconds till the shooting!
Muenchhausen! I will destroy you!
Too late!
Amano, you lost!
Hold, wait.
Fortsetzung folgt...
To be Continued