Where always there is a God
there is also a devil.
Where always "Chojin" is there
is also Kyo-O not far.
The destroyer Nagumo visited the world...
with rage if annihilation.
What came about up to now...
20 years later as already hew power
structures had formed themselves...
Chojin awoke from his sleep...
100 years before the prophesied time.
Chojin had awoke because in the
east Kyo-O, the evil, was born.
Why now? According to prophecy you
should not be born before in 100 years.
Did you lie to me?
What happened?
That what needed to happen.
In the east the evil was born.
It will try to kill me.
Ordered by Chojin, Amano went to east.
There the apocalypse has created a new race...
neither human nor animal nor demon.
They are called Makemonos and are
misfigured creatures of the inferno.
Beyond them was a scruple-free and merciless chief.
They called him Buju.
In this realm all women belong to me.
The evil of the east!
Caesar we found them they are in the eagle's valley.
Bring me Alector back, in am unscathed way.
Buju is alike to me.
Please spare Buju.
Please... Father...!
Buju!
You mustn't die...
Amano ordered by Chojin to find and kill Kyo-O thought...
that Buju is his enemy.
Yet Amano wandered - Buju and
Alector, Caesar's daughter,..
escaped from Caesar's palace...
and had to pay their love with their lifes.
Damn...
Then this baby must be...
Kyo-O!
Meanwhile the event is pursued by an opponent of Chojin...
the mage Faust Muenchhausen.
Now as we have Kyo-O it's the end of Chojin...
What? This baby!?
Yes Himi was kidnapped by Faust.
However before he still managed reviving you.
Nonsense!
Only Chojins has the power to revive dead.
Himi has maybe the power to kill Chojin.
So what...?
That isn't a reason for me to release the baby.
Yet there must be a reason why it revived you.
I guess that it chose you to protect it.
That's your fate.
Fate...
Meanwhile Caesar, the arch-enemy of Chojin, prepares...
a missile attack on Chojin's whereabout in Osaka.
Faburil and Kyo-O are supposed
to form a devastating alliance.
Suffer Ko-O! Pain is fhe key to the union with Faburil.
While Chojin in Osaka is in big danger...
Amano tries to release Kyo-O in Caesar's palace.
That's enough Faust! Leave this baby alone!
Too late, Amano. Kyo-O is already under my spell.
To free it you have to kill me!
Can you kill me?
Wait for it!
Hold, wait Muenchhausen!
Oh, Faust...
You don't want to kill Faust, do you...?
You again! We have a fight open!
I'm ready!
Damn!
Only 30 seconds till the shooting!
Muenchhausen! I will destroy you!
Too late!
Amano, you lost!
Hold, wait!
Urotsukidoji III - Return of the Overfiend
Volume 2
What the hell is this?
It looks like a gigantic cocoon.
Is Kyo-O for instance in there...?
The missiles... they fly to Osaka direction!
Finally the day of pay back has come...
Wait only, Chojin!
You sick bastard!
These missiles will never reach their destination!
Cursed scum! I don't have the time...
to see to you!
Help!
Caesar's palace! Storm Caesar's palace!
Finally the hour of the Makemonos
has come! Down with Caesar!
Let the world know that a new age began!
They reached the palace!
Caesar is still busy with his missiles...
But what if he notes the attack?
Will we still have a chance then?
We can think about that later!
Do you hear that?
The baby cries for help.
However how did it come into there?
We can clarify that later...
Go go, we have to conquer the palace.
If we don't overturn Caesar he will revenge terribly.
What?!
What should we do?
Just now!
These bastards!
Caesar, the Makemonos revolt.
They already have the prisoner camp under their control.
Doesn't matter we have more important things to do!
But Sir!
Shut up! Pedro, finish that.
Yes!
Situation report!
What is with Faust and the missiles?
Everything runs to plan.
They reach in a minute and 35 seconds the Fuji-sound.
Our fleet is 100 miles before the Ise-Bucht, course on Osaka.
The air wing is ready.
Fine... there should be nothing left of Osaka.
And now, Faburil... your time has come.
Do you still think that you can save Chojin?
Muenchhausen! What do you plan?
Now you will find out the power of evil!
It's stronger than all your powers.
Missile number 1 got off the course! It loses to height...
What?!
With best greetings!
Brother!
Damn...!
My brother is in danger!
Akemi...? Chojin!
What... What happens to me?
It's getting hot in me...
I burn!
The situation demands that I use also your powers...
Aren't you Amano's sister, are you?
I... how can I help you...?
My powers...?
You are so powerful...
Give it to me, please! I can't stand it! I need it...
Fuck me... fuck me! Please do it!
I'm coming! Oh, I'm coming...!
I'm coming...!
I'm still hot...
Fuck me... now fuck me!
So it be...
I will raise your Chojin-powers!
No! No, please... no!
Finally! He is born!
Where you hide yourself, Faust?
Fool!
I don't fall in on the same trick twice.
Give up, Amano!
Death waits for your Chojin!
What do you want to do against that?
Don't you prefer to serve me?
You would like that, don't you? You bastard!
What...?!
Another missile descended! Another missile descended!
What!? What does Faust there in fact?
Muenchhausen! You will never be able to realize your plan!
There are only 4 missiles left! And I will get them too!
Didn't you forget something, Amano?
What...?
The time of truth has come! Now
you can prove your strengths!
Damn! This monster is really giant!
Muenchhausen! That is only the beginning!
What the hell does he do there?!
Shit! A dead-end street again!
The sectors A4, B3 and C5 are again under control.
Good! No one mustn't reach Caesar's palace.
Shit!
You poor devils...! I will revenge you!
Enko! If it goes on like that we are lost!
What should we do now? And there is Ruddle with his people?!
What happened?
Energy fall in turbine 2...
Did it!
That wasn't hard...
What the... What's going on here?
Malfunction in reactor room 3. Turbine
2 destroyed no control anymore!
What?!
The Makemonos must have penetrated there!
Energy fall in turbine 1 and 3.
In this state we can't hold the balance anymore.
The palace slopes!
Therefore increase the energy in turbine 1 and 3!
The Makemonos keep on penetrating.
They come more and more closer...
Intruders in sector A4 and B5.
They move onto the palace!
Now do something about that! Am I only surrounded by idiots?!
The palace! They storm the palace!
Don't panic!
Attack! Don't show any mercy! Our time has come!
You are still alive?!
How you see!
You worm!
What?!
Now only one is left!
We lost contact with the fleet!
What?! To hell with that! What's with the missiles?
Four are destroyed, one holds still the course.
What about Faburil?
We still get his signal but it's very weak.
Caesar, the signal gets better again!
I knew it... this creature is unbeatable!
I... I'm coming! I'm coming...!
I'm coming...
Now my power will show itself...
Muenchhausen, admit your defeat! You lost! Give up!
Amano! Do you still think you can defeat me?
This beast is still alive...?
Faburil is the personified hatred! Try to destroy him...
and you create even more hate!
Brother...!
Megumi...
Last missile destroyed!
Faburil changed his direction!
That is all done by Chojin! We are lost!
Even Faburil and Kyo-O together aren't strong enough...
to defeat him.
The palace's balance is reconstructed to 89%.
Status is held. State of the supporting-system is still critical.
Find Caesar! Destroy him!
They are in the palace! They move onto the headquarters.
Caesar! Caesar!
Caesar, where are you?
Show you, Kyo-O!
Kyo-O, who gave you your power?
I can't remember to have testified you.
What...?!
No... that can't be...!
It's like this...! I wait for you in Osaka!
Stop it... Stop it...
Stop it!
We don't obtain a signal of Faburil anymore!
Part of the palace assails!
Withdraw!
Where are you, Caesar? Show you!
Alector... Farewell!
Alector!
Forgive me!
I couldn't revenge you...
It seems I lost everything although
everything worked very well...
Till this bastard appeared!
These cursed Makemonos should pay for that!
I congratulate you, Caesar.
Don't be disappointed like that...
Since finally you managed creating a new world.
Over 20 years passed since the great destruction...
and a new being arose like you wanted it.
What do you mean with that?!
The Alector-module which you
constructed was an perfect Androide.
It's impossible to distinguish her from a human being.
That's right! Das stimmt! But I still broke down!
Tell me, how will Chojin's realm look like?
What will happen to the world as we know it?
Caesar, in your task I have analyzed.
to 100 percent these ruins created by Chojin.
But about the Makemonos and the Alector-modul...
was nothing recorded here.
The world moves in a direction...
which even Chojin couldn't predict.
And more strange is that the Alector-modul carries...
new life in it.
The Makemonos and this new life...
will determine the fate of the mankind...
because they outdo Chojin's imagination.
And because it is Kyo-O who will lead them.
When Chojin and Kyo-O will meet each other in Osaka...
then there will be the answer for everything.
However I won't have this concurrence anymore.
The Makemonos have already made too much damage.
This also is fate...
Farewell... Caesar...
Fresh meat!
Buju! Buju!
Buju!
Hey! That bitch is Caesar's daugther!
The small one makes us to heros among the Makemonos!
Catch her!
Alector!
Himi! Himi!
What happened? What's wrong?
Buju!
What the hell...?
Damn Makemonos! I will never forgive them!
Anything might happen but I take them with me into hell!
No...!
Caesar, do you hear me?
No... please, stop it...!
Come out and show!
Show or we kill her!
But first we will have a bit fun with your daugther...!
Father, don't come! They will kill you!
It doesn't matter what they do to
me but stay where you are father!
Alector, are you ok?
Daddy's small daugther, eh?
No! Please...!
Stop...! Stop it... please!
She hardly awaits it...!
Ouch! No, no! Please don't...!
Where are you, Caesar?! Your small bitch is afraid!
Stop!
We still want to have fun till Caesar appears...
Do you like that?
An iron-hard steel penis, just for you!
When he starts you will be just dead meat!
But we won't kill you yet.
Say that you need it!
I need it...
You need it? You really need it...?
We help you!
Then go...
I want it...
Look at that!
That bitch is already as wet as a whole lake!
Come on let's give it to her!
I... I do everything you want. Everything...
That sounds well!
Then let's take a look on your juicy arid randy pussy!
Come on spread your legs!
Very good...
Hey, what's this?!
Spread your legs if you want to live on!
Yes...!
Hey, she is already very horny!
Hold, stop it you hurt me!
Me first! Yes... this is good!
Spred your legs more!
And how does my cock feel like?
Do you like it?
Oh... she is so warm... so wet...!
I'm coming...!
Yeah the perfect cock massage!
I want next!
No me!
Ouch no! Stop, it hurts!
That hurts... it hurts...!
Stop it!
Caesar!
Too late Caesar! Your daugther is already sucking our cocks!
Alector...!
To hell with you!
Father...
We got him!
We killed Caesar!
Alector was everything what I ever had!
For that I will tear your heads apart!
Enough talk! Let's kill him at last!
What the hell...?!
He will kill all of us! We can't do any harm to him...
Uworthy mortals!
Did you really think you could measure with me?
No more step asshole or your daugther will die!
We will tear her apart in front of you...
Alector!
What's wrong...? Stop it!
Stop it! Stop to cry Himi!
Now tell me, why do you cry?
Himi!
Withdraw!
Give us back our town!
Kill them! Don't leave anyone alive!
How could they become just that strong?
Pedro! Our last hope is the Genocydroid D-9.
If we can reach the R&D sector...
we will even still have a chance to win the battle.
D-9...
Go to hell!
Pedro!
Ruddle! We waited for you!
What's going there outside?
Everything worked smoothly.
Tell us!
Meanwhile already more than a
hundred of us must be in the palace!
Do you still want to take more fighters in?
Yet we still have to find Ceasar!
I think it's enough to storm the palace!
We shouldn't exaggerate it.
Never! Not before we find Caesar!
He treated us Makemonos always as scum!
He killed many of us!
This all ends only when Ceasar pay for that.
Let's go!
Idaten what do you want to do?
Enko!
Forget it I stay here!
D-9... on the day your body became to metal...
was the last time I cried...
Now we meet again... yet nothing is like it used to be.
Please... use your powers to help us in this time of need.
D-9...!
Hello soldier bitch! What does a so pretty girl as you do...
at a place like this?
You...?
Fetch her!
Well up to now did you and your troops always fuck us...
But now...
No! Leave me! Disappear!
What the...!
What the hell is that?
D-9...
Your regeneration isn't finished yet...
P...e...d...r...o...
Make him harmless, now!
Leave him to me!
D-9...!
P...e...d...r...o...
This thing wasn't even as worth as a clothes rack!
D-9...
Hey you act like that scrap pile was your lover!
After all now no one will disturb us from...
having fun with the girl...
Ready for a small party, soldier bitch?
Let's go...
We sure will have a lot of fun with her...
You girls belong to the troops only to amuse the guys...
I want to taste her first!
Hey it seems you like it, bitch...
Your nipples are already hard!
I will put in mine first...
Prepare yourself for something real good, soldier bitch!
My cock will make you happy...!
No! Please, stop it!
Yeah... what is cool!
I think I'm in heaven!
Please stop!
And how does it feel?
She... she is great!
I could fuck her forever!
I take care of one of the other holes!
How does it feel for you?
Better than in my most beautiful dreams!
The girlie isn't bad!
But now I want something special...!
No... not that...!
Alector!
Was everything for nothing, Alector?!
Good...!
We got him!
Caesar is ours now! We defeated him!
Long live Enko!
Soon also Caesar's country will belong to us again!
That means finally freedom!
At last the bastard had to pay!
We made it, Enko!
Yes...
And now since he can't help her daugther anyway...
should we take care of her...
No wait! If you do that then you
aren't any better than Caesar!
What do you talk there?
It's none of your business, small one.
What the...?!
This bastard!
Damn! He is the only obstacle in our way.
Enko...!
Oh... my Alector!
Caesar!
Now it's your turn!
Enko!
Enko...
What is this...?
Megumi...! What is this?
Kyo-O... Kyo-O... His light fills the palace!
What's his intention...?
What's going on?! Why do they fight each other?!
The weak will be kissed by the light of justice!
Light of justice...?
From the voices of people hatred rings...
The child will be the messenger of destruction...
Unless it's released before...
Hey... man...
She is damn good to fuck!
Idiot!
She is mine! Don't touch her!
What...?!
Help!
Stop! Stop it!
D-9...
Pedro...
I... I feel...
I will die...
Release me...
from the pain... please!
I have never forgotten you...
Please... the pain... kill me!
Kill me!
You are the only woman I ever loved...
Thanks...
Please stop it...
Don't be afraid...
I'm here with you...
Everything will be good. Trust me, Himi.
Buju...
Who's works is that...?
Incredible! The city is completely ravaged!
Everything will be good again... Himi!
Osaka... we must go to Osaka.
Buju, let us go there.
Osaka, you say?
I must meet Chojin in Osaka.
Chojin? In Osaka?
Damn Chojin! He is probably responsible for that destruction.
Either he or this damn Kyo-O!
What to the hell are you talking about?
Hey, old man! What do you mean with that?
You know well what I mean.
I thought much lately.
Chojin must be in direct connection with the origin...
of us Makemonos.
What did you say...? That's a joke, isn't it?!
I am what I am!
No one created me!
And no one tell me what I have to do!
Are you sure?
How is it then that we arise after...
destruction of the three worlds?
Couldn't it be that we are part of Chojin's legend?
A new race born to create a new better world?
If we want an answer for that we should go to Osaka...
Why only Kyo-O didn't show himself yet?
Megumi! Where were you? Did you help me?
Amano, I am not that what you think of me...
Megumi?! What's the meaning of this...?
Through the annihilation of the 3
worlds my work isn't finished yet...
Chojin! You are him!
What the hell did you do?!
Up to now I ignored Kyo-O's existence...
however now Megumi will be my messenger...
Once more I will bring annihilation to the world...
That's my destiny.
You mustn't! Your time didn't come yet!
Forget it, Amano.
The world which you desire becomes
faster reality than you think!
You can't be serious!
Brother!
Megumi...!
So that's what you want, Chojin...
However, what do you plan to do against Kyo-O?
And what the hell did you do with Megumi?!
Fine! Let's go to Osaka!
Really, Buju?
Yes, just for you...
However before we go I would like to take along someone...
Ruddle! It is dreadful!
Enko! it's Enko!
Enko? What's with him?
Caesar killed him...
Caesar...!
That all was unnecessary at all...!
Alector... my graceful Alector...
Just how can I use my powers to help you?
You shouldn't live on in this cruel world...
For you there is only one way left to go...
Wait!
Caesar, I came to fetch your daugther!
Buju...! You are really still alive?
So you want my daugther...?
So it's like that...
But my daugfher is too graceful so I
wouldn't give her to a beast tike you.
She is the most valuable treasure which I ever owned...
Alector was always my everything for me.
Yet you took her away from me...
and brought her death!
You...! And now you dare meeting me again...
Do you think that I simply accept the fall of my empire?
Do you really think that...?
Well, Buju.
The time of pay back came.
If you can defeat me Alector will be yours.
You will die, Caesar!
What!?
Buju...!
Don't approach...!
Don't approach!
Buju...!
Buju, now the fight really starts!
Not bad!
Don't talk that much and come here now!
Did if finally take him?
Not like that...!
Don't just think that you...
can beat me that easy!
Alector!
Buju...
Alector...
Finally... I found you...
I never imagined that a Makemono could love a human.
I think that's a good sign...
I think so too... It's better than killing each other...
Father...?
Father! Buju, where is my father?
He... he is...
Father...?
Buju, you defeated me...
Since you was you able to do that
Alector should be yours now...
Father!
I... I give you my daugther...
Because I... I'm defeated...
Father... Father!
Oh, Father...
Please don't say something like that...
Forgive me... Buju...
You must understand me...
I can't leave my fater alone... father...!
Alector...
I'm the one who lost... Caesar...
For me...?
Thanks... the time of destruction is past. Sorry that we...
treated you so bad...
Why did we fight that long?
Why did we fight anyway?
Everything for nothing... without sense...
Please don't die! Please no!
Stay up, please!
Let's go... you look like you're ready...
You too, Buju...
Oh really?
Then let's go!
Father... took. Everything looks so
beautiful and peaceful from here...
Do you really think that it was the right decision, Alector?
Yes... I would only restrict Buju...
Buju, the father of your child...?!
You knew it?
Yes... it's his child...
It will be very strong as he is.
Yes.
Alector, do you remember my last wish...?
Yes, Vater.
Ok! Still a long trip awaits us.
What the hell do you want here?!
We accompany you. Also we want to
find out the reason of our existence.
It might be that we won't return alive.
We know what dangers there outside in the world...
await as.
That's right!
You can use the aid of a few friends well.
Since we have to protect the child the key to everything...
Who are you?
I'm the Genocydroid D-9.
The woman I loved is dead.
There is nothing that holds me still here.
Take me with you!
You too...?
I'm D-9. I'm strong...
Do what you like!
Good it's settled!
I'm already suprised what will happen...
After all the great concurrence still awaits.
What will happen when Kyo-O and
Chojin meet each other in Osaka?
That will be very thrilling, won't it Chojin?
Alector...
Buju, I wish you luck for your trip.
Sometime we will meet...
again...
Buju...
We will meet again for sure.
OK people... let's go!