O arrogant humanity!
Not all that exists is
visible to your mortal eyes!
Our world consists
of the realm of humans...
...the realm of man-beasts,
and the realm of demons.
And many of the demons
live in the human world.
There is a legend
among the demons.
That once, every 3000 years,
the Overfiend revives.
And upon his revival,
the three realms are...
...united to form
an eternal kingdom.
O arrogant humanity!
Heed well the voices of those
of the demon realm.
Humans are not the
supreme rulers of all.
You shall know the truth
when the Overfiend revives.
And the promised time
is close at hand!
300 years since Amano Jyaku
went into the human world.
And not one word
of him since.
But I smell it...
Yes, I can smell it!
It can only be the stench
of the Overfiend!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Overfiend
Part One
"Birth of the Overfiend"
"Myojin University"
So he's the one...
He's got the moves, and that
smell that drives women wild.
Cut it out!
I've gotta change!
- I was only kidding.
- What are you doing?
Holy...
Hi!
- How's it going?
- Not bad.
It's Akemi!
Better give
it me all today.
Akemi...
Who's there?
Oh shit!
"Boys keep out!"
Anyone in here?!
Anybody there?
I don't see anyone.
Weird...
I'll bet someone was.
Go, Myojin!
Definitely not him.
Oh, yes...
I'm coming again!
That was great,
Ozaki!
Forget it. But men, someone's
defiling our hallowed gym!
Him!
What an idiot!
Hey man,
sorry I lost control.
I'm okay, Ozaki.
What part of Akemi
were you looking at?
All swollen,
aren't you?
Well, I, uhh...
Not just swollen...
I'll use my magic
charm to heal you.
See you later, Boner!
Thanks...
Oh god..."Boner!"
Goddam Ozaki!
How humiliating!
Miss Togami.
She doesn't look too happy.
Akemi!
Come in.
Yes, ma'am.
I wonder what she
wants Akemi for.
You wanted to
speak with me...?
It's very important.
I'm in a bit of a jam.
I'm looking for something,
and I need your strength...
No, your body.
What are you
looking for?
Well now...
It's the most wonderful
thing for us, as women.
Understand?
- No...
- You don't?
Then I'll show you.
Wha...
What are you doing?!
I haven't seen it yet,
but it's very near.
Don't you want
to see it, too?
Stop it!
Stop it, please...!
Akemi!
I think you'd better
watch a little longer.
You're that new transfer
student, Ama... Ama...
Amano.
It's a pleasure.
Look at 'em go!
You can see
behind the curtain?
I'll give you pleasures
beyond this realm!
What the...?
I can't take this!
I'm going in!
Don't!
Someone's watching?!
I wondered who...
Just some little shit!
And you're a miserable
excuse for a monster!
Little shit
with a big mouth!
You came all the way
from the demon realm...
But you just couldn't resist
a little pussy, could you?
You're no human!
At least I'm not
a fuckin' monster.
You little...!
Who are you?
You don't know me?
You really ARE a loser!
You're Amano Jyaku, the
half-breed of the beast realm!
You're after him too, right?
But you'll never get him!
Satisfied?
WELL DON'T BE!
I'll tell you, as a favor.
It's Ozaki!
Later!
What a day...
Boss!
It's been too long!
You come by
yourself, Kuroko?
Hi, big brother!
You too, Megumi?
Nagumo...
You saved me!
Oh, thank you!
Bottom of the 8th.
How will Yamaki play it?
The third pitch, and...
A hit! Going long!!
Going, going... gone!
So Megumi, do you know
who the Overfiend is?
- Sure!
- Really?
Since you bring it up,
what do YOU think?
Come on.
The Overfiend, who's been
sleeping for 3000 years?
Maybe he doesn't exist.
Cut the shit.
You've found him, right?
Hell yes! My nose's
extra-sensitive.
Better than yours.
Then let's bet on who
the real Overfiend is.
Suit yourself.
Good! If I win, we both go
back to the demon realm.
He's gotta
be the Overfiend...
That bullshit this afternoon'll
bring more demons here...
God dammit! Some guys
get all the luck!
What a horny bastard!
There you go. Enjoy.
Thanks a lot.
Here.
I'm not hungry.
Sorry.
Then I'll eat both.
It didn't happen!
Miss Togami turning
into that monster...
And what it did to me.
It didn't happen, right?
Say it wasn't real!
It wasn't!
Come on, it was your
imagination or something.
Thank you.
Let's sit down.
Look, Akemi...
I've liked you for
a long time now!
The smell... The smell!
I'm sure of it!
It's that guy, all right.
Don't be embarrassed.
I'm glad you told me.
Great.
But I'm still afraid
it'll happen again...
Even if it was
just my imagination.
As long as I'm with you,
Akemi... I'll protect you.
You will protect me,
won't you, Nagumo?
Of course.
Ozaki...
Ozaki... Please...
You're different tonight,
Ozaki. A lot stronger.
I...!! Oh god!
What's going on?
What's happening?
My body...
What's wrong with me?!
So you're
the Overfiend, eh?
He's the Overfiend,
all right.
But how do I
make him manifest?
Here he comes.
Now we'll get a good look.
Boss, he ate
him so easily!
What the...!
I don't get it!
There he goes!
I finally found you!
Those punks were nothing.
Try me on for size!
It's the Overfiend,
all right!
I've found you!
At last, I've found you!
The hell...?
What's happening?!
No... It can't be!
Shit! And I really thought
he was the one!
Boss, he must've taken the blood
or semen of the real
Overfiend.
That's why he had the
Overfiend's power.
Blood or semen...
Blood? You said BLOOD?
Holy...
That guy's the Overfiend?
Oh, I can't take it anymore!
Don't look...
Who are you?
You don't remember,
after last night?
What?!
I've never...!
You jerk!
Akemi!
You're the Overfiend,
aren't you?
Take your real form, quick!
I've been waiting a long time
to get screwed by you!
Hey... Cut it out!
What's her problem?
Maybe I should
take her up on it...
No...
He's too far gone.
The EEG's flat.
The heartbeat has stopped.
"In Surgery"
We did all we could...
I didn't think
he could die.
Guess he wasn't
the Overfiend, either.
There IS no Overfiend!
Let's go back to
the demon realm.
What the...!
I sense a demon!
What's wrong?!
It's so strong...! I've never
felt anything this strong!
Stop it...!
After 3000 years rest,
I awaken!
No! Stop it!
My first in 3000 years!
How very, very sweet...
Oh man,
I'd better tell the boss!
Boss! I saw him!
Nagumo IS the Overfiend!
What?!
- I'll check this out!
- Wait for me!
I'll stay here.
Help me...!
Megumi!
Well Megumi...
I guess you won the bet...
O arrogant humanity!
Not all that exists is
visible to your mortal eyes!
Our world consists
of the realm of humans...
...the realm of man-beasts,
and the realm of demons.
And many of the demons
live in the human world.
There is a legend
among the demons.
That once, every 3000 years,
the Overfiend revives.
And upon his revival,
the three realms are...
...united to form
an eternal kingdom.
O arrogant humanity!
Heed well the voices of those
of the demon realm.
Humans are not the
supreme rulers of all.
You shall know the truth
when the Overfiend revives.
And the promised time
is close at hand!
Myojin, a private school
in the city of Yokohama.
It is here that a
strange drama unfolds.
Tatsuo Nagumo,
shy but lecherous.
Akemi lto,
the school idol.
Amano Jyaku of the beast realm,
who searches for the Overfiend...
The shadow of the demon
realm encroaches from behind...
You don't know me?
He engages in death matches
with creatures from the...
...demon realm who come
to destroy the Overfiend.
Amidst the chaos, Nagumo
and Akemi fall in love.
What the...!
I sense a demon...?
After 3000 years rest,
I awaken!
My first in 3000 years!
How very, very sweet...
Who is the Overfiend, awakened
from 3000 years slumber?
Can he really
be Nagumo?
And what will the Overfiend
wreak upon our world?
September 1, 1923 - 11:32 AM
Tokyo
Christ!
What's that jerk up to?
Hold it, Suikakujyu!
Too late, kid!
This will finish Tokyo.
And him.
What?
You didn't...
This will destroy
the Overfiend!
You've summoned the
Demon King of the Sea...?!
Don't celebrate yet!
He isn't the Overfiend!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Overfiend
Part 2
"Curse of the Overfiend"
That's it for today.
Class dismissed.
Hear about the gas explosion
at the hospital near my place?
And I heard this
weird moaning.
And Ozaki burned himself
to death. It's really weird.
"Tatsuo Nagumo survived
the huge explosion..."
Is that true, Amano?
Sure it's true.
He's fine.
Really?! You're not
making it up?
Sure.
It's the truth.
Thank God...
He's too lucky to let
himself be killed that easy.
I bet he's on his
way here to see you.
No way...!
Akemi,
you like Nagumo?
With Ozaki dead...
Why pick a jerk like him?
A total lech that
everyone laughs at.
How does he wind
up with Akemi lto?
Niki!
You'll catch a cold
sleeping up there.
Hey, wait... Akemi...
Here he comes.
Akemi!
Darn it, I'm crying!
Go on.
He came to see you.
Akemi, I sorta have these
concert tickets, and l...
Sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
Hey, wait!
Nagumo!
I'm glad!
You think she'd want
someone with YOUR face?
We'll cheer you up.
Come on.
Really? Great!
So you believe that
I don't know her?
I don't care,
as long as you're okay.
Akemi...
Remember to
use a condom!
What the...?!
Hi!
Amano?!
Get a grip, bud.
This is my pal, Kuroko.
Kuroko...?
Sorry to interrupt, but can you
come with us for a sec?
I'll introduce you to my sister...
The girl you met last night.
She's your sister?
Oh God...!
Relax. He's just a punk
from the demon realm.
Punk from
the demon realm...?
Some show, huh?
What happened?
Why did it...?
You may not believe this,
but we're not human.
I haven't come that
good in a long time!
Hey, Megumi!
Big brother! Were you
watching? You perv...
Give you two
some ideas?
Standards going down?
You and that slime spot...?
That's the type
you find here.
Probably after the
Overfiend, too.
Overfiend?
I know! Let's take 'em to the
beast realm to see the Elder.
Good idea!
Wanna do it, Nagumo?
What's a "beast realm?"
He's got such a small prick!
Why'd we bring him along?
He's homely, too.
Zero dick...
...and zero technique!
Yeah, compared with him,
Nagumo looked like a stud.
Oh, you're so
good today...!
I mean it! I've never
felt like this before!
Just stay on lookout,
you dickless wonder!
Should I let him
have a lick?
He wants to...
That impotent nerd...
Say you'd love to!
I'd love to.
Say, "Thank you."
Come on...
Th-thank you...
What're you
trying to do?!
If your scummy mouth touches it,
how can I use it again?
This is what you lick!
Lick it! Such a
beautiful, white foot...
And be thankful
for this much.
And keep your
dirty hands off it!
Yeah...
Just like that.
- He can't even moan right!
- Don't you like it?
Hey, what's that look?
The hell with Akemi!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you all...!
What the hell...?!
We only did
what you wanted.
Who's there?!
Don't you want
power like that?
Not just the power to kill,
but to lay any girl you want.
Anyone you fall for
will happily come to you.
Monsters!
You like what
you are now?
An outsider? A virgin?
You want to stay like this?!
A stupid, homely,
dickless wimp?!
You want Akemi,
don't you?
You hate Nagumo,
All right, then! Swap this
for your own little prick.
Take it easy.
The pain won't last long.
After that, spill the
blood of two humans.
Then no one can
stand in your way!
Shaddap!
I'll teach ya to
steal from my wallet!
Who d'ya think you are?!
Ya little shit!
That's right!
Hit him good!
M... Mom!
Come here! I ain't
through with you yet!
Why do I get treated
like this? Shit...
You want to be strong,
don't you?
It's a small price to pay...
To be strong...!
To be strong!
What're you
trying to do?!
Lick it...
- Little shit!
- Hit him good!
Little shit!
LITTLE SHIT!
So? Are you convinced
we're not human?
Yes.
Akemi!
Hey, Kuroko!
Can't you go faster?
You little piece of...
Hey, thanks.
I REALLY mean it...
Did you enjoy
your sky-diving?
Hang on,
we're almost there.
Well? This is the
beast realm, our home.
It's beautiful.
See it? No one knows
when it was built.
But it's the symbol
of the demon realm.
It's written there that some
high and mighty yahoo...
...called the "Overfiend" is
reborn every 3000 years.
And that he will
combine the realms of...
...humans, beasts, and demons
into an eternal kingdom.
Ever since I learned what
that meant, I haven't rested.
I've wandered the human realm
to find him when he's reborn.
I'm not sure why, though.
It's not like I don't
like the world now...
But if the Overfiend can
make a better world for us...
l... I just had
to see him myself!
It's taken me 300 years!
And at last I've found him!
Nagumo,
you're the Overfiend!
No way! He can't be!
Anyway, the Elder will tell
us whether or not he is.
Amano Jyaku!
Your obsession with the
Overfiend defies reason.
Elder, take a good look.
He's the real deal!
Begone! This realm has no
use for that monster!
What's...?
Out with you!
Begone!
Wait, Elder! I've seen him
with my own eyes!
I've seen him!
Niki's fighting the gang!
He's crazy!
This is too weird!
Ow, shit...! That senile...!
What's with him?!
Akemi!
Is that the best your
punk mob can do?
Don't think I'm
as easy as them.
You still have time
to apologize, Niki.
You dickless wimp...
Excuse me...
What's happened to him?
He's changed.
Hey, Akemi! Come on.
We'll have some fun...
N-no thanks...
Just follow the
man who's strong.
What the...?!
What the hell is this?!
Lay off, Niki! You can't
force her. It's wrong...
Nagumo... Enjoy her
while you can!
Okay, you girls...
Follow me!
Big brother... He smelled
like a demon.
Yeah, he sure stank
all right.
Shit! That little prick,
Nagumo...!
Who does he
think he is?!
I'll rip him apart!
It hurts! Stop it...!
Shaddap,
you fucking bitch!
Niki...
Akemi! Akemi...
I love you...
What's wrong?
It's burning! Ow, God...!
What's happening?!
It's rotten... Rotten...
This wasn't
part of the deal!
Help me!
Help me...
Don't panic, kid.
It'll grow back soon.
What should I do?
Actually, there are a couple
more things you need...
Blood and semen...?!
Drink it, and the
whole world is yours!
Wait!
All right then...
Don't! You sure it's
okay to do this?
My folks are out
at a funeral. Come on!
No...
I really envy them!
This happens whenever
we watch them.
Akemi...
Do me, now...
Hurry...
- Akemi, I'm sorry...
- It's okay, really...
Akemi!
I told you
I'd come for her!
Niki!
I see.
The sperm works!
Nagumo, if you want
Akemi, come to the...
...old factory in Yamate
at ten tonight!
Akemi!
What are you up to
with that guy, Niki?
Niki? What're you
talking about?
Don't laugh too soon,
Amano Jyaku!
He will take
care of you!
"He"...? He who?
I sense...
Murderous intent...?!
Who's there?
Suikakujyu...!
You're alive!
Thought I'd forget how you
scarred my lovely face?
You're still after
the Overfiend?
Die!
No you don't...
The Overfiend will die...
But you come first!
Nagumo!
He's playing for keeps...
Damn that Niki...!
Hello?
My name's Nagumo.
Is Yuichi here?
What's that smell?
A monster...
Niki's a murderer!
We told him he'd need the blood
of two humans to be strong.
So he butchered
the two nearest to him!
You're a murderer too,
Overfiend!
You'd drink your own parents'
blood to save your dear life.
That's what you
humans are like!
Is it true...?
What's happening?
Say your prayers,
Amano Jyaku!
Just tell me...
What're you doing
with that kid, Niki?
All right, I will.
The Overfiend is born
of the human realm.
So the one who fights him
must be of the same world.
And the best
one for the job is...
...one who has uncommon
human hatred.
Is that so?
Oh man... You thought you
could kill me that easy?
You little...!
What can be
keeping my brother?
Yeah.
He sure is late.
I guess he'll get
here eventually.
Nagumo...
No! Niki, stop!
He's here.
You like Nagumo
that much?
Then I'll try not
to make him suffer.
Wait!
Stop it, Niki!
Nagumo, get away!
Nagumo...!
Glad you could
make it, Nagumo.
She's real nice down here,
you know that?
Way too good for a guy
with a tiny prick like yours.
Keep coming...
That's right...
After I destroy you,
I'll fuck her in half!
Now!
Not quite!
Please, help Nagumo!
Maybe if we get him
to a hospital right now...!
It's too late.
Please help him!
I'll do whatever you want!
Masturbate.
Can't do it, huh?
Not even for his sake?
Please... help him.
Help Nagumo!
Shut up!
Do as I say...
Niki, you'll catch a cold
sleeping up there.
She was the only one
who was ever nice to me.
I... I...
The girl is mine!
Lmpossible!
Die!
Freak! I have your blood
and your sperm!
Suikakujyu! Why are you
trying to kill the Overfiend?
I like this world as it is.
He might destroy the 3 realms,
and I can't allow that!
We don't need him!
But he'll make the
world even better!
Don't you want
to see that?
You're wrong!
Oh... yuck!
Don't you see,
Amano Jyaku?
See what?
The Overfiend
isn't what you think!
- What?
- You'll see...
What? What was
he trying to say?
Cripes... Nagumo!
Fukakuki...
Stop it!
Stop! Please!
Please...
Nasty! They didn't
have to go so far.
What a relief! Now I know
you're the Overfiend.
Niki!
Akemi...
That's my...
I guess he
really liked you.
Why did he do
this for me?
What have I done to you?
L- I did it.
I turned into a monster
and killed Niki!
Nagumo, wait!
Nagumo!
Hold on!
Well, now I'm totally confused.
What the hell is the Overfiend?
All he did was
kill one skinny punk.
How is he
the god of gods?
Begone! This realm has no
use for that monster!
That old fart
knows something!
Dear Suikakujyu,
we'll meet again soon.
Elder, I'm confused!
What the hell
IS the Overfiend?
He's supposed to rule all 3
realms to build a better world.
But all he does
is wreak havoc!
Or is he the Overfiend at all?
Elder, tell me!
Say something, dammit!
Elder!
Amano Jyaku,
even I fail to understand.
But if he
is the Overfiend...
...the legend about him
may be wrong.
What? No way!
It's ridiculous!
Calm yourself, Amano Jyaku.
There is a way to find out.
What way?
What do I do, Elder?
You will see into
the future, for yourself.
I've lived 993
years in this world.
My time is
nearly come.
But while I still can,
I'll send you into the future.
Elder!
Look well into the
future... for my sake too.
Look well with your
own eyes, Amano Jyaku!
Where am I?
What's all this? Is this the
human world of the future?
It can't be!
Where'd that senile
old bastard send me?
I see... So this is Osaka?
Huh? Nagumo?!
What? What are
they trying to say?
Help! Help me!
For pity's sake!
What?!
Why's he doing this?
What the...?!
It's Osaka Castle.
Why isn't it damaged?
That's it! The secret of the
Overfiend legend is in there!
More time, Elder!
I'm almost through!
Come on, you old fart!
Elder!
Please!
Oh no...
Just a little more time!
There's something here!
Let me see!
According to legend,
once every 3000 years...
...the Overfiend is reborn
into this world to...
...unify the human, demon
and beast realms...
...and build an
eternal kingdom.
Amano Jyaku, a beast,
has come to the...
...human realm in search
of the legendary Overfiend.
His prime candidate
is Tatsuo Nagumo...
...a seemingly ordinary
college student.
Meanwhile, Suikakujyu,
of the demon realm...
...a realm opposed
to that of the beasts...
...fears the rebirth
of the Overfiend...
...and sent his minions
to attack Nagumo.
As if moved by Fate, Nagumo
approached Akemi lto...
...the idol of the school,
and fell in love with her.
Niki, a classmate of Nagumo's,
also fell in love with her...
...and sold his soul to a
demon to transform himself...
...into a powerful monster
to destroy Nagumo.
But when Nagumo was attacked.
A "power" awakened within him...
...changing him into the "Overfiend"
and causing him to murder Niki.
While observing the ugly scene,
Amano Jyaku began to wonder...
...if Nagumo was in fact
the true Overfiend...
...and what the promised
"eternal kingdom" would be like.
In response to his request,
the Elder of the beast realm...
...has sent Amano Jyaku into
the future to seek the truth.
Where am I?
What's all this? Is this the
human world of the future?
It can't be!
Where'd that senile
old bastard send me?
I see. So this is Osaka?
Now what?
The Overfiend?
Save us!
Save us, Lady lto!
Lady lto?
Help me!
Please, help me!
For pity's sake!
Take me to
Lady lto at the castle!
Are you talking
about Akemi?
What?!
Why's he doing this?
What the...?!
It's Osaka Castle.
Why isn't it damaged?
That's it! The secret of the
Overfiend legend is in there!
More time, Elder!
I'm almost through!
Come on, you old fart!
Elder!
The secret to the whole
legend is in there! Please!
Just a little more time!
There's something here!
Let me see!
UROTSUKIDOJI
Legend of the Overfiend
Part 3
"Final Inferno"
I beg the Gods
not to forsake him...
Return Suikakujyu
to life and to me.
I beg you all,
now and forever.
Protect him! Revive him!
Let him live again!
O deities of all the realms...
return my love to me.
Suikakujyu, my love...
I lack the strength
to be reborn...
Fukakuki... Enkakuki...
Give me your bodies...
Suikakujyu...
My Queen...
Suikakujyu, something is
happening in the human world.
The demon realm will be
destroyed if it isn't stopped.
Hurry... You must kill
the Overfiend now!
You're my only hope...
By your command.
Nagumo!
Nagumo...
As long as I'm with you,
Akemi... I'll protect you.
I'll protect you...
You will protect me,
won't you, Nagumo?
Of course...
Nagumo...
I... I'm a monster...
Nagumo?
Nagumo, it's me.
Go away.
I'm not human
anymore. Please...
Nagumo, open up.
No.
It was a lie,
wasn't it?
That stuff about always
being there for me.
I love you, Nagumo...
I don't care what's
happened to you...
I just know I love you!
Akemi...
Nagumo...
I love you.
I love you, too.
Don't let me go!
Never let me go again!
Fantastic...
What'll we do now?
Let 'em have fun.
You've returned?
Elder!
I'm done for. I've used
the last of my power.
What're you saying?!
Hang on, you old fool!
Amano Jyaku!
I saw the future
through your eyes.
Then tell me: Was that really
the future of the 3 realms?
Elder!
Amano Jyaku...
The only thing I can say is
the eternal kingdom...
...the Overfiend will build
may be very different...
...from the demon, beast and
human worlds as they exist now.
What?
You're beautiful, Akemi.
Why...
Why are you crying?
I'm happy.
We'll be joined forever now,
body and soul.
And no one will ever
stand between us again.
Never...
No one will
ever separate us.
I'll never let anyone
do that... Akemi!
Nagumo...!
May I?
Nagumo!
L- l-
Oh god, I...!
I can't...!
Please...!
Not so hard...
Nagumo...
He's changing...
Nagumo!
The 3 realms
are collapsing!
ELDER!!!
Run!
It's the Overfiend!
Horrible...!
This is the Overfiend?
The god above all others?
He's an enemy!
The devil! KILL HIM!!
No! You'll die!
Megumi!
Big brother!
Boss!
Look! He's just
killing at random.
Is that all he was born
to do? Big brother?!
Nagumo...
Why...? Why?!
What the...?
That chant... No...! He's trying
the same thing he did 70 years ago!
Amano Jyaku! It's too late!
I, Suikakujyu, control
the Demon King of the Sea!
This will finally
destroy the Overfiend!
What the...?
What's he trying to do?
NO!
Amano Jyaku!
It's time you
faced the truth.
Suikakujyu...
Amano Jyaku... The 3 realms
will never be as they were.
This is what the
Overfiend really is.
A devil, bent on destroying the
human, beast, and demon worlds.
But... there's still time.
Kill him!
He's still weak
from the battle.
Use this chance
to destroy him.
Now that the Demon King
of the Sea is dead...
Our only hope is you,
Amano Jyaku...
I beg you!
He will destroy every...
Nagumo... Have I wandered
for 300 years just for this?!
Just to find a
bastard like you?
Big brother...
Boss! You gotta
kill him, quick!
Nagumo! Even me?!
Nagumo!
Change back!
Stop being the
Overfiend! Nagumo!
Boss!
Kuroko!
Why are you hesitating?
This isn't like you!
KUROKO!
MEGUMI!
Nagumo! Why are you
doing this to me?
Nagumo! Nagumo...
Stop it! Nagumo...
Nagumo! Damn you!
I'll never forgive you!
Give me back Kuroko!
Give me back my sister!
Amano Jyaku...
Akemi, why...? What are you
doing here?! Akemi!
It's no use
calling her name.
Mama no longer
has human feelings.
Mama?
Yes. I'm speaking to
you from her body.
What?
Then... you're...
Yes. I am the child of
Nagumo and Akemi.
The true Overfiend
you've been looking for.
The true Overfiend?!
Then what's Nagumo...?
What the hell is he?
Merely a male,
necessary to give me life.
And now he's become
the Demon of Destruction...
...who must destroy the 3 realms
so that I may be reborn!
Demon of Destruction?!
Papa is destroying all the
worlds for my sake.
Why?
Because it was decided
3000 years ago.
3000 years ago?
Yes. 3000 years ago,
so as to bring order to chaos...
I created the human
world you know today...
At the same time I made
two other worlds:
A world of man-beasts,
for the superhuman...
And of demons, for those
who could not become human.
Thus were born the
beast and demon realms.
And, at that time,
I made a promise...
In 3000 years,
I shall be reborn.
If I find that humans are "good,"
then all will be as planned.
But, if I find that
they have become "evil..."
...I shall reduce the worlds to
void and begin again!
That's the real legend
of the Overfiend?!
Humanity hasn't
become what I intended.
So now I have to start over.
The humans must be destroyed
so that I can replace them.
What?!
You're saying you'll
destroy the 3 realms...
...just so you
can be reborn?
DAMN YOU!!!!
Amano Jyaku...
Amano Jyaku,
don't be foolish...
There's nothing I
can do to stop this?
Nagumo, stop it!
I like the world
the way it is...
Nagumo!
I thought I'd erased all
of Mama's consciousness.
How can she be...
A-ma-no...
Amano!
Amano... It's all right.
Take it easy...
Akemi...?
Amano.
I'll help you. Come on.
Get out of here... Hurry!
Akemi...!
Megumi!
Big brother...
Megumi... you're...
Nagumo...
You still know me,
don't you?
With all your power,
you can easily kill me.
End my life now,
while I still love you.
What're they...?
I don't want the Overfiend
to control me.
I won't live as a tool.
I won't!
If you kill me,
the Overfiend will die, too.
And you, Nagumo.
Nagumo, let's choose
to die together. Together...
A... ke... mi...
Nagumo...
Nagumo!
KILL ME NOW!
Mama... Papa... You can't.
This is our destiny.
NO!!!
Amano Jyaku,
this is as it must be.
Mama cannot die before
she gives birth to me.
And Papa cannot die before
he's destroyed the 3 realms.
Stop it! Change them
back to themselves!
Stop it...
Overfiend, please...
Do not grieve,
Amano Jyaku.
When I create the new
worlds, centuries from now...
...they will be reborn,
as they appear now.
You will?
Do you mean that?!
I do. And they'll love
each other, as in this life.
All destruction leads to rebirth.
This a beginning, not an end.
Can you live to see the
new world, Amano Jyaku?
So that's it?
Sure, I'll live.
A hundred years,
a thousand...
I'll just keep on wandering
until I see the future...
Yours,
Nagumo's, Akemi's...
And until I do...
I WILL NOT DIE!!!
O arrogant humanity!
Not all that exists is
visible to your mortal eyes!
Our world consists
of the realm of humans...
...the realm of beasts,
and the realm of demons.
There is a legend shared by
the beasts and the demons.
That once, every 3000 years,
the Overfiend revives.
And upon his revival,
the three realms are...
...united to form
an eternal kingdom.
O arrogant humanity!
Humans are not the
supreme rulers of all.
You shall know the truth
when the Overfiend revives.