No! Stop it!
Mimika-chan, it's dangerous to struggle.
But...
Please, don't hurt us!
If you're aiming at us, do it properly!
- No!
- Stop it!
Hit
/
Missed
A Gift of a Kiss
Too bad!
That's right! Please pay on your way out!
Thank you very much!
Please come again!
Good job! You really
helped our club.
This kind of thing is easy money.
I can give you good money
for this part-time job.
Lots of money! Carrots! Carrots!
So, we have one more request.
Will you enter the Miss Banzai
School Contest?
Miss Banzai School Contest!
Entries Wanted!
What? Both of us?
Actually, the favorite entrant is
very popular, so it looks like we'll lose.
No, we can't. Right, Mimika-chan?
Fan of Queen Koshka
- Mimika-chan!
- Koshka-chan!
I was looking for you!
You're going to enter as well, right?
That.
Miss Banzai School Contest!
Entries Wanted!
Okay? It will give you
delicious memories.
Delicious? Is the contest delicious?
Okay! I'll enter!
Their eyes are nailed to you.
I love Koshka
Forever Koshka!
Will Haru's eyes also be nailed to me?
Of course.
Nail! Nail! Nail!
Miss Banzai Contest Entry Form
Not that kind of nailing!
Now, sign this.
It can't be helped.
Well, I'll be her guardian.
You make everything worthwhile.
This will be the most profitable
event in history!
All right!
Haru should use his head a bit more.
The 14th Banzai School Cultural Festival
Female Breeding Committee Members
Animal Land / Very Cute! / You Can Hold Her!
Is there anything exciting going on?
My heart is pounding.
Hey, look at this!
Female Breeding...
You Can Hold Her!
All right!
They've done well!
Oh, welcome!
What's this?
There aren't any girls!
Hey, where are the girls?
Girls...?
Are you mocking us?
Are you making fun of us?
Wait... What are you saying?
Shut up!
Please stop!
Shut up.
Bring out the girls! The girls!
Hold it!
Who's there?
Inaba Mikami... san
Inaba-san!
How are you today?
I-Inaba... is it?
Haru!
Are you all right?
I was so scared!
It was Inaba... right?
Female Breeding Committee Members
Very Cute!/ You Can Hold Her!
The boundary between them is blurring.
That's why a merged being is a nuisance.
If I don't hurry...
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
Inside of me, the power of fire sleeps.
Watashi no nake ni hi no chikara ga nemutteru
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
To make the dream come true once again.
Mou ichido yume wo kanaeru tame ni
Usagi-chan de Cue!!
The days when we laughed like fools.
Baka mitai ni waratta hibi wo
The memories where we cried till it hurt.
Itai kurai naita kioku wo
If they were all lies,
Zenbu itsuwari nara
My nature would be sad.
Watashi rashi sa ga kanashii ne
Since when have you
Aimai ni ne itsu kara
Remembered only how to give up?
Akirameru koto dake wo oboeta no
Get back. Just get.
Get back just get
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
"Something is different."
Nani ka ga chigau
When I have that feeling...
Sonna omoi ga aru no nara
Change my destiny!
Change my destiny
People give in all the time.
Itsu datte hito wa merikonde
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
Like my heart...
Kono mune mitai na
With the future I've always looked for.
Zutto sagashiteta mirai to
Change my destiny.
Change my destiny
There is only one real me.
Hontou no watashi wa hitotsu mikakeru
= Servant =
Our plan to eliminate
Inaba Mikami is on track.
It's running late.
As expected, you knew that.
Everyone is disappointed.
You say that, but...
I told you that excuses are useless!
Eliminating her is the highest priority.
We are counting on you.
= Fortune Family =
I swear on this badge.
I'll trust you on this.
Sir, I have one concern.
Do you know about Dekao?
Someone revived him.
But he couldn't defeat Inaba.
Winning or losing isn't the issue.
There is an organization powerful
enough to revive him.
Did you think I revived him?
- Or someone greater than you?
- Keep you mouth shut.
Sir.
I don't employ just dogs.
It's just... please tell me.
What is your nose for?
If you can't sniff it out, you're useless.
I want results, not just progress.
If you don't want to be fed to the
lions, learn to do it yourself.
The situation is spiraling out of control.
She's influencing many people.
If she merges, she will threaten our work.
It's just like I heard...
It might be your turn soon.
I understand. I'd already made a plan
even without hearing from you.
Cats hate being ordered around.
Oh. So what's your plan?
I will reveal Inaba Mikami's
true form to the public.
What do you think they'll do
if I reveal her true form?
If she turns into her combat form...
she'll be expelled from school.
I will make Inaba suffer and hurt Mimika.
Can we do this without
dirtying our hands?
Cats are very spiteful.
That's where we're different from dogs.
It's interesting to see what
dogs can do on the brink.
They can do many things
and not get noticed.
Inaba Mikami... I'd like to have
you as an opponent.
Female Breeding Committee Members
Animal Land / Very Cute! / You Can Hold Her!
This looks good. But maybe
Haru would prefer this...
I didn't see anything.
Haru! It's about to start!
Sorry, I've got to feed them.
It's more important that we go!
- More important?
- Sorry.
This contest might be more important
to you right now...
- I didn't mean that.
- ... but I cannot abandon them.
They can't live on their own.
They...
"I want to be a vet who can understand
the language of animals."
"I want to hear you speak."
I wanted you to be happy!
Everyone's waiting, right?
Hurry and go!
Lately... you don't look at me at all!
Sorry for disturbing your fun.
We want to join your fes--
Fools! Follow her!
The 14th Banzai School Cultural Festival
Thank you very much!
Next up is entry number four!
Nekoi Koshka-san, go ahead!
Men are all such fools.
That's strange.
What happened to Mimika-chan?
Geez, there's no time!
Don't fight!
Haru!
You mustn't fight!
You're not Inaba Mikami.
Mimika, everyone's waiting for you!
Haru!
Go!
Geez, it's about to start.
Oh, this is bad. We're out of time.
Oh well. We'll have to use our last resort.
Do you have another idea?
I Love Koshka!
Forever Koshka!
Okay, that was Koshka-san.
Now, who's up next?
Ah, yes! Entry number five.
Mitsuki Miku-san!
Miss Banzai School Contest
U-um... well...
Do a pose! Do any pose!
"Pose"...
You said that so suddenly,
I can't think of anything.
What the hell is that?
What on earth is THAT?
What happened?
Chou's troops are engaged in
combat with Inaba Mikami.
What did you say?
That stupid dog. Why is he
interfering with the plan?
That's why I said I didn't want to do it!
What are you doing, Mimika-chan?
Get over here!
Just go!
Inaba Mikami!
= Fortune Family =
Your destiny ends here!
You're...
The Saotome School's headmaster!
Your duty ends here.
The Board made a decision to
subordinate you to our group.
W-what did you say?!
- Then, I'm no longer needed?
- Follow them.
Mimika, let's go!
Mimika's late!
Why am I the only one dressed like this?
Miku! I let you wear my
special costume! Do a cuter pose!
You have to flirt with the crowd!
What?! Again?!
Geez, I don't want to be
embarrassed again!
Oh, what should I do?!
I-I've got no choice!
* Wordplay: chu = kiss; chusha = injection
Anyone want to give me an injection?
Did I mess up again?
That was awesome!
Huh? What's that?
- What's that?
- What's going on?
Haru!
I'll come later. Go on without me.
Yes.
Miss Banzai School Contest
This is going according to plan.
What will you do, Mimika? No... Inaba?
I'm entry number five!
Inaba...
Inaba Mikami!
- Awesome!
- She changed so quickly!
Oh crap! I forgot about that.
You'll have to pay for
ruining Mimika's fun.
Hold on. Inaba Mikami.
Get out of here, you weaklings!
Although it may make the Board
members angry, I've changed my mind.
Naive and rude girls like you
who know nothing...
If I allowed you to live,
I would be in danger.
Since we're comrades I don't want to
kill you, but I will defeat you.
Comrades?
Are you a merged being too?
It doesn't matter anymore.
You will fall here!
Oh, you got away. Just as I expected.
But I won't let that happen again!
W-what?
You certainly are quick, but don't expect
the same move to work on me twice.
By the way, what's this "Board?"
Do they know something about
merged beings like us?
That's why I called you a naive girl.
Answer me!
Why does merging happen?
I don't know.
Investigate it yourself!
Dekao. He should have been
beyond repair!
I didn't hear about this!
To think that he would come out...
This leaves a bad taste.
Geez, what a persistent guy!
Dammit! The Board decided to go this far?
If that's so, I'm outta here!
Shit! There's no way to get near him!
Now!
Stupid robot!
Why don't you ask them to fix
you brain next time?
What's going on?
An angel...
Haru...
Haru!
Mimika-chan.
Wake up! Haru!
Are you okay? Wake up!
Haru! Come on, Haru!
Let's see... merged, merged...
- Here, I brought these.
- Thank you.
What's with that "Thank you?"
My muscles are getting tired.
Who do you think I'm doing this for?
Oh, did you say something?
No. Now, time to study!
- Ah, this is it!
- Eh?
Where is it?
Here.
Merged
- So it's like I thought.
- What does it say?
- Merged.
- M-merged?
Yeah.
T-that's... It's still too soon!
No, it's not too soon...
We're childhood friends, right?
I have to prepare myself...
You're such a bad boy, Haru!
The merged being is not yet mature.
Not mature... I'm very mature!
Mimika's merging is still immature.
Mimika-chan?
Oh... yeah.
Are you the animal caretaker
or an old friend?
What's up all of a sudden?
Why do you care about
Mimika-chan so much?
She's a rabbit after all.
I see. I guess so.
It's already late, so I'll go home.
Ah, look out!
Hurry up and move! Hurry!
I can't!
Miku-chan?
- Hurry up!
- Haru too!
No!
I can't hold on! I can't stand it!
Haru!
Haru prefers a regular girl after all.
And I'm a... I'm a...
W-we've got a problem!
Mimika!
Finally! I finally found you!
Why did you chase after me?
I... I wanted to sort out
the misunderstanding.
That's a lie! You prefer
a regular girl, right?
There's nothing going on
between Miku and me.
Really? Really and truly?
Misunderstanding! Misunderstanding!
Misunderstanding!
- Hold on a minute.
- What is it?
I want to hear the truth.
"I want to hear you speak."
Really?
Why you and Mimika merged.
Why did something like that happen?
I want to talk to the Inaba inside you.
There are two hearts within
the same body,
but I think that Inaba controls
the switch inside.
Inaba-san is hiding inside me.
If that's the case, why does
she let you control her?
Just... so she can use me.
Please answer me! Inaba!
I-I thought so! You like Inaba-san after all!
On the day she fell off the roof,
you were relieved that
Inaba-san was unhurt!
Is the Mimika that looks human
in the way?
That's not it. I...
You really love Inaba-san, don't you?
- Bye bye!
- That's not it!
Mimika!
Even when you were put
in a human body,
and had to live in a way that
you weren't used to...
I thought you'd be happy because
you'd be living with me.
Mimika would have been
happy with that.
And I... and I would too!
I want to be a vet who understands
the language of animals.
I want to hear you speak.
But is Inaba having her mind stolen
by Mimika? Or the other way round?
= Grin =
Chou of Benten!
= Something's Going On =
You're more precious to me than anyone.
Dare yori daiji ni omotte iru no ni
I can't say it well, so I disguise it with a smile again.
Jouzu ni iezu ni mata egao de gomakasu
The thing shaking in your eyes...
Anata no hitomi no naka de yureru
I don't understand it right now.
Ima watashi ga wakaranai
The more I like you, the more confused I become.
Suki ni naru hodo fuan ni naru
And even so, my heart wants to understand.
Kokoro dakedo wakaritai
I put the pieces of my feelings together
Omoi no kakera ima tsunaida
Gently with these hands.
Yasashii sono te kara
C1 Anime Credits
Translated by Futanari
Edited by Nameraka
Timed by egelteek
QCed by Collectr
Next Episode
It'll be exciting next time, too!
By the way, viewers, you want to know the
secret behind the merged beings, right?
= Chou =
If you really want to know,
I, Chou of Benten, won't tell you.
What is it? You really want to know?
I see. You want to know that badly.
Well... I won't show you!
Well, that's in the next episode.
All will be revealed when Chou-sama
defeats Inaba Mikami.
Please watch for this Chou-sama
of Benten's heroic plan!
Creditless Opening