Energy reaction detected in
Government Service Block B!
Current time is 15:23!
The dimension is warping!
Energy concentration detected
in the air! Emergency level 4!
- The speed is impossible!
- It's a UFO!
So it's finally here.
You from Benten never give up, do you?
No matter what you do,
you can't defeat me.
Well, I'll commend your
fighting spirit at least.
= One Fixed Pattern =
By the way, it's slightly different this time.
He seems strong today.
= Sure of Victory =
Don't cry this time!
Dekao! Go get her!
Let's go!
Rabbit Journal
Morning!
Geez, you're really keen.
Oh, morning, Miku.
Hey, hey, rather than working on that,
there's a new hamburger shop I'd like
to visit this afternoon, Haru--
There's a fight!
Hey, Inaba's started fighting with
the leader of Benten High School.
- Where?
- On the roof.
T-the roof?
T-this is bad! Mimika!
Your strength's not bad,
but your speed isn't good enough.
- Well then, time to finish this.
- Mimika!
Matogi?
I've got you now!
Crap!
Mimika!
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
Inside of me, the power of fire sleeps.
Watashi no nake ni hi no chikara ga nemutteru
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
To make the dream come true once again.
Mou ichido yume wo kanaeru tame ni
Usagi-chan de Cue!!
The days when we laughed like fools.
Baka mitai ni waratta hibi wo
The memories where we cried till it hurt.
Itai kurai naita kioku wo
If they were all lies,
Zenbu itsuwari nara
My nature would be sad.
Watashi rashi sa ga kanashii ne
Since when have you
Aimai ni ne itsu kara
Remembered only how to give up?
Akirameru koto dake wo oboeta no
Get back. Just get.
Get back just get
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
"Something is different."
Nani ka ga chigau
When I have that feeling...
Sonna omoi ga aru no nara
Change my destiny!
Change my destiny
People give in all the time.
Itsu datte hito wa merikonde
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
Like my heart...
Kono mune mitai na
With the future I've always looked for.
Zutto sagashiteta mirai to
Change my destiny.
Change my destiny
There is only one real me.
Hontou no watashi wa hitotsu mikakeru
So Inaba's body is like this.
Her skin is so smooth.
Buy why did this happen?
I can't remember no matter
how hard I try.
Oh well.
Amazing! Inaba-san is great!
Great! Great!
Somebody help!
Stay away!
Well, if you put it that way...
Gramps!
You should check first to see who's inside.
Oh, I was careless.
There's only one lady
in our house, you see...
Oh.
So, who's this girl?
Um... well...
Isn't she Mimika-chan?
Mimika...
Geez, Gramps. You have such
a bad memory.
Was she here all this time?
Yes.
I see. I see.
That's right.
That's bad, Gramps.
You shouldn't do that.
Don't take baths without asking.
I've kept you a secret from my parents.
It's all right! I have these.
I have special waves in these ears.
They convince people
there's nothing strange.
More importantly, have you
remembered anything?
I really don't know. I remember up until
Inaba-san saved me, but...
At the moment when we fell...
I only remember feeling like I was
wrapped in a warm light...
W-what happened to Inaba?
You like Inaba-san more than me!
- That's not what I mean.
- Really?
Y-yeah.
YAY! Haru!
M-Mimika.
I love you. I managed to
meet you as a human.
I'm so happy.
Mi... Mika...
Um... well...
Hey! What are you two doing?
Miku.
I-it's not what you think!
There's a reason for this.
I know that.
It's Mimika-chan, so you
can't help yourself.
Otherwise, I also...
Here you go. Anyway, I brought
some clothes and food.
Haru!
How long are you going
to keep that up?!
I want to keep doing this forever!
Haru! Haru!
Hey, you, you're really
Mimika-chan, right?
If you were Inaba-san,
I wouldn't forgive you.
Mimika. Your ears.
They don't work on Miku-chan.
Why not? They don't work on me either.
Listen up! Hurry and let him go!
I'm sorry, Miku-chan.
I'm happy when I'm with Haru.
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
What?! Don't start again!!
Like I said, it's not what you think!
I'm not talking to you!
Oh, this won't work at all.
Haru!
Well, I'll go home, so...
Oh, it's dark, so be careful.
Stop it, Mimika.
I'm grown up, so I have big breasts too.
Mimika-chan's so lucky.
She's alone with Haru.
She's finally asleep.
Okay.
But why did Inaba and Mimika...?
Oh well.
She wasn't injured even after
that fall, so that's good.
I should take my time
thinking about it.
But even though she can send
those signals, I have to be careful.
Anyway, I have to make sure
she doesn't go out naked.
Yeah, I'll do that.
It's Haru! It's Haru! It's Haru!
She's so outgoing!
Well done, Mimika!
Huh? Was she here all this time?
More importantly, is Miku okay with this?
Mimika will take Matogi-kun away.
That won't happen.
We're just childhood friends.
But don't you and Matogi-kun
make a good couple?
No way. If the woman is serious,
the man must be carefree.
If the man is serious,
the woman must be carefree.
My parents are like that too.
There needs to be balance in the world.
Boys his age like outgoing girls because
they're easy to understand.
Stop, I said. Mimika, that tickles.
Geez, he's so simple.
Hey, have you gained weight recently?
Sorry about yesterday.
I don't know what happened to me.
Somehow, I got a bit jealous.
Oh, those candies were nice.
Yeah, by the way,
I heard they finished building a
hamburger shop near the station.
Want to drop in on the way home?
There we go!
It's finished.
Sorry, what were you saying?
Geez.
It's okay. It wasn't important.
Haru! Let's go home!
Oh! You fixed my house!
Yeah.
Bye bye, everyone.
I'm going to Haru's house.
Okay, let's go home.
- Let's go home for an afternoon snack!
- Afternoon snack?
Oh, let's see what's left
of Miku's groceries.
- Gila Jello...
- Gelato candy?
What is it, Miku?
Huh? Miku-chan gained weight?
Inaba... Mikami!
Brother!
What is it?
= Afternoon Snack =
= Surprised =
Inaba Mikami is alive?!
No enemies around.
I already told everyone
that I killed Inaba.
Hold it!
= Hold It =
Hey, Inaba, why do you look so healthy?
Dekao's in the hospital.
That's right! We'll kill you today!
What? Brother! That's Mimika.
She's so cute!
What are you saying?!
That's Inaba, right?
I-NA-BA!
Mimika.
What is it?
Who's this little boy?
= Don't Call Me Little! =
Shut up!
You can't say that you forgot me!!
Hello, little boy.
= Eh? =
H-Hello.
= Huh? =
What am I saying?!
= No! =
= Prepare Yourself! =
= I'm Coming! =
Chest!
= Oops! =
Miku-chan!
= Fortune Family =
I missed. But next time...
T-this is...
W-what's that?
So pretty...
- Hey! Withdraw!
- What? Why?
Let's watch a little longer.
- Just withdraw!
- Yes, sir.
Miku.
Haru.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
You were worried about me?
Haru!
I was so scared!
Now, now, calm down.
Oh, anyway, let's go in there. Okay?
All right!
Grand Opening!
Hey, Brother! Please wait!
There's no doubt about it.
They're merged.
Yey! It's brand new! Brand new!
Oh, they're just built this shop.
Did you know?
No.
- Haru! I'm thirsty!
- Okay, okay.
- Here, healthy carrot juice.
- Yay!
I don't have much money,
so I got us some cola.
Okay.
I'm having the same as Haru.
Thank you.
Awww! You have a different drink!
How nice! I wanna drink it!
Hey, carrot juice is expensive, you know.
I want some cola too!
Give me a little.
Mimika!
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
It just spilled on the table.
I'll get some paper towels.
You really are dumb.
You were in such a rush.
But I wanted to try the cola.
I don't have any more money.
The cola went bye-bye.
Then have some of this.
Thank you!
Haru's cola... an indirect kiss...
How nice, Mimika-chan.
You can do that so naturally.
Oh, you really are dumb.
You hands are all sticky.
Oh, Miku, sorry.
I'll take her to wash her hands.
All done, all done.
Oh, I'm all right, so...
I guess it can't be helped.
It's Haru's job to look after her.
My master, I saw them merge.
So, where is it now?
Right now, it's at a classmate's house.
So, what is its current intelligence?
It seems smart, but it's still a rabbit.
- A rabbit?
- Yes.
That's different from a dog like you.
A dog works for his master.
Never take your eyes off
the merged being.
Yes, sir.
Is his way of speaking reliable?
He's bad at finding out details.
Even though he's a dog,
his nose isn't as any good.
She's finally asleep.
Anyway, what happened to her today?
Maybe she should stop seeing people.
I won't take her out so much any more.
I'll do that.
It's the beach!
We came to the sea, but...
Me first!
What are you doing, Mimika-chan?
Inaba's butt looks unexpectedly
good in that swimsuit.
Hey, Miku-chan! Don't laugh!
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy!
When I think about it, I've never come
to the ocean with Miku before.
I never knew she was
that much of a woman.
I've always been friendly with her, but I've
never looked closely at her before.
She's quite beautiful.
Why is Haru standing there,
when the sun is so strong?
He should put the tent up already.
I put up a tent but in the wrong place.
Shall we go?
O-okay.
- Are you all right, Miku-chan?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just stepped on a seashell.
Is something troubling you,
young ladies?
If you have a problem, leave it to us!
Do you need CPR?
We can play with you if you're bored!
We are called the Sailors of Sinbad!
We're fine. We're going now.
We won't allow that!
- Surrender!
- You must be saved by us!
Miku-chan!
How is this supposed to save me?
It's all right. We're gentle.
Stop that!
Get away from her!
We're saving her. You go away!
NOOOOO!
Stop it!
You are the first to be saved.
Sinbad!
Continue! Resuscitation!
Final blow! Tari tari kick!
Haru!
I-it's so sad!
Now it's time for real lifesaving!
Who's there?
Didn't you learn that the ocean
belongs to everyone?
You behavior is completely unsuitable
for such a beautiful beach.
Mimika-chan?
I-Inaba Mikami...
As promised, we made
the black rabbit come out.
= Good Work =
Chou of Benten.
I've been waiting for you, Inaba Mikami.
= Professor of Everything =
No... merged being.
Where should we attack her?
What?
She could jump that high
on loose sand?!
This speed...
= The Red Comet =
Because she's a rabbit.
You're...
Dekao!
= We've Won! =
I see! You've come back
from the hospital.
Inaba Mikami, we have one
final card to play!
On top of that, you can't do
what you did before.
This time, there's no place
for you to fall.
Now, it's time for revenge!
What are you doing?!
So you're a messenger who's
come back from hell?
Time for revenge.
There!
Okay! I'll borrow this for a bit.
That bastard! This time,
I'll crush his stomach!
What a big bastard!
Take this!
= Mommy! =
Who...
Mimika?
I-Inaba?
Inaba Mi...
- You're awake, Haru.
- Miku.
Where's Inaba?
Haru!
- Hi.
- Haru...
I thought you were gonna die!
My chest, my chest was pounding!
Right here.
Haru, feel it.
H-hey!
I've been wondering from before...
What's wrong with you? Get off him!
- No!
- Get off him!
= Death of an Insect =
Where did Dekao get transformed?
N-no. Not where did he get transformed...
Who transformed him?
Well, please look after this girl.
Please rest easy, father.
Yes, I've heard a lot about this school.
I'm not worried.
I'm honored.
Well then, I'll call the homeroom teacher.
- Take care of the rest.
- Yes, roger that.
I'm trusting you.
Leave it to me.
Oh, Koshka-kun, in there.
Y-yes!
Koshka-kun, this is the homeroom
teacher Yoshimura-sensei.
Nice to meet you!
Well then, shall we go to the classroom?
Yes.
* "Koshka" means "cat" in Russian
You're more precious to me than anyone.
Dare yori daiji ni omotte iru no ni
I can't say it well, so I disguise it with a smile again.
Jouzu ni iezu ni mata egao de gomakasu
The thing shaking in your eyes...
Anata no hitomi no naka de yureru
I don't understand it right now.
Ima watashi ga wakaranai
The more I like you, the more confused I become.
Suki ni naru hodo fuan ni naru
And even so, my heart wants to understand.
Kokoro dakedo wakaritai
I put the pieces of my feelings together
Omoi no kakera ima tsunaida
Gently with these hands.
Yasashii sono te kara
C1 Anime Credits
Translated by Futanari
Edited by Nameraka
Timed by egelteek
QCed by Collectr
Next Episode
For you who finished watching
the first episode...
Oh, you thought that Mimika
was the main character?
How silly. You're wrong.
The main character is m-e.
I'm the cute kitten, Koshka-chan.
If I get serious, I can kill that
stupid rabbit with one blow.
Just you wait, Mimika!