All my parents ever did was fight.
Let me go, I said!
Let me go!
- Shut up, bitch!
- Hands off!
After my mother got divorced,
she'd bring lots of men home,
and they pushed me
out of the way every day.
My mother would never listen to me.
To be a gangster, shoplifter and fighter...
they all called me a god of death.
Even so, he... he alone would...
Hey, Inaba! You're here today, too!
Why don't you give her a hug
sometimes, too? She's so cute!
I... I have to change myself.
There we go.
Matogi... kun.
I've always liked you, Haru!
Go out with me!
Was that too direct?
I can't say that either.
Hey, Miku. Don't let Inaba-san
take him from you no matter what!
I wish.
I have to change myself.
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
Inside of me, the power of fire sleeps.
Watashi no nake ni hi no chikara ga nemutteru
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
To make the dream come true once again.
Mou ichido yume wo kanaeru tame ni
Usagi-chan de Cue!!
The days when we laughed like fools.
Baka mitai ni waratta hibi wo
The memories where we cried till it hurt.
Itai kurai naita kioku wo
If they were all lies,
Zenbu itsuwari nara
My nature would be sad.
Watashi rashi sa ga kanashii ne
Since when have you
Aimai ni ne itsu kara
Remembered only how to give up?
Akirameru koto dake wo oboeta no
Get back. Just get.
Get back just get
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
"Something is different."
Nani ka ga chigau
When I have that feeling...
Sonna omoi ga aru no nara
Change my destiny!
Change my destiny
People give in all the time.
Itsu datte hito wa merikonde
Cha cha fantasy.
Cha cha fantasy
Like my heart...
Kono mune mitai na
With the future I've always looked for.
Zutto sagashiteta mirai to
Change my destiny.
Change my destiny
There is only one real me.
Hontou no watashi wa hitotsu mikakeru
You fool, your opponents are
incredibly tough.
Public Welfare Bureau
General Assembly of the
Public Welfare Bureau.
Well, I guess you haven't heard of it.
This remote self-governing area
is organized under the Bureau.
Strange things are happening
in this area...
that is, beings are merging.
You people are sick!
We can't predict what
merged beings will do.
Get rid of them!
It's not a good idea to do nothing
and cover up the problem.
- What should we do?
- Catch them and experiment on them.
Experiment on them properly.
And we should make this world
normal again... without them.
= Knowledge =
To follow up on this, they have made
an example of this district.
Banzai is to be a special district,
with no merged beings.
I wasn't to let it happen there.
They wouldn't let it happen here.
Until Mimika appeared.
Don't be so hasty.
I am a spy, a running dog of the
General Assembly!
But in reality, I am a dog!
Y-you're also a merged being?!
= Cool =
I can smell merged beings,
so I've been looking for them.
So, you're betraying your own kind?
= Sober? =
That was the only way
I could remain alive.
We are abandoned so easily.
= Embarrassed =
So, the huge guy that
looked like a robot...
Yeah. Dekao is an enforcement cyborg
sent by the Department...
an Admonisher.
- Then, Mimika, is...
- Umm.
Hey, why do merged beings happen?
= Explaining =
Merging happens when someone loses
their mind and their humanity.
They're lonely people.
They get more and more lonely,
and if they can't handle it,
they become a merged being.
Inaba...
I'm home.
Mimika! You came home ahead of me!
I... I have to... change myself.
Mimika!
I-Inaba?
I-is this strange?
N-no... that's...
Be honest with me.
C-cu...
-- you look odd.
Geez! Can't you say anything else?
Sleep with me!
Honestly, is she really Mimika or Inaba?
Why do merged beings happen?
They get more and more lonely,
and if they can't handle it...
Come to think of it, I've never seen
her play with friends.
Inaba...
We have captured all the merged beings
in our test district.
Yes, but something is not right
in the most important place of all.
It's because of Inaba Mikami.
We have received a report
from the Academy.
They found out that merged beings
can affect humans with telepathy.
We cannot lose this world because of
one little merged being.
Big Summer Thank You Sale!
Clothing And Goods 30-50% Off!
GAP Sale 60% Off!
Flower Shop Opens Until 10PM!
Hey, how's this?
A G-cup... that's huge!
Oh? What's wrong?
- Oh, but wouldn't that be okay?
- That's really cute!
But it might not be big enough...
Yeah, I guess so...
Why was I dragged all the way here?
I'm so embarrassed.
- Oh! Haru will fall head over heels for this!
- What did you say?
Hah! Because I like him! I like him!
Hold on! What do you mean?
Because we go to bed together!
S-sleep together?!
Now, come here Mimika.
Let's sleep together!
Oh, Haru! I'm so happy!
That small, tiny, fluffy, soft, cute tail.
It looks like it'll melt if I touch it.
And those cute, smooth, thin,
attractive, lovely long ears.
Those melting front teeth...
they're so passionate that they remind
me of the Caribbean Sea!
And on top of that, an ultra
super-dangerous body...
that makes me nosebleed and drool!
I'm so embarrassed!
Ah, you are the perfect person for
someone like me, who loves animals!
I'm so happy! Haru!
We're doing something like that!
And this!
And even this!
What have you two been doing?
Aren't you really a rabbit?
You're a rabbit, so Haru adores you.
Haru is worried about you
and keeps you at home.
I understand, so I'm on his side.
I also love animals as much as anyone,
so I've kept quiet...
but I'm envious of you because
you're always with him.
Miku-chan...
He's never thought of me as a girl,
but I've always thought of him as a boy,
and we were always together.
I know Haru much better than you do,
so I really love him.
- Miku-chan!
- Leave me alone!
I'm sorry.
Mimika-chan, I know you don't mean
to do any harm.
What are you doing?
Haru!
Hmm! Inaba Mikami! Now there's
nowhere for you to run!
We have completely
occupied this building!
- Who are you?
- Customers, we're just customers.
Mimika-chan...
You useless wretches!
Let's go!
Run away!
Hey, wait! You're not getting away!
That's good! We can get out
through there.
Hold it.
This time we'll finish our duel.
H-hey...
- Never mind that, just go!
- But...
I'll be fine.
More importantly, get Miku
out of here somehow.
Got it. I'll get Miku out of here, and then
I'll definitely come back to help you.
Thanks for that.
You finished?
Yeah. Sorry for the wait.
You won't get away!
Excuse me!
You're quite good!
Never underestimate a cat!
Miku, hurry up!
Hey now, where do you
think you're going?
Ah... Chou!
I knew it... you...
= Chou =
Eat this!
Why you!
- Amazing!
- They're monsters!
We're no match for them!
= Chou =
Chou... you...
Huh! I don't want you
to misunderstand.
They betrayed me, and this is
how I pay them back.
Thanks!
W-what are you saying?
- Get out of here!
- Yeah.
- Let's... stop now.
- What-nya?
Why do we have to fight?
We're both merged beings.
We're not the same!
We're not the same.
We're different.
You have Matogi and Miku.
I... I...
Your father's a murderer!
- That's despicable!
- A murderer!
I'm home.
Oh? Koshka. Where's Mom?
Mom...
You can't take it to the home with you.
No! I won't go without Koshha!
Koshha...
If I had strength, I wouldn't need
anyone to save me.
If I was strong, I wouldn't need
people to be kind to me.
It wouldn't be painful.
That's why you piss me off!
Koshka, it's bad!
- They tricked us!
- What?
That's ridiculous!
It's Abumidah! They intend to
get rid of all of us!
They're blaming this attack on us
and using it to destroy us!
There's no mistake!
We're useless to them now!
Koshka... you're also...
Hey! What happened?!
Are you all right?
Koshka!
Koshka, come here.
It's time to practice.
No! I want to play!
You want to be strong, don't you?
Come, Koshka!
Goodbye, Koshka.
Play as much as you like.
What the hell is this?!
Dekao again?!
Destroy
Inaba Mikami. Koshka. Destroy.
Koshka?
I didn't really trust them.
What are you doing,
you stupid rabbit?!
If you have the strength to talk,
stand up!
What?
= Fortune Family =
What just happened?
But now we can't go down any more.
We've got no choice. Let's go outside.
He's finally running out of ammo.
This is kind of like the last scene
in an old movie.
Huh?
Hey, can you move?
What? Who do you think
you're talking to?
Then we should go about now, partner.
What? Partner?
D-don't make me your partner by yourself!
W-what are they doing?
Inaba-san!
Damn it! I can't get even close to him!
No... even if you could get close to him,
you couldn't beat him with that pole.
Isn't... isn't there something...
That's... a high-voltage cable!
Shit! How should I fight him?!
Outta the way, stupid rabbit!
Eat this!
Koshka!
Miku!
Matogi!
He's...
It's the same as... that time...
Matogi...
Suzuki's Shop
If I said that I wanted something...
I would get scolded... get beaten...
I mustn't... wish for things...
Because I will be hated.
Don't wish for things!
I... I...
What are you scared of?
That if Haru has come to like Miku, you'll
become an unwanted child again?
Then, are you okay if they die?
What is most important to you now?
What is most precious?
Don't think that what you do
is meaningless!
Tomorrow... tomorrow will surely be fun!
I'll reach them!
It's okay to want things...
and to wish for them.
- Bye-bye!
- See ya!
Inaba-san didn't come to school
today after all.
Yeah.
The newspaper and TV said that
there were no dead or missing people.
I'm sure it'll be all right.
Matogi, I like you...
Inaba!
Where am I?
We were saved?
These are... Mimika's gloves.
Inaba!
Where have you gone?
It's dinnertime!
Come on home!
Am I a dog or something?
Well, it's okay now. Let's go.
Why do I need to look like this?
= Ha? =
= Preaching =
If you live as Inaba Mikami,
the Public Welfare Bureau...
and other institutions from all over the
country will come looking for you.
You are the best evidence for the
existence of merged beings in history.
But you know...
Anyway, you have to run away
as long as you live.
They will chase us for a long time.
Your true feelings...
I am another persona inside you.
All thoughts aren't just those
of a rabbit, but your own.
- I'll go back after all.
- H-hey, Inaba!
No matter who comes, I'll beat them!
= Unbelievable! =
No, that's not what I meant...
Hey, hey... huh.
You're more precious to me than anyone.
Dare yori daiji ni omotte iru no ni
= A Good Time to Depart =
It can't be helped.
We're the only ones who can go.
Hey!
I can't say it well, so I disguise it with a smile again.
Jouzu ni iezu ni mata egao de gomakasu
Inaba!
The thing shaking in your eyes...
Anata no hitomi no naka de yureru
I don't understand it right now.
Ima watashi ga wakaranai
The more I like you, the more confused I become.
Suki ni naru hodo fuan ni naru
But my heart understands.
Kokoro na no ni wakatteru
I can say everything that's on my mind.
Omoi no sumete tsutaenareru
Even things that can't be expressed in words.
Kotoba wa nai koto mo
Standing on a road that's hazy from the setting sun.
Yuuhi ni nijinda machi ni tatazumeba
Just makes me want to cry.
Chiisa na jibun ni tada nakitaku naru dake
My shivering love will reach you, right?
Furueru ai wa todoite iru no ne
You don't understand.
Anata ni wakaranai
The more I like you, the more confused I become.
Suki ni naru hodo fuan ni naru
And even so, my heart wants to understand.
Kokoro dakedo wakaritai
I put the pieces of my feelings together
Omoi no kakera ima tsunaida
Gently with these hands.
Yasashii sono te kara
C1 Anime Credits
Translated by Futanari
Edited by Nameraka
Timed by egelteek
QCed by Collectr
Creditless Ending