Who are you affiliated with?
She's a tough one.
l'll ask you just one more time. Where are the other agents hiding?
You bitch!
Talk!
Talk, damn it!
Tell us!
You're still not going to talk?
She's not going to talk from being tortured. Bring it.
Yes, Sir.
Do it.
Are you going to kill me?
We're not gonna do that.
lt'll be interesting to see the effects.
W-What are you doing?
Hey, are you sure she can take that much at once?
Who cares if one hostage goes crazy?
lt's hot...
W-What is this?
No... What did you do...?
lsn't this truth serum?
Let's see how well it's working down here.
N...No... Nooo!
Let's take a look...
No... Let's take a look...
No...
No!
Let's see...
Holy shit!
No!
Hey, let me have some... No!
Hey, let me have some...
Wait, l get first dibs.
l'm the one who started this.
lf you guys want something fresh, fight over who gets her ass first.
l can't wait anymore.
No... Stop... No...
What?
Talk louder or l can't hear you.
St... Stop... Stop! Stop!
l've been waiting to hear that!
lt hurts! lt hurts! No!
No! Pull out... Pull out! Please pull out!
Virgin pussy is always great!
No...
H-Hey! Stop tightening up!
Fuck me harder!
That's more like it...
Yes...
No... This... This is...
No... No... M... More!
l'm all wet inside!
She was awesome.
All right. l'm next.
Let me have some fun, okay?
H-Her ass isn't that bad either...
lt hurts...
Don't spill it, all right?
Yeah! Yeah!!
l can't anymore!
Her ass was great too.
That should be enough.
Looks like she fainted.
Let her down and take her to the infirmary!
Yes, Sir!
We'll resume when she wakes up.
Your death is my pleasure...
The most powerful strength in the world...
...is...
...the instinct to fight, fueled by hatred!
hohoemu namida michibiku kaze wa
Tears with a smile, the guiding wind.
yasashii nioi nareta nukumori
A gentle scent, your warmth seems so familiar.
ima kagiri aru sekai to
ln such a limited world,
kuusai no hate ni
beyond the skies.
kanjyou tabane hitomi wa
Your eyes are full of emotion,
nani o mitsukeru darou
what will they find?
mienai hoshi kokoro nokoshi
A star l can't see, leaving my heart behind,i
saten no sora e to
to the satin skies.
kikoenu you ni mienu you ni
Be sure they can't hear, be sure they can't see,
chiisaku hakisuteta
say it softly.
ima naraba mabayui kako utte
Right now you can shoot your bright past.
yuganda sora mo tsumetai yoru mo
Twisted mornings, cold nights,
genseki ni kaeru
turn them into gemstones.
utsuro na namida yurusareru nara
Tears with an empty look, if it can be forgiven.
kono mama zutto mamoraretetai
l want to stay like this, l want you to protect me.
ima hosoi hari ga hitotsu
Just now a thin needle...
toki oikoshiteku
...pierced through time
yagate bokura no ue ni mo
Dawn will come soon,
asahi wa noboru darou
even for us.
Hold on. l swear l'll win, brother...
Brother!
Your brother attacked me first.
l just came to get back what l lent him.
l'll be back next week.
You'll get all your money in two months!
Really? You can get it?
l swear l'll have it.
l swear...
Waaaaait!
Please!! Wait up!
You shouldn't be running here, it's dangerous!
B... But... My bag is on the seat next to yours!
l'm so sorry.
l'm Ayumi Okamoto. Nice to meet you.
l'm Yuu Asuka. Nice to meet you too.
l wouldn't have guessed you'd be participating in VG too.
l never would have thought you were a contestant either!
Let's fight honorably, and get to know each other better!
Huh? l wonder what's with all the commotion?
One.
Two.
Three!
Sh... She's coming this way!
No way!
Phew, now l'll make it to VG!
l'm Yung Ching Jyu! Call me Tama-chan!
O... Okay...
This is VG, the Family Chain Restaurant Warrior Waitress...
...Martial Arts Competition. The Venus Games!
This is the last round of participant match ups!
Now entering is the final contestant!
Sanari.
Yuu.
Now, the final matches have been decided.
The first VG match will be Yuu Asuka from M x Y x Home versus...
...Sanari Misumi from Koudaya who looks completely pumped and ready to go!
l'm not gonna lose this time!
Yuu Asuka's M x Y x Home isn't a member of the JFR, but...
...she will be participating as a specially endorsed contender.
The second match will be Ayumi Okamoto from Ekibasha...
...versus Diane Ryan from Rock'n Cafe!
Good job, big chief!
The third match will be Kei Sagara from Petit Panini...
...versus Anna Fairgold from Propaganda!
The fourth and final match will be Yung Ching Jyu from May Dream!
Hi! Nice to meet you all!
Her opponent still hasn't arrived!
That's so unfair!
Everyone, please give a big hand to the glorious VG contenders!
Yuu, we're round one again! Let's have a good fight!
Please, you have to leave!
You shouldn't be in this competition!
Trying to chase me away isn't fair, Yuu.
l'm not going to lose this time!
This isn't the honorable competition that you think it is!
Yuu, this competition is... VG... or Variable Geo.
Variable Geo?
Variable Geo is...
lt's the most passionate, most beautiful...
...and the most perverse battle in the world.
The winner gets all and the losers lose everything.
lt's the most pure and yet the most profane battle of its kind...
What do you mean?
l'm talking about the penalty the loser must endure.
lt robs a woman of all her dignity and virtue...
You don't mean...!
You must not enter!
Yuu, you're too innocent to enter that competition.
But if l win the competition, l'll win ten million yen.
And with that money...
But if you lose...
lf l lose...
You'll lose everything. lt might even break your soul...
l came knowing what the consequences were,
but Sanari doesn't know anything.
l can't let her be subjected to that...
Maybe l should lose...
lf l get the penalty, they'll leave her alone...
But if l don't win, my brother... and the store will be...
l'm sorry to bother you so late, Miss Asuka.
l'm Takigawa, the commentator for tomorrow's match.
l'd like to request an interview with you if possible.
l guess that's a no.
Well, l have something from Miss Misumi.
l'll just leave it here.
Keep your chin up, Yuu.
Make sure you eat before the match, okay?
Sanari...
Rice balls?
lf l don't lose, she will.
She really doesn't get it, does she...?
lt's too salty... but it's really good, Sanari.
l came here to win. l came here to fight!
Thank you for waiting!
The first round of the Venus Games is about to begin!
First, in the blue corner is Sanari Misumi from Koudaya!
Next, in the red corner is Yuu Asuka from M x Y x Home!
l came here to win. l came here to fight!
Even if my opponent is Sanari... No...
...because my opponent is Sanari, l have to fight with all my might!
Yuu Asuka...
Misumi versus Asuka!
They're best friends, but who will be victorious?
l'm not holding back!
l'm not going to lose this time!
S-Such incredible offense and defense at unbelievable speeds!
What is the story behind these two?!
Why you...!!
They're completely even!
No, it looks like Asuka has a slight advantage?
Yuu! Attack! l'm not going to hold back!
Here l come!
This match is mine!
A no motion Kikoudan to the right... She's got it.
T-This is...!?
She did it! Yuu Asuka is the winner!
Sanari Misumi has been defeated in Round 1 !
Sanari!
Sanari, wake up!
Sanari, you have to run!
Hurry... You have to get out of here or else...
S... Stay away! Stay away from her!
What's going on? Get away from Miss Misumi!
This is a disgrace to martial arts!
Shut up.
Let her go! Let her go!
Get away from her! Sanari!
Sa...nari... run...
Yuu...
What?
That's right... l lost...
Run, Sanari!
H...Hey! What are you doing! Stop!
That's gross! That's gross!
Damn it! Let me go! Let me go!
l can't move!
S... Sanari...
Stop fighting back, will ya?
No! What do you think you're doing? Let me go! Let me go!
Something really good.
No! No!
No... Stop!
Yeah! Do it!
What's happening? Stop looking... Everyone stop looking at me!
No... No... Sanari... No...
W... Why? Why is this...
Yuu, why is this happening?!
Sanari...
W...What? What are you planning to do next?
N...No. Stop it! Stop! No! No! l don't want this!
Please! Please stop! No! Let me go... Let me go! lt's gross!
lt hurts! lt hurts! lt hurts...
Let me go! Let me go!
No! Stop... Stop looking down there!
N...Nooo! Don't take that off!
Let me go! Let me go! No! No!
l said, no!
You pervert! l said stop!!
No... No... No... Stop!
Nooo!
S... Stop... l'm telling you... this is gross...
lt's about that time.
Yeah.
No! What are you going to do to her?
Don't... Don't...
This is... A joke, right? l... l'm still a...
Please!!
No! No! Stop! Have mercy!
l'll take her place!
l'll take her place so... Let Sanari go!
Rape me instead!
Yuu knew this would happen to the loser?
She knew and that's why she told me to go home...
She's too much...
Sanari... Sanari...
No! Stop!
lt hurts...
lt hurts...!
lt really hurts...!
l want Yuu... to stay pure, so...
That's too... hard...!
Stop it...! Let her go...!
Sanari... Sanari... l'm sorry... l'm so sorry...
l'm okay... lt means... nothing to me...
lt hurts...
lt's my fault...
Why is this happening to Sanari...?
See... it's starting to feel good...
Yes... lt feels good...
So... D... Don't worry... about me... Yuu...
S... Sanari?
lt feels good... No... Don't look at me...
Nooo!
Yes... lt feels so good...
l... l'm going to...!
lt... lt's hot... lt hurts... l... l'm going to cum...
Nooo!
lt's almost time. The cruiser will be arriving shortly.
Please look at this.
This is...?
Please take a good look at the girl.
She's my little sister.
Doesn't she look like someone? Like you.
W-Who is she?
Yuu Asuka.
She was born from an embryo injected with another woman's nucleus.
lt can't be...
She's definitely my sister, but she's also your clone, Yuka Takeuchi.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
What's with that outfit?
Come on! lt's my competition outfit, of course!
lt makes you look even younger!
People always tell me that l haven't changed a bit.
Let's get going.
Okay.
l'm going to fight and l swear l'll save both of them!
The contestants of the second match of Round 2 are...!
The hot-blooded blonde American, representing Rock'n Cafe, Diane Ryan!
This will be the first time Diane has entered the ring in Japan!
Yeah!
And her opponent! She's synonymous with Ekibasha...
...she's just a beginner, but she's a martial arts genius! Ayumi Okamoto!
Time to battle!
hohoemu namida michibiku kaze wa
Tears with a smile, the guiding wind.
yasashii nioi nareta nukumori
A gentle scent, your warmth seems so familiar.
ima kagiri aru sekai to
ln such a limited world,
kuusai no hate ni
beyond the skies.
kanjyou tabane hitomi wa
Your eyes are full of emotion,
nani o mitsukeru darou
what will they find?
mienai hoshi kokoro nokoshi
A star l can't see, leaving my heart behind,
saten no sora e to
to the satin skies.
kikoenu you ni mienu you ni
Be sure they can't hear, be sure they can't see,
chiisaku hakisuteta
say it softly.
ima naraba mabayui kako utte
Right now you can shoot your bright past.
yuganda soramo tsumetai yorumo
Twisted mornings, cold nights,
genseki ni kaeru
turn them into gemstones.
utsuro na namida yurusareru nara
Tears with an empty look, if it can be forgiven.
kono mama zutto mamoraretetai
l want to stay like this, l want you to protect me.
ima hosoi hari ga hitotsu
Just now a thin needle...
toki oikoshiteku
...pierced through time
yagate bokura no ue ni mo
Dawn will come soon,
asahi wa noboru darou
even for us.