Venus Games, round one, second match is Ryan versus Okamoto!
Their offense and defense are completely even!
lt's still too difficult to predict the outcome of this match!
She's fast.
lf it keeps going like this, l'll definitely lose.
l have to do it...
Here l come!
Ayumi!
We have a winner!
The last one standing is Ayumi Okamoto!
Diane Ryan has lost!
Ayumi, good job!
Tama!
Take care of Ayumi.
l don't want you guys to see it.
See you later! lf we're lucky, we'll fight again!
Where are you going?
l have no plans to hang around for your sick show.
My job is done.
hohoemu namida michibiku kaze wa
Tears with a smile, the guiding wind.
yasashii nioi nareta nukumori
A gentle scent, your warmth seems so familiar.
ima kagiri aru sekai to
ln such a limited world,
kuusai no hate ni
beyond the skies.
kanjyou tabane hitomi wa
Your eyes are full of emotion,
nani o mitsukeru darou
what will they find?
mienai hoshi kokoro nokoshi
A star l can't see, leaving my heart behind,
saten no sora e to
to the satin skies.
kikoenu you ni mienu you ni
Be sure they can't hear, be sure they can't see,
chiisaku hakisuteta
say it softly.
ima naraba mabayui kako utte
Right now you can shoot your bright past.
yuganda sora mo tsumetai yoru mo
Twisted mornings, cold nights,
genseki ni kaeru
turn them into gemstones.
utsuro na namida yurusareru nara
Tears with an empty look, if it can be forgiven.
kono mama zutto mamoraretetai
l want to stay like this, l want you to protect me.
ima hosoi hari ga hitotsu
Just now a thin needle...
toki oikoshiteku
...pierced through time
yagate bokura no ue ni mo
Dawn will come soon,
asahi wa noboru darou
even for us.
This is the part we've been waiting for.
You only brought this many to fuck me?
Come, let's try to make this fun.
lf you want to fuck me, just try it,
but be prepared to lose an arm!
What?!
L... Let me go! Let me go!
Damn it!
Be a little more gentle.
How do you expect to satisfy a woman like that?
No...
Noooo!
Be more gentle...
lt... lt hurts...
N-No...
Apparently the eighth contestant has finally arrived.
Misty from Hanna Miller's, right?
Yeah, that's her ring name.
Hey.
What do you want?
Leave me alone!
Your opponent for the semi-finals match has been set.
lt's Ayumi...
She completely overpowered Diane.
This is a DVD of the match.
l don't want to see it.
Don't worry. lt's only up to where she won.
l guess it's okay if you want to sulk like that. lt's up to you, but...
...at this rate, you'll definitely lose the semi-finals.
lf you lose, Sanari's sacrifice will have been in...
l'm sorry.
l have to go fight Anna now.
l plan to do everything in my power to win...
...but, if l lose...
Please watch the video.
l made it specifically for you.
The Venus Games! This is the third match of round one!
From the red corner, Anna Fairgold from Propaganda!
Anna! Anna!
From the blue corner, Kei Sagara from Petit Panini!
Kei!
This is going to be interesting.
l hope so, too.
Please watch the video.
l made it specifically for you.
She made it for me?
Why would Kei do that?
That's no ordinary technique.
That goes for the both of us.
Okamoto! Such incredible speed! lt's absolutely divine!
The last one standing is Ayumi Okamoto!
Diane Ryan has lost!
What kind of strategy should l use?
Either way, l need to catch her.
l'll watch it from the beginning again.
Yuu, are you watching?
Kei!
l wonder when you'll see this?
Before or after the match?
Am l there with you?
At this point, l have no idea how my match against Anna will go...
...but, if l lose... Yuu, you're the only one who can stop her.
Me?
You have incredible power and potential within you.
The one who called you here believes that.
That's why you're fighting.
The battle isn't for you or Anna.
lt's all for his selfish desires.
Anna will probably defeat me...
...and l doubt l'll be spared...
Yuu, please! Defeat Anna Fairgold!
She's turning into a monster...
Please stop her path of destruction.
l believe in you.
Goodbye, Kei.
Kei!
But, if l lose...
The victor is Anna Fairgold!
Kei Sagara is unconscious!
...l'm leaving the rest in your hands, Yuu.
Let's go. The match is over.
The penalty is about to begin.
l've been waiting for this!
Hey.
Nooo!
No! No!
No! No! No! No!
No!
Let me go!
No, don't...
W... What are you...?
Nooo!
So they throw you in a cell if you lose, huh?
Figures, since it's an illegal competition...
l wonder how the matches are going?
l bet Yuu's next opponent has already been decided.
Can you hear me, Sanari?
Rita?
You idiot! l told you not to come!
Rita, what's happening in the competition?
Who is Yuu's next opponent? Tell me!
Who is it?
lt's me.
ls something wrong, Masaki?
Did you know... that Anna Fairgold is Yuu's twin...?
Just like Yuu, she's also your clone...
Masaki, right? Nice to meet you.
How do you know who l am?
l wonder?
What are you planning to do with me?
Do with you?
l'm not on the guest list. Are you going to arrest me?
Or are you going to torture me to make me confess, and then kill me?
You're rather attractive.
lt might be fun to tear you apart in front of Yuu.
But l'm not going to kill you or turn you in.
lf something were to happen to you, Yuu would be heavily distressed.
l thought you wanted to beat her?
lt's not about wanting to win. l will win!
l especially want to beat Yuu when she's desperate to win.
Plus, l already know your story,
so there's really no point in torturing you.
What?
You teamed up with the Original, right?
To save Yuu...
You guys share a mutual interest so working together makes sense.
The Original?
That's what we call her. Yuka Takeuchi, also known as Misty.
Anna... Who are...?
Could it be...!?
You figured it out...
Nice to meet you, brother.
So you knew... Why didn't you tell me?
No big reason really.
Of course there is!
At this rate, you'll be fighting our little sisters!
But that's why l came.
So we can all be happy.
We can all...?
They're your little sisters, but they're also my little sisters...
...and while they're fighting right now, l'm going to make them into a family.
ln order to do that...
Round one, fourth match!
From the red corner, representing May Dream!
Yung Ching Jyu!
From the blue corner, representing Hanna Miller's!
Misty!
Misty! Misty!
l'm leaving the rest in your hands, Yuu.
Oh no!
She did it! The mysterious Misty is moving on to the semi-finals!
Can you really? You?
l swear l'll have it.
Winning is hard, but l can't lose.
l don't want to lose. l will...
...win!
hohoemu namida michibiku kaze wa
Tears with a smile, the guiding wind.
yasashii nioi nareta nukumori
A gentle scent, your warmth seems so familiar.
ima kagiri aru sekai to
ln such a limited world,
kuusai no hate ni
beyond the skies.
kanjyou tabane hitomi wa
Your eyes are full of emotion,
nani o mitsukeru darou
what will they find?
mienai hoshi kokoro nokoshi
A star l can't see, leaving my heart behind,
saten no sora e to
to the satin skies.
kikoenu you ni mienu you ni
Be sure they can't hear, be sure they can't see,
chiisaku hakisuteta
say it softly.
ima naraba mabayui kako utte
Right now you can shoot your bright past.
yuganda sora mo tsumetai yoru mo
Twisted mornings, cold nights,
genseki ni kaeru
turn them into gemstones.
utsuro na namida yurusareru nara
Tears with an empty look, if it can be forgiven.
kono mama zutto mamoraretetai
l want to stay like this, l want you to protect me.
ima hosoi hari ga hitotsu
Just now a thin needle...
toki oikoshiteku
...pierced through time
yagate bokura no ue ni mo
Dawn will come soon,
asahi wa noboru darou
even for us.