l am Rita.
My ring name is Diane Ryan, an agent of VGN.
l was sent to expose Fairgold's illegal actions.
l infiltrated the luxury cruiser where the Venus Games were taking place.
Yuu Asuka.
Anna Fairgold.
Misty, also known as Yuka Takeuchi.
Sanari Misumi.
Yung Ching Jyu.
Ayumi Okamoto.
Kei Sagara.
l entered the games with these contestants.
Fairgold's secret plan... the ''Alchemist's Plan''... was to create...
...a perfect Material, or pure Material.
Material is a term describing a powerful human weapon.
They are dangerous beings that could alter the world's military balance.
And the loathsome conspiracy that robs a human of their dignity...
The real truth behind the Venus Games being held on the luxury cruiser...
lt's no ordinary martial arts competition...
lt's a place to showcase the abilities of the Materials...
...to the arms buyers from various countries.
The one at the heart of this conspiracy is Dr. Garret,
also known as The Professor.
The Professor is a mad scientist and his only goal is to prove his theory correct.
He thinks nothing of illegal cloning or inhumane experiments.
The fruits of his Material experiments are Yuu and Anna.
They are The Professor's perfect Materials...
...and that is the reason they continue to win in VG.
They are the most powerful warriors on earth.
Two clones produced from Yuka's biological information.
Meaning, Yuu and Anna are fraternal twins.
Now, not knowing this, they are about to fight.
Their surrogate mother and her biological son are currently listed as missing.
Even the son seems like he was part of The Professor's other experiment,
the M-series.
There are accounts that there are others...
...who look exactly like him and they could only be his clones.
What we don't know is whether he is under The Professor's control.
This is currently under investigation.
The last of the Venus Games matches is swiftly approaching.
Yuu and Anna... l must do something before their match begins!
Winning is painful, but l can't lose.
l don't want to lose. l will...
...win!
hohoemu namida michibiku kaze wa
Tears with a smile, the guiding wind.
yasashii nioi nareta nukumori
A gentle scent, your warmth seems so familiar.
ima kagiri aru sekai to
ln such a limited world,
kuusai no hate ni
beyond the skies.
kanjyou tabane hitomi wa
Your eyes are full of emotion,
nani o mitsukeru darou
what will they find?
mienai hoshi kokoro nokoshi
A star l can't see, leaving my heart behind,
saten no sora e to
to the satin skies.
kikoenu you ni mienu you ni
Be sure they can't hear, be sure they can't see,
chiisaku hakisuteta
say it softly.
ima naraba mabayui kako utte
Right now you can shoot your bright past.
yuganda sora mo tsumetai yoru mo
Twisted mornings, cold nights,
genseki ni kaeru
turn them into gemstones.
utsuro na namida yurusareru nara
Tears with an empty look, if it can be forgiven.
kono mama zutto mamoraretetai
l want to stay like this, l want you to protect me.
ima hosoi hari ga hitotsu
Just now a thin needle...
toki oikoshiteku
...pierced through time
yagate bokura no ue ni mo
Dawn will come soon,
asahi wa noboru darou
even for us.
She did it!
Misty, the mysterious fighter is moving on to the semi-finals!
She's gone... She spared me the humiliation... Thank you.
Are you the one?
Don't you like me?
Y-You're much better looking than l expected.
Thank you.
lt's a penalty so...
...the audience won't be satisfied if we don't do something like this. l'm sorry.
You're going to make me feel good without using your hands.
Also without these...
Wait...
lt's okay. Open up to me...
Open up your body...
You're going to do everything to satisfy me.
Yes...
Good girl... Make me feel good.
Bring your mouth a little forward...
Yes, right there...
Yes, that's good Miss Ching Jyu...
Roll it around inside your mouth...
More... Let it go deeper into your throat.
Make sure you use your tongue.
That's very good, Miss Ching Jyu...
More... More...
Don't spit it out.
Stand up, Miss Ching Jyu.
Come on, stand up!
Yes.
l'm going to lie down and l want you to straddle me.
l want you to spread your legs wide so the audience can see.
N... No, l don't want them to see.
Drop down.
No... lt's warm... lt... lt feels so strange...
Shake your ass.
But...
l said, shake your ass!
Y-Yes...
Move faster!
No! l don't want this! Please! Stop!
No... Stop...
lt hurts!
lt really hurts!
Hurry up and make me feel good.
l... l can't... l can't... Th... This is...
What are we going to do with you, Miss Ching Jyu?
Does it feel that good?
No, that's not...
Not... Not right there...
No...
l'm going to cum! l'm going to cum!
Hey! Let me out!
Just let me see Yuu's match!
Damn it... bastards!
The four goddesses that won the first round will now descend!
Two more matches until one is crowned the most powerful!
Yuu...
Let's fight honorably... and become friends.
Let's fight honorably... and get to know each other more!
Okay!
l... l'm in pain!
My head... My head hurts!
Hey, what's wrong?
M... My head... Hurry... Get a doctor...
lt's an emergency! We need backup!
Hey, get a hold of...
There's no way she'll get up with that.
Asuka is down! ls she done for?
ls this as far as l go?
Brother... Kei... l'm sorry.
l'm sorry for what happened, Sa...
What are you doing? That's so lame!
Sanari?
l'm the only one that's allowed to beat you!
Did you already forget that?
T... That's right... That's right.
l can't lose now.
This is the end!
Asuka won! What a comeback!
Come with me!
S-Silvermine?!
Rita!
Hey! Hey! Hey! What's happening?
What was that? What's going on?
What about the show!?
There has been a change in the competition schedule.
Please relax until the next match.
What's going on? Hey!
After them! Don't let them get away!
lt's really rowdy.
l can't get any sleep with this.
Quiet!
Misty?
Can you hide her here for awhile?
l see. Now l know the reason behind the commotion.
Okay. l'll take care of Ayumi.
Sorry for the trouble.
l see... Ayumi lost... l see...
Ayumi's so soft.
T-Tama?
Tama?!
T-Tama, that's...
No... N... No...
lt... lt feels so good...
lt's okay, Ayumi.
l'll make you feel really good.
You're so cute, Ayumi.
Ayumi, l want you to make me feel good too.
What am l supposed to do to make you feel good?
l'll do anything for you, so...
l'm sorry, Tama...
l couldn't save you.
Ayumi...
You're hurt down here. l'm really sorry.
Ayumi, it's okay.
l'll be fine because you're going to take care of me...
T-Tama!
l... don't know if l'll be able to do it, but...
...if l can help you even just a little bit...
That's... that's wonderful... Ayumi!
Yes! Yes, it feels so good! Ayumi is healing me...
Ayumi... Ayumi...
l'll make you feel much better...
Forget everything. Just think of me...
l'm going to cum!
Ayumi... Ayumi!
Yes...
Ayumi...
Tama... Tama...
Tama, l'm going to... l can't anymore...!
Together... Ayumi... Let's cum together...
l can't anymore... l can't anymore...
Ayumi... l'm going to cum...
l'm going to cum... l can't anymore...
Together... Together...!
Let's cum together...
Ayumi, grab your shoes.
Lets get out of here!
Tama, wait for me!
Why don't you take off your shades?
l already know who you are, Original.
Original?
Don't call me ''Original.''
l'm Yuka. Yuka Takeuchi!
Yuka Takeuchi. Champion of the fourth Variable Geo.
She's from Hanna Miller's, Chikushi store.
You knew?
She wasn't trying to hide it.
Misty... Miss T... Miss Takeuchi...
My first Material candidate.
Yuka Takeuchi... The legendary fighter from the Kyokushin Federation....
Rita! Who are you really?
l'm an agent from VGN.
l'm investigating Fairgold's experiments, project code ''Alchemists''.
Your DNA was useless because it was full of impurities.
ln order to get rid of the impurities, the experiments continued...
...to create human samples. The latest model is...
Stop calling yourself that!
You don't have to forgive me or our father...
...all l want is for you to be happy!
Thank you, Yuka.
My... flawed Original!
lt's ready. Download as much data as possible.
What the...?
Rita, get out of there! They've got us!
lt's a trap! lt's going to blow!
l will defeat you and Yuu to become the Material that takes over the world!
The only one standing on the ring is Misty!
l won't let anything scare you or make you sad so...
Yuka! Wait!
Misty is down!
She's completely unconscious!
lt's... Anna's victory!
Yuka!
What's happening?
Run!
Anna, give me a hand!
Yuu, fight me!
Now's not the time!
Yuu, when we were born,
we were destined for one of us to defeat the other.
That's why...
...we have to settle this now!
That explosion was near the ship's storage area!
You need to hurry and get out!
Yuu!
Takigawa, please take care of Yuka.
Here l come!
Die!
Wait...
l want to see this match with my own eyes...
Same goes for you, right?
Goodbye, sis!
Sis?
Maybe you're the younger sister.
We're fraternal twins.
The goddess with white wings, Yuu Asuka versus...
...the goddess with black wings, Anna Fairgold!
Venus Games, final round!
The match is about to begin, twenty-two hours early!
Professor!
Just a little more... l'll know the result of my research...
lt's dangerous here! Please get out!
Come, Professor.
Masaki...
Farewell Professor... And thank you... For letting me meet Yuu.
But l won't let you have your way with her anymore.
lt's over Yuu. Your left arm is useless now.
Even if it is, l'm not giving up.
l'm going home with you!
Then l'll use all my powers...
l'll destroy you!
l got you.
This can't be!
This will be the final strike.
l'll give back the powers you gave me.
lt's decided... lt's decided!!
The new Venus Games Champion is Yuu Asuka!
Come on, Anna. Let's go home.
We're saved.
Anna...
The ten million yen VG prize was paid by the JFR Chairman...
...and our damaged store was back to normal.
For some reason, my brother who should be celebrating with me was missing.
Newly renovated! Opening tomorrow!
lt's been over two weeks, but he hasn't come home.
But l remember...
Brother...
l can't believe it...
Brother!
l was worried about you.
l was really, really worried about you!
Yuu...
Brother...
Brother!
Y... Yuu...
Yuu...
Brother...
Congratulations!
Grand opening!
Long time no see!
We came to help!
Hey!
Guys...
Does this go here?
Over there! Over there!
Are you sure?
lt's not over yet.
lt's not over until l destroy the remaining Alchemists...
...and put an end to everything...
Also, until l can tell Yuu that she has nothing to worry about and to just be happy...
Are you going to pick Yuu or Yuka when it's all over and you can go home?
Let's go, Anna!
Yes, brother.
Come back whenever you want.
This is M x Y x home. This is our home.
Hey, wait!
Brother...
hohoemu namida michibiku kaze wa
Tears with a smile, the guiding wind.
yasashii nioi nareta nukumori
A gentle scent, your warmth seems so familiar.
ima kagiri aru sekai to
ln such a limited world,
kuusai no hate ni
beyond the skies.
kanjyou tabane hitomi wa
Your eyes are full of emotion,
nani o mitsukeru darou
what will they find?
mienai hoshi kokoro nokoshi
A star l can't see, leaving my heart behind,
saten no sora e to
to the satin skies.
kikoenu you ni mienu you ni
Be sure they can't hear, be sure they can't see,
chiisaku hakisuteta
say it softly.
ima naraba mabayui kako utte
Right now you can shoot your bright past.
yuganda sora mo tsumetai yoru mo
Twisted mornings, cold nights,
genseki ni kaeru
turn them into gemstones.
utsuro na namida yurusareru nara
Tears with an empty look, if it can be forgiven.
kono mama zutto mamoraretetai
l want to stay like this, l want you to protect me.
ima hosoi hari ga hitotsu
Just now a thin needle...
toki oikoshiteku
...pierced through time
yagate bokura no ue ni mo
Dawn will come soon,
asahi wa noboru darou
even for us.