For demons to be in this place...
I'm sure it's because of Youki.
Even so, my body feels light.
Was what he said before true?
No...
He did such a thing to me...
I thought that he's a good man after he saved me.
He's nothing but a mere demon in the end!
I was a fool to believe him for even a second.
A lightning strike?
Were you trying to save me, by any chance?
You didn't need to intervene.
I can manage myself without you
against enemies of this level.
But still, thank you.
So, you're here.
What does a man who tricked me,
had me get attacked by that monster,
and forced me to give birth to
a demon child, want with me?
Wait, wait. Just like I told you before,
the "Egg-laying Method" treatment is a vital
step to gain immunity to the blood moon.
Your body's condition has actually improved, right?
That's...
And another thing, that is a guardian.
It's appearance quite resembles
a demon's, but don't get mistaken.
A guardian?
Its growth is remarkably fast.
It gets quite attached, follows orders,
and has a magnificent form.
I now understand that this little one who
protected me is different from the usual demons.
I'll believe you on that at least.
I'm glad that you're broad-minded.
My condition certainly got better,
and you obtained mana for yourself.
In short, we can say that our deal
has already been fulfilled, right?
Yes. Well, you're right about that.
I'll be on my way, then.
H-Hey...
You... You seem to be alright now.
Uhh... Yes...
Thank you for coming to my rescue.
Don't worry about it.
Umm, your name is...
Akris.
I'm Akris Menor.
I'm Leona... Leona Amaral.
I'm Hain Volgal.
You two seem to be fighting against the demons.
Well, I do. He doesn't have any part in this.
Will you let me join you in battle?
Huh?
As a priestess serving under the goddess Yuran-sama,
I'm capable of using restoration spells.
I surely will be of use for you!
That sounds good, I'll join in as well.
Huh? What are you saying...
I changed my mind. I'll accompany you on
your quest to subjugate the demon king.
What do you think? Aren't you glad?
H-Huh? Just wait for a second!
Why are you deciding things by yourself?
Then, what is it? Are you planning
to keep fighting alone?
You would've been in a dire situation
last time without me and Sheila, though.
Th-That's...
I'm begging you!
I understand. Let's fight together from now on.
I'm glad to be with you.
Episode 2: The Innocent Girl is Embraced by a Sea of Tentacles
Umm, what's the important
matter you told me about?
I'll get right to the point and ask you, then.
Do you think that we'll defeat the demon king's army with our current power?
Th-That's...
It might be difficult with our current state,
but if we'll bolster our force and get stronger...
Correct. We have to get stronger,
and as soon as possible.
I'll need your cooperation for that to happen.
Of course, I will! As someone bestowed by Yuran-sama's divine virtues,
let me help if there's anything that I can do!
Alright, then... I'll have you
cooperate with me immediately.
H-Hain-san, what are these?
They're tentacles just as you can see.
Mr. Tentacles?
They're my loyal servants,
a product of magical arts.
Th-Then, they're not enemies, right?
Of course, they do what I say
and I can order them around.
Just like this...
N-No, don't come any closer!
Aren't they cute?
I'm sorry, they're not cute at all!
Well, you'll get used to them soon.
Alright, then. Let's get it started.
What do you mean?
N-No, let go of me!
Hain-san, what are you going to do?
Isn't that obvious when a man
and woman are together?
No... It feels gross!
Hain-san, please stop!
This doesn't have anything
to do with fighting demons!
This is of great relevance in
that regard. I'll explain later.
Please explain it to me first!
No... S-Stop...
Please don't touch me.
Not there... N-No!
No... Y-You can't do that... That's...
I see... So, it feels good at this spot.
Y-You're wrong, that was...
No... No...
What's happening? My voice is coming out on its own!
No—!
Th-That's my... Not down there.
I-I'm begging you, Mr. Tentacles... No!
Stop that, please!
H-Hain-san, I don't want this—!
N-No... Stop, this is embarrassing...
N-No! Don't touch me down there!
No... Hain-san, this has to be some sort of joke.
Please let me off already!
Not after going this far. Brace yourself.
That's too much for me!
No! I-It went inside!
It hurts—!
Relax your body or it would hurt otherwise.
Wait... It still hurts, after all!
My body won't relax at all!
It can't be helped, then... Master?
Okay.
N-No... H-Huh?
My body is getting hotter for some reason...
The tentacles' secretion is an aphrodisiac,
No...
so it should make you feel better.
Aphrodisiac?
I'm feeling light-headed... It's a strange sensation...
No! I-I'm not yet prepared to get it so rough!
Master...
Yeah, that's right. You did a good job as well.
Master!
It feels hot! It feels good!
Isn't this enough? Please hurry up
and pull this thing out of me!
What are you talking about?
Aren't you two only getting started?
Didn't you start to feel good
from the tentacles' secretion?
The pain has already subsided, but...
B-But it's not like I'm feeling good...
You can't! Not both of my holes at once...
They're so thick, this is incredible!
It feels so hot! I'm going to melt down!
Don't stir my insides into a sloppy mess!
It's getting hotter behind my cervix!
My body is acting weird!
I'm melting down, master...
This feels too good, I'm melting down!
So deep! They're ravaging inside,
they'll wreck my insides!
I'm going crazy!
Master, you'll end up breaking me...
You really will!
Hain-san, you're a brute! You're a demon!
So you want it deep, Akris?
Y-You're wrong... No...
Don't keep hitting that same spot—!
You're shaking your hips even
in such a situation, Sheila.
You truly are the ultimate woman!
S-So intense...
You'll break my body!
I'm going to wrap this up.
Will that be alright, Sheila?
This is incredible... Incredible, incredible!
I'm breaking... I'm gonna break from
too much pleasure and happiness!
I-Is this semen?
...where babies come from?
N-No way...
I got violated
and even had semen poured inside me...
This is too much!
Sorry to interrupt your weeping,
but the main event is about to start.
Huh?
It's not over yet?
Sheila-san?
Your belly...
My belly feels strange.
S-Something's moving inside!
What's happening here?
My belly is shaking...
C-Could it be that I already have Hain-san's baby?
That's not it.
Your guardian egg is developing.
Guardian egg?
I don't understand any of these.
Master, it feels so cramped inside me.
Please pull it out as soon as possible!
No, bear with it longer.
Even if you tell me that, I'll really end up
bursting if this goes on...
It's excruciating.
It feels like my belly is gonna burst.
I'll tell something good to both of you.
If you manage to hold it in as long as you can,
the pleasure will shoot up at the
moment you lay your egg.
N-No way...
That's not the issue...
It's about time for you two to give birth.
It feels good!
Whenever it moves, it pulls my insides with it...
This feels amazing!
I'm giving birth... I'm gonna give birth...
I will... To an egg...
I'm going crazy!
I can't think of anything else anymore!
I now understand the reason,
but suddenly doing such a thing to me is...
If this is necessary, then it can't be helped...
But couldn't you have at
least been gentler on me?
I thought that you were ready
for this much, though.
In any case, I'll have you help me
as long as we're together.
My master is a brute, after all.
That was quite a show there.
However, your roles end here right now.
The show of Youki-sama,
at your service, is about to start!
All of you, are you alright there?
It's been a while, seemingly self-proclaimed heroine.
I went out of my way just to meet you!
Ouch! It hurts!
Stop that!
I think you already understand the situation.
Drop your sword already!
No—!
I understand.
Humans truly are foolish creatures!
To think that a helpless human will
voluntarily throw her life away.
You won't be killed if you'll become a breeding sow.
You think that you'll have another
chance as long as you're still alive.
But that's too bad, I won't send you
away to become a breeding sow!
I'll turn you into my personal seedbed!
I'll make you regret making a fool out of me!
Aren't you just planning to impregnate me?
Just get it over with already!
Isn't that lovely?
It sure is better when you act tough at the beginning
or else you're not worth breaking!
Seedbeds only need a womb and a heart, after all.
I'll break both of your mind and sense of reason!
Let's play a game. The rules will be simple.
I'll use my brain-sucking tentacles for each mistake
and eat your memories until you're mindlessly crippled.
Brain...
C-Cripple...
If you manage to keep your ego as I keep violating
you until the moon wanes, I'll release you.
That's why you should do your best
and endure this. That's all!
You came already!
Well, well...
It seems that the self-proclaimed
heroine loved it as well.
Hey, you... What was your name again?
Name? My name is...
Huh?
W-What is my name?
Leona-san? What's wrong?
Please hold yourself together! Your name is...
Leona Amar—!
Huh?
Why... Name...
Her name is...
What did you do to me... To us?
Try saying the name of that rotten scholar next!
I can't remember, I don't know his name—!
Is that so? I'll have the tentacles
ravage you again, okay?
Come as many times as you can and
your memories will fade as well.
Don't break me even further!
Stop erasing my memories—!
You are both losers that I vanquished!
As a victor, I somehow feel like
I should show you a little pity...
So let me see you both beg
hideously and miserably for mercy!
No! I don't want to turn crazy!
I'll become your slave!
I-I am a heroine! It's because I am a heroine!
I am a priestess of Yuran-sama!
So, I'm sure that I'll be of some use!
Here, come on!
Shout my name loud with all your breath!
Don't you want my help?
I don't want my memories wiped out, please help me!
Whoever, whoever you are!
Her name...
Remember that demon's name!
If I don't, my memories will get wiped out!
I'm coming! I'm coming! I'm coming!
Alright, then! I had enough fun.
You both should waste no time and
fulfill your duties as my seedbeds!
Make sure to find a fertile loam soil,
and bloom healthy sprouts from
both your heads and wombs!
They definitely are to end up mindlessly
crippled when I made them my seedbeds,
but they still tried to endure it and
desperately begged for mercy.
Their faces were terrific!
I just remembered that I need to train now,
so I won't bring shame to my daughters.
I feel like I'm forgetting about something...
Oh, well! Whatever!
Master? Master?
Oh... Is that you, Sheila?
We're saved thanks to Youki's stupidity.
Leaving us here by ourselves...
There's no way for us demons
to die just from this much.
Goddamn right you are.
Alright, then... Shall we go
and help those two now?
Will they be alright?
Well, they should be.
After all, I know the way to treat them.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization