We have a blood moon tonight!
It is the time when the power
of us demons is at its peak.
Alright! Let loose and run amok, everyone!
Show to all of the inferior humans in this world
how terrifying the demons truly are!
There may be a blood moon,
but they're actions sure are bold.
There's still a human wandering around here.
Don't fight back. I won't
kill you if you won't resist.
Don't move!
Huh?
Are you alright?
You are...
...the heroine who recently came to town?
Oh my... It seems that I got quite famous, huh?
Before that, this place is dangerous.
There's a shelter right over
there, so make a run for it.
Master...
Is that you, Sheila?
I met someone intriguing.
We'll tail her.
Episode 1: Creeping Tentacles Under the Crimson Moonlight
Please stop!
Somewhere around rank C, huh?
No—!
So this one's a rank B?
What a great catch!
Their average mana is between C and D rank!
This should be enough to please Isabella-sama!
And this one...
Oh—!
This one's a rank A
This is such a nice find!
Alright, then.
I will personally take care of you!
Hey there! Hurry up and
take the other girls away!
No...
Youki-sama, I'm glad to see that you're having fun
but please don't forget about our order
to capture the renegade demon!
I-I never forgot about it, you boor!
Now, find anyone who fits that description
aside from your job of searching for humans!
Understood.
Now, then.
P-Please don't kill me, I'm begging you!
Hey, you don't have to be that scared.
I won't get an urge to kill you
as long as you won't resist.
Our job here is to only catch humans.
The demon king never gave us
permission to kill for pleasure.
I-Is that so?
Though instead of killing you,
we'll have you give birth to plenty of demons.
P-Please save us, Yuran-sama!
I'm begging you, please stop!
Will it be alright?
We're fucking them without asking Youki-sama first.
I'm begging you!
We're doing our job properly.
I'm sure that Youki-sama won't mind us
getting ourselves two or three women.
Right? Don't you agree as well, miss?
What, they messed up again? How pathetic.
The one who can catch her can do
whatever he wants to her.
Let's settle this!
These low-level demons are usually no match for me...
The blood moon's boost on them truly is troublesome.
So I only have this much mana left. What should I do?
Hey, what's the matter?
Are you already tired, little girl?
Looks like we'll have to teach
you about how you are
nothing more than a powerless female human!
Hey! Over here, you pigs!
Wh-What the hell is happening?
I can't move!
This is my chance!
Are you alright?
That fume only affects demons.
It doesn't have any effects
on humans, so don't worry.
You're the man before...
L-Listen...
There's another girl captured
by the demons further inside.
Please save her!
Leave it to me. I will rescue that girl.
So you should get away from
here without any worries.
Thank you for helping me earlier.
It's not like I did it expecting to be thanked.
You still saved me, nonetheless.
Aren't you quite strong?
Hain.
Huh?
Hain Volgal, that is my name.
I've been researching on countermeasures for blood moon demons
I'm a magic scholar from the temple.
My name is Leona.
Leona Amaral.
I'm a heroine in a quest to defeat the demon king.
I'm not fond of formalities, so just call me Hain.
I'll also call you Leona in return.
Then, it's nice meeting you, Hain!
Yeah.
At any rate,
the blood moon's magical power sure is immense.
Oh, is this your first time to fight
demons in a day with a blood moon?
No... I've already fought against
them at least a couple of times,
but it was the first time that I fought that many.
The blood moon...
It appears on the day of the
demon king Lagar's resurrection.
Unlike the normal moon,
it appears in the sky as an ominous crimson moon.
The light that moon emits
affects some creatures, especially the demons.
Creatures basked in that light goes
in an intense state of arousal.
They easily lose any sense of reason.
That effect will reach its peak on the day
that the blood moon turns full.
And the town of humans beneath it will
perish, or so the rumors said...
And the humans that the demons didn't kill...
...I wonder if those rumors are actually true.
Rumors?
Oh...
Did you mean about the human captives
being used as egg-layers and sperm banks?
It's all true.
Only a handful of types of demons
can reproduce asexually.
Humans are capable of cross-breeding with demons,
thus they are an ideal race for reproduction.
That's why the demons use them to propagate.
So, it really is true.
You're quite knowledgeable.
Well, I specialized in research about that subject.
Hush!
I can sense a powerful presence just beyond here.
The one they referred to as Youki
should be just beyond here.
Thinking about how the captured people
are, we shouldn't waste any more time.
We should go at once!
Well, hold on. There isn't any need
for you to heedlessly rush forward.
I have a plan so lend me your ear.
You got some guts even when
there's only two of you, humans.
Who are you?
My name is Leona.
Leona Amaral.
I'm just a heroine who happened to pass by.
Heroine?
Well, seeing cocky self-proclaimed
heroes isn't really new to me.
But this is the first time I saw a snotty
brat like you who calls herself as one!
And, is that man wearing a hood your babysitter?
I'm taking that girl with me.
Prepare yourself!
I'd like to see you try if you think you can!
This is strange, I can't use my power!
I sprayed a chemical that greatly weakens
plant type demons in the air.
Your power will never go beyond
that even on a blood moon.
You rotten bastard!
Let go of that girl!
Tsk...
Get yourself together! Are you alright?
W-Wait, what's happening?
You were too laid-back, master.
Yeah, sorry.
That woman, your ears... Could you be...
You are a demon?!
That's right, I am Hain Volgal, a magic scholar.
Identifying me as a demon instead
of a human would be correct.
Wh-Wh-Wh...
Why is a demon on the human's side?!
Don't tell me that you're
the one Isabella-sama wanted.
The renegade demon!
Renegade?
I'll leave that to your imagination.
More importantly, prepare yourself.
I can't just let you go after finding out my identity.
Th-This is bad...
I'm not sure why, but this man is dangerous!
I'm no match against him in my current state.
Then, take this!
She's cunning despite how she looks.
Master,
this smoke seems to be
rigged with a strong poison.
Pursuing her is out of the question.
Let's go back, Sheila.
Yes, master.
Are you awake?
Where are we?
This is a town inn.
although we're the only ones in here.
What happened to Youki?
And is the girl we rescued now safe?
The one called Youki escaped.
The girl suffered from being planted with seeds,
but she's been purged and given an antidote.
She'll get better soon.
I see, thank goodness...
And then, just who are you?
You even helped me fight the
demons. What are you after?
Forgive me, but I can't tell
you my reasons right now.
Talking about it won't amount to anything as well.
More importantly, how about you?
The smokescreen that Youki made
contains a toxin that amplifies
the effects of the blood moon.
You should be throbbing right beneath your navel.
Th-That's out of your concern!
What if I told you that there's
a way to gain resistance from that?
Huh? I-Is there really such a method?
What should I do?
Well, that's simple. You should
just let me copulate with you.
Huh?
Don't worry, you don't have to do anything.
You can just let me take the lead.
It will hurt at first, but you can
expect feeling pleasure afterwards.
I
I-I can't!
I-I can't! I can't
I-I can't! I can't, I can't
I-I can't! I can't, I can't, I can't!
I absolutely can't!
Moreover, why do I have to sleep with you?!
Mana is something that becomes
harmful when it exceeds your capacity.
That means we should just
reduce it to stop your throbbing.
I am going to suck out that excess mana
that got accumulated in your body,
and then your mana capacity
with increase at the same time.
You'll have more mana at your disposal.
Well, that would be the quick explanation for it.
I can't do that after all! Even if
that means I'll gain immunity,
I just can't have sex with a man so easily!
Is that so? What a shame.
But this is a good chance so
I'll have to be more coercive.
What is this?
W-Wait, what's the meaning of this?
It is what it is since you are being stubborn.
I'll just have to forcibly rape you.
How dare you utter of such shamelessness!
Wh-What is this weird creature?
They are the fruits of my research.
Although each has a life of its own,
they are all linked to me.
They come in various forms,
and I can control their strength.
In other words, they're something like a familiar.
I've never heard of such a tasteless familiar!
Anyway, hurry up and take these tentacles away!
I don't want to be raped by these disgusting critters!
I-It feels gross, stop moving!
Th-This man...
He smirks while watching these critters
have their way on me... Unbelievable!
Getting teased like this means nothing to me!
W-Wait, not there!
D-Don't touch...
S-Stop! I never agreed to this!
Somehow, my body is starting to feel hot.
I can't think straight...
No, I can't let myself get dragged along.
W-Wait! A-Anything but that!
Don't worry, it will only hurt at the beginning.
It'll start to feel good as you get used to it.
H-Hain...
Don't forget what you did afterwards!
I-I can't breathe! My consciousness is lapsing...
You seemed like someone who gets along with men,
but you were actually a virgin.
Stop running your mouth!
Release me from these monsters already!
Well, it's not like you'll start to feel
good right after tearing your hymen.
However, you'll only get to feel
better from here onwards.
I-It's not starting to feel good for me at all!
What is this?
It feels like my belly is getting drained inside!
Has it started?
That sensation is from the
tentacle sucking out your mana.
My mana?
That's because they are mana-sucking creatures.
A woman's womb is a place that produces mana.
That's where it sucks out your mana.
That sensation is from your
womb being penetrated.
Don't faint while having your mana
drained and savor the feeling for now.
Stop, stop...
Looks like you're quite hooked on
sex with tentacle suckers now.
Wh-Who would get hooked from
having sex with these monsters?!
I absolutely won't lose against these tentacles!
Don't! Don't do that!
It's churning up my insides!
That's a nice expression.
Lastly, let the tentacles bring
you ecstasy as they ejaculate.
Ejaculate...
N-No, not inside...
Anything but letting them come inside me!
No, this is bad!
This is messing up with my mind!
No, stop... Stop!
Coming... I'm coming...
I'm coming—!
Your womb is getting thoroughly deformed!
It'll make you come a lot.
I-I'm coming... I'm coming!
Alright then, the important part is about to start.
Wh-What is this?
Looks like it already started.
The semen that the tentacle poured
inside you has a special property.
The mana it sucked out of you is used
to rapidly develop its spawn.
D-Does that mean...
You are about to lay an egg right now.
An egg?
N-No...
No—!
I-I don't believe this!
I was violated just now!
Making you have an orgasm isn't enough.
You have to lay an egg to gain an immunity
from the effects of the blood moon.
I can't! I can't give birth to a baby!
Wh-What is this?
I'm feeling weird!
How is it? Doesn't it feel good?
This special procedure is called
"Egg-laying Method".
I can't! I'm coming...
I don't want to come from laying an egg... No!
Neither training nor pain is necessary.
Extreme pleasure is guaranteed.
I don't want to come!
I'm about to lay a tentacle's egg,
but why am I feeling so good?!
No, this is bad!
If this goes on, I'll really end up laying an egg!
I-I laid an egg...
It was my first time and I laid a tentacle's egg...
This is strange... This is strange!
Even though I went over something like this,
why did I end up feeling good?
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization