Welcome home, Master.
Victoria Maid.
Maria's Service.
You seem even more fatigued than yesterday.
My, you're saying such things again.
It was quite difficult, wasn't it?
By all means, please relax yourself.
I, Maria, like always, shall.
There, there.
Shall do this for you.
How splendid it has become.
Now, Master.
Please let it all out,
let everything out... in my mouth.
It really... looks lively now.
But,
it'd be difficult to eat supper with that, right?
Now,
just cum to your heart's content,
and quell its urges.
I am now prepared.
Master,
just use me as you please.
My insides now feel very full,
all thanks to you, Master.
Oh my, what vigor.
It looks wonderful, Master.
Umm... could you please not stare
at me like that too much, Master?
My body is merely.
Alright. I do need to widen it it too, correct?
Here, here is what you are going to take before supper.
It has "opened" for you... and is now ready.
Master, no.
Your hands are going to be sullied.
My, Master, you're such a tease.
Oh, but you might get cold.
I shall warm you up.
Here.
Master,
how is the water?
Is the temperature just right?
Master, your thing feels very hot.
How do my specially reserved breasts feel, Master?
I'm glad that I seem to have been able to satisfy you.
It was, it was really exquisite.
Master.
Will this really be alright?
You seem to be fatigued already.
I'll just take care of it in the morning.
My, you really are susceptible to this, Master.
Until your fatigue finally overwhelms you,
please, just use me however you want to.
For I am your exclusive maid.
Is it about time?
I understand.
Th-This is.
After receiving your tender caress,
I can no longer restrain this warm sensation.
Please, do not tease it further.
No, not again.
There, it's clean now.
Please have a nice, good sleep.
Good morning, Master.
I'm sure today will also turn out to be a good one.