Welcome back, Master.
You seem more tired than you were yesterday.
Oh my, something like that again?
It must have been rough huh?
Please, relax.
As usual, Maria will...
There, there... I'll help you.
How splendid.
Well then, Master, please let out a lot inside Maria's mouth.
It's become... incredibly energetic.
But...
It will be difficult to have dinner like this, right?
Come now, ejaculate as you please.
Please sate our desires.
Maria's preparations are complete.
Master, please use me as you like.
Maria's stomach has become so full
because of Master's semen.
How manly of you.
It's lovely, Master.
Please don't stare so much Master,
my body isn't all that...
Yes, you want to do it again right?
Yes, the snack Master gave me before dinner,
is starting to come out.
That's what this stain is...
You can't, Master...
You will dirty your hand.
Please get into the bathtub, Master.
You will catch a cold.
Maria will warm you up.
Okay?
Master, how is the temperature of the water?
It isn't too warm, is it?
Master's thing is so hot and stiff.
Master, how do you like the feeling of
my nipples that are just for you?
It pleases me to see that you're satisfied.
It was... It was just delicious, Master.
Are you sure?
Even though you are tired.
You will start sweating, you know.
What a troublesome Master.
Please use Maria however you want,
until you are fully satisfied.
I am Master's private maid after all.
Should I do it now?
As you wish.
T-This is...?
Receiving all this kindness from Master...
I can't help but get wet.
Please... don't tease me so much.
No way, again?
Now, it's clean.
Please have a pleasurable night's sleep.
Good morning, Master.
I'm sure it'll be a great day for you today.