Here's your kimchi and beef ribs
rice bowl dish! Enjoy your meal.
This sure is delicious!
Then, see you tonight in-game online.
Yes, yes, with our usual lineup.
Okay! See you, then.
What...
Wh-What's this?
What could that be?
There's something over there.
Hey, this will hurt you!
You'll end up getting hit!
Whoa...
Water...
My Household's Liliana-san
She doesn't have anywhere else to go,
so I ended up letting her stay
here in my house at the moment.
Whoa!
Tatsuya-san, I really am grateful to you.
Tatsuya-san?
It's my first time to see them.
They're so big... Such beautiful breasts.
Liliana-san!
Yes?
Umm... Y-Your breasts are exposed.
Huh?!
I'm sorry!
It's just that I felt too relaxed
after you saved me from the streets.
A-Ah... O-Okay...
Wear something first, then we'll talk.
Yes... Umm...
What should I wear?
Oh!
Tatsuya-san?
Oh..
Umm, what do you think of this one?
Whoa...
I-It's cute.
Umm, Liliana-san... People around
have been staring and it bugs me...
Stares, you say?
You should go inside, then.
No!
Is this alright?
Have you calmed down?
Liliana-san's breasts are so close!
Y-Yeah... I'm okay now.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh... God...
You look cute too.
Oh, no way!
What should we do next?
Well...
Tatsuya-san!
Here, I bought you a Corn Dog.
Want to eat over there?
Yes.
Sorry for making you stand in line for it.
No way, I'm the one who
volunteered to do it.
Tatsuya-san, umm...
H-Here, say "aah"!
Hmm?
U-Umm, Liliana-san...
Oh? I'm sorry if I was putting you on the spot.
Th-That's not the case at all!
A-Aah...
Tatsuya-san...
Wow...
Doesn't the night breeze feel good?
Yeah, I'm glad that we came.
It seems that this is a popular spot even overseas.
Whoa!
Uhh...
Thanks, Liliana-san.
I'm glad that you're not hurt.
Wow...
It's like Liliana-san is...
Hey, buy some of these!
This one!
It's so cold!
Right?
I'm home!
Welcome home, Tatsuya-san.
The snow's gonna pile up
next morning at this rate.
Whoa!
That's the one we bought at that time.
Yes!
This one is very important to me, so I
wanted to wear it for Christmas.
Now that I think about it, it's been about a year.
Liliana-san, thank you as always.
What's up with you, Tatsuya-san?
Thanking me all of a sudden...
I just thought how great it is
to have someone greeting me home.
Oh...
No way, rather than thanking me...
No, I mean... A-Aren't you tired?
I'll prepare some tea, so please wait in your room.
Okay, thanks.
I'll be waiting in my room, then.
Yes...
Alrighty!
Tatsuya-san...
Here's the tea.
Thank you!
The tea you brew...
...tastes so good, Liliana-san!
Tatsuya-san, u-umm...
Hmm?
I'm, umm...
I-I'm not wearing any underwear right now.
Huh?
Huh? U-Uhh...
Huh?!
U-Umm... I'm not wearing any...
...underwear.
U-Uhh...
Uhh, uhh...
Ohh...
Tatsuya-san,
If you haven't saved me on
that day, I would've been...
L-Liliana-san!
I've been meaning to thank
you back for all this time,
but I don't have anything
else to offer besides this.
So please accept this.
Tatsuya-san...
Liliana-san, are you really okay with this?
Yes...
I've already decided to give both
my body and heart to you.
So please penetrate me
with that thing of yours!
O-Okay...
But let me say one thing to you...
I am in love with you, Liliana-san.
That's why instead of your gratitude,
what I want is to be loved back and be one with you.
Tatsuya-san, I'm so happy!
Me too, I feel the same!
Please go on, I'll leave everything to you.
Tatsuya-san!
Liliana-san, are you alright?
Y-Yes!
I'm fine, everything's alright!
Deeper... Please thrust it...
...deep inside me!
W-Wait, Liliana-san!
Tatsuya-san! Tatsuya-san!
I can feel it in my deepest parts!
Your stuff keeps on flowing
inside me, Tatsuya-san!
It keeps coming out!
Tatsuya-san!
It's hot... It feels so hot!
I'm getting filled with such a viscous fluid!
Thank you, Liliana-san.
That felt so great.
But, this...
Your important place is still hard.
Th-This is no problem at all.
No, please don't hold back.
Tatsuya-san, please come to your heart's content.
Liliana-san...
Tatsuya-san...
Tatsuya-san!
I'm coming again, Liliana-san!
Yes!
Please come!
Liliana-san...
It's still way hard. Here you go.
Please come as many times as you wish.
Please shoot it all inside me until it settles down.
Please keep making love with me, Tatsuya-san.
L-Liliana-san!
I can feel it through my whole body! I'm already...
Tatsuya-san, I'm already...
I feel dazed...
My body feels like it's gonna drift away!
Liliana-san, I'm about to shoot everything out!
Liliana-san!
Liliana-san, thank you...
Tatsuya-san...
Good afternoon! You have a package!
Yes, thank you.
Please sign here.
Okay.
Thanks!
Thank you for the hard work.
Huh? It's from Tatsuya-san's elder brother.
I'm home!
I'm pooped!
Ah... U-Umm, welcome home...
Tatsu... Master!
U-Umm...
Please excuse me!
Ahh!
W-Wait, Liliana-san!
Umm, thank you for making an effort
to greet me home wearing that.
I'm a very lucky man to have you, Liliana-san.
Tatsuya-san...
Umm, I'd prefer it if you
won't take the costume off.
Okay.
It's a dress given to you by
your elder brother, after all.
Here you go, master.
You're one pampered master, alright.
Well then...
Feel free to release a lot inside me for tonight.
It's so good that I feel like you'll squeeze me dry!
Master!
No way!
Master, I should be the one...
...working at your service!
Tatsuya-san! Tatsuya-san!
Tatsuya-san is pouring it all inside me!
I'm happy to receive a lot
of your baby seeds, master!
Liliana-san!
Huh?
I-I am happy to know
that my insides are making
you feel good, Tatsuya-san!
Tatsuya-san...
This is bad, Tatsuya-san!
My belly is full of your stuff right now.
I'll squirt it all out!
Tatsuya-san, now it's my turn to clean you up.
No way! I'm fine, Liliana-san.
That's amazing...
I-I'm coming already!
You did great, master!
You're still lively down here.
Sorry...
I'm glad, though.
There's another costume in
your elder brother's package.
Huh?!
Pyon!
Tatsuya-san, umm... Do I look good in this one?
I gulped so loud...
What do you want to do, Tatsuya-san?
I-I want you to act like a bunny while we do it.
Pyon! Pyon!
Pyon!
Am I doing a good job, Tatsuya-san?
Pyon! Pyon!
Liliana-san, I want to kiss you!
Okay!
Oh... Tatsuya-san!
If I keep feeling this good from
continuously getting penetrated,
I... I will reach a point of no return...
I'm sorry, Liliana-san. Let's have a short break.
I-I'm alright.
My body was just overwhelmed with pleasure.
I'm sorry!
Tatsuya-san, my one true wish is
that I really want to see your face as you climax.
Huh?
That's what I wish for.
Liliana-san...
Tatsuya-san?
We're so happy together, aren't we?
Yes, we are!
Mwah!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization