No!
Please, stop! No! No!
Please, stop!
No!
Please, stop...
Please...
What was that cry?
It's just a crow.
Just a crow, Ms. Aria.
Is that all? It really scared me.
Oh, yes! I was so touched.
About what?
That the principal came
to pick me up personally.
Oh, that.
I always pick up the freshmen,
including you, with my boat.
One day you'll be a hot commodity
of the 21st century music industry.
But until then, I'll raise you
like a beautiful butterfly.
Very carefully. Very... Huh?
What's wrong? Another crow?
No. Crows don't play the guitar.
Isogu! You came all this way?
Aria's prince in shining armor,
her lovely lover and true supporter...
...the rock'n'roller, hip-hop star,
and champion athlete...
...Isogu is here!
How can you brag about
yourself that much?
That damn stalker.
Is that your boyfriend?
No way! What are you...
H-He absolutely is not.
I've never seen that
vulgar man in all my life.
Very well, then.
Aren't you worried at all? I really don't
know him. Skinny guys aren't my type.
Hey, are you puckering your lips
because you want to kiss me?
He's flying away.
That's strange. There's no wind.
B-Breasts?
No, it's a really distinctive building.
Thank you. That is my country's
traditional architectural style.
Oh, you mean that building is...
Yes, that is the Royal Elegance School
you will be attending.
Wow. That ugly, boob-shaped
building is the school?
Unbelievable!
You were chosen because you are the
most talented people in the world.
You will all be stars of the 21st century
after learning classical music from me.
Excuse me.
Oh, Shinbi.
This is my sister, Shinbi,
who will also be teaching you.
How do you do.
Nice to meet you.
Binan Izumo is here.
Binan?
Right. It means beautiful man.
You are what you wear.
You must be Mr. Karma.
I'm sorry I'm late. I was
at a competition in Italy.
That's strange.
I've heard of you, but this
is a women's school.
Unless you are very special, we don't...
I am special.
What?
I have permission from the
government, as well.
His father recently made a
very generous donation.
Pleased to meet you.
And you, too.
Binan Izumo, classical guitarist
and computer genius.
I've also heard that you're a hacker.
You make it sound like
I'm some sort of criminal.
We've decided to formally
reject your application.
But the government gave me permission.
Huh? Again?
I wish that thunderstorm would just come.
What's going on?
And what about you?
I was asking your names.
My name is Aria.
I'm Yan.
Aria and Yan. Pleased to meet you.
And you?
I'm Luna, and this is my sister Monica.
You just won first prize in the Italian
Music Competition, didn't you?
You know about that?
Yes, they call me the prince of classical
guitar in Europe nowadays.
I'm Karen. I just love
your guitar technique.
I know. I have a strong style.
It hits you right there.
Don't behave so vulgarly!
I concur.
To become a superb musician,
you must have class.
Especially when you're the elite of
millions of young, talented musicians.
You shouldn't disgrace the spirit of
music and the dignity of my country.
Wow. You're a martial arts master!
I'm not really a master. My grandpa in
Hong Kong used to teach me.
My father also taught me
some martial arts.
Is your dad a samurai?
He's not a samurai, he's a ninja.
What's that?
It's a joke. You're pretty hip, Yan.
Thanks. So, is he really a ninja?
Yeah. He’s from the Koga clan.
And your mom was
of Russian royalty?
I guess.
She might have been a witch.
A witch? No way!
Yeah, I don't think so either. No way.
What's that?
Isogu?
Hey, my pretty girl!
Will you ever give up?
I wish he would just go away!
I'm being blown away.
He really was blown away!
Maybe I really am...
I'm sorry!
What's wrong with you?
I know!
I'm too handsome to be
in the classroom.
What are you talking about?
It's all right. It was my fault.
Why are you so self-centered?
My country, Orgam, is a
small country in Europe.
But we are dedicated to helping educate
young, talented musicians at this school.
With pride.
If you aren't serious,
you can leave anytime.
I'm sorry, Principal.
I'm glad you understand.
I'll be more careful, too.
Understood.
Karen, come to the principal's
room tonight at eight.
He'll give you a private lesson.
He'll do that for me?
I'm so honored!
What are you doing?
He was trying to touch your hips!
No, I wasn't! I was trying
to get something off of her.
What?
If you feel lonely, look up?
Yoo hoo!
Isogu!
Let him go!
Aria?
Will you let me go, Yan?
Don't try to mock me!
Ouch...
Won't you just give up?
This is destiny, Aria.
If anything happens, I'll
always be behind you!
You're giving me a headache.
Listen!
Where are you, Isogu?
I'll always be behind you.
Don't scare me like that. What...
Huh? Where? I know...
You'll always be behind me.
Is he your boyfriend?
No! He's a stalker!
Then you have to leave now.
Don't worry, I won't harm you.
And I won't tell the principal.
You're so kind.
Aren't you a woman?
Ouch!
That's it.
Now, I'll give you a special lesson.
Close your eyes and...
...take this sound into
your mind and body.
Into my body?
Yes, into the center of ecstasy.
W-What? No!
Hold it!
I'll take her first.
All right.
It's pretty funny that you're
being raped by a woman!
It's a shame you won't
have any memory of it.
I'll enjoy your lovely lips.
I'm sorry!
What's wrong, Karen?
Are you okay?
Don't tell me you're also falling for me.
Be quiet!
We'll take a fifteen minute break.
What's wrong with her?
Ever since that private lesson,
she's been getting worse.
Yeah, she's made more
than one mistake.
Wow. You noticed that, too?
Not just me.
Luna and Monica, too.
Our turn?
Yes. Tonight, you two will have
a private lesson together.
I'm so honored.
Thank you so much.
So, it's their turn tonight.
Then, it's going to be
you or me tomorrow.
I hope we can take the lesson together!
Yeah.
If we keep taking the energy of youth
and talent like this, we will live forever!
The Earth is such a great place to live.
I agree.
What's going on?
Luna and Monica are
doing very poorly today.
What is the principal's private lesson?
I'm starting to get
concerned about it, too.
Tonight, it's your turn to come to me.
What's wrong? You look
bothered by something.
Oh, it's nothing. It's just...
You must be wondering why those who take
my private lessons are making mistakes.
Yes, actually...
Sir, what did you do to them?
This is the answer.
What is that?
Spirit.
Spirit?
Yes. You have been playing
with just your fingers.
Playing with...
...just fingers?
You all are musically talented,
and have good techniques.
But you have to play from here! Here!
Play from here!
You know.
With your tender breasts.
And this wet area!
What are you going to do?
I'll inject a beautiful spirit into you...
Ms. Shinbi!
What are you two?
We are the messengers of pleasure.
Damn it!
Let's do it together!
We have to save the students
from those impostors.
They're just like you.
But she had something down there.
When I touched it...
...come to think of it, it
was different from mine.
We have to save them now!
I know! I know!
No, stop!
Let me go!
Stop!
No!
What a beautiful view!
No! Stop!
Stop!
Ouch!
No... Please, let me go...
Stop it!
Let them go!
You devils! I won't let
you get away with this!
We're not devils.
We're just...
...aliens.
All right! Since you're all together,
we'll take all of you!
What a brilliant idea!
I came for you, Aria!
What are you doing, you bastards?
I'm flying too fast!
I need your power, Mama.
I'm losing my power!
My arm!
Hang on!
A-Are you an alien, too?
H-How dare you?!
How can a pretty girl
like me be an alien?
But what's really going on?
Don't fool around with me!
Are you still trying to abuse us?
I won't let you get away with that!
You don't like this sound, do you?
Oh, ouch...
Yan, Karen, Luna, Monica,
let's fight together!
Let the winds blow!
Let the storm come!
You want more? Okay,
I'll give you more!
My neck...
Aria!
Now you've made me mad!
I won't take it easy on you anymore!
You ugly monsters, disappear!
H-Huh?
What happened?
Where did that power come from?
It must be because of my mom's ring.
I guess I am a witch after all.
But keep it a secret!
What's wrong, Shinbi?
Nothing. I'm fine.
They really are such fine, pretty girls.