Wanna. SpartanSex Spermax!!!
Did I gain some weight?
No way.
This is just me growing up!
Lately I didn't get to eat to my heart's content either.
There is just no way I could have have put on weight.
My simple life as an ordinary high school student,
came crashing down when my father disappeared
and left us with his huge debts.
The remaining members of the family
were forced to flee from the weight of his debts.
My younger sister left with my mother while I,
escaped separately in hopes of finding safe haven with
my childhood friend and cousin, Yoshiyuki Onii-chan.
However, before I had even gotten to him,
Onii-chan seems to have fled himself and is now missing.
I really can't stand my demeaning aunt,
but I don't really have anywhere else to go.
So, my aunt is paying for my living expenses
in exchange for me trying to find Onii-chan.
For now, I'm at an Internet café near the
school that Onii-chan was attending,
and after a bit of investigation,
it became clear as day that Onii-chan s disappearance
was the direct result of extensive bullying.
Alright!
I was worried about how my body would turn out in this.
But you look quite good, Nagisa!
Now that my feminine physique is hidden,
it's time to fool those bullies.
I was really lucky to get my transfer completed so quickly.
After changing my student file, I was readily admitted
as a male student to this delinquent filled school.
Now, I have successfully infiltrated Kengou Academy.
and to find out where he is now.
Wait for me, Onii-Chan.
Wanna. Spartan Sex Sperm ax!!!
Woman to a Man?! The Hell of Endless Impregnation
White Stickies!! Kiri Nagasaki school transfer Chapter
Yo-kun, Yoshiyuki-kun really contacted you?
Yeah.
He sent this.
Thank you Kubozuka-kun. But,
I don't want any bullies to find me.
Show her this message.
I want you to bring her the
gym's storage shed after school
I wish to see her again.
I'm glad.
Yo-kun...
Like the message says,
he doesn't want to be seen,
so he wants me to bring you to him.
So, would you please come with me?
Yes, I understand.
Yo-kun...
But Tanabe sure is lucky.
He must be to have a cute girlfriend
like you to worry about him.
Eh? I'm not his girlfriend...
Yoshiko-kun is just my childhood friend.
Eh? Really?
I really thought you were his girlfriend.
But I think Tanabe really wants you to be his girlfriend.
If there's a cute girl who genuinely worries about them...
anyone would surely...
No.
I don't have the right to.
The one who pushed Yoshiyuki-kun this far
was probably me.
It's because I told him that I want
to go to the same college as him.
I wanted to encourage Yoshiyuki-kun,
because he tends to skip school.
But I ended up pushing him too hard.
I would've done anything for him...
But now that I've learned he was being bullied...
Does he hate me now?
Come on, Tanabe is waiting.
Yes.
Just wait, I'll definitely save you this time.
No!
Don't do this!
Yo-kun save me!
Sorry to tell you this, but Yoshiyuki-kun isn't here.
The person over there is...
Yeah, that would be me.
No way.
You tricked me!
No!
Let's see those beautiful, pink nipples...
As I expected of a lady from Ekou Academy.
Hey, keep that camera nice and steady.
We're going to show this to Yoshiyuki later.
No! Don't film this!
I can't believe you were tricked so easily.
You're Hiiragi Akim-Chan, right?
Those bullies who were harassing Yoshiyuki
were none other than us.
Eh?
Stop!
You know, teasing him was really fun.
Especially when we forced him to dress
like a girl and suck our cocks.
That one was really great!
No way. You lowlifes,
I won't forgive you!
Oh, it looks like you get aroused
pretty easily there, Aki-Chan.
How much did you do it with Yoshiyuki-kun?
Did you have your first kiss with Yoshiyuki!
I don't have anything to say to a scum like you!
Oh yeah?
Then it's time for a little game.
How terrible.
I was saving my first kiss for Yo-kun.
I won't forgive you.
How naughty of you, Kubozuka.
Then I'm taking one, too.
Me too...
Oh, we truly are looking for Yoshiyuki though.
Once we find him, we'll let you have Yoshiyuki's first kiss.
We'll teach you different techniques for it right now.
Cute girls really do have tasty saliva.
Now, I'll have you use that cute mouth of yours for this, too.
It stinks!
What was that?
Just shove it in already!
You're no good at all.
Don't you dare try to use your teeth.
Use 'em, and I'll pluck 'em out.
That'd be such a waste.
We'll be using her to cut off Yoshiyuki's dick.
That's a great idea!
That guy's really great at fellating.
I'll get turned on even more if he finally becomes a girl.
Hey there, Aki-chan.
If you can't do this properly,
you don't have a chance of becoming Yoshiyuki's girlfriend.
Still not as good as Yoshiyuki?
This is how you do it!
You suck it in until it reaches your throat.
Oh, could it be that you're already
"experienced" down here?
This wetness is really amazing.
Still don't feel like talking?
Then why don't we check it out directly?
Oh, I guess it was your first time.
Well then, we need to open it up as much as possible.
This silky hair, I can't get enough!
I'm cumming!
Whoa, she's squeezing me down here.
I'll have to do my part, too.
No, don't!
Don't push it in further!
It hurts.
Pull it out already.
Please!
If Aki-chan's begging me so much,
then I guess I have no choice.
I'll "pull" out to your womb but not
before releasing lots of cum in it.
No, you can't cum inside!
You can't cum inside!
I'll get pregnant!
No!
No...
Please, I'll do anything!
Don't cum inside!
Cum outside.
Please, cum outside!
No!
He came inside me...
Even though I begged him not to...
His hot thing is filling me up inside.
I'll get pregnant!
Me too!
Whoa, I came inside right after taking your virginity.
That's a big load of cum.
Man, her uniform is all dirty now...
What if we cleaned it?
So?
How does it feel to get cummed inside for your first time?
I won't forgive you.
I'll never forgive you!
Eh? You weren't satisfied with me?
Igarashi, you're up next then.
What are you saying?
I'll make sure to get you really aroused.
No...
It's so twitchy that it wants to thrust into you right away.
Looks like we've got a nice toy to play with.
As long as you're our toy,
we won't hurt Yoshiyuki.
No...
Do it already!
It'll be dawn soon!
No!
You're totally free to choose the father of your child.
No...
No!!!
I never thought that this high class
chick that was looking for our toy
would be so easy to catch.
I can't believe that I can have sex with a
girl from Ekou Academy anytime I want!
I'm getting the urge to do it again.
You're too much for her, Igarashi.
She was already at her mental and physical limit,
and you still kept on pounding her.
That's what so good about it!
She must have realized that she's
just our tool to cum inside!
What are we going to do next, Kubocchi?
If she's getting that every day,
we won't be able to use Yoshiyuki as
a reason to keep her much longer.
Human relief tool
Cum Inside!
For Cumming Inside
We need to fill her mind completely with
the pleasure of being a woman.
Kudo!
Now is the time to bring out your collection.
No!
We'll do cosplays and use some-other "tools."
Like making her wear a maid's outfit and
leaving a vibrator inside her pussy.
Next, we can shift to some bondage
play while she's wearing a swimsuit.
Then, we can top it off with a gang
rape party in front of Yoshiyuki.
As expected of Kubozuka.
You really have good ideas for this.
Please, don't look Yo-kun.
Now then, I still have an appointment with Aki-chan,
so I have to find Yoshiyuki.
Speaking of Yoshiyuki,
the guy that just transferred here is asking about him.
I want to ask you something.
Isn't there a guy in your class named Tanabe Yoshiyuki?
Do you know where he is?
The guy that beat up the entire gang
in Class C single-handedly?
Yeah, Kiryuu.
He's that pretty boy they to looks like he could
crossdress as good as Yoshiyuki?
I rather like the guy.
I want him to be my friend.
Are you for real man?
But something's bugging me...
Everyone, return to your seats!
Okay.
Starting today, Hiura-sensei will be
teaching you classical literature.
She's trying to complete her education training.
Well then Sensei, please introduce yourself.
Umm...I'm Hiura Shiori. I'll be teaching
you classical literature for some time.
It will only be for a short 3 weeks,
but I hope we can all get along.
Hiura-sensei, can I ask a question?
Yes, go ahead.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Eh?
I have...hey, that kind of question is...
Then, how many times in a week do you have sex?
What's your favorite position?
Eh? Those questions are not...
Are you still a virgin, Sensei?
Vir...
When was your first time?
Sensei, how big are your breasts?
Have you done anal sex?
Do you let your boyfriend cum inside you?
Sensei, please let me have a titty fuck!
Getting back to business, I'll leave it
to you to gather info on Shiori-chan.
Like her hometown and people around her? Roger that.
How about you?
Sorry, but I think I have an idea to help
us find out where Yoshiyuki is.
If I keep a close eye on that Kiryuu guy...
I bet that I'll be able to catch up to Yoshiyuki.
Man, I always have to be so careful about exposing
myself or even using the toilet at that school.
It's really difficult to crossdress as a guy.
That felt good!
But I was a little careless.
The guy that I talked to about Onii-chan
on my first day at this school
was the main leader of all the bullying, Kobozuka Kouya.
If I'd known it then, I would've beaten him to the last
inch of his life to try and get some details out of him.
I have to get him to an isolated place,
so I can ask him about Onii-chan.
I'm positive that he knows something.
If he tries to fool around, then I really will
beat him to the last inch of his life.
Kiryuu'sa woman?
Well, well! That's certainly interesting.
Here's what I've learned about
Shiori chan over last few days.
She is currently living with her boyfriend, who was
her childhood neighbor at an apartment complex.
Later, that boyfriend was her senior at college,
and he's currently a teacher at an all girls school.
Being a teacher can be rather stressful.
It's even more agitating at an all girls school.
Maybe they're going all out every night?
Maybe he's making her wear his student's uniform,
while they play teacher-student.
Seriously, I think they're actually doing it.
So, what about Kiryuu then?
Basically, that person seems to be Yoshiyuki's cousin.
Something happened with her home,
so she's currently based at some Internet café.
She's managed to infiltrate the
school to try to find Yoshiyuki.
After that, she found out that I had been bullying Yoshiyuki,
and she wants to beat me up to squeeze some information
about Yoshiyuki's whereabouts from me.
Damn, Yoshiyuki again.
The guy's really popular.
But, I was really surprised when you
first showed us those pictures.
She's really good at hiding that sexy body.
And now, during today's lunch break,
I invited Kiryuu to a date.
Oh man, those are the clothes from the pictures!
I left a love letter in her locker when I "borrowed" that.
It's a woman's scent.
But do you really know where Yoshiyuki is?
Wait, I didn't?
I'm pretty good at capturing toys
that try to escape from me.
I've been waiting Kiryuu.
Kubozuka.
Give it back!
I never knew.
That you had something like this as a hobby.
Shut up!
Just give it to me this instant!
Hey, don't misunderstand.
I'm just happy that I've found someone
with the same hobby.
Huh?
How did you get this rare thing?
What do you mean?
It's not surprising for someone to have women's clothing.
We're starved for the presence of women.
But, women's clothing that's actually
been worn by a woman,
that's something that's hard to come by.
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb.
These clothes are filled with a woman's smell.
Where did you get them?
I'll trade you for them.
That's the main reason I'm here.
Stop messing with me.
If you don't give it back right now, I'll have to beat you up.
Sorry about that.
Here.
Now, you're going to spill everything
you know about Tanabe Yoshiyuki.
If you mess around like before, I'll...
You're late.
Sorry.
This is a one-shot gamble you know.
Kubozuka...
Sorry, Kiryuu, but I have another request.
Why don't you wear these clothes?
What... did you say?
I think they would fit you if you wore them.
Don't fuck with me!
You can't seem to move though, so I'll put them on for you.
I'm sure they would suit you well.
Stop!
No good...
No!
You're... a woman?
Breasts!
For real?
So what about it?
Get your hands off me!
You really don't understand anything, Kiryuu.
In this school, the one who throw
spits first is the one who wins.
What do you mean?
I mean this!
No!
So you're good at screaming passionately after all.
Stop! If you keep going, I'll kill you!
Scream even more passionately.
Stop... no...
You're really something!
Hey, let me fondle those boobs.
We'll take real good care of you.
No!
Stop... No... No!
I'm amazed that you were able to hide breasts this big.
This is really good.
No, no!
Not there...
This smells like a real, lewd woman.
Just like that last one.
Don't lick it...
No...
Stop...
I'm cumming!
It stinks. No...
Now, we're going to start bathing
you in this potent, male scent.
No, what are you going to do...
I'm going to test whether this cock that
you just kicked still works or not.
No, stop!
It's my first time!
I'll do anything else.
Just not that!
Oh?
If you agree to become my woman, then I'll let you be.
No.
Did I forget to say that I'll also tell you where Yoshiyuki is?
You actually know?
Yesterday you told me you were looking for him, right?
If you want, I'll let you meet him after this.
Really?
Then...
If you get me to him first, then I'll do whatever you want.
If I can just get out of this situation,
I'll be able to beat them back.
If I can figure out Onii-chan's whereabouts this way...
That's fine with me.
Then I'll have you swear to what you said earlier.
You're going to become my woman, right?
Yeah, I'll do what you say.
Say what?
If you don't say it properly, I'll shove it in right now!
I'll become your woman!
Isn't that enough already?
Just take me to him already!
Okay, right after this.
You liar!
You said that you were going to take me to him first...
Yeah,
but you're my woman now,
so I can shove it in whenever I decide to!
I can't believe this.
This lowlife is going to be my first time...
Stop moving!
I made an effort to find him for you.
Calling me that is a bit harsh.
It hurts.
Please don't move.
Shut up!
This is terrible.
This lowlife even stole my first kiss...
Now you're completely mine.
I've taken your first kiss and your virginity.
Stop joking around!
Who would want to be with a scum like you.
Now, to honor my new woman,
I'll give you a gift.
It hurts, it hurts!
Don't thrust in so intensely!
I'm cumming!
No, I'm not safe today.
Don't releasee it inside.
Cum outside!
You're my woman, so bear my children.
No!
I'll kill you!
If you cum inside, I'll definitely kill you!
It's coming out.
I'm not safe today,
and yet something hot is being released inside me.
Hey, stop lying around and start changing already.
Do you plan to meet Yoshiyuki looking like that?
Wow!
She looks like an entirely different person.
As expected of my woman.
Don't stare.
Die, you liar.
Who would want to be your woman?
That can't be helped.
What are you going to do?
If you don't want to be my woman,
then you'll become our woman.
Well then...
Don't come near me...
It hurts!
Don't thrust it into my ass!
Hey! Don't stop stroking me.
S-st...
Stop.
Stop cumming inside me.
Don't...
Leave me alone already...
Isn't your pussy used to this by now?
There's no way that's true!
What if I thrust it to here?
No, not there...
I'm feeling weak...
If you're too loud,
you'll be heard by those shmucks down there.
No.
That's..
You're thrusting...
You're thrusting in there again...
Hey, don't just cum all by yourself.
But...
Stop.
Don't take pictures!
You can't take pictures here!
Why? Can't face Yoshiyuki this way!
I wonder what will happen if I show these pictures to him.
St-st...
Please don't do that!
I'm gonna cum again.
I don't want anymore.
Stop this...
Don't cum...
No more!
No!
He came inside me again.
I already said that it wasn't safe today.
So many times, over and over...
I'm going to get pregnant.
This is...
terrible.
This is terrible!