What are you doing?
This? I am trying to save you, Miura-sensei.
I'm going to give you better control over your pleasure sensations.
No, don't!
Sensei!
Don't fondle my breasts, sensei!
So, if you want me to save you,
then I have every right to state my terms and conditions for it.
No, stop...
Don't.
Shiori-sensei.
I'm sure you won't regret this.
That I guarantee.
Stop.
Please stop.
Sensei.
If you touch me there...
Shiorj-sensei, you're really cute.
Please stop.
Don't continue this any further.
Please, let me be already!
No, no!
Oh wow, this is really something.
It feels even tighter and better than I imagined!
Stop this, sensei.
We're in a classroom.
Pull it out.
This is...
No...
That is...
I already...
I already have a boyfriend!
Wanna. SpartanSex Spermax!!!
Cum inside, aphrodisiac, boy as a girl, and Gestaltzerfall chapter
No!
Please stop!
This is...
Stop.
I beg of you please don't watch!
Shut up will you?
Sensei, if you don't comply with what I tell you,
we're going to show this to your boyfriend.
Hey sensei, why don't you try this on?
Shiori-sensei, next is this PE uniform.
As for me, I want this...a naked apron.
There, you've hit the spot.
You do this regularly for your boyfriend, right?
Please don't say that...
There, that feels good.
This-is embarrassing.
Please no...
Let me be already!
No!
Shiori-sensei, your pussy seems to be wet already.
How lewd.
No!
Don't thrust it in too intensely.
Oh no...
No...
This feels great.
I'm going to cum now.
Not inside, not inside!
It's entering me.
This thick, and warm thing...
Stop.
Stop this already.
Wow, she's wrapping me real tight.
No!
Don't!
It's all wet, this is the best!
Keep it up!
This feels good, Shiori-sensei.
Oh crap, I can't hold it in any longer, sensei.
Not inside again.
Don't, I'm going to get pregnant.
Sensei, I'm cumming!
No!
No, please stop.
You say that, but your pussy is getting wet.
My insides are getting opened up.
I can't keep it in anymore.
Shiori-chan, I'm gonna cum.
Semen is going to flow into my pussy again.
I'm cumming!
I'm going to get pregnant!
Shiori-chan, that feels good.
Doing this is...
Your mouth pussy also feels great!
Shiori-sensei, you're holding it really good.
Oh no, I'll get aroused if you keep doing that.
I'm at my limit already.
I'm going to cum.
Me too, I can't hold it in anymore.
I'm going to cum too.
Oh no...
Man, that felt really great.
Cosplaying Shiori-chan sure is the best.
Now Shiori-chan is under our bidding.
Now then, let's proceed to our next step.
Why did you call me out here to this place?
Why you ask?
Since you have been raped so much by us,
I've prepared a special even just for you.
Special? You want...
Hey, come on here already!
Onii-chan!
The reunion that you have been dearly waiting for.
Nagisa-chan?
What's...
...with that outfit?
And why are you here?
This is...
As to why Nagisa is here.
Why don't you listen to this story first.
She went away due to her father's debt.
And decided to come ask for your help, despite
being unsure of what that could accomplish.
But you're supposed to have been gone somewhere.
That's when she tried to investigate and collect info.
Until she finally found herself at Kengou Academy.
There, she infiltrated the campus and continued
her investigation disguised as a guy.
So it is my fault that you're...
That's right, it's all your fault.
You've just thrown your innocent cousin into this situation.
Stop!
Please, no further!
Kubozuka-kun, don't tell me you've done something to her?
I haven't done anything to her.
She's still the pure and perfect virgin that she can be.
Ain't that right, Nagisa?
And now, you're going to have sex with her here.
With that you'll be the subject of envy amongst
boys for taking the cute Nagisa-chan's virginity.
They would probably even accept you.
Hey, what are you saying?
You don't like it, Yoshiyuki?
If you're not gonna do it,
then we're going to do it in front of you.
What are you saying, Kubozuka-kun?
Wait, don't I have a say in this?
So, you want to be raped by us instead
of having sex with your Onii-chan?
That's not what I meant.
We're cousins.
And that's exactly why it's arousing, right?
So, what are you going to do, Yoshiyuki?
Okay.
Onii-chan!
This is embarrassing.
Nagisa-chan.
No...onii-chan!
Hey Yoshiyuki!
How long are you just going to rub it like that?
Just be one with her already!
Even Nagisa is already waiting for it.
No...don't...
Nagisa-chan!
Onii-chan!
I'm sorry, I've just taken your precious virginity.
Onii-chan.
Eh? Huh?
You're a virgin, right? No...
Onii-chan, don't look there!
Nagisa-chan.
Onii-chan.
I'm sorry.
Nagisa-chan, your pussy is really wet mine goes all the way in!
The cross-dressing guy violates the cross-dressing girl...
Yoshiyuki, I somehow feel especially horny,
from this really perverted scene.
Nagisa-chan, your pussy is getting even wetter.
It feels good.
Onii-chan!
Oh no, don't...
If you keep on thrusting in and out like that...
Nagisa-chan, could it be...
Nagisa-chan, so you're really...
No... Onii-chan please don't ask me...
It's embarrassing.
Don't look at me!
Oh no...
If you keep moving intensely like that...
What am I to do?
I'm...
Nagisa-chan, sorry for making you suffer like this.
But it feels good, and I'm about to cum.
I can feel it too.
This is embarrassing...
Please don't look down on me.
I'm about to cum.
I'm cummmg.
Nagisa-chan!
Me too, it's about to burst out!
Onii-chan!
I'm absolutely... It's embarrassing...
Nagisa-chan...
Nagisa, you really are very cute.
Stop this.
Onii-chan is watching us.
Onii-chan is watching us!
I am letting him watch, you know!
I'll show him that you are mine!
Don't do that!
Stop this, Kubozuka-kun!
She doesn't want to do it!
Hey, just keep still there Yoshiyuki.
As a man, you have to stay silent there,
in order to keep your end of the bargain for doing it earlier.
No!
Don't rub it on me!
Don't!
Oh, so instead of rubbing,
you want this instead?
Stop this already, Kubozuka-kun.
If you want to harass someone, then do it to me instead!
Don't hurt Nagisa-chan!
I'm not doing anything terrible to her, you know.
Right, Nagisa?
I'm actually doing something that feels good.
Pull it out immediately.
I'm all exposed.
Oh no, not that intensely!
Yoshiyuki, watch this closely.
This woman here, cries in ecstasy when she is raped just like this!
No!
Onii-chan, don't look!
Nagisa-chan!
oh?
Hey, Nagisa.
Your dear Onii-chan is having a boner
while watching you get violated.
Onii-chan, no...
I don't want this!
Don't make it big.
This is embarrassing.
I'm...
Nagisa-chan...
Idiot!
I hate you!
Stop this already!
Hey, Yoshiyuki, jack off for me will you?
If you don't, I'm gonna cum inside her!
No, stop.
No cumming inside!
Don't cum inside me!
Now, jack off as you watch your cousin here.
No...
No, Onii-chan...
Please don't do this...
It feels great, right?
Being violated like this, while being watched by your cousin,
even getting the truth about your virginity leaked out.
You're getting horny about it now, right?
Don't say that.
Oh no, I'm getting horny.
I'm going to lose it.
Nagisa-chan, it feels good.
This is the best, Nagisa.
I'm about to cum!
Don't!
Here I go!
Nagisa-chan, sorry, I'm about to cum too!
Oops, I just came inside.
You really came inside me...
You idiot...
Umm...You're Aki-neechan, right?
Nagisa...
Wait, you're Nagisa?
Yes, it's me.
Long time no see!
Y-yeah, you seem fine, but...
What's with that outfit?
Ah, this?
Well, actually...
l-ls that true?
Onii-chan wants to meet you too!
So, can you come with me today?
Yes, of course.
That's good.
Follow me then.
Onii-chan will surely be happy.
Yokkun.
I can now meet Yokkun...
I can finally.
Nagisa, where is this?
Welcome, welcome!
Nagisa, what's the meaning of this?
Aki-neechan, I'm sorry.
can't hold myself anymore.
What are you...
What do you think this is?
What's that?
This medicine is said to make "it" all the more pleasurable.
Well, even If It does wear off,
you'll come out as a fallen woman already.
Now then, let's introduce our special quest.
This is Hiura Shiori-sensei, a student teacher at our school.
What is the meaning of this Kubozuka-kun?
Basically, you three fair ladies are about to be one with our cocks.
That's the only reason why we called you all here.
Understood ladies?
Please, give me my reward already.
I'm at my limit already.
Nagisa...?
Okay, okay, good girl.
You've indeed done quite well.
I'm going to give it to you now.
We'll be injecting these into you two next.
No, stop!
Kubozuka-kun,you...!
Woopsie.
Here we go.
Maguro-chan, Shiori-chan.
No need to worry.
It's very effective.
In fact, its effect happens almost instantaneously.
I can feel your cock rubbing hard inside my pussy.
Your pussy and my cock are now connected.
Take this, and this!
Stop, don't do it intensely.
No...
I guess you can't even be yourself after taking that drug.
My body is...
The inside of my pussy is...
I'm getting horny.
Shiori-chan, you're really getting horny there.
It's really squeezing me in.
Oh no...
Don't get too intense already from the start.
This feels great.
It's all wet, and it's the best!
No...
Hey, hey Nagisa.
Open up some more.
Let me rub this into you more!
No...
Oh man, it seems her mind is really muddled.
Yes...
More.
There, expose your masochism here!
It feels good.
There, that feels great.
I think I'm about to cum already.
No.
Please, we can't do this...
Don't...
If you keep that intensity up...
Your cock...
It feels great.
My pussy Is overflowing!
Oh no...
This thick cock is inside me.
Inside me.
It feels good.
Yes.
I'm about to cum too.
This feels good.
I can't hold it in any longer.
Here, take my cum!
Okay, me too.
Me too!
I can feel it.
I feel horny.
This feeling.
This sensation...
I never thought that cocks could feel this great.
Oh wow.
This cock is amazing.
Does it feel good my sex pig?
Yes.
Do it!
Do it more!
No...
I'm about to lose myself.
You won't lose yourself.
Because this is the real you!
This cock is piercing right through me.
Do it more.
Thrust this big and strong cock into me more.
Hey, Shiori-sensei.
Which is better, mine or your boyfriends?
This one is better.
Release it.
Release it in me!
I'm cumming!
I'm about to cum!
Here I go!
That felt really good.
My body is itching for it, and I can no longer move.
Master, let's do our next session quickly.
Let's do it.
Wow, the power of aphrodisiacs are really something.
Okay, here we go then.
It's piercing me.
It's going right through to my deep parts.
Your cock is rubbing me.
And it enters even deeper inside.
This is too amazing.
Your cock inside my womb...
I can't take this anymore.
Do my pussy more and more!
This feels good.
It feels the best.
This is the best!
Your cock...
I'm about to cum.
Now, you beautiful ladies have now become one with our cocks.
A perfect 3-on-3, I guess?