Amazing... Onii-chan... Onii-chan...!
Manami you're so good!
Manami... Manami...!
I... I'm cumming!!
Fansubbed by http://shin-hentai.com *X-Death
I can't believe that...
It's an Incest...
Onii-chan! I love you... so much...!
No... I'm cummming again...!
That Kazuhisa... watching this kind of video...
but... It's not so bad...
No way... What's this strange feeling...
Akane-san...?
What are you doing inside my room...?
Welcome back, Ba-Kazuhisa.
"Welcome back" my ass!
No matter where you look, you've an obsession for Loli-Imouto!
You're really a pervert!
Not like this!
It's cute, Manami.
It's embarassing!!
"It's embarassing!!"
Damn you...!
AKANE!!
Give me the remote!!
Not a chance!
If you want it, you've to earn it!
Damn it!
Better luck next time!
Try in a hundred years!
That's right! The TV buttons!
It's fine... Let's watch it together!
Akane-san...
Let me go now...!
The rope is to tight...!
These movie scenes are really lame!
She really has a huge breast though!
You do too...!
Say... Do you always watch this kind of movies alone?
Shut up!
If you've time to be watching this, you should be able to find at least one girlfriend!
Shut up!!
That's why you'll always be a virgin...
O... ni-chan...
I said, SHUT UP!!
Whoa... You're really pissed off!
How scary!
Alright! I'll stop bothering you!
Take it easy!
Wh... What are you doing!?
Seriously...?
Wait... Calm down...! Kazuhisa...!
Crap...!
He's gone crazy!
Hey... What are you...
His tongue...
This isn't really good... We're siblings...
I'm even... cause of that film...
This is not good!
If it goes on like this, this is gonna get dangerous...
Knock it off already! Idiot!
Do you realize what you're doing!?
Hey...! Listen to me...
No! I'm really feeling it...
Hey... Wait!
Hey... Stop that!
This is... Akane's...
Don't look...!
Not there!!
N... No...! Stop!
Is it here? or It's here?
Stop... that...!
We're... siblings...! Idiot!
Even though you said were siblings...
There's no problem.
Since... we don't have any... blood relation...!
You're talking nonsense...!
Kazuhisa... is inside me...!
I can't... this hard and thick...!
This awesome... Akane...!
Whoa!! They're huge!
S... Stop staring...! Idiot!
No!
No! Don't move...!
How is it, Akane? I'm not a virgin anymore!
What are you talking...? I'm not even cumming yet...
And it doesn't feel good at all...
Damn!! You're still making fun of me!
So... How is it...!?
Still no good...
Then, why it's gripping me tightly...?
No... It's not...!
Whoa... from this position, I can see everything... Akane's sexy ass!!
Are you embarrassed!?
It feels good... Akane's inside...!
That sort of...!
Whoa...! What's wrong Akane...? It feels good, doesn't it...?
It feels good, isn't...? My thing...
Tell me... If it feels good...!
No... No way...!
No...? If you don't, I'll stop...!
No!
What's that "No" for!?
Are you cumming...? or are you in ecstasy...?
Hurry up and say it!
Say "Onii-chan dick feels so good"...
No more...
O... Onii-chan!!
Forgive me...
Onii-chan!! Forgive me...
AKANE!!
I... I'm going to cum...
S... So good!! I'm going to cum...
Onii-chan... You're making Akane...
You're making me cum with your dick...
I'm... cummming...!!
AKANE!!
ONII-CHAN!!
What did you say?
If you want it, beg for it!
Beat me, please!!
Hey, beg more properly...!
I... I'm back...
Ba-Kazuhisa...
It's obvious you're trying to train me! Ba-Kazuhisa!!
Looks good on you!
It... It's Warm...
They're meat buns...
They're so soft...
A meat bun fouton... It's feels good!
But I don't really like meat buns...
[Ane-Imouto]
It... It's tits...
So soft...
this tits...
Wake up... Yasuda!
I... I'm so sorry!!
What the hell are you dreaming about... Yasuda!?
Yumiko-san!
Yeah.
N... Now I remember...
I think... the party got messed up by Yumiko-san.
She's already drunk...
So I carried her back on my shoulders...
Uhm...
Take some water...
Th... Thanks!
Give me that!
Geez... Onee-chan!!
Yumiko-san...
Yumiko-san!! Th... That person is watching us!
Don't worry!
She's my little sister Aki-chan.
I'm her little sister... Nice to meet you!
Onii-chan!
O-NI-I-CHAN, you say...
I want you to make her lose her virginity!
Yasuda-kun!
Wh... What are you saying!?
Wai... Yumiko-san!
Are you ready, Aki-chan?
Take a close look!
This is how you do a deep kiss...
Onee-chan...
Onii-chan Penis... It's kinda weird...
I saw father's during bath... It's totaly different...
That's called Pseudo-phimosis.
Pseudo-phimo...
It means he has a really special dick!
Th... That is...
Now kiss the tip...
And then, put it in your mouth...
Gently Aki-chan...
Onee-chan!
The foreskin has retracted...
Next, start licking it!
It has a weird smell...
Don't worry!
You'll enjoy it gradually.
After that, start sucking it! Akane!
Does it feels good? Yasuda-kun!?
It... It feels good!
Not only his dick Aki-chan... You should lick his nipples too...
It's time for you to feel pleasures too, Aki-chan!?
Oh? I wonder what's this slimy...
Such a huge stain on your panties just for sucking dick...
Yu... Yumiko-san...?
Can you just shut up your mouth, Yasuda...
Onee-chan!
O... Onee-chan... Stop...
Even if you touch that... It wont go big...
But it's already big...
There... It feels good, doesn't it?
Look it's big like a Penis...
Aki-chan your place is dripping out your juice... It's saying "I want a Penis"...
No more... Onee-chan...
Then, lets start...
Onee-chan... It won't fit...
Don't worry! It's already wet...
In this position it shouldn't hurt at all...
So, Aki-chan...
O... Onii-chan... I want your dick to make me a woman... Onii-chan...!
It's in... his dick...
How do you like your first dick... Aki-chan?
I don't know...
Does it hurt...?
It's my intention to put the Penis there...
Well then, you can start now, Yasuda...!
Okay... Here I come, Aki-chan...
It... It feels so good... Aki-chan!
Me too... Yasuda-kun...!
Here... Stop looking at it...
Yes... Right there!
Right there... in my clitoris...!
It's so good... My clitoris feels so good...
Aki-chan! Don't... Don't pull my nipples...
Onee-chan... Aki place feels so hot...
Aki-chan... Onee-chan feels so hot too...
The penis feels so good...
I love it!
You can't, so suddenly...
I couldn't stop it... I licked your pussy so much...
T.. There...
With this our juices will blend...
Onee-chan and Aki-chan juices are blending...
Next do it like this, please... Yasuda-kun...!
Listen Yasuda-kun... Our pussy feels so hot...
Onii-chan!! Onee-chan!!
Yu... Yumiko-san!! Aki-chan!!
Are you cumming? You are cumming, right?
It's okay... Cum...!
ONEE-CHAN!!
AKI-CHAN!!
I... I see...
Aki-chan has found a boyfriend...
She told me "It's thanks to Onii-chan that I was able to ask him out".
Oh, I see...
Onee-chan! Onii-chan!
You know...
My boyfriend...
He doesn't have the Phimosis in his Penis like you do Onii-chan!
I'm... a big Phimosis-Dick...
You're the best! Aki!
Huh? What's wrong Onii-chan?