Girls Changing Room
There's no other place but here!
Th-This place is!
Awesome! I've always wanted to get in her at least onc...
W-Wait!
Th-This isn't good!
I can't just enter in here!
It's okay.
Almost every club member's already finished
their business in here at this hour.
Shower Room
Besides,
this room right here has a pretty tight.
Huh? Someone else is inside.
I can hear voices in there.
Shiho-chin should have already gone home by now.
Wh-Why are you opening the door?!
I'm still right here, you know!
Shiho-chin?
O-Oh! It's you, Saki!
It's quite rare for you to head by the shower at this time
I could say the same about you.
You sure are taking your time to shower today.
Th-There's really someone else!
Well, I think I want to take a nice shower.
I-I see.
Yup! I'll be taking my shower now, then.
N-Now's my chance.
I'm going to scream if you ever try to run away.
I can't let you off now that we're this far already!
Come on, over here.
W-We can't do it right beside her!
She'll definitely notice!
She'll hear the noises and our voices!
It's okay!
If you use the shower like this,
as long is it's not too loud, no one will
ever notice it on the other side.
Shiho-chin is also quite thick-headed, you know.
Besides,
you're the one who made the first move earlier.
So I'm going to have you take responsibility for this as a man.
Whoa, what the heck is this?
It's far too limp.
Can't be helped, then.
We did happen to have worked ourselves
out there on such a short notice.
I'll have to work harder for its warm up, then.
And it looks kind of cute.
It's gotten stiff.
I'll speed it up now, then.
Okie-dokie.
He's starting to get quite stiff already.
It's steadily warming up, I see.
All that's left for me to do is to match the timing
to prevent it from twitching out of control.
If you keep on sucking it like that I'll!
And stop!
Wh-Why?
It really does look great.
The look of it just about to burst is perfect.
This is payback from earlier.
No way.
Just kidding!
Just thinking that this dick is about to pump everything
inside me makes me totally horny!
Weill then,
this is the main game.
Warm up is finished already, right?
For both of us I mean.
Okay, ready.
Position.
Go!
I just put it in and I already came!
But...
I'm not satisfied just yet!
Sa-Saki-san!
Please do it a bit more gently!
Does it feel hard for you?
It feels very good for me, though.
Sorry about earlier.
We were left hanging earlier so now I just can't stop.
Also, today I'm.
A lot lot more into this than usual!
He's about to cum already.
His thing is going wild inside me.
It's alright.
Just cum.
I'm going to cum really soon!
I can't stop myself.
He's about to cum inside me.
And I'm cumming along with him!
A-Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
As I thought, the intensive of his squirts are
far stronger whenever it gets built up first.
Forget my pussy, I thought my womb was about to melt.
H-Huh?
Even after cumming that strongly?
What in the world is this?
Are you too aroused?
It's far more lively than usual.
Well, that sports swimsuit just turned me on so much.
Oh.
This sports swimsuit did?!
N-No, I mean.
You also aroused me just as much, Saki-san.
Me too?
I-I'm sorry!
You're the one that turned me on!
Oh come on.
Jeez,
you're always so insensitive at times like these.
I'll let it slip, because it happens regularly, anyway.
In exchange though,
you'll have to work harder, Toshi-kun.
I'm not quite satisfied just yet, you know.
Or so I said.
I-I'll try my best!
Honestly, he's all over the place.
But, if he ever ends this too quickly after showing off,
I, as the girl, will feel let down!
Y-You're fondling me, too?
And here I thought he was about to run
away from all of this a while ago.
He's starting to become bolder by the second.
Is this due to my swimsuit too?
Th-This kind of feels complicated.
Hey, j-just wait!
Th-That spot right now is!
I'm cumming. It feels like I'm about to cum already!
Oh yeah.
I remember Toshi-kun was the type of guy to do it like this.
Y-You can't rub your dick inside while playing with my clit too!
It's okay.
I'm about to.
Well I'm not!
I'm... about to.
I'm about to cum!
He's really such a...
terrible guy.
H-How can you cum so much like that
even though it's our second round?
And it's still completely aroused.
This is definitely the swimsuit effect.
I just can't hold myself back.
So it really was about the swimsuit after all?
Really.
He's such a terrible guy.
I'm really loving you now.
Your dick is really hitting all of my soft spots,
as it rubs hard deep inside me.
But aren't you the one who's pushing it all the way inside?
You're the man, so don't worry about those details!
True...
I'm the one who moves and pushes it inside and out,
so I guess, I'm the one making it hit?
Shiho-san, I'm... I'm about to!
Ah, whatever.
It's okay.
But...
We usually go all the way if we're about to cum, right?
Y-Yes!
I'm sorry!
Here it comes!
Such thickness.
You're also able to finish the entire
normal training course nowadays.
I guess your stamina's built up for this as well, eh.
Th-Thank you very much.
It's making strands on my hands.
Jeez, please give me a break already.
I don't want to be constantly dragged into this room anymore.
It'd be bad if someone sees us.
You say that,
but you did it way more vigorously earlier than usual.
W-Well, even I... when asked to do it.
I just can't stop.
Then there's absolutely no problem!
We both like this anyway.
Well, I kind of wanted it to be more normal.
Or, more wholesome, I guess.
H-Huh? Oh yeah.
Have we gone out to meet somewhere else other than in campus?
Oh, now that you mention it... we haven't.
Th-Then, would you like to go out with
me to watch movies this weekend?
Movies?
If you don't like movies, th-then... we could go shopping instead.
I-Is it a bother for you?
No, not at all.
I don't really have any other plans this weekend.
Anyway, this sure is the first time.
The first time for you to actively ask me out.
Something wrong all of a sudden?
W-Well...
When I realized I haven't seen you in your casual wear,
I kind of just really wanted to see it.
Casual wear, huh.
Now I'm really looking forward to this.
I'm already excited!
I don't have anything to wear for the occasion!
Huh?
I don't have anything else to wear other than my jerseys,
or my uniform.
I don't think wearing one is bad at all.
You've nothing to lose on your jerseys, anyway.
That's not the problem!
Anyway, I beg of you!
Lend me some of your clothes!
Something cute, please!
I don't have any clothes that can fit you, you know!
Oh, that's right!
I do have one.
Something that might just fit you.
I'll lend it to you, then.
Th-Thanks.
Wh-What's what that smirk?
I'm feeling uneasy about this.
What's up with that girl?
She's hot.
Aren't her clothes small?
A model perhaps?
Wh-What's happening?
Is there a photoshoot around or something?
Let's ask for an autograph.
She sure is tall.
Oh my.
She's getting more attention by the second.
People are coming over one by one.
She already stands out by default, so
when paired with those clothes.
You knew this was going to happen when you lent her that?
Of course.
What are you getting a boner for in this situation?!
When I saw you wearing that, it just kind of.
I-Idiot!
What the hell are you saying in this place?!
She ran away.
Of course she would.
Sh-Shiho-san.
N-Not in this place.
Someone will see us here!
Jeez.
Why am I doing this immediately on our first date?
But, this sure is strange.
He should have finished already by now.
Then just cum and make it limp already!
I should have, but...
I just feel too nervous being in here that I can't cum!
Oh come on.
Boys sure like to make things complicated.
On top of that, it's starting to get difficult
for me as well as I keep doing this.
If it's come to this then.
There's no other way!
Before I become unable to resist...
I'll take it all in!
Th-This intensity!
Just cum already dammit!
Besides, though I haven't said it yet,
I've become so attached to your dick,
that even just sucking it makes me totally horny.
I need to make sure I don't suck too deep.
Shiho-san, I really!
I really can't hold back anymore!
Wait, just wait!
If I suck it this deeply...
I'll... I'll get too horny.
I-I'm cumming.
Wait... no way!
His hot stuff,
Is getting pumped directly in to my throat.
I never thought I'd cum from a blowjob in a place like this!
On top of that,
it's still stiff!
I'm done for.
If this keeps up, I'll eventually.
Shiho-san!
Th-This is bad!
This time, I'll be the one to do it to you.
Idiot! Do you realize where we are right now?
We're at a park! At-a-park!
Once this starts, nothing could ever stop it!
Because, while you were sucking me,
you eventually became like this!
H-He knew!
That's why this time, I'll be the one to.
Forget about the explanations!
I'm still sensitive due to having cummed earlier.
If he tries to put that in me now.
I-I'm really going to lose it!
And... instantly cum.
I just put it in, but it's already throbbing and twitching all over.
It's amazing!
Come on, don't be so rough.
Stop!
I really can't!
You don't really hold back when you're
the one who starts moving, huh.
But... well.
Shiho-san.
I'm... I'm again going to!
This isn't some sort of harassment, right?
Also, he matched up the pacing with me again like normal.
Pumping it all at the very end!
Really.
You really do know when and where.
Wait, what are you doing?
Pushing your hips again like that.
I'm...
What?
I'll be sure to do it well like always.
Wait, you don't have to push yourself too much!
Today let's just!
No good. My body won't listen to me.
It's alright.
I can still do it!
My womb's about to get torn apart!
This can't be.
For me to get fucked this far.
I just can't stop anymore!
Jeez.
Why... did it ever become like this?
Anyway, you think those two are okay?
They're okay!
There aren't many noobs out there
who can keep up with Shiho-chan.
You're right!
Huh? Those voices.
By the way,
why did you have such revealing clothes?
Oh, those are my sister's.
She said she used those for work.
Oh, if it's your sister, then I guess those clothes would "fit".
For work, huh.
A cat's ears headband actually comes with it.
How about we get her to wear it next time?
Oh, that's good! I definitely would want to!
Along with that,
a cute pantie is also good.
Cat ears headband, you say?
H-Huh? Shiho-chin?!
Wh-Why are you here?
Shiho-chin, you reek of squid!
Shut yer mouth!