I'll be your slave and have sex with you 02
Girls' Changing Room
It's gotta be here.
Here?!
Hell yeah, I've always wanted to come he...
Wait no!
I shouldn't be here!
It's fine! Nobody is usually around at this time.
Shower Room
This room is sound proof too, so...
Huh? Someone's still here?
I hear a voice.
Shiho-chin should be one by now though...
W-Why are you opening it? They'll see me!
Shiho-chin?
Oh, Saki?
Wow, for you to be at the showers,
what are you doing here?
I-I could say the same!
Usually you go straight home after showering.
There's totally someone here!
Oh, um... I was thinking maybe a shower
here every now and then would be good.
Oh, I see.
Okay, I'm going to take a shower too.
This is my chance to run!
If you try to run, I'll scream.
We've come this far, you're not getting away!
Come on, come here.
We can't do this next to her!
She'll definitely be able to hear us!
Don't worry so much.
If we turn on the shower, like this...
As long as we keep our voices low,
no one will be able to hear us.
Shiho-chin is pretty dense, too.
Anyway, you're the one who came on to me first,
so man up and take responsibility.
What the hell? You're so limp!
Oh, well. They say that exercising without
warming up is how accidents happen.
So, I guess I'll have to warm this up first.
It looks so cute.
It's gotten so hard already!
Let's go a bit faster.
Good, good! He's ready hard now.
Looks like we're good to go.
Now, all that's left is to make sure that I time this right.
If you keep sucking my dick like that, I'm gonna...
Time to stop!
W-Why?
I love seeing it twitch like it's about to explode.
This is punishment for before.
Oh, come on!
I'm just kidding!
Just thinking about how he's going to cum
inside me makes me shiver in anticipation!
And with that...
Here's the main dish.
We're both done warming up, right?
So, on your marks...
Get set...
Go!
I only just put it in, but I came!
B-But...
This isn't even close to enough!
S-Saki, why don't you go a little slower?
Is it tough for you?
It feels good for me, though.
Sorry, but I'm so turned on I can't stop moving my hips!
That, and you're going even deeper inside than usual!
He was already on the verge of cumming.
I can feel you twitching inside me!
You can cum whenever you want!
I'm going to cum soon too!
I want it now! Cum inside me!
I'm cumming!!
Y-You okay?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Just as I thought, stored-up cum being
released has a different feel to it.
Forget about cumming inside me,
he almost came in my womb!
H-Huh?!
Even after cumming that much?!
What the?! He's even harder than usual...
Seeing you in your swimsuit really turns me on...
The swimsuit?!
I-I mean, you do too.
I do too?!
Sorry, I mean, you turn me on too!
Sheesh, seriously?
You never had enough subtlety when it came to this.
I'm used to it, so I'll let it slide, but...
This time, you do the work, okay?
I'm not satisfied yet.
Just kidding.
I'll do my best!
Actually, my legs are pretty tired after that,
but I can't tell him I'm done after he
just showed me his rock hard cock!
I can't tell him that, can I?!
You're finally doing this?
You were being such a pussy until now!
He's becoming more and more aggressive.
I-Is this because of the swimsuit?
I-I'm breaking...
Wait! Don't touch that...
He's rubbing my clit!
I almost forgot. He's this kind of guy.
You can't fuck me and rub my clit!
It's fine, I'm about to cum.
I'm not fine, though!
I'm cumming!
He's such a horrible guy.
How can you cum so much on your second go?
You're still so hard too.
Yeah, it must really be the swimsuit.
It just keeps turning me on!
Is it really because of the swimsuit?
He's really such a horrible guy.
Girls' Changing Room
Really, you are just so...
You keep hitting my weak spots!
You're grinding it all the way into my stomach!
Are you sure you're not doing that yourself?
If you're a man, don't sweat the small stuff!
Well, to be precise...
I've been moving myself, so...
I've been making him hit my weak spots all along.
Sh-Shiho-san, I'm gonna...
It doesn't matter either way.
Good, but this is the last spurt, right? Go all out!
Yes! Sorry!
It's here!
Look at how much you came!
You've cum over the quota I set for you.
I guess you've been building up your stamina.
Thank you very much.
Oh, this is great.
Please stop dragging me here all the time.
It'd be really bad if people find out.
You say that, but you seemed happier
than usual to be here today.
W-Well, if I get turned on... It's hard to get it down.
So there's no problem since it's consensual.
No, you see, I'd rather do this more normally, or healthily...
Now that I think about it...
Have we ever hung out outside of school?
Now that I think about it, not once.
Then how about you and I go see a
movie this weekend or something?
A movie?
If you don't want to see a movie,
we could go shopping instead...
Would it be... inconvenient?
Nope, not at all. I didn't have any
plans this weekend anyway.
But hey, you taking the lead to
invite me out is a first, isn't it?
Something wrong?
Well, I was just thinking that I've never
seen you in your own clothes,
and then I started to really want to see you in them.
My own clothes?
I'm really excited. I can't wait!
I don't have any clothes!
I only have tracksuits and my school uniform!
There's nothing wrong with wearing a tracksuit.
I'm not talking about whether there is
or isn't something wrong with them!
Please, just lend me some cute clothes!
I don't have any clothes that'd fit you.
Oh wait, I have one outfit that might.
I'll give you that.
Th-Thanks...
What's she laughing about? I have a bad feeling...
What's up with her?
What a sexy body.
Aren't her clothes a bit small?
Is she a model?
W-What?
Is she doing a photo shoot?
I'm taking a picture.
She's so tall!
Oh wow, she's getting so much attention.
She's attracting so many people.
She'd stand out even without those
clothes, but with them on...
Did you lend her those clothes because
you knew this would happen?
Hell yeah.
Why are you getting hard in a place like this?!
W-Well, looking at you, it just kinda...
Y-You idiot, why here?!
She ran away.
Yeah, I would too.
Teisou Public Park
Sh-Shiho-san, we can't do this here!
People will definitely see us!
Jeez, why are we doing something like this on our first date?
That aside, usually he would've cum by now...
Then just hurry up and cum so it's small again!
I-I'm trying, but in a place like this, I'm so
nervous that I can't even if I want to!
Jeez, guys are really a handful.
Now that we're doing this, I'm getting turned on too.
If it's like this...
I'll just have to do it!
I'll make him cum before I get too horny!
If you're so rough, I'll...
Just, cum already!
I never told you, but I'm so used to your dick
that I can cum just from sucking on it.
I need to be sure not to put it too deep in my mouth...
Sh-Shiho-san, I'm really gonna...
I can't take it anymore!
W-Wait!!
If I take it so deep, I'm gonna get really turned on!
I'm gonna cum...
Wai... You're kidding!!
It's so hot and it's going straight down my throat.
I can't believe that he came in my mouth
and made me cum at a park!
He came so much too. At least now we can go...
Shiho-san!
Crap!
Now I'll do you!
You idiot! Do you know where we are?!
We're in the park! A public park!
Now that he's like this, he won't listen to me at all.
But look at you! While you were
sucking me off you got like this!
H-He knew!
That's why this time I'll do you!
You don't have to do that for me!
I just came and we're already going for
round 2?! If he puts that in now, I'll...
I'll cum!!
I only just put my dick in, but your
pussy is twitching like crazy!
Slow down, then!
Wait, don't...
Seriously, you don't hold back when you're horny.
But, well...
Shiho-san... I'm gonna, I'm gonna...
I guess I don't hate it when he's like this.
Just like always, he's so good at timing our orgasms!
You really are the best.
Hey, wait. What are you doing, moving your hips?
My quota...
I need to cum enough to make the quota!
You don't have to try so hard to do that today!
No, I can't fight back anymore, I feel so weak!
I'll be fine! I can still keep going!
My womb's gonna break!
Shit, if he keeps fucking me this hard...
I won't be able to stop cumming!!
Jeez...
H-How'd it end up like this?
I wonder if those two are okay?
I'm sure they are.
Shiho's fast, so I doubt any of those people
crowding around her could catch up.
Yeah, good point.
Wait, is that...
By the way, why did you have those clothes?
Oh, those are my big sister's.
She said she uses it for work.
Your big sister? No wonder it fit
her. But she uses it for work?
Truth is, they come with cat ears too.
We should put them on Shiho next time!
I like that! How about we give her some cute panties too?
Give cat ears to who?
Oh, what? Shiho-chin?
Why are you here?
Shiho-chin, you stink!
Shut the hell up!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: bis | punk4real
encoder: punk4real