It's been one month since I moved here.
I just came here to return this circular notice and yet
I'm getting my dick sucked by some random girl.
Pre-cum tastes so good.
Moving
Center
One month earlier, right before my child
was due to be born, I moved into this apartment.
Wow, this is such a nice place.
So this'll be our home from now on?
Yep.
Oh, it was today?
Oh, hi there.
We'll be in your care.
Sure!
Hi, I'm the landlady of these apartments.
Who's that girl behind you?
This girl is the daughter of a resident here.
Her name's Fuu-chan.
Hello.
Oh? What's going on?
New people?
Oh my.
I'm Morioka.
I'm his wife, Yukiko.
I'm Ikushima Misako. Ask us anything.
Let's have a welcoming party now that you're here!
Let's drink a lot!
I-I'm pregnant, so...
What? That's no fun!
– Okay, make that juice, then!
– Surrounded by very kind neighbors,
we took the first step towards our new, happy life here.
– Okay, make that juice, then!
– Surrounded by very kind neighbors,
we took the first step towards our new, happy life here.
I'm a sexaholic!
Okay, dear. I'll see you later.
Okay, be careful.
Just another normal day...
Hm? Is your wife going somewhere?
Oh, Ikushima-san?
Yeah, she's doing some shopping.
Oh? I see.
Here's your circular notice.
Oh, thanks.
Circular Lewd Notice?
What the heck is this? Did they mess up?
Meet in the communal area.
Bring your body... What is this?
Are they playing a joke on us
because we're newlyweds?
For now I guess I'll just return it to the communal area.
Yes? Oh, Mizuyama-san?
Hi, landlady.
I came to return the circular notice.
Oh, thank you. Come on in.
Oh my god, my pussy feels so good!
My pussy feels amazing!
Let it drink your cum!
It's so hot!
What's going on?
More! Give me more!
Give it to me!
Wha...
What's going on here?!
– Oh my god, it's so good! I'm in heaven!
– Wait, that's my heighbor...
– Harder!
Welcome to the communal area, Mizuyama-san.
I welcome you.
L-Landlady... What's going on here?
Huh? Did you not read the circular lewd notice?
No, I skimmed it...
As you can see, this room is where everyone
shares their bodies with one another.
You're serious?
Yes, I am. People who want dicks get dicks
and people who want pussy can get pussy here.
Even just wanting nipples is fine.
Even pee or poop. All that matters is that if you
want something, you give something in return.
Oh, but money's off limits.
Usually, people just have sex like they're doing now.
But isn't that adultery?
Here's the most important part of this.
Everything that happens in that room stays in there.
None of us are cheating or committing adultery.
We're just trying to fulfill our sexual desires.
None of the people here have any intention
of ruining someone else's family.
You know that the couple next door
participates in this too, right?
But I have a wife.
Yes, she's a wonderful woman. But since she's pregnant,
you've been getting pretty backed up, haven't you?
W-Well...
Your cum is building up?
Y-You're...
Oh, Fuu-chan, you're awake?
I want some milk...
Will you give me milk?
Sorry, Mizuyama-san, right now we're short on guys,
so could you give your semen to Fuu-chan?
Sit down. Fuu-chan, come on.
Time to dig in.
Wai... Wait! Is this really okay, landlady?
Landlady?!
Fuu-chan is cum-dependent.
Cum-dependent?
It seems that she was bullied a lot in school
and was forced to take in a lot of cum.
She's not going to school anymore,
but she can't forget the taste of cum.
So she lends her mouth to
the guys here and drinks their cum.
You can only use her mouth, though.
You can't have sex with her.
Is that what the seals are for?
So if you ever want somewhere to put your dick into...
Please put it in me.
I won't give you any of this semen.
Yes, I know.
But it's so weird. His pre-cum's taste is strong.
It's so strong that it's making my head spin.
I want more.
You can be a quickie, I don't mind.
Just let me drink a lot!
It looks like Fuu-chan has really taken
a liking to your dick, Mizuyama-san.
You think so?
Yes, she's really into it today.
She doesn't usually lick the balls.
Your milk pouch is bulging.
So much... hot stuff... I want to gulp it all down!
My wife doesn't give me fellatio at all.
Does fellatio really feel this good?
If you suck there, I'm gonna...
Your cum is so taste, mister.
Oh my, look. Now that she's full, she's fast asleep.
Y-Yeah...
But it looks like you're still wide awake, Mizuyama-san.
I need to go back to my wife...
I can't hold on any longer...
There we go.
Landlady?!
Please do what you want with my pussy.
Come on, isn't it giving off a really nice smell?
It's been so long since I've seen the real deal.
It's twitching so erotically.
Could I trouble you to have a taste of my pussy juices?
If it's just tasting it...
It's different than my wife's.
It's a bit sour. I could get hooked on this.
It tastes so good!
Landlady, it tastes delicious!
Thank goodness.
It's absolutely great!
I'm so happy.
Even my nipples are getting excited.
Mizuyama-san, please, I can't wait any longer!
I'm putting it in, okay?
It's swelling up!
Landlady!
This is it! This is the feeling!
The feeling of my pussy being stretched wide open!
No...
My body is rejoicing!
Sex really is...
This is the first time I've done it in a while.
Riding a penis like this is the best!
Landlady!
My morality is...
I'm so happy.
You're going to help me feel good, right?
Oh? You had a visitor?
It looks like this might take a while.
Well come back later.
It's thrusting into my stomach!
It's coming in so deep!
Your dick is kissing my deepest parts!
My body is craving your dick! It loves it!
Now that people are watching us,
I'm getting more aroused than usual.
Landlady! Landlady! Landlady!
Mizuyama-san, please keep pounding
the deepest depths of my pussy! It feels so good!
Like here?
Yes, right there!
It's rubbing me! It's rubbing against my walls of flesh!
Landlady...
Okay.
You like kissing, huh?
When we kissed, your dick got even harder.
It's so hard! It's sliding in and out of me!
Harder! Deeper!
Let me squeeze your cum out inside of me!
I love how your dick touches my womb!
Your tip is hitting the entrance to my womb!
I want to cum with your hot sticky
baby juices inside of me! I want it!
I'm close!
Now, do it! Cum inside!
My pussy's so happy!
Th-Thank goodness...
You came a lot, didn't you?
All done?
Oh, good morning.
Milk... What a waste.
I've really done it now...
I...
Oh, hey, you're our neighbor.
Oh, hello.
So you came here too, Mizuyama-san?
It's a great place, isn't it?
Y-Yeah...
U-Um, do you ever feel bad for your husband?
Well, we're kind of tired of being married.
At first, I was mad because my
husband did it with the landlady,
but really, people here don't break the rules at all.
So, as soon as I started to think that this
might be better than cheating, I got hooked.
Would you like to have sex with me?
You'd have to use a condom though.
No, that's okay.
Yeah, thought as much. Maybe another time.
Everyone here might be a pervert,
but I don't think anyone here is indecent.
That might be true, but...
I'm home.
Welcome back. Dinner's ready.
I felt really bad for my wife.
I'm sorry, it's just been so long...
It didn't feel good, did it?
That's not it.
I might just be too tired.
Sorry, I'm gonna go out for a bit.
Seriously, don't worry about it.
O-Okay...
We tried holding off on
having sex until we had our child,
but now that it's born and we've moved,
things have been slowly getting weirder.
Is he cheating on me?
Where's he going?
Communal area?
– Don't lick it!
– Wh-What?!
Good evening, mister.
That feels good.
That's my husband's voice.
Lick my ass more!
Mister, you're so stiff.
Honey?
Your ass tastes so good! So delicious!
Mizuyama-san, you're so good!
Mister, hurry up and give me your cum.
What's going on here?
Welcome to the communal area.
translator: hikarucon
timing: steinr
typesetting: hdr
editor: fyurie
quality control: fyurie