Where's he going?
"Communal space?"
– Lick me there!
– Wh-What?
M-Mister...
That feels good.
That's my husband's voice!
Play with my ass more!
You're so stiff, mister.
H-Honey?
Your ass... Your ass tastes so good!
Mizuyama-san, you're great at this!
Mister, hurry up and give me your cum!
What's going on in here?
Welcome to the communal space.
I'm a sexaholic! 2
Yuuko...
What are you doing here?
This place is great.
Wha... He's not acting like normal at all...
Please, do not be worried.
Your husband isn't cheating on you.
What do you call this, then?!
This is a place where people
lend other people their bodies.
All emotional baggage is checked and left at the door.
Well isn't that just convenient.
What you offer, and what you desire, can be
almost anything, as long as you follow the rules.
Have sex with me today as well, Landlady.
I'm terribly sorry,
but I'm helpings tenant move today.
He didn't want to do it with me,
but he gets that hard when he's here?
I need to do something...
I understand.
If those are the rules, then I have a proposal.
I will provide anything but my genitals,
so please keep my husband busy.
As long as you're here,
there will be no problems with that.
No need to worry. The rules are absolute.
I understand. In return, my husband...
Wai...
You need to keep your eyes on me, mister.
Mizuyama-san, you're still filled with milk,
aren't you? How nice, I love that.
It's only for a limited time too!
My turn.
No, it's not. You know the rules.
Let's get to business, then.
R-Right.
Honey... I'm going to make you snap out of it!
My nipples are getting so hard!
My legs feel so weak.
I love how sensitive your boobs are.
It's been so long, I can't help it. I'm sorry!
You make me want to tease you even more!
They're so pink! You can barely tell that
you've had a baby. What a beautiful shape!
They're so mushy, it's amazing!
They might even be bigger than the landlady's!
No! My nipples feel so hot!
Mizuyama-san, if your nipples are sensitive,
I have just the toys for you.
Huh? What?
I have many items that may help.
N-No, don't!
Who would want something like that?
It looks like it'd feel good...
Here it comes.
N-No... it feels so good.
The pleasure from my nipples
is spreading through my whole body.
Whoa, I can't believe you're getting
this turned on from your nipples.
I-It's not just my nipples I'm feeling good from.
I can't stop thinking about the pleasure...
I can't stop thinking about my nipples...
O-Oh God...
I can't hold it in anymore.
My milk is going to come out!
Breast milk! It's breast milk!
The breast milk... don't let a drop go to waste!
No, stop. This is for the baby.
We know, but it tastes so good!
You really love breast milk,
don't you, Yamamoto-san?
Yeah, of course.
You gotta get it while you can, you know?
Breast milk coming out feels so good!
Did you just cum from your milk shooting out?
I wonder if that was too much
stimulation for her first time.
Oh, Morioka-san and Tsukishima-san.
Mizuyama-san, as long as we don't go inside,
your pussy isn't off limits, right?
What about your ass?
Yes...
Wh-What?
What's happening? My clit's being sucked on!
There's so much pleasure coming from my clitoris!
Well then, let's get started back here too.
Wh-What are you...
My ass is expanding like a balloon!
Yeah, and it's not over yet.
No, any more than this, and my...
My sanity won't last!
Now, you're good to go.
Anal feels good, doesn't it?
Looks like this feels good too.
All right, let's all help pleasure you.
What are they going to do to me now?
Can you feel it? Your whole body
must feel like a sex organ now.
They're right! My whole body is in ecstasy!
My whole body feels like it's my pussy!
I'm... I'm going to go crazy!
That's fine, go crazy! We'll help you
feel even better, every step of the way.
My ass and clitoris feel so amazing!
The buzzing vibration... I can feel the vibration
all the way inside my womb!
No! It's gonna leak out!
I can't hold back my pee!
No, not my nipples!
You're moving them around so much!
My clitoris... it feels so good!
I'm gonna cum!
Mizuyama-san, you're so hot!
Let us hear more of your moaning!
My moaning?
My clitoris is being played with...
I'm panting, and I cant keep my voice in.
Damn, it sucks that we can't put these inside you!
All they're doing is watching and yet
they're so hard. It must be frustrating for them.
They're really following the rules.
I'm cumming!
Me too!
They're looking at me while cumming.
If this keeps up, I won't be able to... hold back!
Wait...
Honey, I'm sorry.
I can't control myself anymore!
With that, all of my holes are open now.
This doesn't count as cheating, right?
Please fill my pussy to the womb with your dicks!
Please stimulate me by cumming deep into my womb!
My pussy won't stop throbbing!
I guess I lost to pleasure, huh?
Mizuyama-san, you really mean it?!
Yes...
– Yeah!
– Thank you so much, Mizuyama-san!
– Hell yeah!
Okay, here I go!
This is so sudden...
It's going in so deep!
This isn't my husband's dick,
but my womb is so happy!
Move it...
Y-Yeah.
Move it, play with my pussy!
I can't hold on anymore. It's hitting my womb!
My pussy is craving your dick!
I'm so happy! There are so many dicks...
even though they're not my husband's...
I guess it doesn't matter anymore.
Something like that doesn't matter one bit.
This feels so good, after all.
Use any part of my body however you want!
I'm being spread so wide!
This is the best I've ever felt in my life!
It's in my ass, but I...
Let me lick your dick!
It just keeps getting sucked in, it can't get out!
Dicks just feel too good, I can't...
My entire body feels like it's my pussy!
Dicks...
The way they're rubbing against me feels so good!
Fill my ass and pussy with your semen!
I can feel your dicks cumming
into the deepest parts of my body!
I still want more!
Honey, why didn't you tell me
about this amazing place?
Mizuyama-san, you're the best!
Your dicks, I'm gonna...
I love all of your dicks so much!
Honey, you're starting to fade from my mind...
My ass feels so good!
I-I'm cumming!
Cum! Cum in my ass and pussy!
I don't care if I get pregnant!
My pussy feels so good...
I'm satisfied now. That was amazing!
Fuu-chan?
N-No, you can't.
Let me have sex too!
I'm back.
L-Landlady!
What's the matter?
It's so deep inside me!
Oh, dear me.
translation: hikarucon
timing: mrmew
typesetting: juular
editor: biskoi
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч