Why did it turn out like this?
You're a swimming club member, right? So you can
enter that place without arousing suspicion.
If you fail, you're not going to get away unscathed, got it?!
But, I don't know what they'll do it I refuse them.
Wh-What was that?
Oh, it just wasn't closed properly.
It looks forcibly overstuffed.
What's... this string?
Wait, these are panties?!
I think.
You really saved me back there.
Don't mention it. I did get a nice swim even
if I'm a track and field member, anyway.
O-Oh no.
They're back already?
Jeez, you could have just joined the swimming
club if you're always coming over this often.
You then get to swim as much as you want, you know.
Just kidding. This is just part of my training program.
I'm still a land lubber.
What a waste.
Though, if he suddenly decides to have a swimsuit
fetish, I'll probably reconsider transferring.
Wait, you're still dating that bloomer fetishist?
Is something wrong, Shiho-chin?
I-It's over.
Everything's over.
Nope, nothing wrong here.
Oh yeah, about the rumored camera stalker,
is everything just fine over at your place?
Well, it's just fine.
Even if someone bugged a camera there, my boyfriend
would probably find it and crush it right away.
Our security there is perfect.
I see.
As expected of your hidden camera junkie boyfriend.
He can sniff out people with the same taste, right?
Hey, hey, Tooshi-kun's not a hidden camera junkie!
Don't let out your voice now.
He's been given permission to use a camera before.
Oh yeah, right, sorry about that.
Forget that, what about the swimming dub?
You don't close this place often to keep things here, right?
Nah, no need to worry about that.
I'm technically the only girl here, so it's
not a particularly good place to peep.
That's definitely wrong!
You do know you're popular with boys with that
cool attitude and great style of yours, right?
Cool, eh.
I'm not really that cool, though.
I'm actually a bit of a hothead.
More about actions than words.
Without consideration for other people.
I can be pretty pushy when I want to do something.
And that's just me.
Well, it's true that you suddenly become very
spartan when it comes to actual exercises.
Oh, and speaking of exercises, I heard
rumors about a really pushy boy.
He takes it slowly, but can more or less still do the regimen...
What was that just now?
Oh, oh! Well.
Hey, Shiho-chin, are you okay?
Oh uh, yeah! I'm... perfectly fine!
You certainly don't look perf...
Oh, it's Tooshi-kun.
I'm going to take a sec to answer this call, okay?
Ah, yeah, go right ahead.
Sorry for the wait!
We just finished training earlier.
Oh yeah, Tooshi-kun, do you happen
to have a thing for sports swimwear?
Saki, I think I'm going to shower a
bit, so you can just go on ahead.
Ohh, so you want to see?
Now what should I do
was quite surprised.
This place is soundproof, though.
Saki also doesn't usually shower here, so you're fine now.
Why did you do that?
Why, you ask?
I should be the one asking that.
You were there at my locker checking my panties.
That's.
You even brought something like that here
I reaallly wonder what you're planning here.
I'm sorry, I'll never do it again!
Please cover your breasts!
It's okay, you don't actually need to apologize
I happen to know the situation you're currently in.
Because, you'd never really do things like this if it weren't for it!
Oh, as I thought.
It's as "magical" as I imagined it to be.
No, maybe even better.
If I can remember, the part up here, and
down here should be soft and tender.
Despite this entire body being absolutely stiff.
Boys sure are amazing.
It's my first time holding something like this.
It's your first time, Sh-Shiho-san?
You're lying, right?
Because you're being very rough with it
I'm not lying!
It's really my first time seeing it.
Knowledge-wise, of course I already have an idea
was a bit curious about boys after all.
Though, maybe because I've been swimming for years
men's bodies didn't really strike me as attractive.
However, when I saw yours during our club practices
I just got aroused.
Regardless of that underwear covering it
my female instinct or something just triggered.
Even now, I'm still very aroused.
I'm very wet right from the start.
And so
I actually felt really happy when I saw you inside that locker.
Because,
this is finally my chance to do this.
Boys are really amazing.
It gets more and more aroused the more I do it.
Anyway, why don't you do your share of work as well?
Might be weird coming from me
but don't you think this'situation is really delectable?
You too, have some sort of default knowledge about this, right?
Or maybe you just want to sloppily cum there like before?
Finally you.
So you're spurring me on to the finish line already, eh.
But
I can also catch up!
I'm not going anywhere, so you don't have to hug me like that.
He's got vigor.
His physical power is also quite something
it goes even through my swimwear.
Hey, you!
Are you listening?
It feels like my entire body's being sucked!
If you keep doing that there, I'll!
You're really amazing.
I thought my insides were about to get sucked out back there.
I-I felt weak for a while there.
Sh-Shiho-san, I'm already.
I-It's even bigger than earlier!
I-I see.
It wasn't satisfied, eh.
Well, we did kind of stop halfway.
Alright then, let's go all the way
I did cum earlier in that manner, anyway
I'm also quite unsatisfied in another way.
Bring it on
I was so bummed that I came first
so I don't plan to lose this time.
Huh? Someone still there?
Shiho-chin?
O-Oh! It's you, Saki!
It's quite rare for you to stop by the shower at this time.
W-Well!
I-I thought it might be a good idea to have a shower today!
I-I see.
It's quite rare for you to be here as well.
You usually go home immediately after a quick shower.
Eh? Oh... oh yes! Well
year was stretching. Yes, was going stretches.
That was close.
I-I see.
It's quite effective to stretch while in a hot shower, you know!
I-Is that so?
So soft... and it smells so good.
Our bath at home is quite small so I can't really do this there.
I've been trying... this out here
for quite some time already, you know.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
A-Are you alright?
You really don't look well, though.
I-'m alright.
I-I just, twisted my foot a bit.
It just hurt a bit, that's all.
I-It feels so good to rub my dick on her!
What the hell are you thinking?
I'm going to!
More.
This isn't the time to be doing that!
More!
What... his dick is... inside me?
What's worse
he pushed it all the way in with a single thrust.
Now I'm about to cum... with.
And I'm right in front of my friend.
What in the world is this impossible situation?
He came?! No way!
That was too much for me.
W-Well, I need to go back before my body feels cold again.
See you later!
A-Alright.
Then I'll take a shower over here, too.
Has he stopped yet?
I guess... he doesn't want to stop anytime soon... I see
I'm sorry.
Well, I was the one who invited you to do this in the first place
so I can't really deny that now.
But he did pretty terrible things to me earlier, and
yet I'm here getting horny with every thrust.
What the hell is happening to me?
I've heard about sex compatibility before.
This is probably it
but if this continues, my body won't be able to take it!
Go on top of me
I don't think I can stand on my own any longer
I'll leave it all to you aftewards.
This wasn't supposed to happen.
But, I've already... so many times
I've already cum, so many times
I'm about to cum!
Jeez, this is just frustrating.
What? You lost the camera?!
I'm sorry! But, I still don't think peeping is in any way good.
Here, take it back.
Come on, let's start our practice.
O-Okay!
U-Umm... thank you very much.
It's nothing. By the way
What was your name again?
I kind of remembered only your dick.
Eh!
Hello! Sorry for the wait!
We just finished training earlier.
Oh yeah, Tooshi-kun, do you happen
to have a thing for sports swimwear?
Saki, I think I'm going to shower a bit, so you can go on ahead.
Ohh, so you want to see?
Now what should I do.
We just swam earlier, so it's really wet.
Well, I don't think Tooshi-kun would even mind.
Wait for me by the usual spot, okay?
Now, now, now!
Presenting!
He's really ogling it.
So you really like it, Tooshi-kun.
The one and only super sports swimwear
which was the culmination of specialized clothing,
compression, other similar fabric effects,
and higher quality surface streamlining!
What?!
True, when compared to separation-type
track and field bloomers
the exposure is a bit less
however the compressive shrinking of
the fabric on the body exposes curves
and contours to a higher degree than the bloomers!
To-Tooshi-kun?
Moreover,
the wet fabric that's sexily dinging onto your skin
shows off the tender meat that is Saki-san
and how it is is wrapped and held firmly
the droplets dripping off the swimsuit itself makes it look like
juicy, tender meat being cooked on an open iron plate.
What the hell-are you mentioning "meat" like that for?
oof
Sorry.
Wait, just wait, Tooshi-kun!
Didn't you say you just wanted to look at it?
I never said I wasn't going to touch it.
You can't do that!
The swimsuit is wet so it'll seep in.
Swimsuits are meant to become wet.
So getting it wet is a completely natural law!
What kind of natural law is that?
I wonder why he becomes so aggressive during times like this?
He's usually more timid.
Something's.
He's just fondling my breasts, but
I think I'm about to cum already.
I've never felt so horny just by having
breasts touched before, though.
Also, during situations like this, it just
comes at the exact right time.
He's pushing in further!
I never thought he'd go this far at a place like this!
I really think it's crazy,
but I'm about to!
Stop, you can't do that... T-Tooshi-kun!
I'm going to cum!
I'm really going to cum!
I can't hold back anymore!
By the way,
you sure he's going to do it?
I'm sure things will be fine.
Setting it up there is easy.
Huh?
Oh, what's wrong?
I'm wondering why that spot is the only place that's wet.
Oh, you're right.
It's... not rain, right?
Maybe someone's been going at it here earlier.
Why in the world would they be doing it here?
Maybe someone just spilled a bucket there.
Haha, you're probabably right.
That was.
That was really close!
I-I'm sorry about earlier!
I got too carried away, and we were almost found out.
I want to do it, I want do to it.
I absolutely want to do it right now!
The place in school where no one's
bound to find us at this hour is.
H-Hey! Just where in the world are we going?
It's getting really hard to keep up!
Just come and do it with me!