I'll be your slave and have sex with you.
Girls' Changing Room
How'd I get into this mess?
You're a member of the swim club,
so you won't attract any attention, right?!
Listen here. If you fuck this up,
don't think you'll come out of it alive.
Who knows what they'll
do to me if I don't do this...
O-Oh, it just wasn't closed properly.
Someone probably tried to force it shut.
What's this piece of string?
Are these panties?
Thanks for lending me your towel.
You let me swim with you guys even though
I'm on the track team, so it's no problem.
C-Crap... They're back already?
Sheesh.
You come here so often that
you might as well just join.
If you join, you can swim all you want.
Nah, I told you, swimming is just
another part of my training.
My true calling is on the track.
What a waste.
Well, if my boyfriend develops a swimsuit fetish,
I'll think about switching over to here.
What? You're still going out
with that bloomer-fetish loser?
Shiho-chin, is something wrong?
I-I'm screwed. I'm so totally screwed...
Nope, nothing at all.
Oh yeah, you know about
the voyeur in our school, right?
Is your club okay?
Uh, yeah, I think we're okay.
Even if we do find a hidden camera,
my boyfriend immediately gets rid of it.
Our security is flawless.
Oh, I see.
Nothing less from your photography-loving boyfriend.
He and criminals are of the same mind.
Hey, Toshi-kun isn't that hardcore or anything.
Don't make a sound, okay?
He has always gotten permission
before taking any pictures.
Yeah, that's true. My bad, my bad.
What about you guys?
Anyone can get in here, right?
Hm? There's nothing to worry about.
I'm the only girl in the club,
so there's no way they'd target us.
You don't know that.
The guys love you because of you've got a great body,
and your cool and collected demeanor.
I'm cool?
I don't think I am.
I get set off pretty easily
and I tend to act before I think.
I'll do that without thinking
about the people involved at all.
I can also be pretty forceful when I want something.
That's me.
Too true! You can be pretty
spartan during training.
Speaking of training, there's one guy who
can actually keep up with your training, isn't there?
He isn't that fast, but he can finish
the whole training regimen.
Huh? What was that noise?
Oh, well, um...
Are you okay, Shiho-chin?
Uh, yeah, I'm perfectly fine.
It doesn't sound like that at all...
Sorry, it's from Toshi-kun.
I'm gonna talk to him for a bit, okay?
Huh? Oh, go for it.
Sorry for making you wait!
Practice just ended.
By the way, what do you think
about competitive swimsuits?
Saki, I'm going to take a shower
before I leave, so feel free to go on ahead.
Huh? You want to see?
Shower Room
Hm, what should I do?
Wow, that was close.
At least this place is sound-proof.
Saki always leaves without
taking a shower, so don't worry.
Wh-Why did you do that?
Why?
That's what I should be asking you.
Someone I know was
in my locker, holding my panties.
W-Well...
And that somebody was holding a camcorder too.
I wonder what he was trying to do.
I-I'm sorry! I swear I won't do it again,
so please cover up your boobs!
Don't worry about it. No need to apologize.
You must have had a reason to do what you did,
otherwise you never would've done this.
It's exactly... No, maybe even more
than what I thought it'd be like.
If I remember correctly, these parts might
be bulging, but they're surprisingly soft.
And then this part is really stiff.
Guys really are amazing.
This is the first time I've touched one.
Th-This is your first time?
Y-You're kidding, right?
You're acting like a complete animal.
I'm not lying.
This is the first time I've seen a guy's thing.
Well, I am knowledgeable about this kind of thing,
so I've been interested in men to a certain extent.
After all, I've been swimming since I was little,
so I've never really cared too much
about a man's naked body.
But when I was swimming during practice,
I saw yours and I felt something.
I didn't even have to see what was above your waist.
I guess, you could call it "womans intuition".
Even now, it just keeps coming out.
I've been soaking wet this entire time.
So with that said...
When I saw you in my locker,
I was happy beyond belief.
Because...
I finally had a chance to do this kind of thing.
Men are amazing.
The more I do this, the more dirty it becomes.
How about you try doing some work too?
I'm pretty content with this,
but I think you should be taking advantage
of this delicious situation.
You know what to do in this situation, right?
Or are you going to be a bitch
and just let me suck you off?
Screw that!
S-So you went straight for my soft spot, huh?
But...
I can do that too!
You don't have to hold on so tightly,
I'm not going anywhere.
He's stronger than I thought he was.
He's sucking so hard!
I can feel it through my swimsuit!
Hey, you. Did you hear me?
It feels like he's gonna suck everything out of me!
Don't suck there!
You're pretty amazing.
I thought my insides were gonna be sucked out.
I-I can barely feel my legs.
Sh-Shiho-san, I-I can't hold on...
I-It's even bigger than before!
Oh, so you're not satisfied yet.
Well, I guess I didn't finish the job.
Sure, lets go the distance.
You made me cum so easily,
so in a sense, I'm not satisfied either.
Bring it on!
I'm pissed that he made me cum anyway.
This time, I won't lose.
Huh? Is there someone still here?
Shiho-chin?
Oh, Saki, is that you?
It's unusual to see you in here.
Oh, I was thinking that taking a shower
before leaving might be good every now and then.
Oh, I see.
It's pretty unusual to see you here too.
You usually go straight home after taking a shower.
Huh? Um well... Stretches!
Yeah, I was doing stretches.
That was close...
Oh, really?
They say that stretching
while showering is really effective.
Oh, you don't say?
Crap she's so soft and she smells so good.
The shower at home is so small, I can't stretch there.
So...
I've been doing my stretches
here before going home...
What's the matter? Are you okay?
You really don't look too good.
I'm good.
I... I hurt my foot earlier, so I still feel a little pain.
Rubbing my dick against her feels so good!
What are you thinking?!
I'll be out soon...
More...
This isn't the time to be doing this!
Not... Eh?!
More!
What? His dick... went inside...
And it's all the way inside me.
I might cum while peeing!
In front of my friend...
What's with this nightmarish situation?!
This can't be real!
That was amazing.
Well, I'm going to take a shower again to warm up my body.
I'll see you later!
Y-Yeah.
Okay, I'm gonna take a shower too.
We got through that somehow.
But I guess you don't have any
intention of stopping, do you?
Sorry.
We'll I was the one who started this,
so I don't have the right to refuse anymore.
Even though this is a terrible situation, it feels so good.
What's going on?!
I've heard that the level of sex is dependent
on how good of a match the two bodies are.
In that sense, I hit the jackpot in terms of bodies, but...
At this rate, my body won't last.
How about you get on top?
I can't stand anymore.
Okay then... I'll leave the rest to you.
This isn't what was supposed to happen.
This much... This many times...
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!
How frustrating...
You lost the camera?!
I-I'm sorry, but I think voyeurism really isn't right.
Here ya go.
Come on, let's go to practice.
O-Okay.
U-Um, thank you very much.
Don't worry about it. By the way...
Yes?
What was your name again?
I only remember your dick.
What?!
Girls' Changing Room
Hello? Sorry for making you wait.
Practice just ended.
By the way, what do you think
about competitive swimsuits?
Saki, I'm going to take a shower
before I leave, so feel free to go on ahead.
Huh? You want to see?
Hm, what should I do?
Well, it's still dripping wet
since we just finished practice,
but I guess you're not really the type to care.
Well then, wait in the usual place, okay?
And here it comes...
Curtains open!
He's really staring hard.
I guess he does like this kind of thing.
The competitive swimsuit. The ultimate form
of clothing developed through much trial and error
to be faster and better than track clothing in water.
What?
Sure, it shows less skin than bikinis do, but...
This swimsuit accentuates the
curves on your body,
cause of the tightness
of the fabric, unlike bloomers.
T-Toshi-kun...
This wet swimsuit enveloping the plump
flesh of this girl named Saki,
perfectly displays the crevices and folds of her body.
And the drops of water rolling down
her flesh almost look like drops of oil
while perfectly complementing her flesh,
making it similar to a juicy steak...
Why do you keep saying "flesh" over and over?
Sorry.
Toshi-kun, wait.
I thought you were just going to look.
I didn't say anything about not touching.
You shouldn't!
You're going to get wet off this swimsuit.
A swimsuit is supposed to be wet, so this is perfect!
What are you talking about?
Why does he only get aggressive in situations like this?
Usually he's much more docile.
I might've already cum just from
him playing with my boobs.
I've never gotten off from just my boobs though.
He's definitely gotten better at doing this lately.
Crap I'm gonna pee...
I don't know how I feel about going
this far in a place like this, but...
I-I can't take it anymore, T-Toshi-kun!
You're gonna make me cum!
I-I really... c-can't... hold on anymore!
So, you really think things
will go smoothly with that kid?
It'll be fine.
The camera's easy to use.
What's the matter?
I was just wondering why this
is the only wet spot up here.
Oh, true. It didn't rain or anything.
Maybe someone peed here.
Why would they come all
the way up here to do that?
Maybe they were going to fill a bucket
with water and dump it on someone?
That's possible too.
Crap...
That was so close!
S-Sorry!
I got too full of myself and I almost got us caught.
I want to have sex! I want to do it now!
There must be somewhere secluded in this school...
W-Wait, where are we going?
It's hard to walk!
I don't care! I want to hurry up and have sex!
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hdr
editor: fyurie | punk4real
quality: fyurie