Jeez, don't stare at me so much.
It's my first time doing something like this, so I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
Asuka...
You can't say anything now, okay?
If it's not any good, then I won't come here again...
Hey-! Don't grope me like that!
Kei...
Who would have thought I'd see you like this.
Okay, it's been decided that you'll be my shield.
Since you're quite useful, determined,
and most of all, obey my commands.
You better be grateful.
Idiot, what are you remembering things for?
And...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
I can trust you, can't I?
Presented by
Shikkaku Fansubs
Original Animation Video
Puchipai Asuka~ The Small and Selfish Wizard of Treason
P-Please be gentle, okay?
Kei... Hey-!
It's touching me; your hot thing is rubbing against me...
Um...
Should we stop?
N-No, I'll be okay, so...
I-I'll try my best to bear with it.
Okay then.
Ke-Kei...
It hurts...! Ke-Kei-!
Is it in?
Nearly.
O-Okay...
Is it in now?
Yeah.
We became one...
I somewhat feel happy...
Go on Kei, it doesn't work unless you move, right?
Are you all right?
Yes. I'm fine.
I want you to move. I want to feel more of you.
I-It hurts...!
Kei...!
It hurts!
Your thing hurts, Kei...!
Kei... Kei...!
The pain is slowly fading...
I can feel you Kei-!
Your thing is rubbing my insides, Kei!
Kei, I'm feeling a bit...
K-Kei-!
Kei, this is a bit much-!
K-Kei, hey please...!
Kei! Hey Kei!
No-!
What kind of position is this?!
Hey! It's embarrassing! Stop it!
No, Kei...!
Hey, I want to be looking at you!
Kei, stop it!
Hey, please, not like this!
No-!
W-Where do you think you're touching, Kei?
Hey Kei-!
No, this is-!
No-! Stop-
Not inside-!
No way...
You mustn't...
Kei...! You-!
Huh, Kei?
H-Hey, why...? You're kidding, right?
No, hey-!
Kei, I don't want this!
No! This is my first time!
Kei's thing is going in so deep! It's too deep!
No, not again!
Kei, are you going to cum again?
Impossible, impossible! I can't believe this!
What are you? Demon! Devil! Pervert!
You damn split personality!
I'm sorry.
Even though it was my first... Even though I said to stop...!
Even though I said you can't, you...!
Even though you were saying such kind words as “are you all right?”
You're not kind at all!
M-My bad.
It's just that Bolf-san said “stop!” meant “go ahead” during sex.
You idiot! You're the worst!
Do you want to try dying?
W-Wait-!
You can't do that now!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
Jeez, fine then.
Changing like that while doing it...
If you showed such manliness normally, then...
It's nothing! I'm going to sleep, idiot.
N-No, don't look this way.
Don't look at me when I'm waking up...
Your face when you were sleeping sure was cute, Asuka.
I-Idiot! Stop that!
Looking at my embarrassing parts from yesterday...
Kei-sama!
Good morning!
It's a nice morning out there!
How about having breakfast together?
K-Kei-sama...?
W-When did you...?
W-What is it Ero? Barging in this early in the morning...
T-That's my line!
Why are you and Kei-sama together?!
And my name is Raphael!
Can't you tell by looking at the situation?
It means that you're intruding.
I can't believe such a flat-chested wizard is with the likes of Kei-sama...
K-Kei-sama! D-Did you and this person... um...
Did you...
H-Hey Ero! Why so serious?
Jeez, you're embarrassing me now.
S-Shut up!
You're mistaken if you think you've won because of this!
And you, Kei-sama...!
W-Well, I understand that girls prefer heroes.
I-I'll see you two later then.
W-What's with her?
Kei, why are you having Ero call you “Kei-sama”?
I honestly don't know why she does.
Oh really?
Well, I said that I'd trust you, so I'll forgive you this time,
but in return, I'm going to train you hard today.
That Bolf, getting us to do his jobs so suddenly.
Even though we have to train... Jeez.
Well, it can't be helped.
I know, but...
It's no use arguing.
But, let's focus on your training first.
No, t-that's...
What? I'm quite good with the sword too.
I have done the Mitsurugi Kojirou initiation after all.
Jeez, it's not fair when you're a wizard too!
I can't go easy on you.
What's wrong?
You won't get me like that.
Think up a strategy.
Damn it!
C'mon, over here!
I won't forgive...
A-Asuka, I'm sor-
I won't forgive you!
Fire of the nature, channel through my hand and become my power!
Asuka-!
Fire Lance!
Oh no...
Kei, Kei?
Kei, Kei! Hey!
Kei... Kei?
K-Kei, are you okay?
Where did I hit you?
Does it hurt anywhere?
Uh, no.
Jeez, you surprised me...
Having lots of stamina is one of your traits,
but for you to go down like this-
Hey, Kei...
What's the meaning of this?
Kei!
Ouch-! It's because you're dressed like that!
You idiot! Why didn't you tell me? Pervert!
Y-You're such a pervert!
If I knew what you were like before, then...
Hey, wait Kei!
D-Don't you be go and get excited!
Kei, h-hey, you look scary...
It's because you're tempting me.
I'm not trying to tempt you!
Y-You were the one who did this to me!
No-! I said that you can't!
We can't do it in a place like this, okay?
Hey, Kei! Someone might see us!
I-I'll get angry-! Jeez!
No, I said that we can't...!
Kei...
No, stop!
That's-!
That spot-! Your tongue, your tongue, it's...!
Hey, stop it!
Please Kei, I said to stop!
No, please!
I can't hold-!
No!
No, no!
N-No!
What are you going to do? No-
Kei, not again!
Not so suddenly-!
No-!
This is...! Kei!
Hey, why are you acting like this?!
Not so hard-!
Amazing... Your big thing is going into me...
No-! Not in this position again!
So deep-!
Kei, your thing is hitting me so deep-!
This... Doing it from the back, it's...
So good!
You're mixing up my insides!
No, t-this feels too good-!
It's too deep!
I'm gonna... No-!
What is this...?
Kei! I'm... I'm gonna...!
No, I'm...! No-!
No, it's too deep!
No... What is this... What is this?
No... this is...
That was amazing...
Impossible! I can't believe you!
Even after everything I said...!
You... You!
I-I'm sorry. I really am!
You, who are you?
You're completely different when having sex!
Jeez, doing whatever you please. Thrusting it in whenever you want...
Pervert! Idiot!
Please Asuka! Not that again!
Shut up! I have to physically teach you in order for you to remember it!
Kei-sama!
You again.
Y-You too together with Kei-sama again-!
I'm amazed that you're so keen on this scumbag, Ero.
What did you say?
And it's Raphael!
A-Anyway, you keep calling me Ero, but how you're dressed is more indecent!
Pervert.
S-Shut up.
This is because of that scumbag's hobby.
How dare you blame someone else!
Kei-sama, if you stay with this flat-chest, you'll be ruined!
If you want him so much, go ahead and take him.
W-What is this? Treating Kei-sama like an object...
Kei-sama, please come with me.
Well then, Kei-sama,
let's leave this perverted flat-chested wizard and venture with me!
S-So let us have make love and...
Wait.
I-I won't give him back even if you ask.
Since you're the one who gave him to me!
He's... a brute.
Kei-sama, that's...!
Kei-sama! I-I have something to do, so...!
Wait, Kei-sama-!
Hey, please...!
W-Why are you doing this?
Kei-sama, I thought you were more wonderful than-
The dark king who rules the land, obey my wish.
With divine intervention, we shall destroy the enemy!
Ice of the truth, come forth and become my strength!
Dragon Flare!
Ice javelin!
Oh, good day.
You...!
What kind of magic do you think you're using in such a place?!
I can't believe it!
W-Well, weren't you saved because of it?
F-From what, I wonder?
If you didn't intervene, Kei-sama and I would have...
No! I thought you were more wonderful than-
No!!
W-What is that you want you perverted flat-chested wizard?!
Hmph I say!
I'll forgive you today then.
Such humiliation, I won't forget it!
You don't mind, as long it's a girl, do you?
Jeez, why do you get like that?
It appears that I have to educate the indiscriminate beast such as yourself...
What? Do you have any complaints?
Do you want to get blasted again?
I will fully chasten you, so you won't be able to leave my side.
So good! My body feels so-!
It seems I'm getting used to your thing...
You can't cum yet.
So good-!
My body feels like it's paralyzed!
This feels so good!
Your hot thing belongs only to me!
That's why, you mustn't do it with anyone else!
I like this!
It's so deep...
I can't take it any longer!
Just like this!
This...
This is...
Impossible...
Amazing, my head is going blank...
This is the first time, that...
I won't forgive you, if you dare to look at anyone other than me...