Geez, stop staring at me like that.
This is my first time, so I'm not sure what to do.
Asuka.
And don't start saying anything weird now.
If you do, I won't come here again.
What you're doing with your hand is so dirty.
Kei.
I never thought I'd get to see this side of you.
That settles it, I'm choosing you to be my meatshield.
You're more reliable than I expected, you've got some balls, and above all else you follow my orders well.
You should feel honored.
Silly. What made you think of that?
And then...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Can I trust you?
FAKKU! Presents
Tiny-tittied Asuka ~ The Selfish Little Wizard's Rebellion
Please be gentle.
Ok, Kei?
Your hot thing is touching me.
Ummm...
Should we stop here?
No. I'm fine, really.
I'll do my best to bear it.
Alright.
Kei.
It hurts, Kei. Kei...
It's inside me.
There's just a little more...
Ok.
Now it's inside me.
Yeah.
I've become one with you.
I'm really happy.
Go ahead Kei. You have to move right?
Will you be alright?
Yeah. I want you to move. I want to feel you more.
It hurts!
It hurts Kei!
Your thing is hurting me.
Kei! Kei!
It's hurting a little less now.
I understand you Kei.
You fit inside me perfectly.
Kei, I'm starting to feel a little...
K-Kei!
Wait, Kei, that's too...
Wa... Kei.. Hey....
Kei, listen to me...
What's with this position? Hey! It's embarrassing!
Stop it.
No, Kei.
Hey, I can't see your face.
No, Kei! Please, I don't like this.
What? No! Where are you touching me?
Kei, Kei!
You're gonna tear me apart!
No, no more!
It's going inside me!
No way.
No.
Kei, why you...
What the, Kei?
Hey, you're kidding right?
No, you can't!
I'm telling you I don't want this, Kei!
This is my first time.
Your thing is so hot.
I regret doing this.
Not again Kei!
I can't believe it! How could you, how could you!?
What the hell are you?
You monster, you demon, you pervert! You've got a split personality!
I'm sorry.
That was my first time.
I even told you I didn't enjoy it!
I even told you to stop!
And there you were saying gentle things to me.
What the hell did you mean, 'It'll be alright.'?
You weren't gentle at all.
I'm sorry about that.
Bolf told me that when girls say 'No' it means they like it.
You idiot! You're the worst!
Wanna die?
Hold on! You can't do that in here!
I'm sorry, please forgive me!
Geez, what's with you?
It's like you turn into a different person during sex.
If only you were always that manly...
Huh?
Never mind.
I'm going to bed, asshole.
Eww, don't look at me.
I don't want you to look at me after I just woke up.
You looked cute while you were sleeping.
Stop it, silly.
You've seen so many embarrassing things about me since yesterday.
Good morning Master Kei.
It's a refreshing morning. Want to have breakfast with me....
Master Kei! Since when?
What's with you coming in here first thing in the morning Ero?
I'm the one who should be asking you! Why are you together with Master Kei?
And my name is Rafaero!
Oh, can't you tell what's going on here?
You're interrupting us.
How could a tiny-tittied wizard like you get with Master Kei...
Kei... did you, you know... With that woman...
What are you suddenly getting so serious about Ero? It's making me embarrassed.
Shut up! You're sorely mistaken if you think this means you've defeated me!
And Master Kei, you...
Well, I guess I understand the need to fulfill your healthy sexual urges.
Fare well.
What was that about?
And why was she calling you Master?
How should I know?
I wonder.
Well, since I decided to trust you, I'll forgive you this time.
But in exchange, I'll work you to death during today's training session.
I can't believe that Bolf was suddenly declared as the prince.
We need him for our special training.
There's nothing we can do about it.
That's true, but... Yeah, there's nothing we can do.
I'll just have to concentrate more on your special training today.
You really can't...
What's wrong? I'm quite a swordsman you know.
I've inherited the Mitsurugi sword style after all.
You're up for this despite being a wizard? That's gotta be against the rules.
Just so you know, I don't hold back.
What's wrong?
You won't get me like that.
Work on your form.
Damnit!
Come on, over here.
I won't...
Asuka, I'm sorr...
I won't forgive you!
Flames of Genesis, bind to my hand to become my power!
Asuka!
Fire Lance!
Oh no!
Kei!
Kei, Kei! Hey!
Kei, Kei.
Are you alright Kei? Hey...
Where did I shoot you? Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh, no.
Geez, I was so worried.
Stamina is supposed to be your strong suit. I can't believe that's all you could take.
Huh? Kei, what's the meaning of this?
Kei!
That hurts! I can't help it with you looking like that.
Idiot! Tell me about these things, you pervert!
You're so perverted.
If I had known you were like this...
Huh?
Wait a minute Kei! This isn't the time to get horny!
Hey, Kei! You've got a scary look on your face!
That's because you're tempting me.
I'm doing no such thing!
You're the one that did this to my clothes in the first place.
No! We can't do it in a place like this!
Wait Kei! Someone will see us!
I'll get angry!
No! You can't do that!
No, Kei!
Not there!
Your tongue is... your tongue is down there...
You can't do that...
Please stop Kei!
No, please!
No! Don't lick it!
What are you planning to do with that? No!
You're doing this again Kei?
This is too sudden!
No!
This is too much Kei!
Hey, this feels weird!
You're too rough.
It's amazing.
Your thing is inside of me.
Not this position again!
It's so deep.
Kei, you're hitting me so deep inside.
Your thing...
This is so stupid, but it feels so good.
You're stirring me up inside! It's too much!
This is too strange! I can't take it!
What am I feeling, Kei?
I'm, I'm...
No!
No, what is this? What is it?
This is...
That was amazing.
I can't believe you! I just can't believe it!
After all I said to you... why you...
I'm sorry, I really am sorry.
What's with you? You're like a completely different person during sex.
Geez, cumming inside me to your heart's content...
You stupid pervert!
Wait Asuka! You're really taking it too far!
Shut up! You're the type who only learns from experience!
Hey sis!
It's you again.
And you're doing things to Master Kei again!
I'm amazed that you're so infatuated with this low-life, Ero.
What was that? And my name is Rafaero!
And what's with you calling me Ero all the time? You're way more erotic with that get-up of yours.
You pervert.
Shut up. This is what this low-life is in to.
What kind of woman are you? How can you blame others for looking like that?
Master Kei, you'll come to nothing if you stick around with that tiny-tittied woman.
If you want him that much I'll give him to you. You can just carry him away.
How dare you treat Master Kei like an object?
Come here Master Kei.
Abandon that perverted tiny-tittied wizard and come with me.
Now let's exchange vows, Master Kei.
Hold on.
I'm not giving him back to you now.
You're the one who handed him over.
He's a brute.
No!
Master Kei! Not there!
Master Kei! Wait! I need to prepare myself!
Wait! Hey!
Please Master Kei!
Why are you doing this? I wanted this to be more special.
Lord of a Million Miles, answer my call, bring forth the flames of judgment and destroy my enemies!
Oh frozen blood, come to my side to create a magic barrier!
Dragon Flare!
Ice Javelin!
Well that was interesting.
Why you... how could you use a technique like that in here?
I can't believe you!
Yeah well, didn't I end up saving you?
What are you talking about? If you hadn't interfered, Master Kei and I would have...
No! I wanted this to be more special!
What are you doing, you perverted tiny-tittied wizard!
Fine then. I'll let you off today.
But I'll never forget this insult.
Are you fine with anyone as long as it's a woman?
Geez, you're really driving me crazy.
I'm going to set some conditions for you, you indiscriminate beast.
Conditions?
What? Have any complaints?
Want me to abandon you again?
I'm going to punish you so much that you can never leave my side again.
It feels good.
My body...
It's getting used to you.
You're all mine for now.
My body's going numb.
This is...
So good!
It's so hot!
Kei, you're all mine!
So don't do it with anyone but me!
This is so good!
I can't...
Stop my body from moving!
If we keep going I'll...
This is...
What is this? My mind is going blank.
This is the first time I've felt this way.
I won't forgive you if you look at anyone but me.