My mother died when I was young,
and I was in a family of three with my father and sister.
But my precious sister, Kaoru, commited
suicide because she had been bullied,
and from a fire of unknown cause, I lost my father, too.
To avenge my sister who was killed,
I found the ones who knew about the truth of her death.
Yukawa Ayano, Inami Misuzu and Tsubaki Rina,
brought them to a deserted hospital ward,
locked them up in individual rooms,
and began to interrogate them.
I wanted to know.
Why was my sister bullied!?
Why did she have to die?
I wanted to the truth.
Well then, let us resume to the action!
Upon the women who are the worst of the worst...
The revenge that is even crueler than death!
Original Animation Disk
Dangerous!
Revenge - Website of Darkness
Hope spreading throughout the world.
The reply from the dead a request to
eliminate those damn bitches!? Arc.
Seems like you were also bullied by Ayano and Misuzu.
That’s... um...
Answer me honestly! So?
I was... not bullied...
There’s nothing... nothing...
Why are you lying? Are you afraid of them?
I’ll tell you... who to be afraid of!
It’s not... lying, so...
No!!
No...
Don’t look at my embarrassing parts!
It’s embarrassing.
Then you’d better answer my questions.
I said I will answer whatever you ask already.
Oh really.
What is this? I’m on the screen... what’s happening!?
This... all my exposed parts are shown, too!
I’ll stop it if you talk!
You were bullied by those two, weren't you?
No!!
Not there!
It’s a girl’s most precious place!
Don’t touch it!
No, don’t tease it... no more...
Hmm. If it’s this wet, it should be alright.
Hey, you’ll let me go home now, won’t you?
Wait until you get home to start talking nonsense!
What are you trying to do...
With that... Don't tell me...
If you tell me everything without lying, I’ll let you go right away.
No!!
It’s coming, it’s coming inside!
Don’t put your... penis inside...
No!
Look, it’s the proof that you've become a woman.
Blood... so much blood...
No way...
I always thought that my first time would be for... Onii-chan...
Well it’s a shame that you couldn't
give it to your dearest Onii-chan!
No!
Don’t move! It hurts!
It... it hurts!
It hurts! It hurts!
It, it hurts... take it out... I’ll do anything if you take it out!
Then you’d better tell the truth about everything!
Like said, I don’t know! I really don’t!
Still trying to play dumb!?
Then how about this!?
Blood is splashing all over...
Are you about to answer my questions now!?
I’m answering! I’m not lying, either...
About time I cum.
Ready for fertilization?
Fertilization? Not inside! I don’t want to get pregnant!
I'll talk, I'll say anything...
It hurts!
It reeks... it’s all over me... this is horrible...
I get it... I’ll tell, I’ll tell you anything.
So, you were bullied by those two, right?
Yes. At first, it was just some chores for Misuzu-san.
But it gradually escalated, I was verbally
harassed and bullied around...
Because I’m like this...
But then it calmed down...
I think Misuzu-san got tired of me...
Then one day, Ayano-san joined, too.
That person bullied me heartlessly... again... and again!
and then...
What about Kaoru? Did she know that you were bullied?
Why do you ask?
It’s not my fault that Kaoru died!
All you need to do is answer my questions!
No, it’s not my fault! Not my fault!
I guess I have to drill it into your body
before you fully understand.
This is inside your pussy until just now.
Clean it up.
With your mouth!
Don’t push it into my face!
There’s no way I could...
C’mon, lick and suck to properly!
It’s gross, it’s gross!
Why do I have to do...
It’s because you didn't answer me properly!
If you dare bite, you’re getting even
more punishment than before!
I’m cumming. Don’t rest your mouth!
Stop... don’t!
Take it all with your mouth just like this!
Stop...
I’ll leave it here this time.
Stop already... I’ll answer what you ask, so let me go...
Then answer me: Did Kaoru know that you were bullied?
That’s...
Answer clearly!
Kaoru-chan, she saved me...
When she noticed that I was being bullied,
Kaoru-chan protected me...
Neither Ayano-san nor Misuzu-san could do anything
while Kaoru-chan was beside me...
I see... sounds like what the kind Kaoru would do.
And that must have been the reason she was bullied!
This... what is this!?
Why am I like this?
My questions haven’t ended yet!
Trying to protect you, Kaoru was bullied by
Ayano and co. and drived to suicide, right?
No! Stop already, let me go!
You know everything, don’t you!?
I don’t anything!
Why, is there need to cover up for those two!?
Kaoru was bullied by those two, wasn't she!?
I don’t know!
I really didn't do anything, so...
Talk!
Why are you doing such cruel things?
Shut up. From now on you are just a bitch.
Bark like a dog now!
But, but I didn't...
Hmph, finally quieting down huh?
Wait! Please, don’t put it in!
No!
It hurts... it’s painful...
I told you just now, yet you've already forgotten!?
Bark like a dog should!
That’s...
Woof... woof...
Sound more like a dog!
It’s painful... take it out! I can’t take it!
It’s not “I can’t take it”! You’re a dog, so act like one!
It’s painful...
Woof, woof, woof!
Not enough. Be more like a bitch you are and cry!
Woof!
Wo... woof!
Hmph, serves a bitch well. How unsightly!
So much sticky stuff... I’m sorry... let me go...
Answer me! Kaoru was bullied by them, wasn't she!?
That’s...
So? Answer me!
Yes... yes she was.
I didn't think it’d turn out like this...
So... it’s not my fault!
Scum.
SECOND DAY OF INTERROGATION
Did you bully Kaoru, along with Ayano?
I’m telling you I have no idea what you’re talking about.
Are you planning to stick with that attitude all the way?
It’s not like you care, is it?
I hate you!
Then I’ll have to make you honest with my hands.
What are you doing!?
What did you guys do to Kaoru!?
Don’t squeeze them so roughly!
You pervert! Trash!
You... how can you do so many horrible things to women?
Your conscience... don’t you have any consci-
Conscience?
Then what were you like when you heard
that Kaoru committed suicide!?
Did you feel guilt or conscience!?
Of course I didn't! I never did anything...
Liar.
Both your body and mind should reflect!
No! I don’t want to be violated by such
an abnormal person... I'd rather die!
Don’t force it inside!
Your hard thing is hitting deep inside... it’s gross...
It’s about time I expect to hear a satisfying answer.
Like I said, I... have nothing to do with it...
I already know that you and Ayano were bullying my sister!
It’s some kind of misunderstanding, really!
We’re merely acquaintances!
I’m tired of that answer!
Too rough... my womb will break, it’ll explode!
My body... no... don’t mess it up!
I don’t want to cum but... I... I’m cumming!
It’s hot!
Dirty stuff is all over me!
You stained my body again... you’re the worst...
Answer me.
Why did you bully Kaoru?
Like I said, I didn't...
Hmph. Rina’s already provided testimony
that you guys were bullying Kaoru.
Rina!?
It’s pointless to refuse to answer.
Those kinds of things don’t count as bullying!
Sure, I got her to do some things, so what!?
So you finally admit knowing Kaoru!
So what!?
You know, it’s also the victim’s fault that bullying happens!
I heard from Ayano!
That you guys are in a love relationship!
So you heard about my relationship with Kaoru?
That's right! It's sick...
Just thinking about it makes me want to puke!
What do you mean, you love her!? It’s just an abnormal lust!
People who have incest sex are the worst!
All of you are trash like that guy!
Who do you mean by ‘that guy’!?
All men are just horrible!
What "father"!? What "I love you"!?
When my mother isn't around, that person always... he...
By "that person" you mean your father?
Shut up! Both that guy and you, you just want to fuck me!
You’re the worst! You’re the worst!!
That’s why I went into the show business, left
home and become independent, and...
There’s no way I’m going back to that house!
That guy, you and your sister should all just go to hell!
Go to hell! Go to hell!!
I didn't think that Misuzu had been
forced to have sex by her father...
So to escape from her father,
she got Ayano to help her get into the entertainment industry...
That’s why she has to obey Ayano...
in addition, she could stand me and Kaoru.
Then why did Ayano pick on Kaoru?
I think Rina may know something.
Hey. Why did Ayano bully Kaoru?
What were her motives?
I, I don’t know... that’s...
Enough already!
If you’re not answering, I’m using this guy this time.
What is that? Are you going to do cruel things to Rina again!?
that’s right. I’m giving you enema.
I’ll clean all waste that has piled up inside your intestines!
No! If you do that... my stomach will swell up!
No... it’s sick...
It’s going inside my butt...
Take it out, take it out!
Don’t put in anymore!
It’s painful... my stomach is so full...
Your finger is inside...
No, don’t stir! It’ll leak out!
You can let it all out, everyone online is waiting for it, too.
There’s no way... I could something so embarrassing!
There’s no way I could let it leak!
Then you’d better hold all the stinky stuff
inside so they don’t come flying out.
It’s coming out... I’m at my limit!
I can’t... it’s coming out!
Don’t look! Don’t look... it’s embarrassing...
No... everyone saw me give a leak...
I can’t live anymore... I want to die...
So why did Ayano bully Kaoru?
And she bullied you, too.
Answer me!
I think... she probably wanted Kaoru-chan
to work in the sleeping business...
The sleeping business? What do you mean!?
She said she would help me debut, and
asked me again and again to work...
You were in the business, too?
I refused...
But, that person didn't let me go.
She... did many cruel things to me...
So many things that made me want to die...
And then one day, she said that,
If I couldn't do it, as long as I got someone
else to do it, she’d let me go.
If I could help her get to Kaoru-chan, she’d let me go...
She said that Kaoru-chan was pretty, so she’d
surely be popular in the business...
THIRD  DAY OF INTERROGATION
Hey, what are you doing, you...
Rina talked.
Turns out Ayano was asking Rina and Kaoru
to work in the sleeping business.
Is that true?
Hmm, who knows?
I’ll make you regret your attitude just now.
What? What are you planning to do to me with that?
It’s exactly what it seems like.
You know what this is for, don’t you?
E-Enema...
Correct! The type to put in from the front too!
Don’t joke with me! That’s just wrong!
Hey, stop messing around! Are you
really going to give me enema?
If you dare pour it in I’ll never forgive you!
Never forgive me?
It’s you who needs to beg for forgiveness!
No... disgusting liquid is coming in...
It’s stimulating my insides to...
If you’re feeling like excretion, you can any time.
Don’t joke with me. Like I’d ever let it out.
I won’t let you get... whatever you want...
I see. Then hold in all you can.
What are you...
You’ll tear it if you pull that much!
No... it’s painful... stop... I'll...
I’m sure it’s obvious, but there isn't a toilet here.
If you want to go, you’ll have to spray
it all out in front of the camera.
I don’t... want to go!
Stop stimulating it! If you’re that rough, it’ll leak!
I’m at my limit... It’ll leak, let me go!
Like I said, you can let it out whenever you want.
That’s not it! The camera! move the camera away!
Are you actually serious about live casting it on the internet!?
Exactly. What’s wrong with that?
Are you still sane!? That’s just abnormal! It’s mad!
Turn the camera away! No!! It’s coming out!
Don’t look!
This is insane...
I’m asking you again.
Did Ayano ask you girls to work in the sleeping business?
Yeah, that’s right. It’s your sister’s fault for being so sick.
She let Ayano get her hands on her.
FOURHT DAY OF INTERROGATION
I hear that you were forcing Kaoru and
Rina into the sleeping business.
I didn't! I wasn't doing that!
Misuzu and Rina confessed. The internet was listening, too.
Do you still insist otherwise?
That’s not true... I really didn't do those things...
The ropes... are skinning into... my skin and my chest...
It’s painful...
Are you planning to violate me again?
No! Enough already! How filthy!
Here, I’ll give you pleasure.
Let see you take it in yourself!
Cock... is... inside...
Didn't that go in quite smoothly?
Were you in fact wanting it?
That’not it! I can’t hold my weight, so...
The hard thing is... hitting... inside... it’s...
Move your butt lewdly and show the internet your slutty side!
My boobs... hurt! No... don’t shake!
No! The ropes... sinking into my skin...
If you get ugly scars, they’ll affect you in
the sleeping business or something!?
I’m not... in that business!
I don’t need that!
That’s quite a selfish way to put it, when
you’re pulling others into you problems.
Don’t thrust so roughly! You’ll tear my womb!
The ropes are too tight... I’m going crazy... I’ll go mad!
My womb is exploding...
That’s quite a gaudy climax. You must be really hungry for sex.
What is this?
Why... I’m cumming?
That’s... no way that’s...
This is your true self, the SM fetish
pervert actress, Himekawa Ayane!
That’s not it! That’s not true!
It’s just my body being... it’s coming again!
Inside... my womb is... quivering...
You’re getting helpless turned on, aren't you?
There’s no way that’s true! I’m...
My womb is going to explode!
I’m at my limit.
If you don’t want me to ejaculate in your
womb, you have to move away yourself.
That’s... you can t!
No... it won’t stop...
Semen... all over... disgusting...
Do you admit that you were trying to force
Kaoru and Rina into the sleeping business?
I had no choice!
My office ordered me to get other girls!
It’s true!
So then, I asked Rina to go into the business, but...
Rina didn't listen, so you went after Kaoru!? How selfish!
I was just forced to do it by the office!
Besides, no one ended up in the business, anyway!
It’s true!
Broadcasting the interrogation over the internet,
was indeed effective in psychologically
cornering the three of them.
Thanks to that, I know the background of why my
sister was bullied and driven towards suicide.
But, it’s also about time the police notice.
I don’t have much time left.
Ayano had to search for people who could work
in sex service in order to continue her career.
And the girl she found was Rina, but
Rina didn't accept the invitation.
Then in exchange she sought for Kaoru.
Ayano then began to bully Kaoru in order for her to obey.
Unable to resist Ayano, Misuzu and Rina assisted in the process.
This is the truth about Kaoru being bullied.
To run away from her father, Misuzu had to do everything
she could to go into the entertainment industry,
and she was forced to obey Ayano.
Rina betrayed her friend so that she could escape bullying.
All of them are horrible, selfish women!
FIFTH  DAY OF INTERROGATION
So start with, if you never told them about Kaoru
and I, none of this would have happened!
Why do I have to be criticized!?
No... I don’t want anything that hurts anymore!
Let me go!
Kaoru had felt the same!
She was betrayed by you, who she thought of as a friend!
No! Let me go already!
I don’t want to hurt! I want to see Onii-chan!
Just be glad you’re still alive to see him!
No way... there’s... no way that could fit... you’re joking right?
No!
It’s tearing! It hurts!
No, I’ll break! I...
I hurts!
I’ll die! No...
Noway... it... it won’t fit!
I’ll really tear if you put it in... don’t!
As expected very tight. A brand new sensation.
I’ll die! No! Don’t!
I’ll die... No, you’ll break me...
Cumming!
Let me... go already...
Why? Why did you betray Kaoru!?
Even though she truly thought of you as a friend!
It’s Kaoru-chan’s fault!
I was so painful from being bullied, but Kaoru-chan
was too busy being happy with you,
and she looked down upon me...
I wanted to be saved, too!
So I brought up my courage and confessed to Onii-chan,
but Onii-chan just said that it was abnormal!
And all Kaoru-chan smiled as she told me
that I’d be happy with Onii-chan, too!
That one day, he’d understand...
You too, loved your elder brother and confessed to him.
But it didn't go well for you.
is that why you betrayed Kaoru!?
Kaoru-chan’s expression then...
She was so happy, and she was feeling superior to me...
That’s right! She looked so happy because she had everything!
That’s why I let her taste my pain!
That’s just envy and jealousy of you!
Shut up!
I’m not wrong. It’s all Kaoru-chan’s fault!
You’re the worst of the worst.
You betrayed your best friend just out of some jealousy.
Well then, this is the last question.
After Kaoru committed suicide,
my house was set on fire by someone.
It is probably related to the fact that my sister was being bullied.
And the criminals who did that...
Is someone... amongst the three of you!
Are you planning to blame that on us, too!?
That’s totally false charge!
Those words are powerless at this point!
One of you guys did it!
To dear out the evidence that there was bullying!
That’s...
Which one of you set my house on fire!?
I... think it’s one of the two of them.
Because, they’re they main offenders of the bullying!
What are you talking about!?
We could get arrested for the fire!
I just didn't like that kid, there’s no real need to set fire, is there!?
You guys lit the fire because you were
afraid of Kaoru-chan’s diary!
Diary? There was something of that sort?
I never even knew that existed...
Rina. What about the diary? Answer me!
Why... why are you looking at me like that?
It’s all... all their fault!
Rina. You set my house on fire, didn't you?
I don’t know anything!
I was just bullied... I was a victim!
Enough already! You need to learn when you've lost!
It was you, wasn't it? Like I though
you’re a useless piece of trash!
Why did you set my house on fire!?
I knew that... Kaoru-chan kept a diary...
If people read that... they might think it’s all my fault...
Murderer!
Like you have the right to judge!
Even though you’re a monster who feels
nothing about bullying others!
Even so, I hadn't killed anyone!
I never killed anyone, either!
It's Kaoru-chan fault for committing suicide
and her father’s fault for dying in the fire!
Enough.
You close your mouth.
This is the end.
I... I'm in love with Onii-chan.
I love you!
I, too...
Well then, I’m putting it inside.
It hurts!
Are you alright?
Yeah... I want to be... connected with Onii-chan...
Then, here we go.
It's tingling deep inside...
I can feel Onii-chan’s heat!
I’ll move.
Yeah, go ahead...
Your penis is... hot, and... the stimulation...
It feels good, Onii-chan!
Kaoru, it’s really good...
Me, too, it’s good...
Onii-chan... My mind is... going blank...
Kaoru's is... overflowing...
It feels good, Onii-chan!
I’m cumming!
Me too...
I’m cumming, Kaoru...
It’s coming out...
How stuff is flowing out... it feels good...
It feels really good, Onii-chan...
I’m so happy...
It’s over...
I got those women to tell the truth...
There’s no longer a reason for me to stay in this world.
The only thing left to do is getting rid of those women...
My father died from the fire Rina set off...
Then, the same ending suits me...
45.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:25.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
The case from before, is it true that it's solved?
46.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:30.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
It appears that the ward that the women were captured in was completely
Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:34.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
Revenge, I guess?
47.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:34.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
48.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:39.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
Did the culprit die, too?
49.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:44.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
Who Knows?
50.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:49.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
The surrounding areas were burned down, too. Several corpse like
objects were also found, but they we all already unrecognizable.
50.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:49.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
The surrounding areas were burned down, too. Several corpse like
objects were also found, but they we all already unrecognizable.
51.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:53.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
Imagine if the criminal was the only one who got away, lol.
52.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:20:58.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
So the criminal is like, on the run?
53.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:21:02.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
You'll never know. But if it's that guy, I feel like he’s not the small-minded type to run away.
54.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:21:05.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
In the end one Knows what happened.
55.Mirano-san@Loggedin 2014/04/25 (Friday) 02:21:10.ID:Kyxxxxxxxx
Only god Knows.