W-What?
I...
What's this place?
Hey! What's this?
This is...
Oh? I...
Rina? You're here too?
Why?
What's this place?
You girls!
Ayano.
It's bad.
It's bad, Ayano!
Inami Misuzu
This is...
This women name is Inami Misuzu.
Seems that she's a model with name Milly.
This is Yukawa Ayano.
Yukawa Ayano
Other name, an actress Himekawa Ayano.
She's a student like Milly and as an actress she's working in public entertainment.
And Tsubaki Rina.
Tsubaki Rina
Seems that she was my younger sister best friend.
Who's there?
I've met you somewhere...
Tezuka Ryou-san.
You remembered me, even though you ignored me a lot!
What's this?
Why did you manacle us?
It suits you very well.
Hurry up and remove these!
Why are you trying to do with me?
I want to ask you girls about something.
That's all.
So, you brought us here?
I want to know, why my precious younger sister had to die!
Yabai! Revenge Dark Site.
Yabai!
-Revenge Dark Site-
Bullying prompt report, or a fuel drop!?
Asking people on the network.
A murder of my younger sister is among those three sows.
Translation:
Oppai_Lover
Yabai!
-Revenge Dark Site-
Bullying prompt report, or a fuel drop!?
Asking people on the network.
A murder of my younger sister is among those three sows.
Several weeks ago.
-Several weeks ago-
Father!
Calm down a bit!
What are you talking about?
My younger sister died.
I've heard that she committed suicide.
Our Mother passed away when we were young,
and Father was busy with work.
I've spent a lot of time with my younger sister.
A younger sister who was so close to me and smiled to me.
I loved more than sister.
No. We loved each other.
Our house were full of sadness,
so even my Father experienced tragedy.
I lost a place to return.
But miraculously, thanks to the assets my Father left I don't have any problems with day to day life.
On the other hand, I lost everything else that was precious to me.
However, the only one thing I have left....
Was the last massage from my younger sister which she probably left just before suicide.
What is she apologizing for?
She caused troubles? That's why she committed suicide?
What in the hell happened to Kaoru?
W-Why are you looking so silently?
It's disgusting!
Tsubaki Rina, I've herd many times about you from my younger sister.
She said that you were her best friend.
Tell me!
If you were her best friend, then tell me why Karou has to die?
I don't know anything.
I really don't know.
If you were really Kaoru's best friend, then tell me the whole truth!
She said that she doesn't know anything, so that's enough, right?
Right!
I don't have other choice,
so I talked with every girl that come out from Academy.
And I've heard interesting story from the girl who was in the same class as Kaoru.
She said that Kaoru was bullied.
By you three.
You've heard that we don't know anything earlier, right?
This is just false accusation!
I've never talked with your younger sister!
Let's calm down and talk.
It's a pity what happened to your younger sister, but it's a misunderstanding.
Listen to us and then-
It hurts! What are you doing?
Shut up!
Don't say anything unnecessary!
If you haven't done anything to feel guilty about, why did you keep running away from me?
You treated me like a stalker and used the academy and the police to reject a meeting with me!
You're absolutely hiding something!
I have the right to know.
What's this place?
What are you planing to do with us here?
If you girls don't have any intention of telling the truth,
then I'll just have to make you suffer until you're more willing to do so.
You want to torture us?
No. I'll be questioning you.
Questioning?
Your questioning will be conducted in front of a camera and broadcast to the network.
W-Why are you doing something like this?
Society will bare witness.
In a situation where someone else beside me is watching this,
and you girl would say "We did it all,"
then I wouldn't be able to set-up a makeshift room to hear out your confession.
T-This is going too far!
If you'll be willing to tell the whole truth without telling a lies,
then I don't mind letting you go.
But...
If you'll hiding anything or have done anything to my younger sister,
then I won't go easy on you!
Hey!
Open!
Open it!
Stay obediently there for a while.
No!
Let me out of here! Please!
It's pointless!
Originally, it was used as isolation ward.
In other words, it was prison for patients.
This place has been designed so no one can get out.
And the keys for doors are only outside.
Then answer me about your three relationship.
It's obvious that we're friends.
Even the close friends!
If you're calling yourself close friends,
then you know a lot about each other, right?
Of course!
If that's the case, then you're close friends in private life too?
Our private life has nothing to do with your younger sister, right?
I'll decide that!
Ho are you normally hanging out?
It can be anything!
Tell me some story that only close friend should know.
As I thought, you made up that you're close friends.
If not, then it would be easy for you to expresses how close you are.
T-That's...
I don't have other choice if you still don't want to tell anything.
Yabai! Revenge Dark Site.
It hurts!
You're making a women to be in such embarrassing posture and you making her unable to move!
You're calling yourself a man, even so?
Be ashamed!
Hey! Maybe you'll say something?
Maybe you'll introduce yourself to them?
W-What's the meaning of this?
Don't tell me that you really intend to do this?
Wai-
What are you doing?
What do you think? How much worth is my naked body?
Some people wanted to release photos of me half-naked.
Which lead to them receiving a fine for breach of contract for many millions of yen.
And you want to broadcast it like that?
What are you doing?
I thought that you'll be much more embarrassed and troubled.
I'm trying to endure it.
I'm an actress, after all.
Exposing my breast in front of people is not a big deal.
What are you trying to do?
No!
Stop!
D-Don't touch me!
I'm telling you to stop, right?
My body still wasn't touched by anyone and disgraced too!
It's not any shameful body...
That a man like you can touch as he want!
From my point of view it's just lump of meat.
Stop!
Don't claw my body!
Scars will remain!
No!
So what?
You should rather like this, right?
There's no way that I would like this!
There's no women who likes when her body is hurt!
That's strange.
You like to hurt others, but you don't like when someone hurts you?
My breasts hurts!
No way... If you'll use your claws like that...
Then I'm gonna...
I was nothing more than your younger sister acquaintance.
You're planning to play dumb?
What?
Something is touching my butt.
I'll be rap-
Do you really want to rape me?
Wait!
You're misunderstanding something!
I really have nothing to do with your younger sister!
And I'm going to ask this body if that's the truth!
It's true!
Please believe me!
Don't do anything cruel to me!
I'm innocent, after all!
Then complain about it to the people in the network!
Stop!
It hurts! It hurts!
This sensation... Don't tell me that she's a virgin?
It hurts! No! Don't put it in!
My body still wasn't disgraced!
I'm a virgin!
I still haven't done it!
So don't rape me!
Don't take my virginity!
I want to marry with the one I'll love and give it to him, in the future.
It was pretty a fairy-tale dream.
No! That's impossible!
My... My purity was taken like that!
I'm surprised.
I thought that they exposure you a lot in the media, because you're working for porn business.
I sell everything,
without doing such disgraceful thing thanks to my skills.
I always protected it and yet...
Why it was taken by such guy?
I for sure... I for sure won't forgive you this!
D-Don't go so deep!
Good!
Since I don't plan to forgive people who took Kaoru from me!
I'm telling you that I haven't done this!
I have nothing to do with it.
You have clumsy, indecent voice, without any charm!
If Himekawa Ayano fans will hear it, then they'll be disappointed!
No way! Don't tell me that...
You are really broadcasting everything?
No!
Such guy took my virginity!
And yet it was taken in front of everyone!
It hurts!
I really don't know anything!
I have nothing to do with your younger sister death!
Please, understand it!
You don't remember inconvenient things for you,
and you're just saying those convenient things for you, right?
N-No!
Please believe me!
Don't commit more sins for you younger sister's sake too!
Surrender yourself!
You girls should surrender!
If you forget it, then I'll make you remember!
I'm sure that...
Your sister doesn't wish for you to do something so cruel!
The dead ones don't wish anything, neither do they speak!
It hurts!
Don't say what Kaoru wanted because you were her acquaintance!
It hurts deep in me!
Do you know how many times my dick have penetrated your womb?
Dick?
Womb?
Hey! Do you know how violently my dick is twitching inside of you?
That's means...
D-Don't tell me that you want to release it all... Wait!
Don't tell me that you want to cum inside of my womb?
You can't!
Spare me this!
Don't fertilize me! Please spare me at least this!
Save m-
You're asking everyone in the network to save you?
If you keep asking them to save you it will destroy your reputation and a big scandal will occur, right?
No way!
You can't do this!
My current uncensored live broadcast is already going viral,
so this will be Himekawa Ayano's final masterpiece as an actress!
Don't cum in my womb!
I don't want to get pregnant!
Don't cum in me!
No!
I for sure won't forgiv-
Please!
Don't pour it in my womb!
It hurts.
So cruel!
Then, I want you tell me,
are you two really close friends with Rina?
You're not on good terms, right?
Who knows...
We might be a bit similar since we're different from others.
Are you three really close friends?
No.
We only meet inside the Academy.
We're not meeting each other outside the Academy.
In other words, you're not hanging out like normal friends?
That's right!
Ayano!
The other one didn't said that!
What are you doing?
Don't tell me that this is...
I'm really in the network?
You're doing this, even though you know who I am?
You'll be absolutely killed for doing something like this!
Killed?
By who?
Of course that by my fans!
They should be happy if you'll increase the range of services for them.
Wai... What are you doing?
No! Don't look!
Don't touch it!
Let me go!
I beg you, stop it already.
You can still stop!
D-Don't touch it! No!
It's filthy! Wai-
Don't expand it so much!
No! Stop! Don't do anything more!
Seems that everyone is curious if you're a virgin or not.
I-It hurts! Stop!
Take out your fingers.
Don't put your finger any further!
It's disgusting!
Don't scratch me over there!
My pussy will be injured!
You say so, but I can easily put my fingers so deep inside your pussy,
so that means your virginity has already been taken.
So what?
It's none of your business of I'm not a virgin anymore!
Don't be silly!
They don't have an erection! And I'm not wet!
Then what's this sound?
I don't know! I'm for sure not wet!
I'm not excited! I'm not such women!
I see!
But you can find an owner for yourself,
and then you'll still be able to live normally, even if this video will spread and you'll have to retire from public entertainment.
No!
Why everyone are writing weird things?
I'm not Milly!
I beg you! Let me go!
What are you doing something like this?
Don't embarrass me more!
I'm doing this so you'll tell the truth!
I'm telling you that I don't know anything!
I have nothing to do with your younger sister!
You have done something?
I see.
So you cornered my younger sister that easily?
No! That's not true!
It was just figure of speech!
I haven't cornered her! It wasn't me!
If it wasn't you, then who was it?
T-That's...
This is not a joke!
You can't do this! You can't!
Stop fooling around! You pervert with sister complex!
No!
S-Stop!
What do you know?
No.
No way... I end up like this once again.
What do you mean?
So you were really working for porn business?
Yes.
But I swore that I'll never do it again.
You mean porn business?
You girls were doing some secret job, right?
N-No! I don't know anything!
No!
No! Don't thrust your dick so deep!
My womb will be smashed!
S-Stop it already!
Don't put it so deep!
It's so tight over there... So tight!
What do you mean?
Say it clearly!
There's no way that I can say it.
I'll say it! I'll say it!
Pussy! My pussy!
My pussy is tight!
No! I'm not feeling it! That's not true!
That's impossible!
No!
F-Forgive me already.
At the top of the bed...
Don't do it so violently!
No!
Don't be so hard inside of my pussy!
No! I'm starting to feel it.
No! I don't want this, but my body is...
No! No!
I'm going to lose myself.
It's so big! So big!
This feeling...
No way! Don't tell me that...
You want to cum inside of me?
That's not true, right?
You really want to cum inside?
I beg you. Spare me at least that!
You can't cum inside... No!
If you'll do it so violently, then inside of me... Even if I don't want it...
I can't think anymore.
It feels good so deep in me!
I'm feeling it!
Dick! Your dick feels so good!
It's so good?
If that's the case, then I'll make you feel much more better!
No! It's so deep...
My womb is melting!
Pussy! Pussy! Pussy!
No! I'm...
So hot!
Hey! Just hurry up and tell the truth!
Who is Rina for you?
She is a stranger, but she was forced to hang out with us and carry our luggage.
Obviously such behavior towards her was bad,
but it's not my fault!
Rina didn't say "No."
If she didn't want it, then she should've resisted normally!
But she didn't do that and she hang out with us because she wanted to, right?
My sister too?
You sister was...
Seems that I have to punish you more.
No!