What? I... Where am I?
Hey, what is this?
Something like this...
Huh? I...
Rina? You too? Why...
What is this place?
You guys!
Ayano...
This is bad, this is bad...
Inami Misuzu
This is... Ayano...
This woman is Inami Misuzu.
She works as a model under the name of Mirei.
This girl is Yukawa Ayano, aka the actress, Himekawa Ayano.
Yukawa Ayano
She’s a student like Mirei, and is also
active in the world of show business.
And also,Tsubaki Rina.
Tsubaki Rina
She was once a close friend of my sister, apparently.
Who is it?
I’ve seen you somewhere...
Tezuka Ryou-san?
Surprisingly you remember that, after ignoring me for forever.
What’s with this? Putting stuff like this on us!?
It suits you quite well.
Hurry and take these off!
What do you plan to do to me!?
I have some things to ask you guys about, that’s all.
Then so you were to one who brought us here?
All I care about,
is why my precious sister had to die!
Dangerous!
Revenge - Website of Darkness
Report on Bullying, Fuel drop!? Question to the internet.
The murderer of my sister is amongst these three bitches... Arc.
It happened several weeks ago.
Dad, wait, calm down! What are you talking about?
My younger sister, died.
She ended her own life.
We lost our mom early, and our father
was always busy with work,
so we spent much time together growing up.
My sister, who would stand close and smile at me.
I love her more than the love between siblings.
No, we loved each other so.
Overwhelmed from sadness, even
my father was caught in tragedy,
and left the world forever.
Fortunately in the midst of sadness, he had
left enough money for me to live off of.
Other than that, I had lost everything that had mattered to me.
If anything was left,
Then it probably is, what is thought to be
left just before she committed suicide,
a last message from my sister.
What could she have to apologize about!?
What does that mean, that she’d cause
trouble, so she decided to kill herself!?
What in the world, had happened to Kaoru!?
Why are you staring at us all quite?
You’re disgusting.
Tsubaki Rina. I've heard your name a lot from my sister.
"My best friend”, she said.
Tell me!
If you are a close friend, then why did Kaoru have to die!?l
I... I don’t know anything...
I don’t know...
If you really are a friend of Kaoru, then please tell me the truth!
She’s telling you she does know, so let her be!
That’s right, I had no other way, so I talked
to every single girl that came out of school.
And I heard an interesting story from a girl
who was in the same class as Kaoru.
That Kaoru was bullied.
By the three of you.
We've been telling you that we don’t
know anything for a while now.
Stop accusing us of something we haven’t done!
I’ve never even talked to your sister!
Let’s all calm down and talk it through.
It was very unfortunate or your sister,
but it’s a misunderstanding!
Please listen! And then...
That hurts! What are you doing!?
Shut up! Don’t say anything unnecessary.
If you didn't have anything to hide, why
did you keep running away from me!?
You treated me like a stalker, and even brought in the
school and the police just to get away from me!
You’re definitely hiding something!
And I have the right to know.
What is this place?
What do you plan to do bringing me to a place like this?
If you guys aren't willing to tell the truth.
You’re going to torture us or something?
No, just interrogation.
Interrogation?
All of the questioning will be filmed, and
broadcasted live on the internet.
Why would you do that?
I’m getting the world to be a witness for this.
If I’m not the only person watching,
you can’t getaway with some makeshift
confession and deny it later.
This isn't some joke, alright!
If you’re willing to tell me everything you know with no lies,
I don’t mind forgiving you.
However... if you try to hide anything, or
you’ve done something to my sister...
I won’t have mercy!!
Hey!
Open up! I said open up!
Stay put there for a while.
No!
Let me out! Please!
Pointless.
This place was originally used as an isolation ward,
In other words, a jail for the sick.
It’s built so there’s no way people inside can get out,
and can only be locked or unlocked from the outside.
Then, let’s get you to answer on the
relationship between you three.
That’s... we’re just friends, of course!
We’re close friends!
Since you can say you’re close friends with no hesitation,
you must have great understanding between each other!
Of course...
Then, you must know a lot about each other’s private life, too.
Our private lives don’t have anything to do with your sister!
I decide on that!
What kind of things do you do in your free time?
Give me some story where you sound like friends.
Like I thought, you were just lying about being friends!
Or else it should be easy to tell me how
close you are as friends, right?
That’s...
Since you’re hiding things, I guess it can’t be helped...
Dangerous! Revenge - Website of Darkness
It hurts...
It hurts!
Forcing a lady into such an embarrassing
position and limiting her movement..
You can still call yourself a man?
Learn some shame!
Hey! Why don’t you say something!
Why don’t you say something? Like
introduce yourself to these guys.
What is this?
Could it be... you’re actually doing that??
Hey... do you understand what you are doing?
Do you know how much a nude picture of me is worth??
There was a seminude... photoshoot production...
And the money from the contract even though the
shoot was cancelled was in tens of millions!
And yet you’re just broadcasting it with no charge...
What do you think you’re doing!?
I thought you’d be more embarrassed or overwhelmed by this...
I'm holding back from that.
I’m an actress, so just getting my boobs
shown in front of people is nothing!
What are you doing!?
No! Stop it! Don’t touch!
I’m telling to stop!
I've never allowed anyone to touch...
It’s still a clean, pure body!
It’s not something cheap that... a sick person
like you... can lay your dirty hands on.
It’s just a pile of meat to me.
Stop it at once!
Don’t dig your nails inside! Your leave marks!
No!!
What’s wrong with that? You like that, right?
There’s no way I would like that!
There’s no woman that would like her skin being scarred!
That’s strange. You love hurting other people,
but can’t stand yourself getting hurt?
Stop... it hurts!
Don’t... use your nails...
I was merely an acquaintance... with your sister...
You’re stilling going to play dumb?
What?
Something is hitting behind...
I’m going to be...
No way... you really plan on violating me?
Wait! You’re misunderstanding!
I really have nothing to do with what happened to your sister!
That’s why I’m about to ask your body about that!
It’s true! Please believe me! Don’t do such cruel things!
I’m really innocent!
Then, why don’t you tell that to the people on the internet!
Stop... stop!
It hurts, it hurts!
This sensation... could it be that she’s a virgin?
It hurts! Don’t put it in!
My body has yet to be dirtied!
I’m still a virgin! I haven’t done it before!
So please don’t violate me... Don’t take my virginity!
I want to marry the person I love and
give it to him on our first night...
That’s quite the fairy-tale dream of yours.
No! Noway...
My... my first time... being something like this...
That’s surprising. You had quite a lot of
18+appearances in entertainment,
and I thought you must be doing the other businesses as well.
With my talent... I don’t have to do
such things... to gain popularity...
I’ve always protected it... and yet...
Why... to some guy like this...
I’ll never... never forgive you...
Not, not so deep...
I have no intentions on forgiving someone
who took Kaoru away from me!
I said... I didn't do... anything!
I don’t... have anything to... do with it!
What a miserable, disgraceful and unattractive voice!
If the fans of Himekawa Ayano were
to hear this, they’d be destroyed.
No way... could it be...
This is all...
Being raped by such a disgusting man...
and being a virgin... this was all broadcasted??
It hurts...
I don’t know anything about it!
I don’t have anything to do with your sister’s death!
Please understand!
You’re just conveniently forgetting everything
that is inconvenient for you!
That’s not it!
Please, believe me!
Stop adding to your crimes, for the sake of your sister!
Please turn yourself in to the police!
It’s you guys that should be turning yourselves into the police!
If you've forgotten already, I’ll make you remember.
I’m sure your sister didn't wish you
did such horrible things, either!
A dead person can’t wish for anything, and
won’t be able to tell anyone if they did!
It hurts!
Don’t you dare think you know anything about
Kaoru just being an acquaintance of hers!
It hurts!
It hurts... don’t...
Can’t you tell the tip hitting the entrance
to your womb again and again?
The tip... the entrance of my... womb...
Hey, you can tell how I’m pulsing inside you, right?
No way... you’re not going to...
Wait!
No way... not inside... not my womb...
Don’t, just that, please!
Don’t make me pregnant!
Please spare me from at least the creampie!
Help!
Now you’re asking the internet for help?
Well even if you actually get help, it’ll be a huge scandal!
That’s...
No way, don't!
The amazingly popular raw, unedited video spreading right now,
will become the last work of the actress Himekawa Ayano!
Not my... womb... not inside...
I don’t want to get pregnant!
Please don’t ejaculate!
No!
I don’t want to get pregnant...
Please, not into my womb...
It hurts...
You’re horrible...
Well then, I have to ask you.
Are you guys really friends with Rina?
You don’t seem like types that’d get along well.
Who knows? I might actually enjoy her
being the complete opposite of me.
Are the three of you really friends?
No... we only see each other in school...
never outside of school...
So you’re never together in your private life?
That's right.
Ayano!
The other person didn't say so.
What are you doing?
I’m being... broadcasted on the internet??
How dare you, do you know who I am?
You’ll definitely be killed for doing this!
Be killed? By who?
By my fans, of course!
If I give some more service, won’t they be happy?
Hey... what are you... going to do?
No, don’t look! Don’t touch...
Let go!
Please... stop already... it’s not too late yet...
Don’t touch...no!!
Not with your dirty hands! Not there!
No, stop! No more...
It seems like everyone is interested in if you’re a virgin or not.
It hurts...
Pull... your fingers out...
Don’t put your fingers in anymore....
it’s gross...
Don’t stir inside like that!
You’ll hurt my insides!
You say that, but you’re taking fingers in so
easily, you must be doing it quite a lot.
What’s wrong with that?
Me being a virgin or not is completely unrelated to you guys!
Don’t joke around, I’m not getting hard or wet from this!
So what is this sound?
I don’t know!
I’m definitely not wet!
Don’t misunderstand; I’m not that kind of woman!
I see. But at least someone will pay for you.
Even if this video is spread out and you
have to leave the show business,
you’ll at least still find a way to live.
That's not it! Why is everyone writing weird things?
There’s no way... I’m Mirei...
Please! Let me go already!
Why are you doing something like this?
Don’t embarrass me anymore!
To hear the truth from you, of course!
Like I said, I don’t know!
I don’t have to know anything about someone like you sister!
"Someone like my sister”!? “Don’t have to”!?
I see, so you pushed my sister with such light, uncaring feelings!
That's not it! That's not it!
That was just as figure of speech! I didn't push anything on her!
It wasn't me!
Then who was it!?
That’s...
Don’t joke around! That’s the one thing I can’t take!
No way!
Don’t fool around! You sis-con pervert!
No! No!!
Stop, stop...
Talk! What do you know?
No... that’s... I... again...
What do you mean, again?
Were you really sleeping around for business?
Even though... I never wanted anything like this every again...
So you are sleeping around??
Looks like you guys are hiding something!
That’s not it, I don’t know anything...
No... stop...
Don’t thrust so deep inside...
My womb will break!
No... stop already... no...
It hurts there... It hurts!
Where is this “there” you’re talking about?
Give some details!
There’s no way... I can say...
I'll say, I'll say it!
It’s my pussy! My pussy is being stretched out!
That’s not it... I’m not feeling it... that’s not...
No way...
No... please... let me go already...
No!
Don’t...
Don’t be so rough... I can’t...
You’re thrusting to hard into my womb...
No, I’ll... feel it...
No, even though I don’t want it... my body...
No... I’m losing myself...
It’s big... it’s too big! This feeling...
No way... you’re...
You’re going to ejaculated inside??
Please no! You’re not really... inside...
Please! Please spare me of that!
I can’t take it inside, I can’t! No!
If you’re that rough... not inside... but...
Huh... I can’t... think... it’s good...
Deep inside...
No... I’ll feel it...
Cock... cock feels good...
Is it that good?? Well then, I’ll make you feel even better!
So... so deep...
My womb is melting...
More, more, more!
It’s hot!
C’mon, tell the truth already!
What is your relationship with Rina?
I force her to go shopping with me, and she held my bags.
Like a servant of mine. You got a problem?
But... it’s not my fault.
Rina never said she didn't want to...
and if she didn't want to, she should just resist, right?
Since she didn't, Rina was happy with it, too!
Did you do that to my sister, too?
Well, with your sister...
Looks like you still need more punishment.
No!!