It's the first time I've felt something this amazing, Master.
I'm just an ordinary maid.
I simply serve the Zenouji family,
so you'll be acting as the observer.
For myself, that would most likely mean ignoring
whatever thoughts guests may have.
Well, it's because they have the best
family lineage, which is why l...
I'm not about to change my plans now, though.
You have to work hard for it, Master,
or else my salary will also be in danger.
I'll leave everyone in your capable hands.
That's why...
Please give it to my maid pussy!
Wow, your dick is still pouring it inside me.
I came too much with that dick,
no more, please...
Is the sight of it etched in your memory already?
You're going to experience this training every single day.
In order to become a sex slave.
Mother...
I have prepared for this moment for a long time.
To become a sex slave after our household went down in ruins.
W-With our current situation like this,
I have also mentally prepared myself.
From your perspective, what do you think of those women?
They are the finest subjects I have ever worked with.
I am looking forward to training them.
Remove your clothes.
Our clothes?
It'd be a nuisance to our training.
I'd also like to check out your proportions.
I-I understand.
Are we taking our panties off too?
No, keep them on.
It won't be worthwhile to immediately tell you to get naked.
Aren't you used to seeing naked women already?
There is no such thing as getting used to seeing naked women.
I wouldn't be doing this job if that's all it was about.
I see, so you're a pervert, then.
Your job as a trainer suits you well.
This is the first time I've seen this level of quality.
Your household did a good job,
though it's already in ruins.
Not only are you a pervert, but it seems
you also have a sharp tongue.
No need to lose your temper like that.
Since you're my finest subjects, I'm also quite worked up for this.
I'm not sure if you're praising or insulting me.
Okay, shall we begin.
Ruri, come over here.
I-I'm first?
Wait, she's still feeling nervous.
I'll go first, to let her calm down and see what needs to be done.
Ruri comes first.
There's no guarantee that she'll calm down after seeing it, anyway.
Onee-sama, I'm alright.
I've prepared for this already.
Oh, well said.
Then let's begin.
I'm totally exposed to a guy,
in this very shameful form...
I'm being touched...
My breasts are being fondled.
Ruri is now doing it with a guy.
Th-That's...
Would that thing fit?
Seems you haven't even touched it yourself.
You already saw your mother doing it, right?
This is exactly the same.
This is the same thing mother...
No! I...
Okay, here we go.
I apologize for the pain I shall cause you.
However, this is also part of what you need to become a sex slave.
How could that thing fit?
In mother's, and in mine too, that's just...
This big thing is inside me.
I'm feeling all tingly.
Wasn't it painful a while ago?
Umm, I felt a sharp pain as it went in,
but right now it's all tingly,
as it moves... as your dick moves inside.
So it's no longer painful?
Yes.
My insides feel hot, and it wants more.
Looks like you have the potential to become a slut.
I don't know about that.
But my mind's about to wander off somewhere,
so please don't push too hard.
Just immerse yourself in that sensation,
and I'll give you the best pleasure you're capable of feeling.
Your dick is rubbing inside, and something's coming...
Something weird is coming...!
There's lots of sticky cum on my tummy...
The smell is intense, it's making me dizzy.
Get used to that smell,
because you're going to smell it every day.
Yes...
She... just made the same expression as mother's...
You're next.
I-It's gotten big again...
It's my business tool.
No need to worry, because I will make your insides feel satisfied.
W-Who's worried? Don't just blabber things!
Just stand there.
I shall use a different technique I have used with my other subjects.
W-What are you saying?
Don't be afraid.
I said I'm not afrai-
Wait, what is this?
This is called intercrural sex.
I place my penis this way to give pleasure.
This perverted method is just...
His disgusting thing is actually...
Wait, what is this?
So, you also haven't touched yourself before?
You're actually quite pure despite your rebellious attitude.
Touched myself? No way...
It's the same when a man does it.
You comfort yourself, for your own benefit.
Even your mother understands.
Mother? No, that just can't be!
You'll soon understand as I train you further.
No way, I don't want to understand it!
It's useless.
For I shall let your essence as a sex slave seep within you.
Me doing this is just...
It seems you're the same as Ruri,
the level of pleasure you feel is extraordinary.
You're the best subject that I could have as a sex slave.
Hey, this is starting to become rough.
I'm your important subject, so handle me with care!
A lady that likes to have it her way, eh.
Hey, what are you doing?
You're wavering, are you not?
Lady Miki, your words might sound harsh,
but your body is surprisingly honest.
What are you saying?
Just do it already!
I want to end this quickly.
Ogling at me like this,
everything about me is now...
You understand the position you're in now, right?
Is that how you should treat your master?
You want me to beg?
I-I get it already.
Master, please...
I want you to give me the opportunity
for it by doing it with me down there.
Down there? Can you be more specific?
And what is it' that I should do?
I-In my pussy!
I said I want your dick inside my virgin pussy!
That first part you said was quite unnecessary, but oh well.
Well said.
As a reward, I shall penetrate your virgin pussy.
Reward? You made me say those things!
We're just at the tip.
Hey wait...!
No way, what is this?
Why?
This is just natural.
Ruri's reaction was actually the unusual one.
Stop... this...
Already complaining with just this...
This is nothing...
That's the spirit.
It hurts...
What is this?
It hurts, it hurts!
Why was Ruri...?
Just move already.
We're having sex right now, right?
If you want me to move...
You already understand what you should say, right?
Again?
Jeez, alright, I'll say it.
I just need to say it aloud, right?
Push it in.
Rub it inside my virgin pussy like you did with Ruri.
Very good.
You need to get used to this quickly in order to please your master.
Oh no, wait, this is too intense...
It hurts!
Oh no, this is...
This is too rough.
It may hurt right now,
but you'll eventually crave for it as you get used to it.
Me, want more of this?! No way!
That will never happen.
Not with this disgusting and painful thing.
It'd be troublesome for me if you didn't, anyway,
so I'll rape you as I please.
I won't get used to this!
You sure are cheeky for a slave.
Ruri got used to it almost instantly, you know.
Okay then, rape me then!
Push it harder inside me!
Well said.
I shall increase the pace, then.
It's all good that it feels great for you, huh?
I feel like my insides are about to get ripped apart, though.
I'm going to cum inside.
Inside?
I can't say no anyway so just do it!
Are you feeling all tingly inside?
Looks like it's your natural instinct kicking in.
No, what is this?
My insides are getting wet, and it's pushing even harder.
Feels a lot better than earlier, right?
I'm not about to...
Sloppy sounds of pleasure are reverberating inside.
No, oh no, I can't understand this.
My body is...
Why?
You're about to cum inside.
It feels hot.
It's being poured, and it's flowing inside me.
It's hitting me deep.
My insides are filling up...
Will I experience this every day?
Hey now, we're not done yet.
It's your duty to pleasure your partner.
No way, again?
It's being stirred inside.
Your cum...
It's overflowing.
It's even easier to push inside now.
No way, why...?
My body is...
Ruri.
No, don't, Ruri.
Don't look this way.
Don't look at me!
It's coming in and out of Onee-chan's pussy.
No, no, Ruri.
Stop, please don't say that!
Seems you get even more aroused while being watched.
What is this?
This can't be...
I'm going crazy.
For both of you to be able to cum so
shortly after losing your virginity...
So in the end it was the same for me...
This just can't be!
I can't believe I'm feeling aroused by this!
That's good, immerse yourself in that sensation.
No way, I...
Something is coming...
Something is coming!
It's coming!
It's flowing in!
Don't let it burst inside me!
My head is going blank.
My insides are being warped by his cum.
Becoming soiled like this...
So I really will become a slave.
Then, from now on...
You two.
I am definitely going to make you two
the best slaves that ever existed.
Original Animation
Mansion ~The Sensual Mysteries~
The Cheeky Sex Slave Miki ~ Erotik Disciplining of the Haughty Lady
For me to do things like these...
You need to master the art of pleasure.
I know already.
But this is too much for me.
Handle it with care, for it is a delicate thing.
Licking something like this...
Have I really gone so low?
Now take it all on your face.
Huh? Wait...!
What I've prepared for you is exceptional.
Wait, that is...!
No, stop...
Isn't your body unable to resist by now?
That, can't be...
My body feels hot?
No way...
This is too intense.
My body is slowly transforming,
it's being molded by the desires of this man.
What is this?
Hey...!
Giving pleasure is your job.
So it isn't proper for you to feel all the pleasure alone.
I understand that already!
I know that I need to provide pleasure.
I'm going to let you cum quickly then.
Seems you have a long way before you really understand.
Hey, I'm the one moving!
Stop!
If I can only get the technique right...
Oh no, I'm moving on my own.
How lewd of me.
There, keep it up,
do it until you squeeze it out from me.
I get it already.
I'm going to make you cum.
Hey, cum.
Cum already.
Hey!
You're about to cum, right?
It's flowing inside me...
He came inside me again.
I'm... really cumming...
I moved on my own, and even came...
What's wrong with my body?
It's experienced something terrible and yet...
He even humiliated me,
and made a fool out of me.
Also...
I have to hold myself together!
Ruri, is your body alright?
Yes.
It was a bit hard at first,
but lately...
Besides, Master is also looking out for me.
That's just a lie!
We don't know what he's thinking.
You can't just let your guard down!
O-Onee-sama.
Listen Well, Ruri.
You have to keep yourself together.
I'm here.
Nice dress you have there.
You told me to come here dressed like this, right?
The best subject
not only needs to be the best in action,
but also needs to be the best in conduct.
Though, I have no complaints about your potential.
I-I understand already... Master.
So, am I going to suck on that again?
I shall teach you how to do things differently.
Hey, am I really supposed to that... Sir?
Correct.
It is something that is well requested.
Though, they have to be big like yours, or it won't work.
Will it really feel good this way?
W-Well then... I'm doing it...
Your tit fuck.
Does it really feel good?
Good, keep that up,
then suck on it.
I'll even suck on it?
It's twitching, so it does feel good?
This thing? Men really are...
That's good, I'm glad that you learn quickly.
It's an honor receiving your praise.
Are you about to cum?
It's good of you to be able to predict this far,
as expected of Lady Miki.
You're going to take all of it inside of you.
I understand.
A-Are you satisfied now, Master?
We'll end this by training you.
No, please wait!
This is too sudden!
Your exposed ass is really asking for it.
Wait, what are you...?
Don't just...
I don't want this, and yet,
my body is becoming hot.
This is...
No, this is too intense!
It's pushing all the way.
No, please don't...
Oh no, I can't stop.
I'm feeling all tingly.
I'm about to go crazy.
No way, hey...!
Where are you touching me?!
Hey, stop!
What are you doing, stop right now!
I have to start training you here as well.
No, that part is...
That part isn't... stop!
It's not normal for you to do it there!
St-!
Why?
He's touching me at such an unusual spot, but I...
This is too intense...
No, no...!
It's over, right?
Can I go back now?
Yes, we're done for now.
Thank you very much for today, Master.
Jeez, he's such a...!
Treating me like a toy!
Just because I'm his slave doesn't mean
he can just make a fool out of me!
For crying out loud!
What did he just say...?
That man...
It's really a big help that you understand quickly.
Should we continue further down this path,
you shall soon become my greatest masterpiece.
T-That sounds really flattering.
Hmph.
My body feels hot whenever he touches me.
It's an instinct so I can't do anything about it, right?
Just because I'm shamelessly exposed to him doesn't mean...
He's my master, and I'm his slave.
When this ends...
Wake up.
Huh? W-Wait, what's the meaning of this?
Why so suddenly?
There are also times when they request
it in the middle of the night.
A slave's duty is to be able to do it whenever it may be required.
A-A good day, Master.
So... am I suppose to just suck on it again?
I suppose that would be enough.
I'm headed to a meeting assembled by the organization,
so I'll be leaving soon.
Oh, in that case,
have a nice trip, Master.
Yes, I think it will be quite a trip,
which is why I want to do tonight's session right now.
I knew you'd say that.
You seem to be quite honest about it.
Hmph, there's no use for me to act strong, anyway.
I've learned what you've taught me, you know.
So, do I really just suck on it?
I-It's called fellatio, right?
No, in reward for your honesty.
I shall play with your insides, Lady Miki.
Hey, wait!
I'm still all sweaty!
Let me at least take a shower!
You're just going to sweat again as we do it.
Jeez, besides...
This isn't really what I call a reward.
But it is for your body, right?
That's...
Oh yeah! I just have to act it out.
That way he'll end it quicker!
Jeez, you're really helpless when it comes to this.
It's too hard for me in the morning.
I think I'm about to lose it early.
Looks like it really feels good for you.
If it's this intense, then of course it will be.
I can feel it, even if I try to stop it.
I'm going to end this quickly.
Oh wow...
Oh no, my pussy feels amazing deep inside.
Your dick is pushing all the way.
I'm being fucked so much that I'm going crazy.
It's deep!
Your dick is going even deeper.
This is amazing, my insides are being penetrated hard.
It's opening my pussy wide.
That's good, I'm going to cum inside you then.
Are you about to cum?
Are you going to fill my pussy again?
No...
I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum!
Did you really think you could fool your master that easily?
I always know when you're actually serious or not.
It's almost about time for me to leave,
but before that, I'll have to punish my cheeky little slave first.
No, no, I'm sorry!
I won't do it again, Master!
Your acting was perfect, but not good enough to fool me.
Please forgive me, I beg of you!
I have to discipline my slave to be more obedient.
I'll listen to whatever you say.
So please don't punish me anymore!
I've trained different subjects before,
but it's my first time training a woman like you.
I-Is that so?
Anyway, how many women am I being compared with?
Just a few hundred.
Hundred?
Hmph, that's an amazing then.
Then it's nearly not as satisfying with me, huh?
What are you saying?
I told you that you'll be my greatest masterpiece, didn't I?
Y-Yeah, you're right.
I-I remember it now.
Ayame, Ruri, and you, Lady Miki,
I shall make you three the best sex slaves in existence.
I see, so that makes it the three of us, huh?
Then I want you to do it already.
Jeez...
Doing this makes me...
Why?
I appreciate your attitude,
Lady Miki.
Hey, Master.
Can't you do something about that?
About what?
I'm your slave now, right?
There's no point in calling me 'Lady Miki' anymore.
It's too late to change what I call you, though.
Here, I'll pour it all inside and make you crazy with it.
Miki.
Pour it inside me.
Fill me with it, Master.
Punish me with all of your cum.
You really are feeling it already.
Then take it all.
Your cum is coming.
My mind's going blank.
Lots of it is about to come out of your dick.
It's going to make me crazy!
It's coming!
Master, I'm sorry...
For doing it...
Master, your dick is too amazing.
Inviting me all the way here...
I'm about to take lots and lots more of your cum,
so I want to work hard to always take it all.
For me to be able to service your dick anytime.
Amazing...
You've made lots of women crazy with
that amazing dick of yours, right?
Are you feeling jealous again?
What, no!
And what do you mean by again?
That's not true, jeez.
It's so intense!
Did you happen to meet someone named Marina in your work?
Haven't heard the name.
Ah, I see...
She's a dear friend of mine,
but she suddenly disappeared.
I just heard it later on, though,
that her family also went bankrupt.
That's why...
Why bring it up now?
It's been bothering me for quite some time now,
but I just didn't have the opportunity to ask.
I'm sorry, I guess this is not the time to ask such questions.
I have to concentrate on your dick, Master.
Your dick...
It's making me cum lots.
A friend, huh.
It's not really my priority, but I'll look into it.
Really?
I'm happy.
Master, thank you.
I can no longer be separated from your dick.
Cum, please cum, master.
Fill me, let your cum flow inside my womb.
Hurry, and fill me!
It's coming, and it's filling my pussy!