This is weird, my body feels really hot all of a sudden.
This is the body that you will now use to pleasure your master.
Yes, but...
My body feels really tingly, this isn't normal!
Your body seems to be craving for it.
That is a good sign.
Is, is that so?
I'm... but this still feels weird.
Like something's in my body...
And it's trying to well up,
it just feels...!
Do not fret, everything's fine.
Just stay still.
This is... oh no, it's coming!
This is...!
I just... lost consciousness for a moment.
You should try to get used to that sensation.
Y-Yes...
Umm, well...
W-Would it be alright to do it once more?
...What?
I thought maybe your dick still wants to do it,
and still wants to ejaculate one more time.
You're quite astute.
You just thought of a way to satisfy your partner.
It was an excellent reaction as a slave.
Though, I don't really have time anymore.
Getting it properly cleaned will have to do.
Cleaned? What shall I do then?
Try to think for yourself.
It'll get soiled by my fluid so...
It's clean now.
You have surprised me in a really good way.
Your potential as a slave is remarkable.
Thank you very much.
Mansion ~The Sensual Mysteries~
Original Animation
Klutzy Female Sister Slave - Ruri - The Doubt-Widened Lewd 'Openings'
I got praised by my Master!
But, he said I still need more training.
Does that mean I'm falling behind?
I'm falling way behind mom and onee-sama?
It seems it's still not too late to turn you into the perfect slave.
Wait, then would that mean I'm about to fall behind?
If so... then I have to work harder.
I need to be trained a lot.
Huh? Eh?!
Wh-What's wrong?
So you're awake.
I thought of training you for a bit.
O-Okay.
You must masturbate in front of me right now.
Mastur... bate?
To sexually arouse yourself, With the objective
of achieving physical pleasure.
Eh?!
That means I have to do lewd things to myself?
That's too embarrassing.
You said you wanted me to train you, isn't that correct?
You said that it was so that all three of us could live again in peace.
Y-Yes, I did say that.
You have to overcome this embarrassment with your own courage.
I-I've already decided to do my best, so...
I'll do It!
Well I... I'll do it by myself.
I-I'm done preparing.
Looking at it again, I see that it is really beautiful.
Petite, with such an alluring shape.
E-Even if you compliment me...
It'll be so embarrassing that I'll simply want to run away.
Now, now, I don't want you to go anywhere.
Okay, do as I instructed you.
R-Right here...
Do it a bit harder.
O-Okay.
Th-This is embarrassing.
If you can learn to endure that embarrassment,
then you can endure most of the things
that you will soon experience.
If I learn to masturbate, all embarrassing
things will no longer be embarrassing?
I cannot say it with absolute certainty, however,
do you not notice that you can now
do it with more ease than before?
I'll try to do it again.
It's starting to feel really tingly after doing it a bit harder.
It feels the same when Master touches it...
This is quite... weird.
That's masturbation.
The act of pleasuring yourself.
This is really weird...
It's gotten wet, even though I'm just doing it by myself.
Keep your fingers moving.
It's your duty to show it to me.
Y-Yes.
It's making strange sounds, as it gets even wetter,
is this unusual?
It's just a normal reaction.
Miki and Ayame also react the same way.
Onee-sama and mother also get this wet...
This is...
My hips are moving on their own.
I felt the same when I was having sex.
You should let your body act on its own.
I really can't... my body just keeps on...!
This is...!
Oh no...
My head feels completely tingly.
What should I do?
I'm back to normal.
It's not sex, but the sensation is the same...
That's the point of absolute pleasure.
The point of absolute pleasure...
My nether regions still feel like they want to do it.
How long will it take before this feeling subsides?
Now I get it...
I'm going to teach you the difference
between masturbation and sex next.
It's going deep inside me!
Your dick is penetrating the spots where my fingers couldn't reach.
I'm having sex again with you, Master.
It feels a lot better than masturbation, right?
I-I'm not sure.
Both feel so embarrassing, yet so strong and good.
And it's rubbing a lot of spots inside.
It's totally incomparable from earlier.
So deep...
Despite that, your hips are moving on their own.
Your body doesn't seem to feel embarrassed at all.
You can't seem to let yourself go,
so I shall make you feel it more.
No, Master.
If you keep on...
Oh wow...
Your dick is now rubbing the same spot that I caressed earlier.
It feels even more amazing, and it won't stop!
This dick, and even my embarrassment...
Everything feels amazing.
Dicks are far better than masturbation...
Oh no, I'm going to cum again, my mind's going blank!
That is what you call an orgasm.
Y-Yes, I am about to experience an orgasm.
I'm cumming, I'm going to cum!
That was, amazing...
Ruri.
Y-Yes?
I forgot to tell you something.
From now on, you are going to be by my
side when there's no training sessions.
Eh? B-But why would you...?
It'd be troublesome for you to continue
with that same scared attitude of yours.
I need you to do this to get used to it faster.
O-Okay...
So, I am being a nuisance...
I have to work harder,
I have to get everyone's normal lives back as soon as possible.
But, even if I do try to study it...
Oh yes, Ryou-san!
Wait, it won't do me any good to eavesdrop, right?
Yes, he hasn't noticed yet.
I understand.
It is unexpected that we still have to postpone it,
but I'm going to have to end him sooner.
Oh no, I just heard something really serious!
But, I have to tell my Master right away.
So it was Ruri-san after all.
This is disconcerting.
I've brought coffee.
Yes, thank you.
I'm going to start Miki's training in a short while.
You can take a break in your room.
Y-Yes.
S-So.... what are you going to make me do this time?
Just learning techniques won't help anymore.
I'll have to make you accept the fact that you are naturally lewd.
Wh-What?
Pleasure is the only thing we slaves need, right?
It's all about tricking the person's mind.
Such deceit requires complete focus.
For a slave that is.
Learn that, and you can even trick me eventually.
I'm not a slut!
And as a daughter of the Zenouji family, I'll never be!
How long are you going to hold on to that?
You already understand your situation, right?
Even so, I don't remember needing
to throw my pride away even once.
As trivial as your pride may be, you won't need to throw it away.
You only need to accept the fact that you're lustful.
I will never accept it!
I'm...
Your anger is making you more sensitive.
You can feel it, right? It's overflowing.
Shut up.
I'm not...
I can tell.
That I'm starting to overflow down there.
Lustful? I couldn't possibly be...
I'll show you that I can trick you.
I, whose soul has been tarnished ever since becoming a slave.
Hey...
You still won't accept it?
You sure are trying hard.
No.
I'm not lustful!
And I will never accept that I am!
Are you not going to let it out like usual?
The fake voice that you use to feign pleasure.
If I let out a moan now,
then I'll really be...
I will not accept it.
This arousal and these secretions, because I'm lustful? No way...
To accept it is...
I'm...
Just because I'm a slave doesn't mean that I'm also...
I'm Miki of the Zenouji family!
W-Wait...!
You're scaring me!
No, you're really scaring me...
Are you listening?
Jeez..!
Oh, I forgot to mention,
we're going to extend your training program.
All of this to make you the perfect slave.
That sounds really great.
I'll work hard for you then.
In order to be the best.
Yes, the best personal slave that I could ever have.
W-Wait, what are you talking about?
What does that mean?
I'm not about to let go of prospective masterpiece.
Your personal slave?
What are you suddenly talking about?
It's something about your friend.
Your acts may be unrefined, but you were pretty
serious about it, so I did some research.
Sorry for being unrefined then!
I learned many interesting things along the way.
In any case, you are going to serve me as my personal slave.
I want the cooperation of each and every one of you.
Each and every one of us?
Mother and Ruri, too?
Everyone?
Correct. Though I may soon get very busy.
Hmph, what are you saying?
Really, you're such a...
O-Okay, I get it already.
I'll be your slave.
Your personal slave.
I'll dedicate my heart and soul!
And here I was, trying very hard to hold back.
This is just unfair.
Jeez...
Idiot!
What are you going to do to quell my anger?
I'm a lustful woman.
A lewd slut that gets crazily aroused by my master's dick.
Alright.
As proof of our contract, I shall let you cum.
This is intense!
I'm getting hornier than usual with your dick today...
You are now my personal slave, Miki.
I'm your slave, I'm now your personal sex slave.
Please, let me cum.
I want my Master to make me cum!
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming!
Amazing...
I'm cumming... as your personal slave...
What should I do?
Ryou-san's just said something outrageous.
I...
Come in.
Umm...
It is quite late. What's the matter?
My... ass is, well...
I've... I've, now prepared myself for it!
So... please train me...
Ruri, calm down.
I don't understand what you're trying to say.
I'm sorry.
Umm... you were saying something before
about also doing it in the ass.
I was really scared, and didn't want to do it.
But, now that I have to work harder, I thought...
That I should...
Also, I at least want my first time to be with Master.
That's why...
I-I beg of you.
Please train me with my ass.
Teach me how to have anal sex!
For you to expose your asshole like that on your own accord...
Please don't say that, it's really embarrassing.
I like it.
Then I shall violate your asshole right here and now.
Eh? You're licking it?
That's... Master...
Yes, because we need to loosen it first.
You can't do that! My ass is...
Master...
My ass... is starting to feel tingly...
This is...
The sensation is intense.
Why do I feel like this?
It seems to have loosened up well already.
It might be painful at first,
but you'll soon experience even more
pleasure as you get used to it.
E-Even more?
Y-Your tongue is...
It's entering me.
She's about to cum with her ass only?
Perfect timing for my preparations.
Master, something's welling up inside me.
It's my ass, and yet I'm about to cum!
My hips feel like they're melting!
It feels different than in my pussy,
but it also feels good in my ass.
I'm going to take your ass’ virginity.
Not just your purity, as I am also about penetrate deep inside.
Y-Yes, please do.
Your dick... is entering my ass...
It's filling, it's filling my ass' insides.
My dick is all the way inside, up to the base.
I'm going to move now.
I feel like letting it out,
but then it starts pushing hard inside again.
My ass feels amazing.
My insides are all warm and fuzzy.
I can clearly tell that I'm twitching because of it.
It's hard and thick.
Something big is happening inside my ass.
You can even get this aroused with your asshole?
That's good.
I'm going to make you cum all the way then.
It's my ass, and yet I...
It's different from my pussy, but...
Why is this...?
My ass feels all tingly, it's so weird!
My ass... it feels strange...
It feels great, even if it's my ass.
Just like how it feels in my pussy.
I'm going crazy!
Thank you very much, Master...
I'm...
I'm going to work hard.
So please train me more.
You really have a lot of potential.
And it'd shine even brighter if I refine it more.
Which is why I have decided to extend the training period.
Eh?!
I'm going to make you into the best slave there is.
E-Eh?
Eh?!
You, you can't!
Master, you can't do that!
You mustn't!
What's wrong all of a sudden?
You must not do that!
Master, I'm going to really, really work harder,
I'm going to be a great slave!
Yes, I want you to become a great slave,
hence my reason for doing such a thing.
You can't, you can't, you just can't!
Ruri?
You just can't!
Hey!
What have you done?
What happened to Ruri?
Well, I just said something about extending the training period.
Really now?
You didn't do something weird to her, did you?
Wh-What?
You were right beside the window during
the entire time I was training her, yes?
Then I don't have to answer that.
Th-That's...
Hmph.
I'm not going to forgive you if something happens to Ruri.
Hey, why don't you start looking for her already?
Good grief, for a slave to order her own master around...
What should I do?
I just did something unforgivable...
M-Master.
Umm... I, well...
I'm sorry!
It must be about Ryou, am I correct?
Master, how did you...
Both of us have been doing something else in the shadows.
Ryou.
Aww, I've been found out.
R-Ryou-san!
Is... that so?
I'm sorry about this, Ruri.
Miki asked me to quell your worries.
So, what are your plans?
I'm fine as long as it's fun.
So I'm going wherever you're going, Master.
R-Ryou-san...
She's just like that.
Which is why I can actually trust her more.
It's an honor.
Now then, back to the shadows...
Umm...
Master, I...
It'd be troublesome if it'd gotten any bigger.
But, I'll have to settle something to end this problem.
I... I...
I never intended to make you worry.
But it seems I have pressured you instead.
This was entirely my mistake, please accept my apology.
Master, don't!
I was just worried about your safety, so I...
So I...
Ruri.
Will you assist me as my personal slave?
I was really worried.
Having sex with a stranger, and receiving lots of his cum,
but, having been trained by you,
I then wished for this to last forever.
Which is why I am very happy that you asked
me to become your personal slave,
and, for me to also be with mother and onee-san...
Listen.
A slave gives up everything for her master.
Everything, for her master...
You shall forget your training,
and simply learn to enjoy pleasuring me.
You shall give up everything for me, as a woman.
I-I understand.
I shall give everything to you.
Well said.
I-In here?!
Master...
You are now mine.
I shall enjoy keeping you as my personal slave.
Master...!
Amazing... your dick is penetrating me really deeply.
My thing is sucking it in,
your thing is really amazing, Master.
I'm being completely stirred by this dick.
It really is amazing.
Fill this slave pussy completely, Master.
It's so thick, I'm starting to go crazy with it.
Master, your hard and raw dick is rubbing me.
My deepest parts are being hollowed out.
Oh wow...
It's clumsily rubbing me, and I'm about to cum.
I'm going to...
Just let those sensations take control of you.
Master, please rub it harder inside me, make me crazier!
I'm...
I'm cumming.
I'm going to cum with your dick.
Master's going to make me cum!
Master...
We're going to get really busy soon.
I'm counting on you, Ruri.
Yes, it's okay.
I'm going to do my best, so everyone can stay together.
Yes, that's right.
It's alright.
Things are going smoothly on this side.
They've been vigorously trained as slaves
to be taken in by the household.
I believe a report will be coming in the next meeting.
That is, if all of you are still alive at that time.
It's okay now, Marina is safe.
She's currently held at the place we planned for her.
Master, preparations here are also complete.
Alright, both of you go on ahead.
I'm going out with Ruri and Ryou.
Jeez, okay then.
Please be careful.
Master, will you be alright?
I'm done preparing here.
Okay, now we'll have them come during our training session.
Master...
Am I going to be seen by them while doing this?
Ruri, now is not the time to feel ashamed.
I'm counting on you.
I-I'm okay.
I have been trained,
for my master, and for everyone.
Master, your dick feels really amazing.
Your dick is penetrating me deeply, Master.
Oh yes!
Push your dick inside me more, Master.
Make me go crazy with it!