Chapter 1
Ren's Diary
April 16th
Today is the graduation we've all been waiting for from nursing school.
From now on, l'll become a trainee and work in the real world.
XX Year of Heisei- Graduation
Teachers, thank you very much for everything.
l'll never forget the words that l said in front ofthe Nightingale statue today.
l'd like to be a fine nurse capable of dealing with patients face to face.
To tell you the truth, l'm a little worried.
But l will do my best!
l finally found you, my pretty Nightingale.
lt's the finest specimen so far.
Those patients don't deserve her!
l'm not letting you go now, Ren Nanase...
You're my greatest experiment.
l'm going to take the results of this ''female body experiment''...
...and put it on to this digital disc.
l can't wait.
Chapter 2
Ren's Diary
May 7th
l heard disturbing rumors today.
A serial rapist has been attacking many women lately...
...and the trainees think it's my doctor.
This is terrible!
l won't let them say things like that about my doctor!
l'm sure that if l see him, all the false accusations made against him will...
That's why l decided to pay a visit to his home.
But at his place...
Doctor?
Doctor Tosatsu?
lt's Ren Nanase.
l'm coming in. Doctor?
May 7th.
l can't believe Ren would come and see me herself...
Good girl.
l'll treat you real good, Ren.
My experiment begins.
Doctor?
No! What are you doing, Doctor?
No, it can't be!
No, it's not true!
This can't be...
No!
Stop it!
Please stop, Doctor!
No!
No! Don't look at it!
Stop!
lt hurts! lt hurts!
lnside... lt's coming inside!
No! Stop it, Doctor!
No! Stop!
Don't look at it! Don't look at it!
This is terrible!
What are you... Stop... The bathroom...
l want you to beg by speaking in a shameful way!
No, l can't do it!
l can't hold it! l'm going to pee!
lt hurts! My stomach hurts!
Take it out!
No! l can't hold it!
Doctor, it's coming out! Take out the plug...
My feces... My dirty feces...
Let me release it!
Doctor! lt's coming out!
Take a look at that...
Looks delicious.
No!
Chapter 3
Ren's Diary
What happened to me?
Doctor...
l was forced to play along with the doctor...
And did those awful things with my ass...
He's deceiving me.
The doctor is deceiving me...
What a terrible man...
Tosatsu's Diary
May 16th
Ren is willing to accept my love.
lt's the first step to my wonderful experiment.
During her training sessions, l have made her submit completely.
Until Ren becomes mine...
l'm going to try out the echo testing device.
The echo testing device is a machine that uses sound wave echoes...
...to monitor the state of the abdomen and visualize it on the monitor.
Well, seeing is believing.
Come to the front, Nanase.
What? Hurry! There's little time!
Yes.
Doctor! Be quiet!
You're disturbing the lesson!
lsn't this bad?
This is just too much.
Try to relax.
Do you want to be in pain?
Well? Can you feel the liquid going inside?
No... Everyone is watching me!
Doctor! lt's painful!
There's no need to hold back.
This is part ofthe lesson, you know.
Go ahead and discharge.
What? l can't...
No! l can't do it!
Are you sure?
You don't mind if they find out about our relationship?
No... no...
No! Stop it! Stop it!
No!
Doctor...
Nanase doesn't seem to be enjoying it.
What is it?
Any of you want to take her place and shit in front of us?
Well...
Ren, there's no need to hold back.
No, please stop!
There's only the two of us here.
That's what you need to think.
No!
lt's very stinky!
Well? Doesn't it feel good?
Are you going to climax?
Chapter 4
Ren's Diary
They warned me about the doctor today.
They said that the doctor is rumored to be the serial rapist...
...so l should watch out for him.
But somehow, l...
Why? l don't know who l am.
l just want to disappear.
Tosatsu's Diary
May 27th
Today, Ren's colleagues told her to file a lawsuit against me.
l may have done too much in front of everyone...
...but it seems like Ren has ignored what her friends said.
Well, well.
Look what we have here.
Does this mean my experiment is actually working?
Looks like Ren is going to crumble much quicker than l thought.
Doctor!
Get a hold of yourself, Doctor!
What happened?
Sol... Parament... Cyanamide...
These are dangerous!
Doctor!
Doctor...
Ren...
Please promise me that you won't take those pills again.
Ren... why?
Please, Doctor...
l...
Does it feel good, Doctor?
l want your cock, doctor...
No... Why?
Why am l so wet?
lt's inside... Your cock is inside me...
Doctor! Doctor!
lt's all right...
lnside... You can come inside me...
l'm coming!
Do it!
Don't worry. Just come inside me...
l want to have your baby!
So l want you to come inside!
Please give me your semen! Plenty of it!
Release it into my sticky virgin pussy!
l want you to impregnate me!
Chapter 5
l found out about it.
Ren found out about my pills.
The doctor was mentally ill, so he kept taking a powerful drug...
lt's okay. l don't mind if Ren looks down on me...
lf l can be of some help, then l will do anything...
l have to make this experiment work perfectly...
l want to help him...
Just you wait and see, Ren.
l think this is the very first step as a nurse...
Mine... Ren is all mine!
Chapter 6
Ren's Diary
Today, my mother was hospitalized at my hospital.
l was hoping that she would get better...
Her illness is very complicated.
But the doctor asked me if l wanted my mother to take this new medicine...
...as part of an ongoing experiment that may cure her illness.
However, l can't tell anyone about this...
Mother, please don't worry.
The doctor is really a nice person...
Tosatsu's Diary
More.
l want to make Ren crazier.
l'll use any means necessary.
l'll make her lonely and disclose everything...
Then l'll make her my woman!
lt's great! lt's the greatest plan!
l'll do it! l'm definitely going to do it!
With this, l can have Ren to myself!
Please. Let's do it somewhere else.
No! We're doing it right here!
You promised, remember?
But doing it in front of my mother is...
Don't worry.
She's sound asleep from the medicine.
l get more excited this way!
Hurry!
lf you don't do it, then l'll violate your mother.
Squeeze it much harder!
Doctor... how does it feel?
Does it feel good?
Okay, l'm coming!
Ren! l'm going to release it on your face!
l'm coming!
Well? How do you like my semen?
Yes, it's very thick.
Drink it up.
What?
lt's only natural. Enjoy drinking it.
You really want me to...
No, you have to drink it all.
Let me see it!
Use your tongue and swallow it!
Savor the taste slowly and swallow it.
Good. You swallowed all ofit, right?
Yes...
What do you say?
Thank you for the meal.
You're very cute, Ren.
Chapter 7
Ren's Diary
My mother passed away.
She couldn't do anything...
Being with the patients when they die is also a nurse's duty as well.
l can't believe my mother was the first person to teach me that...
lt's just so sad...
But the doctor is not nice to me...
What should l do?
Tosatsu's Diary
Life is too short.
But we doctors are always seeing patients die before our eyes, Ren.
So we should savor these pleasing moments and enjoy them all we can!
l mean, you can't get away from me now!
l'll prove it to you right now.
You're really a slut.
Dripping so much cunt juice...
You're a fine bitch!
No!
You're a no-good cunt who likes being pleasured at your mother's funeral!
Doctor! What are you...
lt's cold!
lt's coming... lt's coming inside!
Why don't you confess to your mother?
Since you're such a lousy cunt.
Don't you feel sorry foryour mother?
No! No!
My pussy...
l'll put it in here as well.
One, two...
That's it! That's what l wanted.
Yes, it feels good.
Stick it in! Stick it in!
Stick your cock in it!
lt feels so good!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
My pussy is coming!
Doctor! Doctor!
No! l'm coming!
Give it to me!
Give me your cock.
My pussy... Stick it inside my lousy pussy!
Do it! Do it!
Do me with your cock!
Stick it in! Hurry up and stick it in!
Stick your cock inside!
Doctor! Doctor!
lt went in!
Your cock went all the way in!
ln and out!
lt's going inside my pussy and out!
Your cock is going inside my pussy and out!
ln and out!
Yes! lt feels so good!
l'm getting numb!
Yes, Doctor!
My lousy pussy feels good!
l can't take it anymore!
My pussy feels good!
Give me your cock!
l want your cock juice!
l want it!
Semen! l want your semen!
l want yourthick and smelly semen!
Shoot it inside my lousy pussy!
Let me have it all!
Please release it inside my pussy!
Amazing!
lnside... Release it inside!
Release it! Release it from your cock!
Do it inside!
Yourjuice! Yourjuice is flowing inside my pussy!
lt's going inside my lousy pussy! lt's fresh!
l'm coming! l'm coming!
Mother! Mother!
l'm sorry...
l'm sorry, Mother...
Chapter 8
Ren's Diary
Mother, l think l might be crazy.
l'm very forgetful these days.
l forgot to go to the hospital yesterday, and the head nurse yelled at me.
Maybe l'll take another day off...
l don't think l'm myself at all these days.
l can only be myself when l'm with the doctor.
When l'm with the doctor, l'm not afraid of anything.
l don't think l'll fear death either.
l have to go shopping tomorrow...
Tosatsu's Diary
l decided where we should honeymoon.
Mars. lf l take you to Jupiter and introduce you to them...
...l'm sure they'll be very surprised.
They thought l was never going to get married...
lf l don't hurry, Ren is going to die.
l'm going to protect you, Ren!
We'll defy death and forget about honest lives. Till death do us part.
Yay! This breakfast looks wonderful.
Bon appetit.
Delicious.
lt's really delicious.
But yours needs a little more flavor.
Much more...
Doctor, l want you to release your load inside my mouth.
Using my mouth, then in and out.
My face looks like my wet pussy...
...so l want you to give me all your semen!
l want you to release your juice all over my orgasmic face.
Let me have it!
Give it to me like you do it inside me!
Release it all over my face!
Give it to me, like they do it in those porno videos!
There's so much!
l can't believe you released this much onto my smelly cunt face...
Doctor!
No, Doctor... What are you...
Doctor! lt's amazing!
lt's cold and feels good!
Feels good!
Chapter 9
Ren's Diary
Christmas! Christmas!
The doctor and l are just like Santa Claus.
The doctor told me...
...to prepare lots and lots of presents...
...for our patients!
l hope you're watching, Mary.
Tosatsu's Diary
Nurse, please stop this!
Why?
You like my dirty mouth, don't you?
lt's all right.
You can let your cock move in my mouth and release your load inside.
Just like you release it inside a pussy...
...you can just go ahead and release your entire load in my mouth.
lf you keep rubbing it that hard...
What is going to happen?
lt's going to flow out!
Think of my slutty face as my pussy...
...and release your load on my face, like in those porno movies.
l want you to come.
Release your load on my face!
l'm coming!
Amazing!
lt's not getting smaller at all.
l'm going to have to punish your horny cock with my lousy pussy!
Does it feel good?
Does my horny pussy feel good?
Amazing!
Hey, stick it in!
l want you to stick your cock all the way inside my horny pussy!
That's it! You're a pro!
Amazing! l can feel your cock!
lt feels so hard inside my wet pussy!
Yes! Yes! lt feels good!
My lousy pussy feels good! My lousy pussy feels good!
You can release it inside!
Just like when you release it while using those sex paraphernalia.
Use my horny pussy!
You can release it inside as many times as you want!
Do it! Use my pussy and release it inside!
Release it like there's no tomorrow!
Do it! Release your load inside!
Amazing! l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
l'm coming! My lousy pussy is coming!
My lousy pussy is coming with your cock!
l'm coming!
Release it inside!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
lt's coming out... Your juice is flowing out!
Your fresh juice is coming out!
l can feel your cock juice released inside my lousy pussy...
Fresh...
Your cock juice was released inside my lousy pussy...
l can't control myself!
Give it to me. l want you to use your cocks...
...and punish this perverted nurse!
Give your presents to this no-good Santa!
Put your cocks in my mouth too!
l'm a perverted nurse with a lousy pussy!
Enjoy this body as a present!
Amazing! Your cock feels good!
Give it to me! Give me your semen!
Give me all you got! Give me your semen!
Take it with your nose!
You have to take it in some more!
Move your hips more! l want to drink this girl's urine!
Use your hand to collect my semen!
l'm coming too. Collect it with yourface!
Anal beads and anal vibrator!
Do you feel it with your ass too? Pervert!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
Hey, she's climaxing!
Yes! Yes! She's one crazy bitch!
l feel like pissing inside her!
Go ahead and do it!
l'm coming! l'm coming! l'm coming!
Release it on my face. Let me climax while you put it on my face!
Give it to me! Release it inside!
l'm coming!
Take this semen spaghetti!
l have some semen banana here!
Ren, l have some milk semen for you!
This is great! lt'll rejuvenate me!
Do it!
Release your semen onto my sticky cunt face!
Make this the best white Christmas!
We're not done yet! Let me do you one more time!
Let us enjoy it some more! Let me do you one more time!
Let me have it...
More...
Chapter 10
Ren's Diary
Everything began from that day.
On the night of the graduation, the doctor took me home with his car.
And then...
lt was painful, filthy, and it made me sick...
My life changed so much that night, and there was no turning back...
l...
Tosatsu's Diary
Double suicide?
l knew he was a shady character.
But the woman is still alive.
Yes!
Hey, why is it that l can find you...
...wherever you may be?
Hey, why is it that you want to be like me?
l wonder.
Hey, that's why you're all alone.
You just end up hugging yourself in the end.
But l always see you from the sky.
l'm always by your side.
l'm opening the window.
l place my cheek near the moon inside my dream.