That memorable smile that you
and I have seen together.
Tonight, alone in a dark room, I'm watching.
I can't remember the last scene.
The one that I want to see is different
it's a more happy ending.
Where the both of us have dream,
the real last scene.
When I look over my shoulder, you're by my side.
Is such happiness selfish I wonder?
I can't decide what to choose...
Nogami...
Huh?
Kuwabara-sensei...
Hi...
Out shopping?
Yes. I was just about to go home, but I saw you.
Without thinking I called out
your name. Is it a bother?
It's not a bother at all... I'm happy, actually!
That's great. I have something I'd like to talk to you
about. Vould you keep me company for a while?
Keep you company...?
It's okay, it won't take too long. I just wanted
to talk to you about something, that's all.
Ok, if that's the case...
Then, let's go.
Okay.
To be invited out by Kuwabara-sensei
is quite surprising.
Hmmm? Why?
Everyone is saying that, although you
look kind, you're more of a strict type.
That's not really true.
Furthermore...
Hmm?
The first time I spoke to you was so sudden that
I was shocked and said strange things...
Hahaha, did you?
Sensei, please don't laugh like that.
Sorry, sorry.
Sensei?
We'll arrive there soon.
Sensei, it's a dead end.
That's alright, I'd like to talk
privately just between us.
But, in such a place...?
If we don't talk in such a place,
it would be bad for you.
Huh?
Nogami... Why did you do that kind of a thing?!
Sensei! What kind of thing?
Don't play dumb with me. That shop earlier...
you should understand now!
That shop earlier?
Are you still trying to dent it? Coincidentally,
I saw what you did!
Huh... what are you talking about?
Sensei, what? Stop it!
What's this! What's this!?
I don't know! I don't know!
When I was just about to call to you in that
shop, I saw you put these into your bag.
I thought that if you would admit your crime and
return the stolen goods that I would forgive you...
But you... you...!
How can this be! I didn't do such a thing!
You did it! I was watching the whole time!
I didn't do it... I didn't do it...
Stealing without realizing it... What
an abnormal stealing habit.
Abnormal...
Yes. Since it would bring shame to our
hospital, I won't contact the police.
Instead I'll report this to the hospital director.
If I just let this go, it would be
even more troublesome.
Wait! Please wait. Don't do that! I'll be fired!
Suzuku, you're sick.
How about staying in the hospital
and curing your sickness?
Please, Kubawara-sensein. Forgive me this once!
Just this once? So you admit your theft?
Oh... How...
Nogami, I don't want to report
you to the police on purpose.
The reason I bought you in such a
place is to give you a last chance.
Cure your stealing habit. Leave it to
me. Accept the medical treatment.
If you do that, I'll wait on my report to the director.
Huh?
Whoah! Great!
No panty?
How could that be!
Wait, what's that?!
How embarrassing,
Hey, look! That's cool!
What?
Let's go!
Yeah!
Sensei, help me! Please! Sensei!
Saiki, you're being watched. You're
being watched by everyone.
That's because...
Sensei, please help me! I can't hold on any longer.
Shop, can I enter the shop?
Ok... this shop?
What's all the commotion about?
Dunno.
Well look at that girl over there!
Ah! As I thought, she's not wearing any...
What?
How can that be? She's wearing it.
But that black thing, it must be...
What should I do? Everyone is looking at my spot.
I'm being watched, Sensei.
I can't stand it any longer.
What should I do? Sensei! Sensei!
Come on, are you done? It's
your fault that we're late.
Sorry, but we can make it on time.
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
This is an amazing public performance
that's coming to Japan.
It's a miracle that you obtained the tickets.
It seems that the tickets were
sold out in just 20 minutes!
Kuwabara-sensei!
Mana, I have business with you. Come with me.
Err... but today, there's...
We are on our way to the concert,
please do it next time.
Is that so?
I'm sorry, please go with someone else.
Making her angry, I wonder what
that boy is planning to do.
Looks like he's planning something.
Don't disappoint me...
My boy!
Have you decided to receive treatment?
Sensei. Sensei! Please believe me!
As I thought, I didn't do it!
Are you still denying it?!
Understood. I will report everything to the director.
Please wait! I beg you!
That's enough!
Please, Sensei! I will listen to whatever
you say! I will obey you!
With that of yours, surely there's
something we can do...
No! I didn't do it!
Are you still denying it?!
What are you going to do?!
This is what I will do.
What are you doing? Stop!
A bad girl needs some serious spanking!
Confess everything you did!
It hurts! Stop it!
Unless you confess it, I won't forgive you!
Oh dear, now my hand hurts.
You're hurting me. Stop it already...
IT HURTS!
Sorry! Please forgive me!
If you confess everything I'll forgive you.
But I didn't do it!
ARE YOU STILL DENYING IT?!
Come!
What are you doing? Please stop!
It looks something that genourous won't work.
It hurts! It hurts! Take it off!
Stop!
How about it? Are you going to admit what you did?
You're really stubborn, aren't you?
Having persisted this far, maybe
you didn't do it after all...
That's why I said I didn't do it...
I'm sorry.
Please take them off quickly.
I would like to do that very much,
but... I'm still DON'T BELIEVE IT!
NOOOOOO!
Here... here is the most painful part.
Let's see if you can be stubborn eve if I clip it here.
No! No! Stop it!
How about here?
I admit it!
Hmmm, what did you say?
I... admit my theft!
You're a thieving woman!
You admit it, don't you?
Yes...
Good, I will cure you of your abnormal stealing habit.
First of all, women that defy me will
experience this kind of pain...
If I don't teach your body...
Sensei...
Arghhhh! Take it off, take it off!
It's treatment so bear with it.
Come, one more over here...
Someone, someone help me! It's hurts!
Oh dear, his attacks are quite brutal.
When you attack a woman, "entertainment"
as we call it is important.
Isn't that right, Ren?
Sigh... after getting aroused
this much, it's still useless...
Stand up, Ren.
Yes.
Lift up your skirt.
Even though you are getting wet this much,
I'm sorry that you're still useless to me.
Well, sensei...
Let's use this today, shall we?
Hmm? What's the matter?
What's the matter Ren. You don't
need to hold back you know.
Bu... bu... but...
Yes. Is it that good? I'm happy that
you're getting so wet. Ren.
Come, lie down.
I'll do it gradually so that you won't be satisfied yet.
My "attack" at the end will do the final destruction.
Why didn't you come straight to
me while you were with Koi?
Caring so much for a lowlife like that.
When putting the lipsticks into Suzuka's
bag, you also did that hesitatingly.
What's wrong with you?!
You're my slave.
Don't think about anything, just obey me.
What are you mumbling about?!
Speak out clearly!
Looks like you need to do some introspection...
I will make every part of your
body obey me completely.
Forgive me, sensei. I will listen to
anything you say! I'll do anything!
No, that won't do.
If I don't make your body move automatically...
Hot! Hot!
Stay still!
Forgive me! It's hot! I can't stand it.
Don't move!
This is training. Until I say it's
ok, just stay still like that.
Respond!
Yes...
Can you endure this painful training?
Do you have the confidence?
Yes...
That's a good attitude.
Looks like you finally understand.
Good. This is the final stage.
Hot! Help! Please... quick... quickly!
Your stealing habit is a childhood problem.
That's why you need to cure it from here.
Yes.
Get naked.
Heh?
Get naked quickly!
Y... Yes.
My panties too?
Isn't that obvious?!
Listen to me. I'm your daddy.
Call me papa. Understand?
Papa...
Yes. You will be an obedient girl and listen
to whatever I say. Understood?
Yes.
Now, come over here.
Now, time for your milk.
Now that won't do, will it? You
just made your shirt dirty.
A bad girl needs spanking.
It hurts! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
It hurts!
Oh yeah, it's painful, isn't it?
That's how you can be a good girl.
Papa, please. Forgive me!
Suzuku, you're not listening to
what papa tells you, are you?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I'll make Suzuku listen to what papa say, ok?
What you just experienced was only your fingers.
Next, it will be your legs.
No... NO!
How pitiful, but if I don't let your body feel it
completely, you can't be an obedient child.
I won't be generous.
Now, the next will be your nibbles. And now here.
I'm sorry, papa... I will listen to whatever
you say, please forgive me. Really...
You'll obey what papa says completely?
I will! I will!
You will be papa's play thing. Understand?
Yes.
Finally you become a god girl. Papa is very happy.
Now, how about I teach you what happen
when you became a bad girl.
This time it will be your vagina.
Sen... sei?
You did well. By now, your stealing
habit should have been cured.
Yes. Thank you...
This time, entrust me with everything.
Yes.
It's all right. I won't do anything bad.
Sensei...
Good girl.
Ses... sei, I fell strange.
It's alright.
It hurts!
You will feel better, just endure it.
How about it? A completely different
kind of excitement, right?
Yes. Yes!
Come. Suck it with your mouth.
Yes.
This much... From now on, you will be my cute doll.
Doll...
What a erotic doll.
But she's beautiful. As if she's alive.
Oh yeah. Surely she's not real?
No, how could that be?
Yeah.
The night where the moon light sways
I continue walking
Inside the maze where I lost my way
Where I found myself from the past.
I wonder if I can return
to the old time when I knew nothing.
There's no way I can return.
The sands of time will only keep falling.
But I will, I will definitely find it.
Believing in something and walking straight ahead
Everything looks so shiny.
And smiling from now on too...