No!
No...
Fuck my pussy
Fuck my pussy harder!
Where am l?
What's going on?
Let me go.
Let me go!
Ouch!
Why?
Hey.
Hey. Free my arms and legs.
Hey! Can't you hear me?
This is a hospital. lf you can't keep quiet,
we'll kick you out!
Hospital? Why? l don't get it.
l can't remember anything.
l want seconds.
No.
Huh.
The soup kitchen at the park is better than this.
Why am l here?
l don't know.
What do you mean?
You hospitalize people for no reason?!
What are you doing? Fool!
l'm sorry. l'm sorry.
l'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- l'm sorry, l'm sorry, l'm sorry.
- What were you thinking?
- l'm sorry, sorry, sorry...
- lf you're done, l'm taking it away.
- ...sorry, sorry, sorry...
l'm going to escape.
l can't pay the hospital bills.
This place depresses me.
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
What? That person is...
Ouch. Shit.
Why?
Are you alright?
The Superintendent said so?
Yes. This patient is to be put in an isolated ward.
l was told to be the nurse in charge.
What is going on?
lt's better for the hospital if we discharged him.
For some reason, l feel that way.
l'm meeting the Superintendent?
Yes. To hear what's in store.
What do you mean, ''what's in store''?
l don't know.
''Don't know''?
l'm going to find out now.
Together?
No. Separately, l heard.
Oh? l have a bad feeling about this.
Adolph!
How's your health?
Do you hurt anywhere?
No. Not really.
You don't like animals?
No. lt's not that.
These babies are my precious partners.
Don't just stand there. Come closer.
l am Reika Rikage, Director and Superintendent of Cross Hospital.
You were found unconscious in front of the hospital with horrible injuries.
Do you remember?
No.
l see. We investigated your identity.
Strange. You don't show up anywhere.
Can you at least tell me your name?
Name.
My name is...
Can't remember?
Sora. People called me that a long time ago.
Sora. That's a nice name.
Hey, Sora.
l need a favor.
Your strong body that recuperated from those injuries.
A favor? Me?
Yes. A favor.
lt's not that difficult.
Be a test subject for a new medicine we developed.
New medicine. Test subject. What?
We want to test a new medicine on your body.
Test a new medicine?
No! lt's going to hurt!
Don't be scared. lt won't hurt.
ls this enough?
One thousand, ten thousand, one hundred thousand...
One million.
Are you kidding me?
Why do you say that?
Why? lt's a million.
So much on me?
What?
Don't be so self-critical.
Does it feel good?
Yeah.
Want more?
Then,
cooperate with us.
Yeah.
Thank you.
All your needs will be taken care of by Yuu Yagami.
lf there's anything you need, just ask her.
l mean anything.
- Sora.
- Huh?
- What?
Sora, wake up.
You have to take your medicine.
Come on, Sora.
There!
What are you looking at?
Well... um...
lt's good to be up in the morning.
What?
What's the matter?
lt can't be helped.
lt's always like this in the morning!
l'm sorry.
Get out.
What?
Just get out!
But, your medicine.
l don't care!
lf you're not going to leave, l will.
What?
Wait.
Please wait.
How can l get you to forgive me?
Show me yours.
What?
Take off your panties and show me your pussy.
Then, l'll forgive.
l will.
But, you have to take your medicine.
Will you forgive me now?
Well?
No! Show me all of it.
Get on the bed and spread your legs!
So this is her pussy.
Can l touch it?
She's come this far. lt's probably alright.
Sora?
lt's time for your medicine. Please hurry.
Supervisor Yunagi
Nurse Yagami, you know how important this experiment is to the Superintendent.
lf you aren't expedient, she will pay a visit.
Yes.
- Sora.
- Huh?
Since you have agreed to cooperate in the experiment,
don't cause any trouble.
- Nurse Yagami.
- Yes?
Please bring him to the Examination Room when ready.
Understood.
She's not my type.
Huh?
lt reminds me of the past.
Sora.
Sora, here.
This is the medicine?
Yes. Some water.
This is it?
Yes. Three times a day. Before meals.
And there is an examination every morning.
So don't sleep late like today... oh...
Oh, yes.
You can go anywhere except No Entry areas.
Feel free to explore.
''Explore'', huh?
NO ENTRY
What an awesome place.
What's that?
Science Room? No. Huh?
An eel? lt's huge.
Hey!
That's my lunch!
What are you doing all of a sudden doing?
Stand down, you lunch thief!
What are you doing? You brat!
l'm not a brat.
l'm eighteen. l'm a lady.
A lady.
So what? You're a lunch thief.
l'm not a lunch thief. l was chosen for the experiment...
l heard about you. You're Sora, the vagrant.
Ouch! What do you think you're doing?
Don't call me vagrant.
lt's not like l want to be like this.
- Oh, um...
- l'm not a vagrant.
l know! You want to eat eel?
There's a lot more. lt's top quality.
lt'll make you full.
Well... bye.
COME
Why did l have that dream?
l can't even touch her.
lt must be this place.
lt's so nice outside.
- Do you like it outside, Sora?...
- Damn. lnnocently swaying your tits like that.
ls she trying to seduce me?
- There's a big park near my house...
- l guess not.
l go there on my days off.
- l just walk around and stuff...
- Will she let me fuck her?
She even showed me her pussy.
Maybe if l ask her...
Sora, are you listening to me?
What? What did you say?
Oh, you.
l was talking about how nice it is outside.
Sora, you're not feeling well?
No. That's not it.
- Except that...
- Whew!
What a relief.
You had me worrying.
- Um...
You first.
lt's not important.
But...
Really, it's not important.
lt's nothing important.
Then l'll start.
Not that it's important.
My lover was a researcher here.
A decent hard working guy.
The Superintendent and his peers,
and we nurses all liked him.
l was really proud of him.
Tall and handsome.
Most of all, he was kind.
He was very kind.
l loved him.
But as a subject in a medical experiment...
Shut up.
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up!
You talk to me about another man?
Sorry to disappoint you. l'm just a jobless homeless vagrant!
No. That's not what l meant.
Enough! Shut up!
l don't want to hear about your man!
Shit. What's going on?
Take it.
No. l'm not wet yet.
Yeah. My cock is in your pussy.
lt hurts.
Sora, please stop.
lt doesn't feel too good.
lt's not slippery.
Yeah. lt's getting wet.
lt feels so good.
Hey.
Hey, Yuu.
YUU YAGAMl
- Nurse Yagami is not in.
- What?
lt's time for your medicine.
Please go to the Examination Room.
How is she?
l gave her a break.
l will accompany your medication.
Break? Where?
l have no obligation to tell you.
Huh?
About earlier...
...hey, hey, bang bang...
Huh?
Hey, hey, barbecue, hey, hey, tempura
Hey, hey, my stomach is full
What are you doing?
Oh, the vagrant... No, Sora, the test subject.
Surfing the internet on my free time.
lnternet?
What did he want to talk about?
You can research like this.
l see. lt's become a convenient world.
lt's already this time?
Sorry, l have an appointment.
Alright, thanks.
Let's see.
HOW TO APOLOGlZE.
HOW TO PLEASE A GlRL
What did you want to talk about?
To apologize for the other day.
l'm sorry.
You may not believe me, but l meant no harm.
Why did you do that?
l don't know.
When l listened to you talk about your boyfriend,
l got so angry.
l lost it.
You were jealous?
Jealous? l don't think so.
l haven't fucked in years.
l feel so bad.
l sincerely apologize.
Forget it.
Forget it. l'm tired of being angry.
You mean?
Yes. l forgive you.
Oh, that's great.
But this is the last time.
Do it again and l'll never forgive you.
l understand. l'll never do anything against your will.
That's a promise.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, l have a present for you.
Present?
Come with me.
Sora, wait.
Sora, you won't turn the lights on?
Yeah. Wait a second.
l'll turn it on.
Sora!
l looked it up in the internet.
How to please you.
- PENlS HEAVEN - NO MORE SMALL PENlSES
- lNTERNATlONAL ANALYST - BlND WOMEN
HUGE PENlS
No.
Sora, please set me free.
l don'twant this.
l know. l understand.
What? You're joking, right?
What?
No, no, no, means yes.
Don't! lt's not possible! lt won't go in!
lt hurts. lt hurts!
lt's going to tear! My pussy is going to tear!
You're going to tear my pussy!
You mean you're really suffering?
Help me.
Yuu, l'm sorry!
Shit! lt's slippery. l can't pull it out.
l'm sorry. Yuu, l'm sorry.
l just wanted you to be happy.
l looked it up in the internet.
l wanted you to be happy.
l didn't know it was all lies!
l'm sorry. l'm sorry, Yuu!
l'm sorry. l'm so sorry.
lt's out!
Yuu!
Yuu, l'm sorry.
Sorry. l'm so sorry.
l'm sorry.
What a hopeless man.
WE HAVE COME TO THE END OF LEVEL ONE
NOW PROCEED TO LEVEL TWO.