The nurse that looks after you, Yuu Yagami, will be reassigned.
ls that understood?
Yuu isn't coming back?
lt seems that you like Yuu.
Don't worry. She has to tend to urgent business at the main clinic.
As soon as that's over, she'll be right back.
Good.
What's the matter?
You look healthy.
Yes. My health is all that l have.
Let me examine you. Lie down here.
Here?
Yes.
Like this?
Don't be nervous, it'll be quick.
How have you been feeling recently?
Anything unusual?
No. l've been eating well since l came here.
l see.
Say, ''ahhh''.
Ahhh.
lt seems you're fine.
Now, your cock.
Stay still. This is part of the exam.
You're giving me a hard on.
That's alright. Relax.
That's easier said than done.
Nice cock.
Long, hard, and thick.
lt's sensitive too.
Your soft hand feels good.
Go ahead. Shoot your cum.
l'll give you a facial.
Shoot all your cum before your balls explode.
Holding it in is unhealthy.
l'm going to shot my load.
Your examination is finished. Your health is fine.
She looks nice.
She's got a nice ass.
But she irks me.
l'm done.
Yes.
Ms. Yagami will return soon, so there won't be a replacement.
lf you need anything, don't hesitate to ask me.
What man would hesitate with you?
ls that understood?
Yes, ma'am!
l'm bored. l wish Yuu would come back.
This is so boring. l wish there were some porn.
Huh?
According to research,
a woman's orgasm is 300 times greater than a man's.
ls that true?
ln typical straight relationships,
the female is on the receiving end
so it's unusual for the male to have his total erogenous zone stimulated.
Then it can be reasoned that a man's total erogenous zone can be enhanced
so that he can achieve an orgasm as great as a woman.
Huh?
Sora?
Hey, what are you doing?
Nothing. l had time so l was surfing the net.
No, no! This is work!
Don't look. You wouldn't understand.
Really?
That's right.
Well, let me see.
Don't!
Hey!
This looks hard. Let me help.
No. Let me down.
Hiyori, you like porn.
Stay out of it.
Wait a second.
What?
You don't have to close those windows.
You're into it, aren't you?
You bet! l love it!
Well... then...
Huh?
Would you like to fuck like this?
Yes, l would.
Will you fuck me?
Fuck you? You bet! l will! l will!
Here l go!
Not here.
Come to my room after dinner.
Yes ma'am.
Sora, where are you?
lt's time for your medicine.
What happened?
l'm not going to ask why you were naked.
But if you do something like that again,
l'll have the Supervisor confine you to your room.
Alright.
Wait.
What is it?
Do you know Hiyori? She looks very young and petite.
Hiyori? What about her?
This is a special ward. Why is she here?
She may look young, but she is an exceptional researcher.
Researcher? She's not a nurse?
She's a qualified nurse, but she works here as a researcher.
Why does she wear a nurse's uniform?
That's what she's into.
''lnto?''
Don't ask me!
l can't tell what a genius is thinking.
She may seem eccentric, but she is a genius.
Achew!
Somebody is talking about me.
Man, l ate a lot.
Now, l'll go to Hiyori's room and...
Oh!
Ouch.
l'm sorry, l wasn't looking.
l'm really sorry.
l'm Sakurako Kujo.
May l ask your name?
Hello?
My name is Sora. They call me that because l'm empty.
You're funny.
So Sora, are you hurt?
No at all. As you can see, l'm fine.
That's good.
Ms. Kujo.
Call me Sakurako.
What do you do here?
Me? l'm a drug test subject.
And you?
l'm also a test subject for a new drug.
Then we're colleagues.
l'll be seeing a lot of you.
l look forward to it.
Oh!
l would like to talk some more,
but it's time for my medicine.
Oh, well.
Good bye.
She's fine.
l'm late for Hiyori!
Sora, you're late.
l'm sorry.
18 YEAR OLD HlYORl'S ROOM
You better make me feel good.
l'll do my best.
You don't want to use the bed?
The bed is for my stuffed dolls.
Oh, okay. What turns you on?
Start with my ears.
Ears?
What, you're not into it?
l didn't say that.
Does this feel good?
Yes. lt tickles.
Here's some more.
No. l'm not ready for this.
Let's just start with my tits.
Tits? What tits?
Say that again and you can't touch me.
Sorry, l was kidding.
Be gentle.
Yeah.
Squeeze my tits.
Pinch my nipples.
You're real good.
Sora, kiss me.
Stick your tongue out.
Yeah, stroke my slit.
My pussy is getting wet.
Yeah, it feels good. Rub my pussy.
Finger my pussy.
l'm going to cum on your fingers!
Wow, you're terrific.
l need to fuck you.
Sure.
l feel flush.
Yeah, suck my nipples.
Pinch my nipples until it hurts.
lt hurts so good.
Finger my hole.
Spread my slit wide.
Turn around and stick your ass in the air.
Let me fuck your hole.
lt hurts!
Roll my nipples.
My pussy is throbbing.
Keep rubbing my tits. lt feels so good.
Fuck me harder!
Your cock feels so good.
l going to cum!
This was pretty awesome.
300 times this orgasm might kill Sora.
l guess l have to stimulate him like this.
After all, Sora's body isn't normal
Welcome.
Do you have identification?
You can check my age on my membership card!
You're pretty serious for a kid.
l'm not a kid. Call me lady.
Oh, you're dominant.
''Ha, ha. Now you're my slave.''
Not quite right.
Maybe a DVD will be a better reference.
NlGHT SHlFT NURSES
How long can you hold it?
l'm bored. l haven't seen Hiyori, and Yuu hasn't returned.
l guess l'll jerk off.
Huh?
Who is it?
What?
Nobody's here.
Huh?
A note?
TO SORA: l'M WAlTlNG lN THE BASEMENT. LET'S PlCK UP WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
This is a creepy place.
Hiyori didn't have to choose a place like this.
Huh?
What's going on?
Ouch!
Hiyori, the Dominatrix. Transform!
Wait a second!
What is the meaning of this?
To terrorize you so that you will find pleasure in pain.
Something like that.
l'll torment you.
What?
Shut up!
Wait. Time out!
What?
Give me a break. l'm not into pain.
But it'll feel good.
You mean that?
Just a little endurance
will give you an orgasm 300 times more powerful.
300 times...
Please. l want it.
Alright.
Does this feel good?
Yes.
lt does, does it?
Do you like my foot?
Get hard, baby.
l'm gushing.
Get off on my foot.
You pig.
Getting turned on by my foot.
You're a pathetic pig.
A worthless disgusting vagrant animal!
You cockroach!
Does it feel good?
Does it really feel good?
Then let's see you cum.
Shoot your load on my foot.
You cockroach.
You little cockroach!
How dare you!
Ouch! l love this!
Shut up, idiot!
You pig. You're a toilet bug.
Tell me more!
You're just a lower life form!
So, you like getting whipped?
You're a hopeless masochist pig.
You deserve some cunt.
My wet hot hole.
lt's much bigger than the last time.
You're thick hard dick feels so good.
Your cock is awesome!
Hiyori, l'm going to cum.
No!
You can't cum until l say so.
Awesome. Your cock is throbbing!
Oh, yeah.
Please, let me cum!
No, you can't. We're almost there.
l'm going to cum.
This is awesome!
l'm shuddering all over.
l'm going to cum!
Cum with me!
Man, that was awesomely good.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Hurry up and untie me.
Not yet.
What?
We're just getting started.
My ass still hurts.
Why me?
Huh?
Whoa! lt's you.
Hi!
What do you want?
Let's do it again.
What?
No.
Come on, please?
This time it won't hurt.
Seriously, l can't take it anymore.
Pretty please.
Alright.
Not this again!
And what are these things on me?
Just a low frequency massager.
Like this.
Whoa, it tingles.
You see? lt doesn't hurt.
lt doesn't hurt at all. lt feels good.
Your body learned from the last time.
Your adrenaline flows easier.
That's why...
See?
l'm already cumming.
lt's still hard.
Do you like this?
Yeah. My body is hot.
Want to fuck me?
Yeah. l want to fuck your hot pussy.
Let me stick your cock inside.
Your cock is so fucking big.
l love your fat dick.
lt's throbbing deep inside my pussy.
Oh, yeah. Awesome!
Your fat cock is rubbing me deep inside.
That was so awesome, l could've died.
Sorry, Sora. We still have our last test.
What?
No. Please no more!
Stop. Stop it.
WARM
The experiment is a success.
Oh, no! l can't stop cumming! Please help me!
l can't believe that made me cum.
lt's supposed to hurt, but l came like never before.
So l'm a masochist.
Does that make me a pervert?
lt felt good, so l guess it's okay.
All this thinking is giving me a headache.
What's happening?
lt's nice to be back.
lt's time to muster my resolve and...
...take care of Sora.
lt's not that he's a bad guy.
What?
Sora!
Sora.
Somebody help.
Somebody!