I'm sure out and I saw it,
that nostalgic smile.
Tonight I'm watching
in a room next to yours
the last scene I can't remember.
It's different from what I want to see.
It's a more happy ending
Dreaming of that last time
when we were truly together.
I look over my shoulder
and you're right there beside me.
Let's keep that happiness
to ourselves!
Mana
Are you taking it that seriously?
I'm sorry! Stop it Sensei!
I haven't done anything yet, have I?
Sensei, please don't get rough on me...
I told you to do it every day in order to raise your
excitability, but you haven't been doing it.
But!
No!
Don't do it!
If you're not capable of practicing
by yourself then I'll help you out.
I have been doing it!
I just couldn't admit it because
it was too embarrassing!
I'm going to teach you everything
from pleasure to pain!
Take this!
It hurts!
Stop it Sensei!
It'll start to feel good after a while.
Or perhaps you prefer taking it in the rear?
Sensei! I don't want to do this anymore!
What silliness are you talking about?
Oh it hurts! It realty hurts!
Don't you ever shut up...
Just stay put for a while.
I need to look for some Nurses...
Teduka Sakuya
We'll have her...
Nogami Suzuka
and her.
I think I'll go take a visit to them tomorrow.
So are you going to undertake the
position at the Special Ward?
I suppose so... under one condition.
What is that?
I'd like you to allow me to handle
everything in my own way.
I'll choose all the nurses and other personnel myself.
That's fine.
Pleases take this.
What's that?
It's a card key.
By using that you can freely come and go
as you pleases from the Special Ward.
And also, if you use the password built into that card,
you can view personal date on all the nurses.
Please put it to good use.
These are listering device. Please use it
in order to perceive the nurses' activity.
I can't believe they're this small. Don't tell
me there's one planted on me as well?
Who knows...
What are you...?
You went to the trouble of making your decision.
I must reward you.
It's all shriveled up...
Are you actually more timid than you seem,
or are you just not attracted to me?
This is how it's supposed to be...
You've certainly suffered a loss of face
by falling for Ruhl, young master.
Sensei... I can't go on...
Hm? What's the matter, Ren?
I can't hold it any longer!
Nobody said you had to hold it in, you know.
It hurts...
We're going to enter!
Good morning!
Morning.
Kuwabara-sensei?
What is it?
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine...
why?
It just looks like you're really tired.
Well I'm not!
Kuwabara-sensei,
examination time has already
started. Please hurry it up.
Ah sorry...
It's nothing.
Konohara Karen...
I'm going to elect you as a Special Ward nurse
and train you so thoroughly that you'll
never be able to act like that again!
Sensei...
Sensei!
Is it ok to let in patients now?
Ah, yeah.
Tabato Maiko-san, please enter now.
It should be around here somewhere...
Huh? What's that sound...
I... can't reach it...
Shall I get it down for you?
Who are you?
I'm Kuwabara from Maternity and Gynecology.
I'm new here. Nice to meet you.
I'm Nagami Suzuka from radiology. Nice to meet you
It's completely visible you know.
Did you get a hard-on?
Eh?
I read in a book that when man see underwear
they get excited, then get an erection.
Exactly what kind of book was that?
Come on I'll get it for you.
Let me up there.
I need to do this myself.
I see. Well then, good luck.
I'll be leaving now.
Ah! I got it!
What the hell is with her?
She had a cute face, but with an attitude like that...
Please don't cry Ken-chan. Your
mommy will be here soon ok?
Tenzuka-san where have you gone
to? We're really busy here!
Ah... Yes!
What am I gonna do...
Get a hold of yourself!
When faced with high stress situations
she experiences mass shivering...
Could these symptoms be...
Autonomic ataxia?
Pull yourself together!
Kuwabara-sensei...
You know who l am?
Yes sir...
the nurses were talking about you...
they said you were a superb doctor.
I'm fine now, but the head nurse called for
you you know. Shouldn't you better go?
Ah! Oh no!
Excuse me!
Oh yes...
My name is Tedzuka Sayuki.
I look forward to working with you.
Tenzuka-san!
Ah... Yes!
Hmph, I can hear that fastidious bitch.
You let out dirty filth yourself after all.
I'll find out your weakness and turn you into
a Special Ward Nurse no matter what!
Are you sure there isn't anything bothering you?
You're my best friend, that's why I want to help you.
I'm sorry to make you worry.
This isn't related to Kuwabara is it?
You've been acting strange ever
since that guy came here!
Kuwabara-sensei has nothing to do with it.
Is that so?
Oh... Mana...
Mana!
Mana...!
I think about you this much, and yet...
Heheh... this is quite something... Not only is she
so fastidiousness but she's also a lesbian?
This is why my charms didn't affect her.
So she's hostile because she feels like
she's fighting me for Mana, huh?
This could come in handy indeed.
Oh Mana!
Who shall I start with...
Karen is dangerous...
She thinks of me as an enemy.
I'm going to have to wait until
later to get a chance at her.
Nogami Suzuka... I'll put her off until later.
I think this one may prove well...
Tezuka Sayuki...
Not only is she timid but she's also in love with me.
I think I'll start with her...
I can't wait!
Sorry to make you come all the way down here,
but it's about that fit you had earlier.
Fit? What are you referring to?
I'm a doctor you know.
I know you had Autonomic Ataxia spasms back then.
You're hiding your illness from
the hospital aren't you?
T... That's...
Sensei, I'm begging you!
Please don't tell her about this!
If I lose my job I don't know what I'll do!
It worked!!
Don't worry, I won't tell anyone.
It'll be our little secret.
Sehsei, thahk you so much.
Ah! Sensei what are you doing?
There's noting to worry about.
I'm going to cure you
In order to stabilize your heart
it's most importan to have a partner
whom you can fully trust.
If you leave it to me you'll be fine.
Yes sir. Please help me.
That's a good girl. I'll protect you.
Onii-chan...
Onii-chan?
Ah, sorry...
It just felt that way...
That's fine. If you can calm down that
way then I'll be your big brother.
I'll be your Onii-chan so you can rely on me.
Se... Sensei!
You can call me Onii-chan now.
Onii-chan!
You're big brother is going to cure you ok?
Yes!
Wow!
Come now.
This is... a surgery room?
Yes, it's brand new.
Take a look. The monitors can display
this room from every possible angle.
Alright then. Let us continue your treatment.
Sit on Onii-chan's lap.
For a girl you, shock treatment works best.
It may geta little rough, but you
can endure it, can't you?
I understand... Onii-chan.
Alright. There's a good girl.
Shh! Endure it.
Take it easy and gradually start to relax.
Let loose the power from your body.
Relax your muscle here as well.
Entrust your body to me.
Oh no! Ahh!
You can't! It's embarrassing!
I'm a doctor. There's no need to be embarrassed.
You're illness cannot be cured unless
you relieve yourself of that shyness.
As I thought, I'm going to be forced to use this.
Onii-chan what are you...?
This is all part of the treatment.
You promised you'd do what Onii-chan
told you didn't you?
Onii-chan... it's too embarrassing!
Just bear with it.
Unless you can be calm while being looked
at like this your illness can't be cured.
What's that mask?
We have spectators today you see. I'll adjust
it so that we don't get in direct shot,
but if my face happened to be filmed
things would become ugly.
Spectators?
The're suite close by.
But more importantly,
how does it feel to see your
own embarrassing figure?
No!
No you don't. Look at it properly.
If you don't lose the feeling of being embarrassed,
your illness won't be cured.
Ah no! You can't, Sensei!
Stop this!
Calm down.
If you get alarmed at this stage you won't be able
to make it through the next level of treatment.
B... But...
That's it. Just leave your body in my hands.
It look like it's started.
Whoa, I can't wait, get it out!
Don't worry, this wall can selectively
control the light passing through
They still can't see you.
But why this?
Unless you can get used to people
seeing you, your illness won't heal.
If you can get used to this many
people looking at you,
then you'll definitely gain confidence
and then your illness will heal itself.
Even if they can't see me it's embarrassing!
Sensei! Don't show it off!
Just bear it. Pretend that you are
being watched and endure it.
I'm being watched... I'm being watched...
Everyone is looking at my body!
Don't worry, I'll take care of everything.
She sure has big titties... they must feel good
man, I can't hold on for much longer!
Onii-chan! My heart's beating
so fast it's about to explode!
Don't worry, you aren't hyperventilating.
Just stay that way, and leave it all up to Onii-chan.
Heh, it's so hot I'm almost burning my fingers here.
It's so embarrassing.
I wonder if this is because you're nervous...
or perhaps you're starting to feel it now?
This is necessary for the healing process
you know. Come now, answer me.
I apologize! I'm feeling it!
There's a good girl. Alright then
let's go down here too.
Not there... if you do it that much...
Oh man I can't hold on anymore!
Neither can I!
Everyone's got their eyes fixed on you Sayuki.
No! Don't look! Don't look!
They can see every nook and cranny!
They can see me... they can see me!
It's so embarrassing! I'm gonna die!
This place is all wet, as if you
just peed yourself, Sayaki.
It's embarrassing...
Take a look, you naughty girl!
Onii-chan... it can't be!
Let's put the finishing touches
to the treatment at last.
Eh?
What are you... going to... do?
Hmm? You already know don't you?
No! You can't! You can't!
What are you saying? If I don't
do this you won't be cured.
Just stay still.
I'm gonna make you feel real good.
Don't do it!
What are you doing? If you don't
relax I can't fit it in you know.
But... It hurts, it hurts!
It hurts! Take it out!
It hurts it hurts! Onii-chan!
This is medical treatment so just endure it!
That's good...
You feel real good Sayuki...
I can't hold it! I can't hold it man!!
Dammit! I wanna do her too!
I'm being watched... I'm being watched
We must make sure they can see everything.
Hey look, you can see it all now.
Sayuki, take look at the screen.
No! They can see everything! It's so embarrassing!
See, it's this embarrassing and yet
you aren't having spasms are you?
Will you gentlemen care to take part
in the treatment as well perhaps?
Eh?!
Alright then, I will!
Yes sir! I will!
Hey, I called out first!
No, I did!
There's no need to rush.
Anyone who wishes to participate
pleases make your way in here.
Sensei... what are you...?
I'm going to get everyone to
cooperate, so do your best.
No! Sensei help me!
This is in order to cure you. Trust
you big brother and endure it.
O dear, what's the matter? I'm
getting soaked here as well.
It was just too horrible!
You entrusted yourself to your
big brother, didn't you?
You may have not noticed it yet,
but the face that you didn't have a fit is solid
proof that the treatment was successful.
I told you I'd cure you didn't I?
How about you show some gratitude?
Thank you.
That's good. As long as you
leave it to me you'll be fine.
From now on you'll show trust in
I me and stick with me won't you?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU!
Yes Sir!
Shaking in the light of the moon
Everyone continues walking alone,
lost inside a labyrinth
where I found myself from the past.
I wonder if we could ever go back
to the past when we were clueless.
There's no way we ever could,
because the sky would only fall down.
I will definitely find it.
Believe in something and march straight ahead.
Everything looks beautiful,
the smiles from now on...
The smiles from now on...