Night Shift Nurses
Yakin Byoutou: Night Shift Ward
Chapter 5.5
Ryuuji Hirasaka's Special
Experiment Record Collection
They're all here, aren't they?
It's like they're all tempting me to fantasize about them...
Hmm, that's OK, but it's not quite right...
That's it! That's the figure of a true human being!
Humans are born naked
and die naked, you see...
Those stupid women who put on an air of importance,
and those who try to gloss everything over,
to me you're nothing but female slaves!
Ren, I want you to sit on this.
Yes, Doctor.
It's cold!
Now, get those juices flowing.
Doctor, I want you!
Yes, Nanase here.
I'm sorry.
Yes. A lot is coming out.
I have a favor to ask.
I want you to listen while you masturbate.
Fujisawa-san...
The basement, right?
I understand...
Doctor! You're not supposed to use cell phones in the hospital!
Oh, right. I'm sorry.
Well, I'll talk to you later.
What a lovely view!
Did you wear the garters so that the male doctors
and hospitalized patients can get a good look at you?
That's not so!
Don't film this!
What are you trying to do?!
What am I trying to do...
I'm trying to make you repent.
No...
No!
Untie me now!
If you resist too much, the ropes will really hurt.
Stop it.
No!
What's the matter? Does that feel good?
It hurts!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Considering that you killed a person!
At least recognize the position you're in.
What are you going to do to me?!
Be sincere and think about what you did.
You should accept what's coming to you.
It's because you're wearing underwear like this that you're not repenting!
You're all wet.
You've got an erogenous zone in an interesting place.
Doctor, I beg you!
Really!
Please stop!
You can't!
No!
It looks like you're really wet.
Stop it! Stop it!
Don't ever go against me again.
Yes, Doctor.
No, no... I can't take this.
Now, Ren! Show the people of this town the embarrassing sight of your peeing!
However, I can't be satisfied at just this...
No! Stop it!
Please! Let me go!
Naoya-san!
NOOOooo!
No, no, no...
Naoya-san, Naoya-san...!
No...
Ren, you were a virgin?
As I thought, you are my woman!
Naoya-san...
Stop it!
It hurts, it hurts...
Don't move!
Father!
Mother!
What is it? I can't understand a thing you're saying.
No! Stop it! Help me! Someone!
Are you sure you want to yell?
Imagine if someone came in and saw this embarrassing view...
...and your sister heard about this.
No, such a thing... no... nooo...
Then, settle down!
That way, we can both enjoy ourselves.
It's so tight...
Come, I'm about to enter your inside!
Nice and tight!
Stop, it hurts... Don't move!
Does it hurt that much?
Just as I thought, you were still a virgin!
Enyjoy it! I'm going to show you what it means to be an adult!
It hurts!
All right! I'm about to cum!
You can't! Stop! Please! Please stop it!
I'll use my cock to mash it up.
No! It's going further in!
But that's okay.
Doctor, I'm scared!
It's moving inside of me!
The egg is moving inside of me!
That's my Ren.
Good. Good.
Ren.
Yes, Doctor...!
I'm coming!
I'm about to cum.
Let me see it.
I'm about to cum!
Everyone's made splendid experiment subject matter.
Being a doctor is my life's calling.
I'm so glad I became a doctor.
What's this?
Stop! Don't look!
I'd say that you managed to get yourself quite wet.
Well? How about I take it out?
Looks like you had quite a bit of fun with this.
Take a look, Hikaru.
This will enter your inside next.
No! N-No! Help!
Move your hands!
You don't care what happens to your sister?
If you try to resist me or try to run away again...
I'll really show those pictures to Ai-kun, you know.
O-O-Ow!
It hurts! it hurts! It hurts!
Seems you're not wet enough.
Yes...
Do you know what I'm going to do with this, hmm?
It seems that your erogenous zone lies in your anus.
Yesterday I explored your virgin pussy,
today I'm squeezing in through the back door!
Stop it!
No! Stop...
No...
My stomach!
My stomach is going to explode!
Is it painful?
Is it embarrassing?
But it feels good, right?
It's turning you on, isn't it?
N-No, you're wrong!
Don't move or you'll get hurt.
Well, as I thought, this suits you better.
So you're not really a virgin, are you?
Being a nurse is a very active job, so I just...
So then you're telling me you are a virgin?
Yes.
What a wonderful fragrance!
What a thing to do for a doctor!
The criminal heiress of a pharmaceutical fortune
isn't in a position to judge the ethics of a doctor.
No! it hurts!
What?!
It's an air pump.
No, no...
Release me!
Toilet...
Let me go to the toilet.
All right, I take it out now, OK?
Geez, talk about naive and gullible!
I-It hurts!
What are you...?!
Have you forgotten already?
I asked you to help me with an experiment!
What're you doing?
What're you going to do with that?
Isn't this nice?
This is what I'm going to do.
I've got to do something about lubrication, after all.
With proper lubrication...
even a brat like you can take a big thing like this.
Nice and cold.
No...
Don't worry. These eggs are only half-boiled.
And I took off the shell.
One...
D-Doctor...
That went in pretty smoothly.
Maybe from all the work we've done so far?
Two...
Doctor, i-inside my stomach it feels kind of funny.
I can't fit anymore.
Impossible, Doctor. No more.
You always give up so easily!
Always telling me, "You can't!", "Impossible!" or "No way!"
Just keep your mouth shut!
Yes, sir. I'm sorry.
All right. Now, relax those abdominal muscles.
Yes, sir.
– Good!
Good! All ready to go!
Hikaru, let's start your practice! Start giving birth!
Yes, sir.
It's coming out!
Excellent! Just a little more!
Come on, go!
It's coming out.
Quick!
Stop.
Oh well.
What new experiments will I try next?
You can't! Stop it! I'm going to go crazy!
I can't take it!
No more! It's coming out! It's coming out!
All right,
here goes!
It's coming out!
I can't anymore!
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
I want you to blow everything you've got out in front of me!
Beautiful!
What a wonderful sound!
I'm going to untie you right now!
No, I'm almost there!
I think you're misunderstanding something, Shinjo-kun.
Like you, Hikaru is doing this because she wants to.
I don't want such a  thing!
Of course you do!
Then, why did you come here?
Well...
Never mind. Let's just hold that thought while we watch Hikaru do her thing.
I'm coming!
Just thinking about it makes me want to take out my penis.
However, I'm going to need more than this if I want to complete my experiments.
One day I'll create my own special hospital ward...
And then my ideal will finally become reality!
By day I'll attend to those big shot drug producers,
but by night those bodies will be consecrated to me.
How magnificent!
In order to obtain those which are colored like a rose, those large 'front gates',
I will have to begin an altogether new experiment!