Anime Kazama Mana
Yes!
My... My pussy...
I'm... cumming...
How's that!?
– Harder! Fuck me harder!
– Suck on it!
I'll pound you like a piston!
More! Give me more!
Please give Mana more of Papa's world-class cock!
Fuck me deep!
I'm... I'm cumming!
Here it comes!
Do it harder, make me pregnant!
Fuck me as hard as you can!
Please! Give me all of it!
Give me all of your wonderful semen!
Amazing!
So good!
Please cum! Please cum inside me!
Do it inside! Inside!
I'm cumming!!
– We aren't through yet!
– I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming!!
Mizukawa
Mizukawa Wataru
Would you like to revise the name?
Yes / No
Now Loading
This time, it won't be another wasted sacrifice.
The hospital project has really produced some unexpected results.
How long will the patient be confined and kept unaware?
And now, the new nurse...
Kazana Mana
Push Start Button
You'll be working here from now on.
Wow!
I'm Kazama Mana! I'm still a student,
and I'm spending my summer working
in the friendly Yamae Sanitarium.
The patient I'm in charge of is named Mizukawa Wataru-san.
He's a young patient and confuses the staff here.
Everyone here is supervised by Tokisawa Miyu-san,
but when it comes to Mizukawa Wataru-san...
Yes?
Excuse me! I've come to serve your
needs, my name is Kazama Mana.
I'm still in training, so please forgive any mistakes I may make.
I hope we can work well together!
Fine.
Small Lily Darling...
sa ririi daarin
If you could only make a sound.
oto torou no nara
It would overflow,
afureru
and you would chow your courage.
yuuki wo misete ne
Idol Angel   Kazama Mana
Even If I faced you,
daishimete mo
no one else would see.
dare mo miteinai
My lips are only centimeters away.
kuchibiru ga ne ato hara ni senchi
Small Lily Darling...
sa ririi daarin
Stepping into spring, you'll be like on angel.
haru ni suteppu tenshi no you ni
So then... That punk Wataru's being taken care of?
It's probably pointless, just like fucking this girl.
Jeez, what a strange brat he is.
Now this girl here, I can't get enough.
She's getting spread wide open.
What a stupid slut this girl is.
She doesn't learn no matter how much we teach her.
Here it comes!
Dammit! I told you to swallow!
I've never seen such a worthless whore before!
That was a shitty orgasm. Here's your reward.
Stop!
My ass! I'm cumming!
Nice job! We really got her this time.
Unbelievable! You're just like a little spraying insect!
Hey, let's give this other vibrator a try.
I can't! I couldn't do anything like that!
This is an order from "Daddy".
I'm in pain, so you have to do it.
I refuse!
I see. That's unfortunate, because I had taken a liking to you.
Follow me. I'll show you something nice.
The truth about this sanitarium.
So good.
So many... So many cocks!
So good!
Harder! Fuck me harder!
Yes! Come inside my pussy!
Give me all your cum!
Oh God! This is too good!
Are you surprised that your job would involve such things?
For a long time now, this place has been a human
trash dump for various upper-class elites.
It was realized that this was a place where money, political
power, and pleasure were concentrated and exchanged.
Should we add you to the mix?
Would you rather become my toy?
Or a toy for those old geezers?
Hey!
Please make way!
Operating Room
Why didn't you keep an eye on him!?
I'm so sorry! I never imagined something like this could...
I don't want to listen to your worthless excuses.
What the hell do you think a human life is!?
I can't stand the sight of you!
Frightening, isn't she?
With this, we've got that punk.
There's no doubt about it.
It's all thanks to my efforts.
You haven't won yet!
What type of training should be next?
Speech Training
Fellatio Training
Come on, I'll teach you to do it properly, so begin.
Hurry up!
Put more spirit into it and suck!
You're hopeless.
Oh that's good.
It's too good...
I'm... I'm cumming!
Swallow all of it.
What a pretty face, Mana.
How long do you plan to stay there like that?
Would it be better if I quit?
Who knows.
Just look at the state I'm in...
Angels aren't real right? What should I do...
I'll be your ange...
Stop!
Could you? It's obvious you could never.
Listen to what I'm saying.
It's my duty to become your ideal girl.
Fellatio Training
Virgin Training
You're doing a great job.
You're wonderful, Mana-kun.
I wonder why she's doing this?
Let's take a look here.
How does that feel?
Check it out, Mana-kun's pussy is the best.
Holy shit... She's a virgin!
That's wonderful.
I thought I'd die before doing one.
It's her secret switch.
You're always playing with yourself down here, aren't you?
I haven't done anything like that!
But just look at how you're responding.
What a cute girl she is.
She's the Virgin Mary!
Wataru-san, please make me feel good!
I want to give my virginity to you.
You won't be lonely anymore.
You'll no longer be alone.
– Become one with me.
– Well then, it's about time we give it a try.
– I want everyone to love me.
Take that! You think you're in Heaven?
We'll show you!
It hurts! It hurts!
Stop! Please stop!
Let's keep going.
What's that? You want more?
Do it harder! We'll send you to Heaven.
Please Wataru-san, for my sake, don't die!
You want to be an angel that bad?
What a bad joke! Take this!
No! Don't!
You're going to get it! You're going to have our baby!
Pregnant! Just the way we like it!
It feels like Heaven now doesn't it!?
You're going to be our pregnant little bitch!
Pull the ropes tighter!
That's right! Try to think only of the man you love!
It hurts! It hurts!
Mommy!
It's coming!
I'm cumming again!
I'm cumming inside!
No! Not inside!
Jeez, what a slut.
She had it coming.
Fellatio Training
Special Vibrator
We're going to have some serious fun with this one.
I want to please everyone here.
Let's use this vibrator!
– Don't worry.
– Wh-What is that?
– Don't be scared.
– No! Stop!
It'll tear me apart!
If you don't relax your insides it'll hurt like hell.
You're about to feel really good.
No!
No!!
Oh shit! It's inside her!
This bitch loves the oversized toys!
Looks like she's going to cum any second.
It's tearing up my insides!
Please stop!
It's so good!
I can't get enough of this girl.
Is it tasty? It's tasty isn't it?
I'm cumming!
Here's my fill!
I can't...
This is too good. This vibrator is amazing.
You're so cute, Mana-chan.
What are we going to do next?
Let's try one in her other hole.
Oh, that sounds good!
Fellatio Training
Special Vibrator
Human Toilet
Give it to me!
A lot just came out.
Isn't that right, Mana-chan?
This chocolate is so delicious.
Give me more please.
So good!
She's such a good little toilet!
Here it comes!
Let's have a look.
I'm cumming again!
No! You're too rough!
So much cum...
You're so dirty, Mana-chan.
It tastes so warm and creamy.
I'll try to swallow it all.
Not yet, do it again.
Mana wants to swallow it all now.
It can't be helped. Go ahead.
Okay!
I swallowed all of it.
You're awesome, Mana-chan.
I'm so sorry...
Wow! Everyone look!
It's so pretty!
Mana-chan, Happy Birthday!
I'm cumming!!
That cake looks good, right?
Doesn't it look delicious, Mana-chan?
Yes!
It's okay if you want to eat the whole thing.
Who's that delicious cake for?
It's for me!
Is it tasty, Mana-chan?
All right! Now let's have a toast with this special champagne.
It looks delicious!
She drank it all! She's number one in Japan!
Thank you, everyone, for coming to
celebrate my birthday with me...
I've put my heart into it, Mana put her heart into it.
I've finally become an angel, a blessed Virgin Mary.
Now I can rest a little, right?
Good morning Wataru-san! It's time for breakfast!
It's so big and hard! Wataru-san's cock feels so good!
It's so good!
Harder! Do it harder!
Fuck the angel's pussy!
Yes! Fuck me silly!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm going to cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming again! I'm cumming again!
Please give me your sperm!
Cumming! Cumming! Cumming!
So good... I feel it in me!
You thought you were an angel? Don't make me laugh.
There's nothing like angels in this world.
Just call me daddy and let me fuck you.
In this world, there's no need for angels.
Wataru-san?
Kazama-san, have you finished tidying up?
The next customer will be arriving soon.
Make sure you clea...
Mana-kun, thank you for coming to pay
your respects to Wataru like this.
He was so young...
Oh Holy Lord, please lay this man
Wataru to rest in eternal peace.
What? Is this really happening?
I'm... not an angel!
I am... Kazama Mana.
Hey, why is it, that only you...
nee doushite anata dake wo
No matter where we are, I can find you.
dokode demo mitsukerareruno
Hey, why is it, that only you...
nee doushite anata dake wo
You only want to be with me? Yup, It's a mystery.
watashi ni naritai no un fushigi
Hey, come on now, why the lonely eyes?
nee dakara sabishii hitomi
All by yourself now, just hug yourself, it'll be okay.
hitorikiri daite ii nande
Hey, I want to always be here for you.
nee sonna ni itsumo iru yo
For your happiness alone. Secretly.
anata dake no tame ni un sotto
I'll open up the window.
madou wo ageru yo
Just let your heart gather
tsuki no shizuku ni
the drops from the moon.
kokoro yoseru yo
In the middle of your dreams.
yume no naka e