I'm sure you and I saw it,
that nostalgic smile.
Tonight I'm watching
in a room next to yours
the last scene I can't remember.
It's different from what I want to see.
It's a more happy ending
Dreaming of that last time
when we were truly together.
I look over my shoulder
and you're right there beside me.
Let's keep that happiness
to ourselves!
St. Julian Hospital has close due to various
circumstances. Thank you very much
for attending our hospital for so long.
The Director.
What the hell?
The hospital... shut down?
That's impossible. What on earth happened here?
Ren.
Where did you go to?
During training when I came
here to St. Juliana Hospital,
I meet you, Nanase Ren.
From the very first moment I saw her,
I became a prisoner
to her smiling face.
I want to make that women mine.
Not to brag, but as well as a handsome
face, I'm set to become an elite doctor.
There's not a woman alive who
wouldn't yield to my seduction.
That's how it should've been.
I will make you happy no matter what!
I'm sorry
I'm not the kind of woman that is appropriate for you.
You should find someone who suits
you better, Kuwabara-san.
But you are the one who is appropriate for me!
Eventually training ended, and since then
I never got the chance meet Ren again.
After passing the state exam with eases,
I looked forward to starting as a
doctor in the hospital with you...
I've done my best to get here!
And yet where have you gone to now?
What are you doing these days, and where?
Hurry up...
If I don't hurry up...
Oh no!
Oh dear...
No... no...
Stop Ittttt!!
Not that dream again.
Ren,
I can't stand the thought of you
sleeping with any other man
It's been four years since Ren vanished.
During that period I've been moving
around from hospital to hospital.
This time, I wonder if I'll find you?
Ren?
Are you alright?
Owowow...
Oh no! Just look at me!
I'm really sorry, I just forgot something
and was in a hurry.
It wasn't her... although she does
look alike, It's not Ren after all.
You're not hurt are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
I see. That's good then.
Yes.
Eh? Are you a doctor?
That's right. I'm starting work in that hospital today.
My name is Kuwabara.
H... He's so cool!
Ah! Oh no, I'm late!
Well then I'll be going!
What's your name?
Huh? Me?
Er... my name is Kazama Mana.
Kazama... Mana...
I wonder why I mistook her for Ren.
There's no way Ren would be as careless as that.
Medical Corporation
Sei-Katorea General Hospital
Cardiology Internal Clinic
There seem to be an awfully large
number of cameras here.
It's as if we were under surveillance by someone...
Come in.
Excuse my entry.
How do you do. My name is Kuwabara Souichirou.
I've been waiting for you.
Please come this way.
I'm the director of this hospital,
Kaneshiro Ruhl.
Please feel free to sit down.
Ah yes. Sorry for the intrusion.
This hospital aims to provide the
latest in medical treatment,
and we have various projects currently in action.
We give an extra warm welcome to young
people with plenty of motivation.
I see.
First there are hidden cameras
now there's this venus flytrap?
Please allow me to serve anyway
I can within my ability.
Anyway you can?
Huh?
I'm expecting great thing of you. Actually,
I have a favor for you to do right away.
Ah, what is it?
Tachibana-Sensei from maternity and gynecology
isn't doing examinations today.
I'm sorry to burden you with
this right after you arrival,
but could you please do your best fill in for him?
Alright.
Hmm. This is really quite sudden.
Alright then, I'm counting on you.
I'll just call for your support nurses.
Kuwabara-Sensei,
sorry about this morning.
Not at all. Kazama-kun, was it?
That's right! I'll lead you to the hospital
room and give you support.
I hope we can get along well.
As do I.
Erm, where is the usual Doctor?
Tachibana-Sensei is off work today
so I will be filling in for him.
I see. I'll leave it to you.
Let's see. You had surgery three days ago didn't you?
Do you still feel pain from time to time?
Yes, it hurts a little, but is that normal?
There's no need to worry.
Your progress is coming along fine.
I see.
If the pain, persists we can try
changing your painkiller.
Yes, ok then.
He's so cool isn't he?
Hey, is he perhaps...?
Yeah, the rumored "Super elite doctor"!
Oh my god, he's so cool!
Isn't he?
Apparently his father is managing
two hospitals at once!
Also, he was supposed to have graduated University
with the best results in his year!
Not to mention those good looks!
I's like he's the perfect man!
I wonder why he came to our place?
He could have lived like a prince if
he worked at his father's hospital.
That's true isn't it...
I's obvious that he was just destined to encounter me!
What did you say?!
Heheh... the young doctor really
seems to be popular doesn't he?
There seem to be no irregularities in the
results from his investigation either.
His educational profile, lineage, and ability
offer no grounds for objection.
It's good that he's a proficient man,
but are you sure such a "prince"
is going to be alright?
You're being deceived as well.
Under that sweet and innocent face of his,
there's another hidden layer, the part
of him which lies in the shadows.
You cannot fool these eyes of mine...
You're a member of the same species as me.
It's ok to hold exceptions for him then correct?
Indeed. I've got great confidence in him.
Kuwabara-Sensei, you're incredible aren't you?
I am?
All you have to do is inspect the patient's body briefly
and you can handle them smoothly!
It's amazing!
You think so?
I think it's normal for a doctor though.
I'm clumsy and stupid, I'm always doing
silly things like this morning...
That's not so bad.
Girls that are a little clumsy are quite cute you know.
Cute? Not really...
I've finished my rounds.
Good work.
That's good timing, let me introduce someone to you.
This is the newly appointed chief nurse
of the maternity and gynecology ward,
Nanase Ren-san.
I'm Nanase Ren. I look forward to working with you.
R-Ren? It can't be!
No... there's no doubt about it.
It's definitely her.
Ren is in front of me right now!
Am I dreaming?
I'm glad to be alive...
I finally got to see Ren again.
I'm really glad to be alive!
Well then, I'm counting on you.
Yes.
Well then Kuwabara-Sensei...
Is anything the matter?
No, nothing at all!
I think some dirt just got into my eye is all.
Well then, there's still work left
to do so I'll leave it at that?
Yes. Good work.
Nurse Station
Is there something the matter?
You seem to be all flustered.
Why are you ignoring me?
Eh?
We finally meet each other again
after all this time and yet...
Well that's because...
I'm still in love with you!
Why are you trying to avoid me like
this? Do you hate me that much?!
No... let me go!
N-No!
For the past 4 years I've used every means
available to me in order to look for you!
It's not a coincidence that we got to meet here.
We're connected by fate after all!
NO!
S-Stop it...
That hurts!
Stop it...
NO! Let go of me!
No!
Ren!
Stop it!
Stop it! Please!
NO!
No!
Ren... Ren!
I said NO!
Kuwabara-Sensei?
Is there something the matter?
No... I'm fine. It's nothing.
Ren...
I've finally found you,
but won't you accept me?
I'm working at the same place again tomorrow.
I'm going to make you recognize me no matter what!
I have no use for these boring women anymore.
Title: It's Kumiko (*^o^*)
Sender: Kumiko
Sou-kun, you're horrid!(>o<)
I phoned you again you know!
Why know, I found a restaurant that serves
really delicious food! I thought that maybe you'd
want to go with me some time Sou-kun...
Title: I want to see you.
Sender: Mii
What do you mean it's all over?
Did you get another girlfriend?
I only had sex with Takashi just the once
so don't say you won't meet with me anymore.
What would you like as a birthday present?
Title
Ren's true
character
I'm
really
unhappy
Huh? Ren's... true character?
Title: Ren's true character
Sender: Unknown
How about I show you the truth
about your beloved Nanase Ren
If you've got the guts
then open this file.
Ren!
This can't be!
This is Ren's true character?!
I... I won't believe it!
It's a lie!
This has to be a damn lie!
Movie files?
Don't watch them! If you watch them you're
doing exactly what they want you to do!
You musn't watch them!
You're starting to feel good now baby!
It's no good! I'll break in half!
Keep going!
No! It's going to come out!
Shut the hell up!
No! Oh noooo!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
I'm begging you Ren! Please stop it!
S... Sto...
Please stop it!
PLEEEEAAAASSSEEEEE!!
Medical Corporation
Sei-Katorea General Hospital
Oh hi granny! You look a lot better, now don't you?
Yes, thankfully.
I'm happy to hear that. Take care of yourself, ok?
Huh? Kuwabara-sensei and Nanase-san?
Those two were together yesterday
as well weren't they?
Of course, I don't believe any of it.
But, I want to hear it straight from you.
It's not you is it? Right?
You're wrong.
I supposed it can't be helped
that you found out about this.
The one in those photographs is most certainly me.
W-Why?
Do you know Hirasaka-sensei from Yuriana Hospital?
Ah yeah, I've heard his name before at least.
I was the test subject in Hirasaka-sensei's
female body experiments.
Female body experiments?!
You're saying that was an experiment?!
It couldn't be helped.
I was too weak to run away and there
was nothing else I could do about it.
All I could do was follow Hirasaka's orders.
That can't be!
You see,
I'm not the kind of woman that you think I am.
My body has already been soiled.
Can you still say that you love me
after knowing what I'm like?
Well then, I'll be returning to work.
W... wait a minute...
Ren!
Damn it! Damn it to hell!
Hirasaka!
HIRASAKAAA!
Damn you! Damn you!! DAMN YOUUU!!!
Thank you very much.
Take care of yourself.
Kuwabara-sensei!
What's the matter?
You don't look so good.
Yeah, I guess.
I couldn't sleep very well last night.
Perhaps you should take a rest for a while?
I thought about it,
but when I looked in the staff room a while ago
it looked like someone else was sleeping in there.
Ah, in that case
I know a place that'll be perfect for you!
In here, hurry up!
Is it ok to come down here?
It's a patient room currently under refurbishment.
If you rest here you surely won't
be disturbed by anyone.
Ehh... this place is good!
Thanks Kazama-kun!
Not at all...
Erm...
Kazama-kun?
Erm... well...
Sensei, am I not good enough for you?
Eh?
Is it impossible for me to take
the place of Nanase-san?
Ka... Kazama-kun! Don't tell me
you saw that this morning...
I... I'm sorry!
I know I shouldn't have but...
I was worried about you so, I accidentally...
I'm really sorry!
I see.
You saw an ugly side of me huh?
No! It wasn't ugly!
It's alright. No-one will truly love someone
like me properly anyway.
Even you are just sympathizing with me...
That's not true at all! I'm serious about you!
Sensei!
It's ok to cry when you face something sad.
As long as it's ok with you I'll take
the place of Nanase-san, ok?
Se... Sensei!!
I'm sorry Kazama-kun.
Can we just stay like this for a while?
Ok. We can stay likei this until you settle back down.
I'm sorry...
Oh no! It's already gotten this late!
Oh no, what's this?
Exactly what you wished for.
Kuwabara-sensei?!
I'm feeling lonely... I was stabbed
in the back by Nanase-kun.
Eh?
You're going to console me right?
But that doesn't explain why you did this!
Unless you do the same thing as her you
won't be able to console me after all.
You can't be serious!
I'm a lot better than your average guy.
And yet, Nanase-kun won't love me.
Even though she allows other men
to do whatever they like to her.
Why aren't I good enough for her?
Why?
Why, damit?!
You're hurting me!
Shut it! Shut the hell up!!
No! Nooooo!
Stop disobeying me!
– Stop it! No, Noo!!
– You bitch!
Please stop it already!
I'm begging you!
You have big tits.
No!! Stop it!
Noo! Please stop this! No!
No!
Don't touch there! Stop it!
Don't get boisterous!
You like me, don't you?
No I don't! Stop it! No!
Even though you let that bastard
take advantage of you!?
I'm not Nanase-san!
Shut the hell up!
Shut our fucking mouth!
I'm not...
I'm not Nanase-san!
Shut up!
You fucking bitch!
I'm not...
I'm not... Nanase-san...
You still won't shut up?!
Bitch!
No!! Stop it! Let me go! NOO!!
You make quite the pretty picture, Ren.
Nooooo!
No!
Please!
Don't go any further!
What's wrong...
Don't tell me you're a virgin?
Is that so?
Good for you, you're first partner is the man you love.
Come on, give me a good look at it.
– Let me took at the secret place you've
never shown anyone before.
– Noo stop it nooo!
How does it feel to show it off to the man you love?
Noo... it's embarrassing... stop it!
What a pretty color.
It appears that you weren't lying about
not having slept with a man before.
No, please stop it!
The taste of a virgin is quite exceptional.
Shall we enter the end-game now then?
No, you can't! Stop it! Noooo!
What's wrong with you? Aren't you overjoyed
to get to have sex with the man you love?
No... I don't want it this way...
Release that tension! Come on!
Ah, I'm gonna let loose!
Stop it! Stop it! Anything but that! Noooo!
Are you satisfied now?
While you were doing it you didn't
even call my name once...
But that's ok... because I'm just a
stand-in for Nanase-san after all.
You're going to help me forget her, aren't you?
Right, Mana?
It appears that things have worked
out just as I planned.
We can certainly use that man alright.
You're right.
Things are going to get interesting from now on.
Shaking in the light of the moon
Everyone continues walking alone,
lost inside a labyrinth
where I found myself from the past.
I wonder if we could ever go back
to the past when we were clueless.
Of course, we could not
because the sky will only fall down.
I will definitely find it.
Believe in something and march straight ahead.
Everything looks beautiful,
the smiles from now on...
The smiles from now on...