Sora...
Thanks to you, everything is going according to plan.
And now, we're going to the next stage.
You might turn into a different person.
lf that happens, please forgive me.
lt will not happen right away.
lt'll happen little by little.
What was that?
Sora!
Does it have to do with the experiments being conducted?
No. lt couldn't...
Supervisor Yunagi, how is Sora?
The seizures have stopped.
The Superintendent is examining him.
He seems fine.
He'll be back in his room in an hour.
Really? That's good.
Please wait.
ls Sora's seizure related to his medication?
lf it is, what about it?
The subject has signed a consent form with the institute.
Even if it is the medication,
there are no problems.
That's cold.
Then this is a human experiment.
lncrease the dosage?
Yes, because of the seizure incident, we're way behind schedule.
We should revise the dosage schedule.
Keep things as they are.
We're seeing good results.
He might suffer physical damage if we push too hard.
Yes, but...
ls there a problem?
No, nothing.
lf there's something you want to say, spill it out.
Superintendent, what do you see in that man?
Are you talking about Sora?
What do you mean?
You don't treat him like the other subjects.
The other day, l saw you two here.
So, you saw us.
You naughty girl.
You must be punished.
Mistress, this feels so good.
Really.
How does it feel when l pinch your nipples?
lt hurts so good.
Mistress, please forgive me.
Lick my pussy.
You call that licking pussy?
l'm sorry, Mistress. l will do it right.
Put some thought into it.
Roll the tip of your tongue around the clit.
Good. That's it.
That's it.
Show more enthusiasm, or else l'll punish you more.
Yes, Mistress.
That's better.
Use a lot of spit and use your tongue.
That's enough.
Like this, Mistress?
Oh, Mistress, please take my virginity.
Which hole should l put it in?
ln my pussy.
My. How selfish of you.
Hurry, Mistress. l can't wait. Stick it in.
Alright.
Take this!
Mistress, you stuck it up my ass!
That's because...
your pussy virginity is being saved for Sora.
What?
You want me to fuck that man?
You're kidding, right?
No. l'm serious.
You're going to give him your virginity.
Mistress, please. Anything but that!
No. lt has been decided.
No. l won't fuck him. l will not fuck him!
lf that's true, then why are you so wet?
That's because it's you that's fucking me.
Bullshit. You're imagining him.
You're imagining that man...
taking away your virginity with his big thick cock!
No. That's not true.
There. You came.
Yunagi, don't lie to yourself.
You're a masochist skank that loves to be humiliated.
What?
He had a sudden seizure?
Quiet. You'll wake him.
Sorry.
Please keep it quiet.
Could you tell me more about his seizure?
lt happened so suddenly, l can't tell what happened.
He suddenly screamed,
and he held his head and fell.
Let's see...
His face was covered with veins when l lifted his head.
lt was strange.
His face was covered with veins...
Maybe l gave him too much.
Hiyori?
Huh?
Do you know anything about this experiment?
Well...
lt's not like l don't know anything.
What's going on?
- Sorry.
- Huh?
l can't tell you.
There's patient confidentiality and it's none of your business.
Sorry.
Wait...
Everybody is hiding something.
What's going to happen to Sora if he stays here?
Huh?
Sora?
Are you alright?
Yuu.
Where am l?
This is your room. You were passed out for three days.
Three days? Why?
You don't remember the seizure you had in the garden?
l had a seizure in the garden?
Yes.
l don't remember anything.
Are you alright? Are you ill in any way?
l'm fine. Everything seems alright.
Oh.
Did you take care of me?
No.
You were in lntensive Care until a couple of hours ago.
Then what's this?
You were running a fever.
l see. Thank you.
lt was nothing.
l bet you're hungry. Would you like something to eat?
No. l'm not hungry.
l'd really like to go outside.
l need to stretch out.
Outside?
But it's been raining all day.
A walk is not reasonable.
Rain... l don't like rain.
lsn't life here hard for you?
Hard? Never. This place is perfect for me.
l'm out of the rain and l get three square meals a day.
lt's like heaven for me.
But they're giving you a strange drug!
lt gave you a seizure!
Why, all so sudden?
Oh. l'm sorry.
But...
Don't worry.
l just have to take the drugs and l'm in better health than before.
And...
l get a million dollars when this drug test is over.
What?
lt's a fortune.
l'm going to buy a house and we're all going to live together.
Huh?
l mean my family...
although we're not blood relatives.
l grew up in an orphanage.
lt was an awful place. They beat me for the smallest infractions.
Like when l made noises when l slept or when l had lint on my pants.
l still have nightmares about it.
l couldn't bear it.
l ran away.
Before l finished my education.
For days after l ran away,
all l had was water.
But just as l was about to pass out from hunger...
The sell date for the bread they gave me was expired,
but it was the warmest thing l'd ever eaten.
These people took me in.
They named me Sora.
They said l'm going to be their child, so they will name me.
They are your family?
Yeah. l'm going to buy a house as big as an auditorium,
and we're all going to live in it.
Sora, can l tell you something?
Sure.
A man l was in love with was a researcher at this institute.
There was an incident and he killed himself.
What?
He let a test subject die from the same drug you're taking.
So he took his own life in anguish.
lf you keep taking this drug, l'm afraid you might also die!
What are you saying?
There's nothing wrong with me.
My health is fine.
Yuu, l can't go on.
l can't be part of this conspiracy any longer!
Sora...
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
A man's voice said, ''l can't be part of this conspiracy any longer!''
That's what my lover said. Why would you know that?
Sora might die.
Hiyori?
That man will be easy to entice.
Was that Sakurako?
What is going on?
Sora, what's the matter? Are you ill?
l wish that man would just die.
Sora, wait for me!
His veins shouldn't have come out.
Cell mutations were supposed to be under control.
Huh?
What's this?
l asked you not to come here.
l didn't want to. l was ordered from upstairs.
Your report has ambiguous points and they wanted me to ask you directly.
What do you need to know?
This experiment is to measure how far you can mutate a human body.
lsn't that so?
That's right.
According to your report, his transmutation is complete.
But then, why isn't the experiment over?
Oh, is that a problem?
lf we've achieved results, the powers upstairs want the specimen.
They are impatient, as usual.
ls the experiment finished, or isn't it?
To be specific, we've finished up to the point that l was briefed.
What do you mean, ''briefed''?
l've been kept outside the grid.
''Outside the grid''? You're the chief researcher of this experiment!
How can that be?
His physical program went exactly as l'd planned.
But l was fooled into thinking that that was all there was.
Then what is the real purpose of this experiment?
That's what l'm looking into.
Do you think you'll find out?
l don't know. But l found something interesting.
Come see.
ls it something l would understand?
Explain it so that l can understand.
This lets you reprogram human genes in any way you desire.
Did you know that?
Yes. l read that in your plan.
This is that program.
But part of it has been rewritten behind my back.
Who would do such a thing?
There is only one other person who could do this.
Who?
The Superintendent.
Superintendent Reika?
l can't believe she has your ability.
The difference between genius and prodigy is inspiration.
Either you do, or you don't, have the idea.
Anybody can dissect and understand what has already been discovered.
Do you know her specialization?
lsn't it clinical neurological physiology?
That is probably something she learned to get into this institute.
Her real specialization is...
quantum physics.
Quantum physics?
Yes. ln particular, the development of computer algorithms for quantum calculations.
Algorithms?
Could she be trying to create a biological computer?
That may be a hasty conclusion.
lt's outside of my specialization so l can't say,
but biological computers and quantum computers are completely different things.
They work on different principles.
Then what could it be?
That's what l want to investigate.
But will the powers upstairs wait long enough?
Can somebody outside the grid find out?
Who do you think l am?
Alright. l'll talk to them.
Great!
But you won't have much time.
- Oh.
- You have three days to figure out what the plan is.
Three days? Can't l have more time?
Another team is demanding the specimen. There's nothing l can do about it.
Do you think the ''specimen'' will come along so easily?
Who do you think l am?
That man will be easy to entice.
Sora, it's time for your medication.
He's not here.
That man.
Supervisor Yunagi!
Ms. Yunagi, has he returned?
No. Nobody is here.
Really?
What happened?
To tell the truth...
l see. l understand the situation.
l'll look around too.
Please do.
What does Mistress see in him?
l wish that man would just die.
ls that so? What does Adolph say?
Alright. l'll leave that to you, Adolph.
You are all such little troublemakers.
That's Sora.
ls he suffering from a seizure?
But this may be my chance.
Sora?
What are you doing here?
- lt's way past the time for your medication.
- Supervisor Yunagi.
- Go immediately to the clinic.
- That troublesome woman.
l'll send Nurse Yuu right away.
Sora...
Sora! Where are you?
Darn. Where could he have disappeared?
Huh?
l haven't looked in the basement.
What should l do? Only researchers are permitted in there.
A man's voice said, ''l can't be complicit in this conspiracy any longer!''
This is no time to by pussyfooting around.
l have to know why he heard my lover.
Nurse Yuu?
Superintendent.
No unauthorized personnel are allowed in there.
l'm looking for Sora.
Sora?
l heard from Supervisor Yunagi that he has disappeared.
You were going into the basement to look for him?
Yes.
No.
What?
Doesn't it say, ''NO ADMlTTANCE''?
But...
Do you care that much about Sora?
lt's not what you think.
Really? l like him a lot.
Huh?
l'm glad you don't like him.
Because he likes you.
Huh?
Go back to your room. l'll go look for him.
Sora likes me?
l don't think of him that way...
l... Sora...
You can't do this. Let me go!
l can't do it. Why?
Why u mean?
This isn't something you would do to people agianst their will.
Yeah.
Sure l can.
l mean...
look how wet your pussy is.
And l can hear your thoughts.
You want me to fuck you.
You want me to stir my cock in your steamy hot cunt.
l'm not thinking about something like that.
Do you really think so?
Then why are your pussy lips starting to open up?
That because of what your doing.
So you don't mind that l'm not the Superintendent.
Huh?
No! Let me go. Please let me go!
No!
Help me Mistress!
Mistress!
What kind of relationship does she have with the Superintendent?
You want the Superintendent to watch?
She's right there.
Superintendent.
We need to talk.
Be a good girl and don't move.
Mistress...
Please help me Mistress. l don't want this.
Like l've said before,
l'm giving your pussy virginity to Sora.
No Mistress! Anything but that!
Sora, go ahead and fuck her.
No! Don't! Stop it!
No!
Congratulations, Yunagi.
You sick bitch.
What about yourself?
Your friend is here.
Friend?
Hiyori.
This party is just getting started.