I'm sure you and I saw it,
that nostalgic smile.
Tonight I'm watching
in a room next to yours
the last scene I can't remember.
It's different from what I want to see.
It's a more happy ending.
Dreaming of that last time
when we were truly together.
I look over my shoulder
and you're right there beside me.
Let's keep that happiness
to ourselves!
Night Shift Nurses 2
What the hell was that?
Has she no shame?
They're looking at me... I'm being exposed.
Get a load of that!
Man she's daring!
Is this shit even legal?
She looks so inviting.
I'm gonna run some game on her.
Your game won't mean much
when her scary-ass boyfriend pops out.
You think so?
What should I do?
They're all looking at me...
I'm being exposed to them all.
Please get here soon,
Kuwabara-sensei!
I'm... just about...
Today's hours of operation will end in five minutes.
We'll be waiting for your next visit.
Kuwabara-sensei...
why, why didn't you come?
Suzuka-chan?
Where's Kuwabara-sensei?
He said we should swim together.
Really?
W-what're you... aah!
Wh-What was that for?!
He said to swim dressed as you are now.
N-No way...
Kuwabara-sensei's orders!
Will he be joining me?
Quit being so arrogant and just swim!
Do it now!
Did you enjoy skinny dipping?
How could I?
It's just like Kuwabara-sensei said.
He said that?
Yeah. He said people get turned on when they're embarrassed and on display.
Female slaves do, anyway.
Female... slaves?
Correct.
N-No way! What're you doing,
Suzuka-chan?
Just sit tight and receive
another of Sensei's orders.
He said that, too?
Yes, Sensei is watching patiently from afar.
I'm so ashamed of that spot.
And I'm looking at it.
Suzuka has been most useful. How should I "thank" her?
Don't look!
Never mind. I need women like her, too.
But I still want more usable nurses.
It looks like I still need to give Karen and Mana the works.
That's right.
What I really wanted to do was change my methods.
I'll test the loyalties
of Suzuka and the others.
No!
As you can see, the nurses' training is making steady progress.
The redesign of the hospital rooms has been slightly delayed.
But by dawn, you will see the special ward in its finished state.
I hope your expectations have been met.
You've made us wait quite awhile, but it looks like it'll be worth it.
Yes. You've built a very
specialized nursing system.
I thought that the training would be the main issue.
But it's only a matter of time
before those nurses are broken in.
Are your demands being satisfied?
Those nurses you just saw are all...
...under the control of the special ward.
We've prepared a light meal
for you gentlemen.
Please eat to your stomachs' content.
To the special ward.
To the special ward!
Could this be...?
I'd love to munch on that  taco!
Does the food suit your tastes?
Please do eat up.
Fuck yeah!
Keep still.
Y-Yes.
Think we can get some of this
in that special ward?
We hadn't considered it,
but if you desire it...
The patients are gonna love this.
That's for sure. I haven't had a salad this good in ages.
Talk about a feast for the eyes.
N-Noooo!!
Oh dear. You've spilled some.
My apologies.
She still lacks training.
By the time we open, we'll have this "Female Flesh Feast" perfected.
No, it's more fun to watch their reactions.
I agree.
My thoughts exactly.
I'm all for this "human platter" idea.
Thank you very much.
Sayuki, are you off?
Yes. I had the early shift today.
Good work.
Good luck to you too, Karen-san.
Thanks.
By the way, it seemed like Kazama-senpai was looking forward to today.
Um... what was Mana
looking forward to, again?
I saw her go out all dressed up.
Possibly on a date with
Kuwabara-sensei. I'm so jealous.
Where? Where were they going?
I-I don't know...
Central Park, maybe?
Kuwabara-sensei...
I did just what you told me.
Kuwabara-sensei?
Hey. You look good.
Aw, no I don't...
You look so refreshing when you're not wearing your nurse outfit.
Thank you so much.
I made dinner reservations for tonight.
But how about a walk
under this beautiful sunset first?
S-Sure.
Hey, babe, what's the big hurry?
Yo, Nurse! Where do you think you're going in that getup?
Butt out!
Oh, hey. Did you see a rich guy
walking through here with a girl?
Oh yeah, we totally saw them.
They went thataway.
I-Is that so? Thank you.
Strange... Is this really the right way?
I-I'm just looking for somebody.
Let me through!
Can't let you do that.
Not after making this big score.
The heck you say?!
Stupid bitch!
Being on a date with you
feels like a dream, Sensei.
Now, now. This isn't the time to be calling me "Sensei."
Don't you know you're not on the clock?
Eh? But what should I call you, then?
"Souichirou" is fine.
Eh?! Souichirou...-san?
Ditch the -san.
Here, kitty kitty! Where'd you go?
You forgot your clothes~!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
This is our secret garden.
She's in here.
Hey, can we come in too?
You mean you guys lied  to me?!?
Hey, we found her!
Over here!
Now "Sou-chan," that's a bit much.
That's what my mother called me.
Oh.
Is it that weird?
I mean...
Oh, hey. Let me read your palms.
That was my minor back in college.
You'll be astonished at
its astonishing accuracy.
Sure, why not?
Caught you!
Ow!
It's no use. I can't get away.
I am so screwed.
You managed to run to a place
where ain't nobody gonna come.
It's my pleasure to welcome you
to our flower garden.
NOOOO!!!!
Noo~!
Now we've got you!
There's no escaping for you now, nursie.
S-Stop it!
Do you actually think you can get away with this shit?!
If you let me go now, I won't tell a soul.
You're the one who won't get away.
Take off the last piece!
Please, stop this!
She's still  begging?
We're gonna put you
in your place real quick!
Hell yeah, we're gonna
make you feel fan-fucking-tastic!
Don't do this, please!
Shut the fuck up!
Stop it, stop it!
Take it like a woman; you'll feel better.
Damn that was fast.
Now get ready for Round 2!
Somebody "fill in" for me!
Don't need to tell us twice!
First time in awhile.
Noo, don't!
Just quit it!
Hey man, there's a line here!
Wrap it up!
I can cum fast or heavy, but not both!
Thanks for the meal, sensei!
It tasted great!
Really? Good to hear.
Kazama-kun...
No, Mana.
Um, yes?
Can you stay out today?
Y-Yes...
There's somewhere I'd like to take you.
You'll like it, too.
Okay.
Suck it, bitch!
Noo--!
Looks like you need some persuasion.
Lick it good. And if I feel teeth, you'll never smile again.
Fuckin' A. That's more like it.
Damn you're good.
Hurry up and drown her!
This chick's awesome!
Hey, no slacking on the (blow)job!
Still, won't we get in trouble for this?
Not according to that
sick fuck of a doctor, no.
Huuuh?
Now that we've all had our fun,
it's time to take her to the drop-off site.
Then we get the rest of our pay,
in exchange for forgetting all about this.
Sensei? Weren't we here this afternoon?
The park's romantic at night, too.
I'll guide you to a marvelous place that you've never heard of.
Okay.
Ah, it's so pretty!
That's right. Night time's
the right time for my kind of fun.
Here we are.
What could be in a place like this?
Calm down, it's all good.
Or at least not all bad.
It can't be!
Let me go! Let me go, Karen is...
...just fine, right?
Mana, getting watched turns me on.
Let's give Karen a show.
No, stop, Sensei! We mustn't--!
You're not going to obey me, Mana?
Hey, get out here!
Sayuki-chan? Nogami-san!?
These two valuable assistants will obey my every command.
It's too late for you, Mana.
That's not true!
That's impossible!
Hey, assist me!
Cut it out...
No, I'm getting all warm...
Stop it!
S-Sensei! You're hurting me!
Our guest of honor can't
see us too well in this position.
Stand her up!
Talk about a great view!
You won't be able to take your eyes off the violation of your beloved Mana!
S-Sensei! Nooo...
Don't look! Don't watch!!
Here goes!
No, don't! Don't put it in!
Noooo!!
How's it feel, Mana?
Aren't you glad Karen gets to watch?
You're really starting to reek, Karen! Very fitting!
I'll wash it off for you.
Nooo, don't!!
No, it hurts!
It's cold!
No...
You two, get them off!
We're gonna have female patients in the special ward someday.
Getting them off means
getting some practice in for that day.
Yes.
No, stop this!
Please stop this!
I'm paying you good money for this!
What's the problem?
Sayuki! Suzuka!
Whoever gets their girl off first
gets exempted from special training.
But the loser gets to join Mana and Karen
in Special Training Hell!
No, stop it!
N-No, don't do that anymore!
Oh, this is so bad!
Yes, that's it! Keep going
until their bodies are trashed!
Fuck them silly until they're ruined beyond repair!
Please forgive us...
A loss is a loss, Sayuki.
It's... itchy. What've you done!?
Nogami-kun's just brushed on
a little medicine.
It shares some ingredients with tree sap.
Insects love  it.
What'd you say?!
N-Nooo!
N-No! Nooooo!!!
Boy, these bugs are showing some hustle.
I... I beg you!!
Let us go!
Sensei, I can't take this!
Don't let them get me!
Sensei, I'm so sorry!
I'll do anything!
Nogami-kun will bring you
a change of clothes in the morning.
Fight the good fight.
Sensei, don't go!
Sensei, please spare us!
No! NOOO!!!
No! Make it stop! Let me go!
Nogami.
Yes?
There's still lots of work to be done.
We've barely scratched the surface.
Will you continue to support me?
Yes, Sensei.
Good answer. Very good.
Shaking in the light of the moon
Everyone continues walking alone,
lost inside a labyrinth
where I found myself from the past.
I wonder if we could ever go back
to the past when we were clueless.
Of course, we could not
because the sky will only fall down.
I will definitely find it.
Believe in something
and march straight ahead.
Everything looks beautiful,
the smiles from now on...
The smiles from now on...