I'm sure you and I saw it,
that nostalgic smile.
Tonight I'm watching
in a room next to yours
the last scene I can't remember.
It's different from what I want to see.
It's a more happy ending
Dreaming of that last time
when we were truly together.
I look over my shoulder
and you're right there beside me.
Let's keep that happiness
to ourselves!
Stop it! No!!
I'm not Nanase-san!
SHUT UP!! SHUT UP!!
I'm not...
I'm not Nanase-san!!
Stop saying that, you bitch!
I really didn't think he was going
to turn out this violent.
Oh? I thought he was the same
species as you though?
Heheh... I prefer a more gentlemanly
approach myself.
That's a good one.
No!
No...
Se... Sensei... We can't do this here.
Kazama-kun, you're going to help
me forget Ren aren't you?
Yes... If it's to help you then I...
I'll do anything you want...
That's a good girl.
Anyway,
with this we can finally pull one over on those
old farts at the medical association.
Doesn't the seduction of the boy come first?
I'll get him to do it whatever it takes.
You were that against it yesterday,
and yet you're already this wet...
Oh no! Please don't stare at it like that!
Why are you wet?
That's because, I doing it with
my beloved Kuwabara-sensei.
Is that so?
I love you too, Mana.
I'm so happy.
I love you too...
It hurts!
Sensei!... I'll try hard... I'll try my best...
So please... Be gentler to me...
I'm going.
If I don't hurry somebody will come in here.
Kazama! You're late!
What have you been up to?
Oh, I'm sorry, alot of things came up.
There's no use in trying to make excuses.
We decided before that we'd come in early
due to the lack of staff didn't we?
I'm sorry,
I'm afraid I directed her to take care of something.
And you are?
This is the new doctor Kuwabara-sensei.
Ah, Sakaki-sensei successor?
The name's Kuwabara.
Excuse my rudeness.
My name is Konohara Karen.
I'm a 2nd year Nurse, the same as Kazama.
I look forward to working together.
As do I.
W... Well then.
I'm rather busy, so I'll have to leave now.
Sorry about that, Konohara-san has quite fastidious.
She's like that with everyone.
I don't really mind.
Ren's not here...
Sensei?
What?
No... It's nothing...
Will it really be alright leaving it up to that young guy?
I guarantee it.
All the data we've gathered from
him shows his aptitude.
Failure is unacceptable.
Just leave it to me.
If we can introduce this kind
of service into the hospital...
there's no doubt that many rich people
would want to spend their money for it.
Please don't do this here!
What are you saying?
This is to cure your fastidiousness, isn't it?
But I'm in the middle of my work!
Patients shouldn't talk back.
That old bastard... All he did
was take his own pleasure.
I'm all frustrated.
You can't tell, can't you?
Wow... Great, Karen!
Look at all this!
Taste it yourself.
It's tasty, isn't it?
You're going to do the exact same thing I had
to do to the old medicial association bastard.
That's good... you're doing well!
Everyone can see you from outside, Karen!
No! Stop it!
Let everyone see your true lewd form!
That's...!
It appears to be developing favorably.
You have nothing to worry about.
You're going to give birth to a very healthy baby.
Thank you very much.
Take good care.
Come in.
Sorry for intruding.
Sorry to call you in here all of a sudden.
I'll be leaving then.
Good work.
What is it that you wanted to see me about?
It's more of a request than a discussion.
We would like the young and elite Kuwabawara-sensei
to participate in one of our currently
undergoing projects.
That is an honor, however...
Exactly what kind of project is it?
We haven't announced it yet.
But in the near future a special ward aimed solely
at wealthy people is going to be established.
So it's going to offer the very best in treatment along
with a reception which rivals high class hotels, huh?
Oh not just that.
Our beautiful nurses will give
their whole-hearted devotion.
And even use their bodies in order to
deliver the best attendance possible.
If a patient enters but once, they'll most likely
not want to be cured until they die.
You mean?!
In order to reliably make this project a success...
We're going to need nurses who are both
obedient and give good service.
And as many as possible.
That is why I wish for you to break them in.
Breaking in the nurses?
W... Why are you asking me?
You're fully competent, aren't you?
As long as you perform in the same spirit
as you did last night to Kazama-san.
You really did something bold considering
you onliy just got here.
That room just happens to be a
sample for the special ward.
The monitoring system installed in order to check the
condition of patients, recorded everything you did.
I was quite surprised
that something like that came out on film.
This can't be...
So, how about it?
Will you undertake that position Kuwabara-sensei?
Or will you
refuse and put an end to your career as a doctor?
Indeed... It was a foolish question to ask the
sagacious Kuwabara-sensei after all.
First of all please make your way to the
surgery room of the special ward.
You should figure out why I requested you
to participate in this project if you do.
But then, the real one who needed this project may
have been you to begin with, Kuwabara-sensei.
Kuwabara-sensei...
Re... Ren!
Who on earth did this?
What the...
Don't tell me...!!
I was Hirasaka-sensei's test subject.
Hirasaka... So all of this is all his doing?
Ren, it was true...
I didn't want to believe it and yet...
Kuwabara-sensei?!
What's the matter?
Sensei... Are you crying?
What happened?
N... Nanase-san?!
W... What is this?!
What were you two doing together?
Shut the hell up!
Don't you dare try and say anything about Ren and I!
Ow! It hurts!
Stop it please!
Don't order me around!
That's not...
Don talk back to me!
Se... Sensei?
I... I don't want this!
I said don't order me around!
You bitch!
WHAT KIND OF ATTITUDE IS THAT?!
You look good Mana.
AHH! It hurts!
Shut up! Relax our muscle
Wait here for a while...
You're horrible,
Sensei!
I'm sorry Ren...
Kuwabara-sensei...
I want to accept you for what you were...
But then I ended up running away.
What's wrong?
I was too weak.
But... I'm alright now!
Se... Sensei...
If it's for you Ren, I'll do anything!
No! Don't...
You can't!
Please stop it Sensei...
It's dirty!
What are you saying?
If it's something that came out of you then I'm fine.
Oh Ren... You're so beautiful.
Bite it... Bite it please...
Eh? I can't do that to my beloved Ren.
If it was Hirasaka-sensei, he would do that...
No... He'd do things even more extreme than that.
Did you just say Hirasaka?!
I won't lose...
There's no way I can lose to that bastard Hirasaka!
I can't lose to that bastard!
Don't look at it!
I care for Ren more than that
Hirasaka! Dammit! Dammit!
I won't lose!
I won't lose to Hirasaka!
Ren... My Ren...
I won't lose dammit!
What else did Hirasaka do to you?
Did he do this?!
How about this?!
Dammit!
Like hell will I lose!
What about this?
WHAT ABOUT THIS!?!
Dammit!
DAMMIT!
I won't lose!
I won't fucking lose!!
I won't lose to Hirasaka that bastard!
Sensei... If you move around that much I'll...
How's that?
I can do anything if it's for you.
No... I don't want this...
Shaking in the light of the moon
Everyone continues walking alone,
lost inside a labyrinth
where I found myself from the past.
I wonder if we could ever go back
to the past when we were clueless.
Of course, we could not
because the sky will only fall down.
I will definitely find it.
Believe in something and march straight ahead.
Everything looks beautiful,
the smiles from now on...
The smiles from now on...