I stumbled on this particular adult site by accident.
She has a son in high school.
Despite this, every evening she falls
back on her lewd fantasies.
When she returns home, she's
just an ordinary housewife.
But when she cheats on her husband,
she becomes like a whore.
So here's this slutty woman.
Everyone, please feel free to fuck her in your minds.
This woman has lived her life as a chaste wife,
and as a chaste mother.
However, one day she met Shousei,
the 'Leader" of a our club.
She was given some perverted training.
And she was taught the way of
"The Female Beast's Ecstasy."
To this day, she devours sex.
Her body shivers as she buries her face in my crotch.
She drinks down all of my lust.
She is known as M-E, and her
occupation is part-time housewife.
She has a son in high school.
Not yet divorced.
She's a hardcore masochist and exhibitionist.
Yama-hime no Mi
Chapter 1          M-E
A computer? That's a luxury item!
Against my mother's wishes,
I bought an expensive new computer.
When I first saw the homepage about this woman,
I remembered what Mom had said.
It couldn't be...
What a terrible downpour. Gross.
The weather forecast said it wouldn't rain either.
You really can't trust it these days.
Did you get wet in the rain, Kazuya?
It was tough for me.
There's going to be a new
supermarket by the train station.
You know, I work part-time at a supermarket.
We had to decide on our special
sales for tomorrow, apparently.
It got really intense there, so I ended
up coming home really late.
What's wrong?
I was just worried about you because of the rain.
You must be hungry.
I ran back here to cook you dinner.
I was supposed to come home much earlier, actually.
They say the economy is supposed to improve soon.
But no change, as usual.
Oh, I see.
Oh, dear.
Something is wrong. What’is it?
N-Nothing!
Just hurry up and put some clothes on already!
But I always dress in front of you.
What a strange boy.
Wait just a bit longer.
Sorry for the wait.
I'll prepare dinner now.
So where's this new supermarket gonna be?
Where the fitness center used
to be at the train station.
Remember that place?
Yeah. Kadoji?
That's the place. They're tearing it
down and opening a supermarket.
So that's why you're doing a special sale.
That's exactly it.
The other place is opening soon,
so our clerks are nervous they'll steal our business.
It would be a problem if your place had to close down.
People would lose their jobs.
But there's nothing you can do about it, Kazuya.
Yes, there is. I can come work there to help out.
That would be nice.
Must be a look-alike.
That has to be it.
I just remembered, Kazuya.
This Saturday I'm going on a work retreat.
Everyone from work is going, and I couldn't back out.
It's going to last until Sunday.
I'm pretty sure I'll be back before it gets dark.
But will you be okay alone?
Wh-What do you mean, "Will you be okay?"
It's just that I've never left you home alone before.
I'm worried.
I'll be fine. I can make it on my own.
So don't concern yourself.
I'm not a kid anymore, Mom.
You're right.
Sorry about that.
It's nice for you to get out every once in a while.
If you do nothing but work, you'll stress yourself out.
You're right. And truthfully, I was looking forward to it.
I'll be back by Sunday night.
I thought that Mom was just treating me like a child.
But letting me have the house to
myself was a great opportunity.
As a result, I could check that
homepage more carefully.
At least that's what I thought back then.
Mom!
My mom raised me all by herself.
Even though it wasn't the most glamorous life,
she provided me with everything I needed.
I'm sure she endured difficulties I can't even imagine.
And I really do believe her job causes her stress.
She wears hand-me-down clothes.
She has no special leisure activities.
I get the impression she never has fun.
I met M-E at dinner.
The part-time worker, M-E, and the Leader, Shousei,
were like master and apprentice.
Because they worked together,
they were naturally drawn to each other.
Eventually, they exchanged small talk regularly.
M-E was a mother, and Shousei was a bachelor.
Talking about these things built trust between them.
M-E is a working-class woman.
But she's so beautiful, you
wouldn't think she'd had a son.
Her voice in particular is very charming.
Then one day, M-E came to the
Leader's house to cook dinner,
when she heard that he was ill.
Well then, I'm coming in.
Be my guest.
I'd noticed her charming smile before.
Her perky body.
Seeing this before my eyes gave
rise to a premonition in my mind.
I must not let her get away.
S-Stop it!
Please stop it!
No!
No...
No, stop it!
Please, let me go!
Against her will, I forced myself oh her,
Please stop it!
Against her will, I forced myself on her,
and squeezed and licked her breasts.
Please, stop this!
No!
Stop it. No...
M-E fiercely resisted me.
Ignoring this, I continued to manipulate her body.
From her breasts to her belly,
from her belly to her lower half,
I licked it all.
No!
Don't resist me!
Please, stop itl
Have mercy!
I gazed down at her struggling body.
The space between her legs was
different from a young woman's.
It was shaped very strangely and
had a very lewd color to it.
It wasn't a soft pink, but a deep, fiery red.
Because it was so red and swollen,
it was obvious she masturbated a lot.
Please, no more.
No!
I-I had no idea you were like this.
Stop it!
Why did you come to my house?
Didn't you want this to happen?
With a hot woman like you in
my house, I can't hold back.
But I had no idea you were so slutty.
I had no idea your body was so lewd.
From then on, I thrust myself
violently and deeply inside of her.
Stop it! Stop it!
Please...
I'm cumming! Cumming inside of you!
Don't! Don't!
Oh, no.
No!
How cruel.
What a lewd body.
It's been a while for you, I bet.
Didn't you enjoy it?
Let me cum inside of you again.
No!
I'll cum inside of you time after time.
Cumming... I'm cumming!
Not again!
How was it?
You like having someone cum in you?
You could feel the squirting sensation, couldn't you?
M-E, there's more.
I'm not finished yet.
No! Let go! Please, have mercy!
Shut up. It's your fault.
You came to a single man's house,
with that lewd body of yours.
Stop it!
It's still so tight.
No matter how much I cum, I wanna cum more.
Please, have mercy.
That's not gonna happen.
The more I cum in you, the better
it feels for you too, right?
Please. Not inside.
No, taste it.
You cum with me!
The next day M-E did not tell her
colleagues what had happened.
She continued work as usual.
It was then that she started coming
to the Leader's house on her own.
Of course, when she did this,
she was "M-E" and I was "the Leader."
At first, she pretended to resist,
but eventually, she was overcome with ecstasy.
Hey, don't use your teeth.
That's right. Envelop it and suck it.
I like this. I think I'll cum in your mouth this time.
I turned her over and thrust my
fingers into her nether regions.
And when I did, she made lustful sighs.
So squishy. So lewd.
Make nastier sounds for me.
You may pretend to not like it,
but your body shows that you love it.
What a lewd woman.
I'll help you cum.
Why?
Don't you want to cum?
Yes. Please help me.
Okay, here I go.
What a lewd woman.
Your pussy is gripping me!
Well? You like it?
How about this?
No... Please... Thrust into me harder!
Just as she asked him to,
Shousei thrust deeper and deeper from behind,
as if trying to burst through her womb.
You really are a horny slut.
But don't worry, I'll fill you up soon.
Yes!
Almost... time... to cum.
Grip me tighter in there.
Don't!
Don't pull your hips away from me.
Yes. That's it. Keep it up!
Let's fuck until we both faint.
Oh, no.
I'm cumming, cumming!
Me too! I'm gonna burst through you with my cum.
I'm cumming!
M-E is a mother second,
and a woman first.
Ever since she left her husband,
her body has been longing for some hot meat.
And so, M-E and the Leader met and
became physically obsessed.
In these lewd and rough conditioning sessions,
M-E continued to absorb more and more.
While partially ashamed of herself, she
learned many different ways to play.
Her perverse side awakened,
to the point where M-E became a pro.
She got a thrill from having her
bowel movements observed.
In time, she turned into a full-fledged
exhibitionist and masochist.
Hey. Hey!
This woman who looks like my mom...
She's learning more and more disgusting acts.
She looks like she's embarrassed
and overjoyed at the same time.
Just how much farther will this woman who
looks like my mom go to pleasure herself?
Could my mother also...
No, could this be my mother?
No way. Not possible.
My mom would never do that.
I mean, there's bound to be hundreds
of thousands of women living like her.
And besides, the probability is slim that the site
I stumbled upon would feature my mother.
Those are just images of a slutty
woman who looks like my mother.
It cant be my mother.
The truth is... the truth is...
Currently, M-E is away at a training seminar.
Currently, M-E is away at a training seminar. Tomorrow we will upload new fetish pictures.
I wonder where Mom really is right now?
The way the coincidences are piling up worries me.
And then, late the next night, just as the
pictures were being released on the site,
Mom came home.