Among the images released this time,
there were pictures of her
having sex with a young man.
Rough sex with a boy the same age as her son.
The disturbing images of this disgusting play...
burned deep into my brain.
Yama-hime no Mi
Chapter 2          Masae
Sorry, Kazuya. I thought I'd be home sooner.
I'll get dinner ready quickly.
You don't need to hurry. I'm not that hungry anyway.
Oh, really?
The retreat lasted longer than I thought it would.
Your boss talks a lot, doesn't he?
See? You understand without me even telling you.
Seeing my mother at home again
made me think it really wasn't her.
That helped me relax.
I was sure that the timing of her work retreat,
and the release of the new images,
was just a bad coincidence.
But then, one day, I saw it.
"Sex Tour with M-E the Masochist"
We're accepting applicants!
As you all know, we're now accepting applications from
you men out there who are eager to get a taste of this
depraved and sick masochist housewife gone bad,  M-E.
Our next play date is scheduled for the 15th and 16th of
this month.
We're especially looking for men in their teens
(18 and over).
For more information, send an email inquiry.
We look forward to hearing from you.
A partner training seminar?
Yeah. A part-time housewife like
me can't get out of it, either.
So it's a trip.
I'm going to be gone for two days and one night.
So, when exactly is it?
Next week, on the 15th and 16th.
Well, we only seemed to get
requests from disgusting old men.
You're a real lifesaver.
We've been having a tough time finding
young men who fit her fetish.
I'm glad to find a nice young man like you this time.
Well then, I'll be off.
You're the last applicant.
Everyone else is waiting inside.
Let's go in.
Um, regarding the blindfold I asked about...
Ah, yes. Blindfolding M-E is a good idea.
Don't worry, kid.
I get how you'd be embarrassed for her to see you.
I hear lots of younger guys are scared
of looking in a woman's eyes, too.
And having M-E blindfolded will
be more exciting for you.
And it will save me time, because I won't have
to disguise her eyes for the Internet.
There he is!
This is Yamada-san.
I'm Yaguchi!
I'm Takedaka.
And I'm Tamashi.
Well, they're all here. The young men you requested.
She seems to have gotten addicted
to young ones since last time.
I saw those pictures on the Internet!
Fucking turns me on!
She's kept it a secret from her
son that she's doing this,
but here she is, having sex with boys his age.
Wow, she's all sweaty!
From having sex with young men,
it seems she's learned the thrill of abnormal sex.
No!
Don't say that about me!
Don't you want me to say it?
You're so lewd, and such a slut.
We can see your true colors, you masochistic animal.
While playing the part of the sweet and
innocent housewife in front of your son,
you've been fucking boys his age every
day behind his back, haven't you?
The masochistic mommy who loves her son so much.
You wanna bring that fantasy to life, don't you?
No! Don't say anything more!
You're the one! You're the one
who made me like this!
Do you resent me for it?
You tease.
You want to, don't you?
You want to fuck boys.
I do! I do!
Then let's make the introductions.
I told you I'd bring them to you.
Hello, boys.
Nice to meet you.
I am M-E.
I always get lots of special training sessions.
Please, have lots of fun with me today.
A-Amazing!
Her boobs are so big, but they're not droopy!
And she's covered in sweat.
Her body is so hot.
Very nice.
I can't hold back anymore.
Amazing! It's all sloppy.
Ow, that hurts!
That hurts!
Very nice, very nice, M-E.
Hey, come on, suck it up.
M-E, what's wrong?
Don't you want his dick?
You're an old woman.
You still want the dick of a boy who's your son's age?
Yes, I want it.
Let me suck it all up.
Suck mine too!
I can't hold back!
Me too!
Wait a minute.
Putting it in her mouth is a waste.
Isn't that so, M-E?
I want all your cum in my pussy!
Yes! It's so thick and so deep!
This feels fucking amazing.
It's great for me! Great for me too!
It's so nice and warm.
Harder! Fuck me harder!
Wait, are you sure you want me to cum inside of you?
Yes, I do. Cum inside of me.
Cum lots!
Very nice.
Cum inside of her.
I've cum inside her many times.
So her pussy has learned to hunger for cum.
Yes. He's right.
Ejaculate lots into me!
Ejaculate so much that it flows out again.
I taught her body to recognize that
sensation and hunger for it more.
It turned her into a woman that needs cum in her.
Please cum!
Fill me up!
I'm cumming!
It's coming!
Very well done.
He got a lot into you, Masae.
Yes. It's hot and feels great.
He said 'Masae"!?
But you're still not satisfied, right?
Now's no time to take a break.
Yes, my Leader.
Well then, let's introduce you a little more.
My real name is Yamabuki Masae.
I keep this from my son,
but I visit the Leader every day,
and he gives me special training sessions like this.
I'm very horny, and I have no shame!
He's turned me into a masochistic slave!
Yamabuki Masae is a slutty masochist!
I need your cum in me!
Harder! Harder!
Tear my hole open with your thick cock!
So your name is Masae-san!
Yes.
I'm Masae. I'm a pervert.
Everyone, fuck me at once!
Well, you heard her.
Fill this lustful bitch full of your young cum.
Time and time again, fill her up.
Masae-san.
I-I'm coming in.
Again...
Inside...
Cum inside of me!
W-Wait, not there!
That's not rightl That's the wrong hole!
Don't!
Very nice. Good boy. Keep going!
Time to go in. I'll fuck you from here.
No...
Don't! Not there!
Not there!
Her pussy is squeezing me!
That hurts.
Hey, everyone together now!
Come on, Yamada-san, you join in too.
Uh, yeah.
Isn't it better with more people?
I love it!
Her ass is so tight.
You really are a pervert, Masae.
You're right.
I'm a pervert!
It's so tight.
Yours is so big, and it's thrashing
around inside my ass!
It's gonna make me cum!
Amazing!
I'm so lucky!
Are you really that lucky, Masae?
You're a slut who fucks lots of boys
the age of your son simultaneously.
You're an immoral slut of a mother.
No! That's not true.
You're my favorite, Leader.
I'm your woman, Leader.
Aw, and I remember you used to tell me your
son was the number one man in your life.
You said your son meant everything to you.
Not anymore, Leader.
You're the most important man in my life.
But you've go one dic in your ass, anoter
in your cunt, and a third in your mouth.
That's not being very faithful, if you ask me.
You meanie! I love this!
And you...
you were the one who made me
like this in the first place!
I love you.
You're all I have!
Masae-san, you only love your Leader's dick, I guess.
Yes, I do!
I love it!
More than your son?
Yes, I do!
Then why don't you talk to this camera
and pretend it's your son?
I'm sorry, Kazuya...
Your mother no longer loves you, Kazuya.
When I've got...
this many men loving me,
I don't really care about you anymore!
I only love my Master!
If my Master commanded it,
I would leave you in an instant!
Master, I'm so happy to be with you!
I can't hold back anymore!
Me too! I'm almost there!
Well then, fill her up, boys.
Right, Masae?
M-Me too!
I want it! Cum! Everyone cum in me!
I'm cumming!
You're cumming inside of me!
So hot.
Me too... I'm cumming!
My insides are so hot.
My butt is so hot.
I'm cumming!
So much...
So hot.
So yummy.
Kazuya! No!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Mom! Mom!
Hey, Mom!
Hey, w-wait.
Hey, what's happening?
Let's get him anyway!
Let go! Let go of me!
What happened? What's going on?
Little punk. What do you think you're doing?
You fucking piece of shit!
What you've done is inhuman!
After both of our identities were revealed,
Mom and I couldn't talk to each other.
Her "Leader” released her,
and we were both sent home.
But Mom never came back.
There was a letter without a return
address in my mom's handwriting.
She said she wasn't coming back.
She said she loved her Master so much...
that she couldn't part with her way of life.
The site dosed down, and I lost my only
way of communicating with her.
Mommy! Hurry! Hurry!
Aw, don't be in such a hurry.
What if you fell down and got hurt?
I'll be fine! Come on, let's go!
I get it. Don't pull so hard.
Jeez, you're such a difficult child.
If only I hadn't sent an email to that site.
Even now, I still remember that day.
And I wonder...
What would have happened if I'd
become one with my mother?
And where is she now?
These things are always in the back of my mind.
So I subconsciously look for traces of my mother.
Special Hot Girl Collection
Special M-Woman: M-E