I had just clicked on a random adult site.
Cheating Wives Site- A mother doing all kinds of-
Unbeknownst to her high-schooler son,
night after night, this MILF indulges in her raunchy fantasies.
She's just another houswife when she comes home, but during her little flings,
she degrades into a simple horny woman.
Everyone, please violate her with your lecherous eyes.
She lives under the guise of a humble, ordinary mother.
But at this club, she met yours truly, and asked me to train her in the pleasures of a bitch.
Next page
She greedily begged for sex again today.
She buried her face in my crotch, and swallows mouthfulls of my lust.
Next page
Her name is "M.A", and she makes her living via part-time work.
Status: A divorced mother of a highschool boy.
Personality: A lewd massochist who delights in being photographed.
Mountain Goddess Sane
FAKKU! Presents
Episode 1: M.A
A computer is a luxury!
Against my mothers strong opposition, I bought myself a computer.
When I saw the woman on the site's homepage, I recalled that moment.
Not a chance...
This rain's ridiculous, I can't stand it!
The forecast said it wouldn't rain too...
Honestly, you just can't trust those things.
Did you get rained on, Kazuya? I wasn't so lucky.
You know the new supermarket by the station right? The one I work at?
They said I had to help prepare for a big sale tomorrow.
Boss's orders, so I had to stay late.
What's the matter?
Just wondering if you're okay after being poured on.
I bet you're hungry, huh? I hurried home just for you.
I would've liked to get home earlier though.
Even though things seemed to be in order...but that' life!
O-oh yeah?
Goodness, what happened?
It's nothing! Just get changed already!
I always change here, you silly boy.
Just wait a bit longer, okay?
Thanks for waiting.
I'll start getting ready.
So where exactly is this new supermarket?
By the station, where that sporting goods store used to be. You know the place?
Oh yeah, Kadoji's?
That's the one. They tore it down and built a supermarket there.
So you're suddenly having a huge sale, huh?
That's right. It didn't take long to set up, so the employees weren't working too hard.
It must be tough having your store torn down, and being laid off.
I'd have to ask you to help out too.
If that happened, I could get a job and make things easier on you.
I sure wouldn't mind that...
I just mistook her for mom.
That's gotta be it.
Oh yeah, Kazuya...This saturday, there's a welcome party at work.
All the employees are going after work, so I can't turn them down.
I'll be gone until sunday.
I'll be back at night at the latest.
Will you be okay by yourself?
What do you mean, will I be okay?
I've never been gone this long. I can't help worrying about you.
I'll be fine! A little time alone won't kill me!
You're just worrying too much.
You treat me like a child, mom.
I guess I do. Sorry.
It's good to take a trip now and then.
Nothing but work will run you ragged.
You're right. To tell the truth, I'm a little exicted.
I'll be back sunday night, okay?
I thought mom was just treating me like a child.
And it was nice to have the place to myself.
Now I could thoroughly enjoy that website.
That's what I thought at the time...
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
My mom raised me all by herself.
I can't say it's been luxurious, but we haven't had much trouble getting by.
I'm sure she's shouldering a burden I couldn't imagine.
Sign: Yamabuki
I'm sure her job is plenty stressful too.
She only wears simple clothes, and she doesn't have any hobbies.
I feel like she doesn't have a single pleasure in life.
I met M.A at a store in the midst of a price war.
She works as a part-timer, and we had a healthy worker-boss relationship.
My encounter with M.A
As we worked together, she gradually opened up like a blossoming flower.
M.A has a child, and is single.
As we talked, we developed a trusting relationship.
M.A's a simple housewife, but you'd never guess from her looks that she's a mother too.
And her speech is quite charming as well.
One day, M.A decided to came to my place to cook dinner.
Pardon me.
Come on in.
That lovely smile had been on my mind for a while now.
And she had such an enticing body to boot.
With that right in front of me, seeds of determination began to sprout.
I could't just let this woman walk away unrewarded.
S-stop it! Please stop!
No!
Don't!
No! Stop it!
Let me go, please!
I took her relucatnt body to another room, and groped her breasts.
Stop that!
Noo! Stop, I'm begging you!
No! Don't do that!
No!
M.A frantically resisted, but I paid her no mind and continued pleasuring her.
From her breasts to her navel, and then her lower half,
I pleasured her with my tongue.
No!
Don't fight it...
Please! Please stop!
I then gazed upon the resisting M.A's secret garden.
Her pussy, unlike the rest of her body, looked used, and was of a nasty color.
Not pink, but precisely the color of a MILF's.
Just from the touch, you could tell she masturbated frequently.
Don't go any further! No!
No! I never thought you could do such a horrible thing...
No! Stop it!
Why exactly did you come here for?
Were you hoping for something?
It's been years since I fucked a woman. I can't hold back.
I'd can't believe you're not even forty.
What a slutty body!
After that, I began moving and thrusting hard however I wanted.
Stop! Stop it!
I-I'm gonna cum! I'm gonna cum inside!
Noo! Don't do it!
No!!
You're horrible...
What a lewd body...
You enjoyed it too? Your first sex in ages...
Let me come inside you again, okay?
No!
I'll cum inside you lots.
Cumming! I'm gonna cum!
No, not again!
How's that? You like getting creampied?
You got a real good taste, didn't ya?
We're not done yet, M.A.
We're just getting started.
What?
No! Let me go!
Please, spare me!
Shut it. This is all your fault.
You just nonchalantly walked into a single man's home.
S-stop it!
Ohh, you're getting tighter!
I've cum so much, but I still wanna cum more!
No more...cumming inside...
You don't mean that, right?
You feel best being cummed inside, right?
I'm begging you, not inside me...
Get a nice taste of it! Cum with me!
The next day, M.A didn't report the incident at work.
She continued her work with me, just like usual.
On the contrary, she came back of her own volition.
Naturally, I had sex with her.
M.A only feigned resistance, and eventually sought out pleasure herself.
Hey, watch the teeth now.
That's it...Wrap your lips around it and suck.
This is incredible!
I'm gonna cum in your mouth.
I relentlessly groped her tense body.
I fingered her pussy too.
She quickly began making dirty sounds.
You're totally wet...
Jeez...your petals are so filthy.
You act like you hate it, but your body's reacting to me.
How do you want it? Go on, tell me!
What do you mean, how?
You want me to do you, right?
Yes...please...
Here goes!
Damn, your pussy's so naughty!
You're clamping down on me!
How's that? Well?
You like that?
Don't say that!
Just pound my pussy!
I fucked her from behind, just as she asked.
I fucked her hard enough to ruin her pussy.
You look like you're having fun, eh?
You're one hell of a slut, aren't ya?
I'll be sure to fill you up with cum.
Oh, Yes!!
There! Ha! Now you're being honest!
Ohh, you're getting tighet!
Do...Don't do that!
Now move on your own!
Good, that's it! Just like that!
I'll squeeze 'em so hard milk'll come out!
No! Oh no! I'm cumming!
Me too! I'm gonna blow my load inside you!
No, don't!
Here it comes!
I'm cumming!
M.A is a mother of a highschool boy, but before that...
She's just another broad.
Ever since she left her husband, her body's longed for the burning pleasures of the flesh.
Training Log
Little by little, we furthered our relationship.
M.A quickly became hooked on my intense, raunchy training.
In her stupor, she quickly took to our slave play.
She awakened to sin, writhing in pleasure.
M.A finally, rejoiced in me watching her releive herself like a dog.
She'd finally transformed into my massochistic slave.
H-hey! Hold on!
A woman resembling Mom sprials down into carnal pleasures from a single taste?
It's like she's living vicariously through her pleasure!
A woman I can only see as my mother, in similar circumstances
Captive to such dirty, lustful activities.
Don't tell me Mom's like that too...
Or could it actually be Mom!?
There's no way that could happen.
No, she's not the only woman that fits this.
Besides, there's lots of single mother households like ours!
That kind of thing's not uncommon.
And what are the odds of my own mother being on an adult site I only occasionally visit?
Lewd pictures of a woman that looks like Mom...
There's no way she could be her...
That's it. That's it, right?
M.A and I are currently on a "training camp"...
Where on earth could she be right now?
The circumstances kept overlapping, and I became a little uneasy...
Both sets of dates matched.
And Mom came home late that night...
To Be Continued