I'm home.
Y-Yo...
What is it, Masaru? You're here again?
Um... Yes.
Didn't you say a while ago that you
had club activity yesterday, huh?
Is... that so?
That's OK.
I'm going home now.
What?
Hey!
See ya!
Hey!!
What's wrong with him?
Welcome home, Kouichi.
Yes, I'm home.
Mother...
That Masaru, he's been here lately...
Is that so? Maybe he wants to
have more fun with you.
Then he should've told me before the club activity today.
It's unavoidable, right.
My mother and myself are living alone.
Even in this little apartment,
It doesn't make me unhappy at all.
Dinner will be ready soon.
If I remember corretly, Masaru always comes here when I have
my club activity and part-time job.
Masaru?
H-Hi...
It's not a big deal.
I'm going home now.
A while ago, last week too...
What's going on, really?
It's wet?
What's wrong?
It doesn't taste good enough?
Eh? No... No.
It's nothing like that, It tastes just fine.
You're an odd kid.
Just as usual, my cheerfull mother.
The same situation, as always.
That's sperm.
Sperm on my mother's panties.
Did Masaru stole those panties to use it for masturbating?
No, even if it's Masaru... He would not do
something like that in my home...
Then, why?
Thanks for today, It's been fun.
Mother?
It's my pleasure too, can I come here again, then?
He's...
Today, he came to my home again?
Sure, come here again.
Well, see you next time!
If I remember, today he's skipping noon class, too.
Yes, please be friends with my son, too.
Of course I will.
Well then...
Yes, It's...
Mother?
Hm, what is it?
Does Masaru often come here?
Um... Tsukamoto-kun?
Well, as you can see, I'm busy with my club activity
and I was wondering If he's coming here.
He's coming here.
Eh, really?
Yes, but not always, though...
But, Kouichi isn't home often, and I just
want to have someone to talk to.
Is... that it?
Good night.
That can't be true, right?
Even if it's Masaru, he wouldn't do
something like that with my mother.
Masaru and mother...
Did they do something like that? ...
Training camp?
Yes, it's from Saturday night till Sunday night.
Well, it's a long time.
Yes.
That's why I won't come home today.
I understand.
Then, I'll go now.
Be careful.
Maybe I'm just being foolish...
In the end, nothing has happened.
I'm ashamed for not believing in my mother.
After all, I'm just thinking of my mother...
It's dark, so please watch your step.
It's making me nervous.
Then, tonight, all through the night...
Mo... mother?
But, wouldn't it reveal soon?
That boy, he's slow about these things.
Then I won't hold back.
Why don't you get naked then?
It's embarrassing.
You want this, right?
Mother, you...
Mother!
So it's true that Masaru is doing that with my mother.
I don't want to see it...
I don't want to believe it...
My own mother...
Like a lewd women with sexual desire....
My mother is sucking Masaru's penis...
It's good.
No!
I can't hold it anymore.
I don't know what to do with you, Sawako.
That's because...
Mother, you have someone beside me calling you like that.
Using your name like that, like you're lovers.
That's because of Masaru-kun.
How come my body wouldn't feel something like this?
I had your penis on my mind all of day.
I can't hold this feeling since morning.
That's because it's almost three days
since last time we did it.
Then, they did it that day, too.
I'm sorry, but I just want to have someone to talk to.
So she's been hiding this from me and doing this at home.
Do you just come out for this taste?
That's true, it's hard for me.
I just can't get it out of my head,
how Masaru-kun's doing me like this.
I always think of this.
That's a lie... Not true!!
Will training camp be hard?
I'm worried about you.
Try your best, I'll praying for you.
Today, I couldn't hold it since morning.
You had to wait for Kouichi to go away, right?
Don't tease me like that.
But you're thinking of it, right?
Yes...
It's true...
I wanted Masaru-kun to come here quickly.
When I wait for Kouichi to go away, I can't stand it.
That's why this morning I went outside without my panties.
I came to pick you up without my panties.
Look at it...
It's already this wet.
Let me see it.
Oh, it's true.
Sawako is truly a lewd woman.
Lewd...
My mother is lewd...
You couldn't put out the nipples in front of your son.
No, don't say something like that.
Right now I don't want to think about him.
I'm not that kind of mother.
I understand.
Tonight we have a lot of time.
I'll make you dirtier than before.
I'm happy.
Did you feel it?
There you go...
Did you feel good, huh?
Do it, do Sawako's lewd body
please do it now!
It's good, Masaru-kun!
My pussy feels it.
Good... It's good!
No, it's embarrassing.
That spot...
More... more...
Masaru-kun!
Please, fuck me harder!
Masaru-kun's penis is the best!
It's great!
Your penis feels good!
It's good!
Amazing... It's amazing!
My breasts feel it!
Suck them more!
Good...
Mother's dirty juices...
It's good!
When I'm not at home,
she's doing these things with an erotic voice like that.
Give me...
Give me more of it...
I'm really loving it!
Do it... Do it more! Please, do it as you like!
Give me a lot of it!
Masaru-kun!
It's really good!
I've never heard something as lewd as that.
With an erotic voice like that, mother...
Masaru-kun, I'm gonna come!
It's gonna come!
That's unavoidable, Sawako.
Good...
Come... I'm coming!
If you're gonna come, say the usual thing.
Yes, Sawako's gonna come.
My pussy's gonna cum from Masaru-kun's penis!
Mother's voice...
I'm...
Good... My pussy feels good!
It's great!
Give me... more of your penis!
More of it...
Give me more!
Your penis is getting bigger...
Do you want it again?
Give me...
Masaru's sperm...
Thrust it deep in my pussy!
I'm coming again...
My pussy gonna come again!
I'm cumming... I'm cumming, Sawako.
Give me a lot, deep in my pussy!
Good!
Cumming... It feels good!
Your penis...
Masaru-kun's penis...
Feels great!
Good... It's good...
More... More!
I'm coming out again!
Great... It's really great!
Your penis is great!
Amazing!
Masaru-kun's penis is really great.
Great... Great...
My pussy... my pussy's... gonna break.
Penis's great... penis's great.
Masaru-kun's penis is great.
Thrust more inside of me!
More... More... It feels good!
It's hitting deep!
It's deep all the way!
It's good!
Masaru-kun is good!
Give me more of your penis!
Penis... Penis..
Dick... Dick... Dick... Dick... Dick...
It feels good... My pussy...
My mother is happy with Masaru's sperm overflowing from her.
On that day, I saw that ten times.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Mother...
Did anything change lately?
Eh? Nothing happened at all, really.
I'm lonely being alone here.
Mother...