I'm home.
H-Hi!
What is it, Masaru?
You're here again?
Yeah.
Didn't I tell you earlier that we don't
have club meetings on Mondays?
Oh, you did?
Anyway...
I'm going home now.
What?
Hey.
Bye.
Hey!
What's his problem?
Welcome back, Kouichi.
Oh, thanks...
Mom.
Yama Hime no Mi
Chapter 3 Bond
Masaru's been coming here a lot lately.
Really?
Doesn't he just want to spend more time with you?
Then he should come when I'm actually home.
He's a bit absentminded, isn't he?
Mom and I live together by ourselves.
This tiny apartment... has been an ideal home for me.
I'll have dinner ready very soon.
Okay.
That reminds me, that Masaru...
I get the feeling that he only shows up at my
house when I have club practice or work.
Masaru?
Oh, hey.
It wasn't anything important.
I'm leaving now.
The other day, and also last week...
I wonder what's up with him?
It's wet?
What's wrong?
Did I make it too spicy?
N-No.
That's not it at all.
It's perfect.
You're a strange boy.
My mother is bright and happy, as usual.
And our home is comfortable, as usual.
But that was cum.
Mom's cum-covered panties.
Was Masaru masturbating behind Mom's back?
No.
Even though Masaru's a bit weird, he'd never do that at my place.
Then, why?
Thanks for coming by today.
I had fun.
It's Mom.
Me too.
That guy...
Is it okay if I come over tomorrow too?
He's at our house again.
Yes, I'd be delighted.
Now that I think of it,
Do well in school, okay?
he wasn't in class after lunch today.
Yes, I will.
Well, bye then.
Mom?
Hm? What is it?
It’s about Masaru. Does he come here often?
You mean Tsukamoto-kun?
You know, I've been busy with my club
lately, so I haven't seen him much,
but he seems to stop by here a lot.
Yes, he does.
Really?
Yes. Sometimes, just a bit.
But Kouichi, you're never home.
So I entertain him with conversation in your place.
Oh, I see.
Good night.
I guess that makes sense.
I don't think even a guy like Masaru would want
to have sex with an old woman like my mother.
Masaru and Mom?
It's not possible.
A field trip with your club?
Yup.
From Saturday night to Sunday night.
Wow, that's a long time.
Yeah.
So I'm not coming home today.
I understand.
Well, I'm off.
Have a nice trip.
I'm feeling a little too paranoid for my own good.
So nothing happened after all.
I feel ashamed for not trusting my own mother.
In the end, I...
I was overprotective of her.
It's dark, so be careful where you step.
This makes me kinda nervous.
Well then, we have the whole night together this time.
M-Mom?
But don't you think he'll find out soon enough?
My son is a little gullible.
In that case, I won't hold back.
Come on, take it off.
I'm embarrassed.
Didn't you want to do this?
You want me.
Mom, what are you...
M-Mom!
So Masaru and Mom really are...
I didn't want to see it.
I didn't want to believe it.
That my own mother was...
Like a wild animal...
Looking maniacally happy...
My own mother was greedily sucking...
Masaru's dirty cock.
Yes!
Oh... don't!
I can't hold back anymore.
Well, you really are a dirty slut...
Sawako.
Oh, please.
Mom!
You're letting a boy my age call you by name?
And you're even letting him talk down to you?
Because of you, Masaru-kun, my body has become very slutty...
...and very lewd.
Day after day, my head is filled with
nothing but thoughts of your cock.
I could barely contain my desire all day.
It's been three days since our last time.
Then, they did it that day as well.
Sorry, but I often entertain him with conversation in your place.
They've been hiding this from me all this time.
All this time, in this very room.
Did you get your strength back from the flavor of my cum?
Y-Yes, I did.
It was tough holding out until now.
No matter what I do, my only thoughts
are of the times that you tease me.
I can think of nothing but fucking you.
It can't be true!
It's a lie!
Is your field trip tough?
I'm worried about you.
Take care, okay?
I'll be cheering for you.
I haven't been calm since this morning.
I wish Kouichi would move out soon.
Stop being so mean.
But you want the same thing, don't you?
Um, well...
Y-You're right.
I wish he'd move out right away.
The times he's home and I can't be with
you feel longer and longer to me.
That's why I got my panties all wet earlier
this morning, from thinking about you.
And when I went to pick you up, I wasn't wearing panties.
Please, look.
I'm all wet.
Oh, let me see.
Yeah, you're right.
You really are a whore, Sawako.
A whore...
My own mom?
A whore?
You never come out when your son is around.
No!
Don't say that sort of thing.
I don't want to think about him right now.
I don't want to be a mother right now!
I understand.
We've got plenty of time tonight.
I'll make you scream at the top of your lungs.
See?
I'm so happy.
Doesn't it feel great?
Fuck me!
Fuck my slutty body! Fuck me lots!
Oh yes!
Masaru-kun!
My pussy... feels great.
Yes!
Oh, yes!
No!
It's embarrassing.
My pussy...
Harder.
Harder!
Masaru-kun!
Rub me harder!
Masaru-kun...
Your cock...
...is perfect!
Yes!
It's amazing!
You're wonderful!
You're so wonderful!
Oh, yes!
My tits love it!
Harder!
Lick me harder!
Yes!
Mom's love juices...
I love it!
I've never heard her yell so loudly before.
I've never heard heryellrso loudly before.
I'm falling apart.
My pussy is falling apart,
and I'm loving it!
Harder!
Fuck me harder!
Do Mommy any way you like!
Fill me up!
Fill me up with your cum!
Masaru-kun!
Yes!
I've never heard her slutty voice before.
My mother has such a sweet and passionate voice.
Masaru-kun...
Mommy's cumming!
I'm cumming!
Oh well, then, Sawako.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
In that case, do it the way you always do.
I will.
Sawako is cumming!
From Masaru-kun's mighty cock!
My pussy is cumming!
Mom's voice is making me...
Making me...
Yes!
I love your cock!
Harder! Harder!
I want your cock!
Harder, please!
I want more!
Your cock...is quivering!
Well? You want it now?
Yes, I do!
Masaru-kun, shoot your cum...
...into my womb.
Shoot it all inside!
My pussy is cumming.
My pussy is... My pussy is cumming!
I'm... I'm cumming, Sawako!
Then cum!
Pump me full with it!
Yes!
I'm cumming.
This feels so good.
Your cock!
Masaru-kun, your cock...
feels so great!
Yes!
Oh, yes!
Harder!
Again, my pussy is... cumming!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Your cock... is amazing!
Amazing!
Masaru-kun... your cock... is awesome!
Wow. Wow!
My pussy... My pussy... My pussy...
...is falling apart.
Your cock is wonderful.
Your cock is so wonderful.
Masaru-kun, your cock is wonderful.
Tear me apart.
Harder! Harder!
Yes. This feels great.
All the way inside... Hit me all the way inside.
All the way inside...
Oh, yes!
Masaru-kun!
I want more of your cock!
Your cocki
Yes, your cock!
Your cock, your cock, your cock, your cock!
It feels so great!
Your cock! Your cock!
My mothen was overcome with ecstasy
as Masaru's cum dripped out of her.
And watching them that day I came ten times.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Mom...
Did something strange happen?
Huh? No, nothing happened.
I was lonely here by myself.
M-Mom...