Are all the girls on this train really sluts?
Sluts just starting out?
Well they're all pure,
but they're definitely sluts at heart. Very sluts.
All of them are.
Is it really that easy?
The amount of sluts in this area is abnormally high.
I'm not sure if this is true or not, but apparently
it was a famous red light district a hundred years ago.
They'll listen to whatever you say.
They're all the pure, homely, gentle types.
They'll all fall head over heels for you.
They're also super into erotic stuff
and love dirty talk. They're bona fide sluts.
Sluts! Train sex
02. The Study Abroad Student is an Otaku!
Sluts! Train sex.
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
You need something, Asahina Mami-chan?
Thi... This is embarrassing.
Aren't you the one who was turned on
by seeing your friends having sex?
What a freak.
Th-That's not...
You're the one who...
You're a dirty girl.
And you're a huge masochist to boot.
I'm not a dirty girl... No!
This is so amazing!
It feels better than when I do it myself!
Your dick is so amazing! I might become addicted to it!
Are you really going to keep moving?
What? You don't want me to?
But I'm still so young. Is it really okay
for me to feel this good at my age?
You're a really perverted girl, aren't you?
Pervert! Pervert!
I'm dirty? I'm perverted?!
Your pussy got tighter.
Looks like I'm right.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry, Mister!
I can't... I-I'm gonna cum!
That's good. Nothing beats a girl who cums easily.
When I feel like it, I'm gonna cum
in your pussy like there's no tomorrow.
I'm gonna become a mama?
Isn't being a mama when
you're a student a little too early?
You're a good girl, aren't you?
It's just a baby or two. You can do it, right?
B-But what about marriage?
Are you going to marry me?
It's starting to feel even better! It's feeling so good!
This is good! This is so good! Your dick is loving me
so much! It's so amazing! I love this dick so much!
So, you'll let me, right? I'm so hard right now.
It'd be a shame if I didn't get to cum inside you.
Okay!
Please do it!
That's a slut for you. You're so bighearted!
Y-You're taking the time to have sex with me and
you're the one having sex with me. You also want a kid.
S-So I'll do my best!
I-I'll try my best!
Then I'm gonna cum! Mami!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! There's so much cum coming inside me!
I never thought having cum being shot
inside me could make me feel so good!
That felt good. It looks like you were right.
I'm really dirty. I liked that.
I like having sex.
And that's how I became more than
just sex friends to some high school girls.
Wait, is that...
Alicia Costa. Tan skin.
Has a body so hot it would burn you.
She loves ero-doujin so much that she transferred to school
in Japan so that she could get them! She's a huge slut!
I need to make this girl mine!
So, about doujinshis.
There are a lot of dirty ones, aren't there?
Y-Yes...
So what happens when you look at them?
What do you mean?
I-Is this sexual harassment?
Th-This is sexual harassment!
This is definitely sexual harassment!
I'm being sexually harassed by an older otaku.
I-I masturbate.
Wow you're just a complete pervert then.
Yeah!
I-Is this the situation that I've seen in my ero-doujinshi?
So all men in Japan are really perverts then?
D-Does this mean that today this guy and I will...
So tell me, Alicia-chan. If you read all these ero-doujinshi,
does that mean you're into that kind of stuff too?
Did you come all the way here to do dirty stuff?
He's a real life pervert!
I-I don't think I'd mind having sex with him.
We're gonna do it right here!
Do you mind?
It's my first time seeing a dick and balls in person!
Is this real?
I can't believe she just got turned on
from what I said and then came onto me!
She's a total whore!
I'm getting wet! I really want it now!
You're really going at it.
This feels so good.
It feels so good in my mouth! I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Master! Master!
If it's with you... if it's you, then I think
you'll be able to make my dream come true!
Master! Master!
Shit! Holy shit! This feels so good!
Shit! She's too hot! This is too hot!
What's going on here?!
Alicia! Alicia!
Your mouth feels so good!
Alicia!
Drink it! Drink down my sexual desires!
You fucking whore.
Take it! Take it! Oh, that feels good.
So good...
I'm not waiting any longer.
It's fucking time! I'm gonna stick it to you good!
So good! This feels better than I imagined!
So this is sex?
Yeah, feels good, doesn't it?
I like girls like you who get off easily.
Looks like it feels good!
It feels good when you move! Every time you move
it just feels amazing! Your dick is so hard!
This is so much better! This is so much better than
when I masturbated while looking at my ero-doujinshi!
This dick feels so amazing!
What the hell's up with this ass?! It's so soft!
My ass is big and really sensitive.
You can be rougher with it if you want.
So, please...
Fuck me so hard that you break me!
Take that! Your ass makes a good drum!
Yes! My master!
Master!
P-Please make me pregnant!
Losing your mind already?
Just how perverted are you, Alicia?!
You read too many ero-doujinshi!
Please use my pussy to satisfy your primal male desires.
I-I want to bear your child, Master.
Please let my perverted bottom half drink your seed!
Okay, no problem. That's fine, Alicia.
I'm gonna have sex with your daughter too,
but that's okay, right?
That's fine. I want to have sex with my daughter too!
I'm sure she'll become just like me and
get wet just from thinking about dirty things...
She'll definitely become that kind of dirty girl.
Just how perverted is your mind?!
You fucking perverted busty blonde!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
Hell yeah. It feels good, you fucking dirty whore!
I'm gonna cum from being spanked!
I'm cumming!
Take it! Take all my cum in your pussy, Alicia!
I'm a rare type. I'm a rare type of girl.
That means that you can have all kinds of sex
that you can't have with other girls with me.
So, please, please stay with me forever.
E-Excuse me.
Do you remember me?
Yeah, of course I do.
You're the girl whose breasts and ass
I fondled then came inside, right?
Yeah! Th-That's me!
Y-You're really smiling from that?
Just how much do you love me?
U-Um, Mister?
I know that you've done the same
thing to me with other girls too.
Huh?
It's becoming a pretty big rumor among all the girls.
You cum in them and then get married, right?
Huh?
I don't care what number wife I am,
but would you marry me?
Shit, you're cute.
I just got proposed to by a cute, nice, dirty girl.
I wanna sow my seed in her right now!
Sure.
Take off your clothes.
We're gonna have sex, so take off your clothes.
Okay.
Look at how hot you are.
I'm so happy.
Then strip down to your birthday suit.
Okay.
You have such an erotic body!
You're so beautiful.
Th-This is so embarrassing.
Yeah, I guess it is.
You're completely naked in the middle of a train after all.
Everyone can see your tits and pussy.
But, you know...
I'm gonna do something even more embarrassing.
You're gonna ride me.
Get on top of me.
O-Okay.
I love ya, Akari-chan.
Y-Yes, I love you too.
I'm happy! I'm so happy!
I'm having sex with the man I love.
This! This dick feels so good!
Everyone is watching!
They're all watching me have sex
while being completely naked on a train!
So, Akari-chan, how'd you get this good?
I-I practiced.
All this time you haven't seen me, I've been practicing tit fucks,
blow jobs, and deep throating to make you happy!
I've gotten better at hand jobs and thigh jobs too!
I'm so happy!
I'm in heaven!
I'm so happy I could see you again!
I'll give you everything I have!
Everything! I'll give you everything!
I'm gonna put a child in you and make you my wife!
I'll do it! I'll be your wife!
I'll become a woman who will make you feel the best!
And I'll make you cum so much
and become the first girl to give you a baby!
I'll do it!
I'll do it! I'll definitely do it!
That's... That's my dream! It feels so good!
And so I took Akari two cars back.
To be honest, I was meeting up
with the other girls that I had sex with.
Thanks for waiting.
Ah.
Everyone looked at me and their
faces melted into that of a whore's.
Sluts are the best!
So fucking cute!
Damn it. Hove all of you!
I'm gonna take care of you.
I'm gonna take care of all of you!
I'm gonna fuck you all with my cock until my hips give out!
And after that, they all bore me children.
They were all healthy.
I've been left in charge of the slut book.
And now I watch over all the sluts.
I wonder how many of them
I will be able to get pregnant?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality check: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч