This is a paradise for all train molesters.
At first glance she might look like the pure type,
but she's the slutty type, no doubt.
You really think it's that easy?
The level of the slutty girls here
in this district is abnormally high.
I have no clue if this is true or not, but apparently it was
a really popular red light district a hundred or so years ago.
Students were among the more popular choices, you know.
The younger they are,
the easier it is for them to bear children.
Basically, at their age,
they're at the peak of their attractiveness to guys.
She'll listen to anything you tell her to do.
She's the pure, homely, gentle type.
She'll love you from the bottom of her heart.
She's also super into erotic stuff and loves the dirty talk.
Sluts! Train sex.
01. The pure looking student...
Is this... This isn't a good thing, is it?
Should I ask him nicely to stop?
He's not even trying to hide it anymore.
What should I do?
Oh no, the stronger he touches me,
the more tingly my butt gets.
Excuse me...
What's this? You're getting wet.
You need to stop right now.
Otherwise this'll get even more embarrassing.
Damn, you're cute.
He called me cute?
That's the first time that anyone
but Papa has called me cute.
I'm so happy!
I'm still getting groped, but maybe it's okay.
You looked away. I guess you know
that you're being molested now.
I-Is that...
No way! That's a guy's "you know what", isn't it?
Wow, it's so big!
I'm starting to feel really strange.
What's going on? I can't look away!
Hey, what's going on?
Looks like there's liquid dripping down your thighs.
Oh my god, there is! This is so embarrassing!
He's gonna think that I got aroused
from looking at his dick and that's why I'm wet.
No, Mister! It feels good!
Not here!
If you do it here... People will see!
I can't hold back!
You're such a hot schoolgirl.
You're so fucking hot.
Mister! Please don't call me that!
It sounds so dirty and makes me
feel happy for some reason.
It feels so good. My heart is racing!
Are you actually gonna cum
from being molested on the train?
You're a pure girl. Are you okay cumming like that?
– You're in public, but you're gonna cum? So hot.
– Don't call me that.
– Don't make me sound so dirty!
I feel so turned on and happy right now!
No! Don't touch me like that!
You're gonna make me feel good! Too good!
No way... A stranger made me cum on the train.
It feels so good, I can't hold myself back!
Let's db this. I'm gonna rape you.
You can't be serious! This is a train!
It's coming inside me! Why?! This is my first time!
What's going on?!
I never knew that a dick could feel
so good just by going inside me!
Do you really like having a dick inside you that much?!
Don't be mean to me! I'm just a student
and I can't take all this pleasure.
Don't bully me with your words!
It feels so good! I can't hold back my voice!
I'm being taken over by the pleasure!
Everyone is going to know about this now!
I'm having sex!
I'm having sex with a stranger!
Sex!
I'm doing the dirty thing that I've always wanted to do!
It feels good! It feels so good!
I can't believe that it feels this...
I can't believe it feels this good! Amazing!
This is too amazing!
Dicks are amazing!
Dicks feel so good!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm cumming!
I'm gonna cum inside.
You don't mind, do you?
You're gonna get me pregnant!
Today is not safe! I'm definitely gonna get pregnant!
But you just feel too good!
It's okay, right? Right?!
Thank you for complimenting me.
I might be falling for you, Mister.
But is it okay? I'm still a student.
Is it okay if I get pregnant?
Of course. I'm at my limit. I'm cumming.
Now? You're cumming now?
Please let me think about this!
Please give me a little more time!
Sorry, that's not happening! Nope. Sorry. Sorry.
Wait!
I'm cumming!
I'm cumming! Stop!
I'm gonna cum again!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You're cumming inside me!
Inside me... I can feel you making a baby inside of me!
How was it? Did your first creampie feel good?
So good! My pussy is so happy!
My womb is happy!
They're both twitching from all the cum!
Um, am I pregnant now?
Yeah, you are. I came a lot after all.
You're probably pregnant now.
I'm gonna be a mom?
That makes me happy.
I never knew anything about sex or baby-making until now.
So you liked it?
Yes! I liked it a lot. I'm very happy this happened.
Thank you very much.
Thanks for having sex with me.
Wha...
You're thanking me?
You're too much of a goody two-shoes.
And at that moment, the doors opened
and a huge wave of people flooded into the train.
I put my member away and slid into the next car over.
I was planning on taking that girl
to a hotel and fucking her wild,
but it seems like she already got off the train at some point.
There you are! Found you!
There you are too!
I found all three of them!
All three of them are sluts?! They're all so hot!
The one on the far right is Natsukawa Emiri.
With a bust of 110 cm, she is one
of the bustiest schoolgirls out there.
She's the type who gets really
turned on from doing forbidden acts.
The girl in the middle is Asahina Mami.
She revels in destruction. She hasn't had sex yet,
but she's given her brother's friends biowjobs.
How nice of her!
And then this girl is Kawabata Miki.
Her chastity is long lost. She's a super slut, so to speak.
She's lacking in brains,
but the ace of her school's swim club.
She's cheerful and tan with tan lines from her swimsuit.
Something amazing is gonna happen on this train!
Damn, I'm so excited! I'm so fucking hyped!
Excuse me, girls.
You all have pretty hot bodies.
Wanna do some dirty things with me?
Ya know, the type that makes sounds!
It's an adult dick!
What are you doing? This is a train!
I-It's so big!
It's so different than my brother's friends's!
Oh wow, it's a cock.
It's getting so big!
Are you a pervert, Mister?
Miki-chan is amazing.
She's not nervous at all.
The veins are bursting out and it's so thick!
If that went into my pussy, I... I think I'd die.
Everything I hold dear to me, my school life,
fun things, important things
will just disappear because I had sex with it.
You're all staring too much.
Are you all perverts or something?
S-Sorry.
Tell me, Emiri-chan, the super slutty schoolgirl,
would you like to have sex with me
in front of all these people on the train?
S-Sex?!
By sex does he mean actual sex?
Just like that? That easily?
I wonder what your pussy feels like.
Oh, also it's gonna be raw
and I'm gonna be cumming inside you.
I can't make sense of what he's saying.
This guy's just so perverted, his perversion is too strong?
I... I'm getting so turned on!
So turned on!
Wait, don't!
Don't!
Ready? I'm gonna shove it in!
With this, you'll be one step closer
to being an adult, Emiri-chan!
This...
Wow, I've never seen that happen before!
If your tits are that big, they really can bust open a shirt!
It feels really good!
It feels good when a guy is rough with my boobs!
Give it to me too! I want it too!
Good! So good!
Sex is amazing!
We shouldn't be doing this, but it feels so good!
I-It feels too good! I... I'm gonna go crazy!
I'm gonna go crazy!
This is so good! This is too good!
Come on! Come on!
Let everyone else have a look at your dirty holes!
Everyone, please excuse me!
I, Natsukawa Emiri, am a pervert!
I'm sorry for hiding it!
Having sex with a stranger on the train is...
It's making me go crazy! It feels so good!
This is just too hot!
It just feels too good! It's too much! It's...
Hey, are you really gonna let yourself
be the only one to feel good?
I'm sorry!
I-It just feels too good! I came!
I've got two hot schoolgirls waiting
for me, so let's finish this up quick.
No! Don't cum inside me!
Please!
Please, I'm begging you!
You really think I could pull out now?!
No! No more! Please cum outside of me!
Please!
Just take my kid inside you and be happy!
No! Wait!
I'm too young!
I'm too young to have a baby!
I'm too young to be a mom!
I'm too young! Too young!
Oh my god.
So this is what a creampie feels like.
I can feel it. I can feel myself becoming an adult.
He had sex with me and now I became this, his woman.
I want to have sex too!
Huh?!
Come on, Mister!
I don't need a condom. You can even cum inside me!
It's inside!
So good! It feels so good!
It feels so good, Mister! So good!
Do it harder! I love cocks, so do me harder!
I love sex! I want to have more and more sex!
Holy shit, I'm gonna cum!
I'm gonna cum!
I'm cumming!
Doggie style!
This is doggie style!
I love doggie style!
Then let your body be mine and mine only!
Okay! Okay! My body is yours!
I'll become yours!
It feels so good!
Doggie style is the best!
You slut! Just how many people have you had sex with?!
Daddy, my brother, Tanaka-sensei,
Hashimoto-sensei, Arai-sensei,
and some senpais too, as well as some older guys,
and the dad of my friend too!
Wow, it's a miracle you're not pregnant yet!
Yeah, but I feel like today might be the day!
I want you to put more cum in me than I've ever had before!
It feels good when you hit my ass like that!
So, Miki, you like more cum than less, right?
Yeah! I do!
Well then, here I come!
Be my schoolgirl toilet
and stop having sex with other guys!
Okay! I'll become your schoolgirl toilet!
I'll do it! I'll marry you!
You're so amazing!
I'll become your wife and become your schoolgirl toilet!
I'll be more energetic than any girl you've ever had!
I'll be sure to give you a lot of...
Healthy children!
I love it! I love you! I love this pleasure so much!
I'm marrying this guy.
We'll get married and start making kids!
Asahina Mami-chan?
You're up next.
U-Um! U-Um! A-Are we really going to make babies?
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: hentaisenpai
quality control: fyurie
softsub: торрент иваниваныч