Bullshit! Why does it always have to be Naotatsu?
Come on, man, we're comrades!
The girls should support the boys, and
help them overcome their 'troubles'.
I just have to keep my eyes closed, right?
Onose-san, your voice is really erotic!
Here I go, Onose-san!
This feels great, Suemori-san.
It's big. It's so big.
Wait, Naotatsu-kun!
I'm going to break. I'm getting torn apart!
Let's have sex, Naotatsu!
Why is it only Naotatsu who gets to make good memories here?
This is unfair!
What is it?
What's wrong?
Who's that woman?
Hi.
Hi there. You guys sure are doing well there.
Se-Sensei, what's the meaning of this?
Come on!
A Field Trip at the All-the-sex-you-can-have Beach.
The Animation.
Suomi-sensei, wh-what's going on?
Welcome...
...to the All-the-sex-you-can-have Beach!
All-the-sex-you-can-have Beach?
It's a small area beside the Nudist Beach.
Very few people know this place, precisely
because it's made for 'that'.
Anyone who can't abide by the other
beach's rules are accepted here.
So long as you can find a willing partner, it's A-O-K.
It's too bad none of you hooked up with
any of your female classmates.
Which is why here,
with me,
along with my slutty friends,
are about to start our special 'social' lesson.
Special... social lessons?!
Just bring it!
You're sucking vigorously already!
I'm about to cum!
You want to release it already?
Just how long have they been holding it in, Suomi?
Sorry, that may have been too much.
To make up for it, we're all going to enjoy ourselves all day.
Suomi-sensei's...!
She's completely sucking my dick dry!
Just cum lots and relieve yourself, okay?
Alright.
I'll make sure to squeeze out every last drop.
I'm about to melt!
Please, do it harder!
Oh my, what a demanding child.
In that case, how about this?
Everyone's dick looks like it's about to burst.
I can't hold back anymore!
I'm... I'm sorry!
It's all right. Go ahead and do it even harder.
Sorry, I'm about to...!
Your stinky cum was so thick!
Sorry, I'm still...
Whoa, that's Suomi's students for ya.
Every dick's superb.
They're all so delectable.
Are you at your limit?
Take mine, too!
Okay.
Just go together... and take me on!
It's bulging so much, it's about to burst.
I'm cumming!
You sure came lots.
The tongue is wrapping around it...!
Just cum as you like, I don't mind.
Come on now.
Oh crap, I'm at my limit!
I'm sorry, I totally got carried away.
It's all right, don't mind it.
I don't actually hate such hard plays.
Th-Then, please do mine as well!
Your dick's so full and stiff.
There's no need to hold back, you know.
So just cum whenever you want to.
Lots came out.
Sensei, please give me a blowjob, too!
A handjob for me, please!
Okay.
I'll take good care of every one of you.
There, that's good. Mess me up more.
Keep it up. Just keep at it till you squirt it out.
You're so wonderful!
Caress that lower part even more.
Oh no, I think I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming... I'm cumming!
Well?
My breasts sure feel good, don't they?
Yes, it's the best!
Alright then.
And a mouth-pussy, too!
I'm about to cum!
Making it stiff like this...
I don't remember all of my students being as perverted like this.
Y-You're even more perverted than us, sensei!
How rude. Time to punish you, then.
So hard and stiff.
I can't hold back anymore!
Jeez, your students are too lively, Suomi.
You think?
They've been holding out in this
beach for quite a while already.
Though, they'll probably soon-
Excellent.
They're still quite lively.
In that case,
next is...
...with those dicks...
...the long-awaited...
Main course.
A Field Trip at the All-the-sex-you-can-have Beach.
The Animation.
That's right. Push it in deeply.
Like this?
Yes, push it in further.
Penetrate me.
Yes. Yes!
You're so amazing.
This time I'll be the one to caress you.
You've really built up stress here.
You're so amazing, miss!
It just feels amazing!
I'm about to cum!
I'm cumming after losing my virginity!
It's alright. Just pump it all in.
Fill me inside.
Take it all, miss!
It's all coming out.
Your young and thick cum is filling me!
This can't be real.
I'm really banging this fairy-like foreigner!
It's so intense!
Oh yes!
My hips won't stop moving!
I never thought I could ever fuck such cute girls.
That's because I...
I simply love sex.
Just keep it up.
Just maintain that pace.
Roger!
Hey, you don't need to do that!
Oh, come on.
I'm cumimng!
It's still like this even after cumming.
Come on, cum some more.
I'm about to cum with everyone watching me closely.
Oh crap!
I'm going to smother with these giant tits!
You love breasts, right?
Now, now, you have to do your part as well.
That's right. Just keep on fucking me hard.
Suomi's students sure are aggressive.
I'm really enjoying this.
They really are doing their part.
But you don't need to focus on my breasts.
Move your hips and make me feel good, too.
Oh my, if you intend to fap like that.
you might as well take this vacant spot.
O-Okay!
Come on, what's wrong?
Just keep pushing!
Keep moving!
Fuck yeah!
More, more!
Do it more!
What's up with that?
Me too, please excuse me!
Hey!
I'm not really into anal.
I'm willing to do other things, though.
Wait, just wait!
Wait...!
It's gripping me really tight!
I'm a bit too sensitive in there.
Coming in!
Hey, just wait!
I'm not used to being fucked both ways yet!
That's Miss Foreigner's pussy for you.
It looks like it could take many dicks at once!
Of course... not...
It's going in deep again.
As expected of Suomi's students.
I cean't take these guys lightly.
Being caressed wildly by these boys...
I'm going to...!
Suomi-sensei...!
My virgin dick's been taken by sensei!
Looks like we have a lively dick waiting on this side as well.
Sensei's mouth is taking my dick inside!
Suomi-sensei!
I'm gonna cum again if you keep sucking so vigorously, sensei!
Harder... harder is simply better.
Sensei, I'm about to cum!
Cumming already?
Alright then, cum lots inside sensei.
I'm cumming!
Sensei, sensei!
Sensei... Suomi-sensei...!
I can't wait anymore!
Please let me cum between your boobs!
Okay, okay.
Just keep the dicks coming.
Se-Sensei, I'm at my limit.
I'm cumming!
There's so many dicks.
Having sex with Suomi-sensei's gorgeous body is the best!
I'm next! I'm next to fuck sensei's pussy!
No need to rush, you know.
There's no stopping this train.
Keep them coming!
Suomi-sensei.
Suomi-sensei!
That's some good hip movements you've got there.
Sensei, take mine, too.
No need to rush.
The dick was pulled out.
Where did you learn how to do anal sex?
I was watching them do it over there earlier.
Your willingness to study is very good.
Sensei, will you take mine, too?
Of course!
Sensei, sensei!
Everyone's so nice.
Sensei's underboobs!
Her armpits are also amazing!
That tickles, everyone.
I never thought all of you could be this perverted.
Sensei... sensei...!
Suomi-sensei!
Suomi-sensei, I'm about to cum!
Me too!
This is the final spurt! Just a bit more!
Everyone's cum is so hot.
Don't leave a drop, and squirt it all on me.
This is the best field trip ever!