Dammit, why is it always Naotatsu?!
We want to do it with girls too!!
The girls need to support the guys with
erections and overcome their problems together!
So I just need to keep my eyes shut, right?
Just as I thought, your voice is so hot, Onose-san!
I'm cumming, Onose-san!
S-Suremori-san!
It's so big! It's so huge!
Wait, Naotatsu-kun!
I'm gonna break! I'm gonna break!!
Let's have some sex, Naotatsu!
Why is he the only one who's allowed
to make these good memories?!
This isn't fair!
What's wrong?
You okay?
Wh-Who is this person?
Hey there.
Hi! Everyone gather up!
Sensei, what's going on?
Come on!
School Trip to the Sex Beach.
School Trip to the Sex Beach, the Animation.
Sumio-sensei, I-is this...
Welcome to the sex beach!
Sex beach?
It's a small area next to the beach we were just on.
You can have sex with people you know.
And it's okay to switch up partners
and have sex with other people too.
It's also okay to find your own partner here.
It's sad that you couldn't have any sex with your classmates.
And that's why you're all going to have a
special sex class with me and my friends here.
A s-special sex class?!
Just bring it!
B-Being that rough all of a sudden is...
It's gonna make me cum!
Already?
Have you taught these kids how to hold back?
Sorry. But, you need to loosen up a little.
You just have to enjoy it.
Sensei's deep throating my dick!
Cum a lot and feel refreshed.
Okay.
I'll be sure to get lots of cum out of you.
I feel like I'm melting!
Please, could you suck the tip a little harder?
Oh my, what a demanding little boy.
If that's how you want it, then how does this feel?
All of your dicks look like they're about to burst.
I can't wait any longer!
Sorry! Sorry!
It's okay. You can even be more rough if you want to.
Sorry, I'm gonna...
Your raw cum is so thick.
Excuse me, I haven't came yet...
You really are her students, huh?
You kids are no joke.
All of your dicks are so taste.
Are you just about at your limit?
I am too!
Alright then, you two can cum together.
Your penises are swelling so much,
they must be about to burst.
I'm cumming!
You came quite a bit.
Your tongue's wrapping around me!
You can cum whenever you want. I don't mind.
Come on. Go ahead.
I'm gonna cum from your mouth!
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
Don't worry about it.
I don't mind it rough.
Then please take care of me next!
You're ready to burst.
You don't have to hold back. Just cum whenever!
Cum whenever and wherever you want.
Look at all this cum.
Sensei, please take care of me with your mouth next!
Take care of mine with your hand!
Okay, I'll take care of all of you together.
Just like that. Very good.
Make a mess out of me!
It's fine. I'll take everything in.
You're so great.
Dig in deeper with your tongue. Twirl it around inside me!
I'm cumming! I'm going to cum too!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!! I'm cumming!!!
What do you think of my bust?
Feel good?
Yes! It's the best!
Then I guess I'll...
You're even sucking it?!
I'm cumming!
You're so big already.
Are all my students big perverts?
Y-You're more of a pervert, sensei!
What's that? I think you need to be punished.
Gnaw gnaw.
I'm done!
Sumio, your students have way too much energy in them.
Sorry, it's because they were teased on the other beach.
But I'm sure they'll start calming down soon...
Excellent!
Oh, they're all full of energy again.
Then... next is...
Using those dicks for...
The long awaited...
Real deal.
School Trip to the Sex Beach, the Animation.
Good! Just like that, go all the way inside me!
Like this?
Yes! Go deeper! Like you're trying to dig inside me!
Yes! Yes!
You're so amazing!
Now it's my turn to make you feel good.
You must've been building up a lot of stress.
You're so good, lady!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I'm gonna fire off my first shot of manhood!
That's fine. Cum inside.
Cum lots inside me!
Please take my cum, lady!
It's coming out! It's coming out!!
Your hot, thick cum is filling me up!
This is like a dream!
I'm having sex with such a fairy like woman overseas!
So good! So intense!
I can't stop my hips!
I can't believe we get to have sex with all these cute girls!
Well I just love having sex!
Good! Good! Just like that!
Got it!
H-Hey, don't do anything I didn't tell you to do!
Oh, jeez.
I-I'm cumming!
You came so much, but you're still so hard.
Come on. Cum some more.
Cumming in front of an audience...
So embarrassing!
I'm gonna drown in your boobs!
But you love boobs, don't you?
Come on, you need to put in some work too.
Yeah, just like that! Shove your dick into me harder!
All of Sumio's students are so good.
You'll show me a good time too, right?
Yeah, you really are trying hard.
But you need to stop focusing on just my boobs
and start focusing on making my pussy feel good.
Oh? You're playing by yourself over there?
There's room for you in this hole here.
O-Okay!
Come on, what's wrong. Try
harder and really thrust it in me!
It feels so good!
More! More!
What's wrong?
E-Excuse my intrusion!
H-Hey!
I'm not too good with anal.
I'll do a lot of other things, but...
H-Hey, w-wait...
It's so tight!
I'm really not good with anal sex...
I'm coming in!
W-Wait a second! I'm not used to
having two inside me at the same...
As expected of a foreign older lady.
You're just sucking up our dicks.
That's not...
It's going so deep again!
These really are her students. I
can't underestimate them at all.
These two dicks are twirling
around inside of me. I'm gonna...
Sumio-sensei! My virgin dick was eaten by you!
I guess this is another twitchy
dick that can't wait any longer.
Sensei's on my dick!
Sumio-sensei!
If you suck it that hard, I'm gonna cum again!
Hard? What do you mean by hard?
Sensei, I'm gonna...
You're gonna cum already?
Okay then, cum a lot inside sensei.
I'm cumming!
Sensei! Sensei!!
Sensei!
Sumio-sensei!
I can't wait any longer!
Please make me cum with your boobs!
Okay, okay. Keep the dicks coming.
Sensei, I'm about to...
I'm cumming!
These dicks just keep cumming.
Having sex with a hot body like yours is the best, sensei!
Now I'm gonna... I'm gonna put my dick in your pussy!
You don't have to be in such a rush.
Today's our break. Just keep coming at me!
Sumio-sensei!
That's the perfect hip movement.
Sensei, please take care of me too.
No need to rush.
Your dick fell out.
Where'd you learn to anal fuck?
I saw them doing it over there.
It's very good that you're so passionate about studying.
Sensei, is it okay if I join in too?
Of course it's okay.
Sensei! Sensei!
You're all doing very well.
Sensei's underboob!!
Armpit! Her armpit's amazing too!
You're all tickling me.
So all of you are really this perverted?
Sensei! Sensei!!
Sumio-sensei!
Sensei! Sumio-sensei!
I'm cumming!
Me too!
Last spurt. Final leg.
All of your cum is very, very hot.
Don't leave a single drop. Give it all to your sensei!
translation: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч