I'm Minorikawa Naoto.
I work at a real estate company in this town.
The only company members are my boss and I.
Higurashi Real Estate
Higurashi Real Estate.
Behind this modest company name,
is something really fishy.
We've been thinking of moving lately.
So we wanted to see if there are any vacant condo spaces.
Sorry if it's a bit sudden.
Somebody told us that we'd be able to find one quicker here.
Actually, we're about to get married soon.
Oh, congratulations to you two then.
Do you have any preferences about the place or about the rent?
We're thinking of renting a spacious one.
A spacious one, right? I'll see if there are any immediate vacancies.
This one has two floors and is 20 years old.
It's old, but it's a lot cheaper than the one beside it.
This one is new and has three rooms for living dining and kitchen.
It's also on the top floor.
Seems you two have opposing views.
How about taking something in the middle? Like this perhaps?
I don't want an apartment.
It has to be at least a condo!
Wow!
Tthis one is three years old.
It's quite close to the station, at the top floor,
with three spacious rooms for dining, living, and a kitchen.
It's a bit over your budget,
but the kitchen provides the latest electrical appliances and equipment.
I love this!
The security here is very good too.
Takeshi-san, you love it here too, right?
Wait, I just can't...
Let's try looking for other vacancies first.
Don't you already feel like choosing this one after having seen it only once?
But it's quite over our budget, you know.
I'll just start working again.
But this would hurt us financially.
I'll just make you packed lunches.
It's close to the station, but it's pretty far from where I work.
Let's just work hard together.
Besides, this will be our first time living together as a married couple.
Well... you're right.
Slutty Real Estate Agency
Room 02
We recommend T.H.I.S
The Female President's Room is Always Open
So, the two newlyweds chose that one.
But, I'm a bit worried.
About the rent?
Or about their relationship?
Both, actually.
Their viewpoints are totally different.
And their total income doesn't seem to be that big.
The husband seems to be working at a pretty standard firm.
So his income is enough, I suppose.
He is a bit of a cheapskate though.
The wife on the other hand, even though she has worked part-time
never really acquired any experience working full-time.
I don't think you should judge our customers like that.
Circumstances did allow them to become engaged, you know.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Sayako-san, you're still awake?
Yes, partly because I was waiting for you.
Dinner's over there.
Thank you.
This is such a joy.
Hey, Sayako-san can we?
You have to wake up early, right?
Well, you're right, but...
Hey, just once, okay?
Hey.
We haven't done it for three weeks already.
Jeez, I'm not in the mood for that.
We've only done it three times since we started living here.
You were keeping count?
Idiot! I'm not going to wake you up tomorrow!
You never did anyway.
You're always asleep.
Sayako-san, l wonder when she'll start working.
Sex services, huh?
I've never been inside one.
No one's inviting me to drink anyway.
I'm home.
Asleep again.
I'm hungry.
Today's dinner is...
Welcome!
What should I eat?
Though, I really don't have money, so...
The regular beef bowl and miso soup, please.
Oh, it's the real estate agent.
Morita-san! Why are you here?
This place is near my workplace so I came to visit.
You look a lot more stressed than before.
You can tell?
Actually, I'm thinking of filing for a divorce.
Why?
Sayako-san didn't cook again, and she even said she'd love to use that kitchen.
She also doesn't do her part of the chores.
And it looks like she has no plans of ever finding a job.
It's the exact opposite of what she said before we got married.
Why did you decide to marry her?
I felt like my age was catching up with me, so I rushed.
Sayako-san is actually quite older than me,
so I thought she'd be more dependable.
I thought it'd be like having free sex,
but she doesn't even let me have that, this is just too much!
I've heard that Morita-san's wife is actually older than him.
I'm surprised.
But, she's quite gorgeous, isn't she?
I heard she never goes to work,
and with Morita-san slowly driven towards sex services,
it'll be just a matter of time before that condo falls apart.
We're fine with just them paying the rent regularly, right?
But they're bound to get divorced if this goes on.
How about I go get the pay for the rent this time?
Good day.
This is Higurashi Real Estate.
Morita-san?
Yes?
We have come to collect the rent.
Huh? Oh, is that so?
I'm going to open the door.
Well then Miss, goodbye.
Okay, good work.
A delivery man?
I'﻿m sorry, were you entertaining another guest earlier?
No, it's alright. Don't worry about it.
Oh, give me a moment.
Eh? Where?
I have it. Okay, I understand.
I'm sorry, the guy must have forgotten this earlier.
I'll be back in a jiffy.
Don't you find that strange?
The way she acts,
and do delivery men usually forget their packages?
Of course they don't.
They're clearly committing adultery.
I'm sure they were at it like this until we came.
Right here, in this very place.
She'll be coming back very soon!
Then we just have to do it fast as well then.
Do it more.
Move more.
Oh yes!
Faster, do it faster!
Sorry for the wait.
Don't worry about it.
Boss, if Morita-san's wife was really cheating,
then it's definitely headed towards divorce.
Normally it would.
Good day!
Is there something wrong?
No, it's just that we were actually talking about you earlier.
Actually, she got pregnant.
We weren't having sex that much,
but I guess if a chance presents itself, it can really come, eh?
Even if it is her child, the baby is still our seed.
Well then, I'll come again.
Boss, it's Morita-san's child... right?
Dunno.
Sorry you had to come in person.
No, thank you very much.
Boss, I think we should really consider accepting bank payments.
You seem to be capable of doing lots of work on your own now.
Minorikawa-kun, do you want to try working as the company's boss like me?
I'm about to quit the job already.
Eh?!
Boss, can you look at this?
I've made a list enumerating all our customers and clients
who want payments to be made via bank deposit.
So you did all this, huh? Why don't you try it then?
I already said I'm about to quit, you know.
Boss... are you really serious?
Is there anything that would bother you about it?
Well...
Is there anything that you still don't understand about the necessary paperwork?
Nothing really...
You see, it may not seem like it, but I actually trust you deeply.
Was boss really serious about quitting the job?
I'll be leaving all the rents that I've been handling to you from now on, okay?
Soon-to-be Mr.President.
Even if you say that... It just got me all worried now!
Excuse me, this is Higurashi Real Estate.
Oh yes, who might you be?
I came to receive the rent.
Oh? It's not Ms. President?
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Did Ms. President have a headache or something?
Well, not really, but...
Have you known her for a long time?
Yes, she has been taking care of me ever since I moved here.
Getting the rent once a month, and visiting the place.
She always gets to be the one I talk with, how sweet of her really.
Indeed she is.
Why are you the one getting it and not Ms. President?
Well, boss is quite busy at the moment, so...
And I just got some juicy info for her.
Were you able to make you debut?
I passed the first screening for the top 500
in HB company's sci-fi short story awards.
Is that good or something?
Ms. President!
Kurosaki?!
Ms. President, this is bad!
He just ran away, and now I don't have anywhere else to go!
Oh, but I'm no longer the President here.
Oh, then who is?
Him, Minorikawa-kun!
President!
Minorikawa-kun, no Mr. President.
Please, I can settle for anything cheap.
But, I just can't suddenly...
I can also stay at your place... If you want me to.
Of course, I'll do my best at night.
Boss...
President Minorikawa, do your best!
I'm going to find a place that you can rent right away.
So just wait, please.
I said I'm okay with your place, you know.
No, I'm definitely going to find one for you.
Well, what a busy day.
Yeah, it was.
I'll sort the papers so that we can write out the necessary documents.
You can go on ahead.
Okay, starting tomorrow, you're now in charge of everything in this office.
Eh?
Do your best, President Minorikawa!
Boss!
Boss, renting a place, can actually be quite hard, right?
What are you suddenly saying now?
You're actually employed and working, and
yet there's no one to see you through it.
Your income might not be enough,
you might get too old.
You might get rejected for various other reasons.
I guess you're right.
I...
After coming to this place, I realized something new that I can do.
That's why, please don't quit.
That's good then.
Now I can retire in peace...
Boss, I still want to work with you.
Minorikawa-kun, weren't you irritated by it before?
You thought that I was some pervert, right?
Well, yeah I did.
But I'm actually... kind of glad.
Oh... I see.
The words that you just spoke earlier,
let me see just how sincere you really were when you uttered them.
Boss...
This is the office, if someone comes...
Just thinking about it makes you feel excited, right?
B-﻿Boss...!
It's so big.
Oh yes.
That's it, it feels good.
It's going deep inside.
Boss...
It really feels good.
Cum inside me!
Minorikawa-kun!
Minorikawa-kun...
Boss, I...
Oh no...
Boss!
I can't find it again.
I wonder how many times this has happened now.
I don't think there are big offices here.
Maybe it's hard for even the locals to find it?
Why don't we just visit that last and final office that they referred us to?
Excuse me, is anybody here?
Welcome!
Minorikawa-kun, introduce it to them.
Sure, boss!