My name is Minorikawa Naoto,
lately I've been working at a real estate agency around town.
This company was one I luckily found when I was job searching.
There are only two employees here, my boss and I.
Higurashi Real Estate.
Doesn't really look that way at a glance though.
It even feels like some sham company.
I want this room.
Thank you very much.
Are you two going to live there?
Just me.
Anyway, don't you think a six-month deposit is too much?
Though, I wasn't able to find any good
deals in other real estate offices.
Our company doesn't require special permits or licenses,
which is why the prices are as given.
In addition, most of our customers are students,
and we usually return the collateral money once they move in.
But I've heard most of what is paid is never returned.
Ma'am, is there a problem?
Boss.
The pre-paid amount is used for repairs, maintenance,
and other miscellaneous things.
The remaining amount would be returned to the customer.
Really?
Also, as for the rent,
we require it to be paid directly to us.
Is that clear?
I can't pay via bank transfer?
You can simply direct your payment to Mr.
Minorikawa at the end of the month.
What?
Okay then.
Be sure to contact me if you're coming to get the payment, okay?
Thank you very much.
Boss, are those two going to be okay?
What do you mean?
The rent for that room seems like it
would too expensive for a student.
If they suddenly decide not to pay...
No need to worry about it.
If they want to rent it, then why not.
There are many ways to pay the rent, right?
So, I'm leaving the visits for their payments to you, okay?
I'm going to take the amount from your
salary if you can't get it on time.
Why?
Isn't the deposit there for that purpose?
That's an entirely different matter.
Slutty Real Estate Agency
We Recommend
The Female Boss is Always Available
Room 1
Good evening, this is Higurashi Real Estate.
Mizumoto-san, are you there?
Wait a bit.
Yes.
Here.
Okay, payment accepted.
I'm sure this is tougher for you.
Why don’t you just accept a bank transfer?
It'd be much easier that way.
Well, it's what the boss wants.
She also said that living alone for a girl can be tough,
so I'm also responsible for regularly checking up on tenants.
Hey, come on over here already.
Got it.
See ya.
She's got a guy over there.
Minorikawa.
You said you weren't able to collect payment
from Mizumoto Fumi, right?
Yes, she always ditches me even if I set up an appointment.
I can't seem to catch up to her.
I think she's at her apartment right now.
Head over there.
What, why?
Do I really have to?
Yes, she's there.
Now, go or I'll slash your salary.
I'll be going!
She's really here!
Wait...
Oh, Mr. Real Estate Agent.
Long time no see.
I've finally caught up to you.
Umm... about your monthly rent...
You came without telling me, so I don't have it right now.
Just come back tomorrow.
Oh, where are you going?
To collect payment from Mizumoto Fumi.
You haven't got it from her yet?
I already gave the payment to him!
Your boyfriend told me that he doesn't have the money with him.
He spent it all for himself again?
So, what will it be?
Then, just wait until I get to the shop.
Though, you'll have to wait until dawn.
If you're alright with that, then...
Okay.
I'll wait.
Mr. Real State Agent, have you ever
thought about a person's value?
Not really, I usually ponder about my next lunch everyday though.
Don't you think it's a drag to work simply to earn money?
I definitely don't want to exchange part of my life just to work.
I also don't feel like having my freedom taken away.
But, for now I have to work to earn money I guess.
That's not right. As a student I think
you should prioritize studying first.
You're in no place to tell me that.
I'll call you when this is over.
So, what time would it be when it ends?
Oh, so she said something like that, eh.
She may have said that she needs to work to earn money,
but she doesn't even want to pay her rent.
Okay, let's go then.
To where?
I haven't slept yet!
To her room of course.
I received a call from where she's working.
I heard that she quit her job already.
No way!
What about school?
She was expelled last month.
This is terrible!
There's trash everywhere.
Well, it’s to be expected I suppose.
It looks like there are no guys in here either.
She seemed to have a habit for tardiness and absences.
She also seemed to have a boyfriend but,
I guess this was the breaking point for them.
Boss, why do you know those things?
She sure bashed the place up quite well.
Now I'm having a hard time restraining myself.
Boss...?
No...
We have to do what we need to do...
Eh? What if she comes home?
She's not coming back.
I got a call from her earlier.
I never heard about this.
She said that I'm free to dispose of the things in here.
What do you think?
Well...
She was here just a short while ago.
She laid on this bed, thinking about tomorrow.
A person lived here.
I wonder how she lived here.
Minorikawa-kun.
Don't you feel excited?
What we're about to do now,
is also part of what we do as a company, okay?
You're not leaving until we're done.
Boss, wh-what are you...?
Minorikawa-kun...
That girl must have been riding boys here too.
She may have been violated at this very spot.
This smell...
The smell...
Fuck me more.
Do it like you're raping her.
Like I'd know how that would feel.
Here's the key.
I have no spare.
Okay, I got it.
I'll be leaving then, I'm a bit in a hurry.
Thank you.
Have you heard?
Tadasaki-san's last apartment was in a big city.
Of course I know, I heard it from her.
She's an entrepreneur, and she earns quite a lot.
Though she said she's more about practicality than lavishness.
Besides, pets aren't allowed here.
Currently 45, single, and living alone.
I wonder how often she used these.
Hey, do you think she cooks for herself?
And what would be her menu?
She's eating here, alone.
Having sex in places where people lived and have left.
Boss seems to have this kind of fetish.
I don't really understand it.
I'm eating outside.
Beef bowls again, huh.
The rent in those apartments sure isn't cheap for me.
I'm a gentleman, believe me lol
Hahaha, no quarreling now
I've uploaded the pics
Woah, just wait a bit
Isn't this godly?
How about here
Here we go
Too dark, can't see
What are they doing now?
Wait, It's a hidden cam?
Wait, The room looks old, the walls are
also thin, you can hear them creak and
there are large gaps between...
Just a poor man's houses right?
No just bed, but the entire room, I can
really hear squeaking sounds lol
Thanks to that though, we can set up lots of things inside,
so I guess its pretty even compared to the quality of the room
More please
No hogging please, everything's neatly packed here password is HN
Here's the payment for this month's rent.
Sorry you have to come here personally, Meguro-san.
I suddenly had to work and leave my old place due to my job.
It's actually kind of troubling.
We're willing to maintain the place nicely,
as long as we have free time.
It's one of the easiest apartments to get though.
The place is quite old, and the walls
are quite thin so we were worried.
No, I only actually sleep there though.
So it's quite enough.
That's all, I'll be leaving then.
Thank you very much, sir.
Meguro-san.
You forgot your bag.
I'm sorry, I kind of forget things a lot lately.
I’m going then.
Good evening.
Good evening...
Today's goodies
Here comes the fresh stolen shots
You"re amazing
You're gonna be found out if you do it too much
Meguro-san, do you have a minute?
These parts were supposed to follow the design.
They don't seem to fit.
That can't be.
Now, now, those areas there still need some work.
It's a bit easy to miss these things, but try
to be more careful next time, okay?
Kuro-san, what do you think of our youngsters?
Boss.
I can't possibly teach them all one after the other.
Please give me back my regular post.
Don't say that.
It'd be troubling if we can't train these workers well.
Just put up with it for while.
Alright.
Meguro-san.
Oh, the Real Estate Agency.
What's wrong?
I was just passing by. I thought I'd drop by your place for a bit.
The president will come to my place...?
Yes, of course.
The place is a bit messy though.
Is it okay now?
Yes, come in.
Woah, that sounds so thin.
I think the gaps inside the walls are bigger than we thought.
I see, that can't be helped.
For an old guy like me, just having a roof
to sleep under is already enough.
Though, we also have young tenants around here.
Ms. President, what are you doing?
Oh, just lurking around a chat site I suppose.
I'm actually kind of hooked into it.
You can see the messages posted in real time.
And you can easily share images and videos.
I think I've heard of that.
Boss has been chatting around all day with that.
It's fun you know.
Is, is that so?
Meguro-san, you don't seem to have a lot of stuff lying around.
There isn't a TV.
Well, a PC is enough for me you see.
I guess you're right about that.
Yes?
Alright, alright.
I understand.
Okay.
That must be hard, still having to go out at this time.
It is my job after all.
Do your best.
Well then.
Boss, aren't we going home?
We're here already, so why don't we talk a bit to his neighbors?
There's something that I need to know about.
I understand, please use it then.
I'm sorry, we'll be borrowing the room for a while.
More, more...
They're doing it at this hour?
Not the usual time I guess.
It's already long over usually when I come home at this time.
More...
Oh, they're really doing it.
Ah, the youth.
It's completely exposed.
Wait, that's not the girl I usually see.
Give it already
Hold your horses
Just wait lol
Give em', Give em'
It'd be a festival hahaha
MUSH, you tryin' to tease us? lol
What's this?
All of the shots are of her looking straight at the camera.
She knows where the camera is set up!
She can't have...
It was publicly released?
What? Lololol MUSH its over for you lolol
MUSH, you're in big trouble lol
It's all over
Peepning tom, got caught haha
You messed up big time, veteran
Farewell, MUSH
Thanks for everything
Publicly released?
What's going on?
Could it be....
From this laptop?
These are all my pics!
I haven't uploaded these yet...
Why is it here?
A virus?
If people find out what I've been doing here...
It seems that Meguro-san already came back.
What are we going to do?
The walls around here are thin so he can hear us, Boss.
He's just hearing it, so I think it's fine.
What?
You're chatting while having sex?
Weren't you just to supposed to be checking for his real identity...?
Well, if we're going to be seen anyway,
it would be much more exciting if many people see us.
Share the fun, you get it?