Girl's Health Check ups Ongoing.
Guys don't  peek!!
Don't ogle them!
I can't do a checkup if I don't examine you properly.
I planned on going home sooner.
However, I decided to stay.
It's not because I want to inherit the household.
Hey Doc! Doing well today?
Lots of people said that they need me in here.
My heart was simply moved by their words.
O-ni-i-sa-ma!
Oh, you're next, Asuka.
Please examine how well I've grown, okay?
O-Okay.
The seven impregnated women who sneaked into the night
Part 02: The Headmaster's Bride
Onii-sama.
I'm going to rub your back, okay?
Why?
Yoshino-san told me that siblings should bathe together.
It's quite enjoyable, isn't it?
Siblings taking a bath together.
I-Is that so?
The expression father had when he was talking about you,
he seemed very happy.
That's why I thought that he must be a wonderful person.
And I was completely right.
I want to hold your back and keep you for myself.
A bride?
Yes.
"Keep the bloodline of the life-giver alive."
This is the final responsibility of the headmaster.
But I can't just...
It's not just about me, but I also have to consider
the feelings of the other person.
The most honorable thing for all women on this island,
is to become the wife of the headmaster,
and bear his children.
All women...?
Would you consider choosing me?
No, I...
It was a joke.
The bride will become someone important for me,
so I have to choose carefully.
Let's stop thinking about it.
I just want to let myself fall back on this dream.
So it's Yoshino tonight, huh.
No, someone more appropriate.
A-Asuka?!
I thought I would I would be happy being beside you.
But, I'm not satisfied with that.
But Asuka, you and I are...
This is a dream.
Please do not concern yourself with that,
and grant her wish.
Then, I want to do it with you too, Yoshino.
No, I...
Yoshino-san.
Let's just do what Onii-sama wants.
It's stiff... and sturdy...!
Masaya-sama, your thing feels like it's very happy.
I want to know all of your soft spots.
Hearing that...
Oh no...!
If you keep pushing me there...
No...
Don't fondle me there too much...
Why?
My kimono's... exposed parts,
will bear those kiss marks...
Don't...
That spot is...
I-It's rubbing me in there...
That's...!
Oh yes...
This is, intense...
It's hot, and it's stiff!
More, do it more...!
A-Asuka?!
Onii-sama...
I want to do it, too.
I'm a bit scared,
but I want to be one with you, Onii-sama.
It's in.
I'm really happy.
My insides feel very warm.
Give me the mark of our union... please.
Now the pain is gone with that kiss.
I already studied books about this though,
I'll try again.
Onii-sama...
Yes.
Don't hold back, just keep on moving.
It's hot, this thing rubbing me feels hot.
My insides are getting hotter,
my mind is about to go blank.
Can I continue?
Yes.
Just forget that we are siblings at this moment.
Onii-sama, you're already...
You're already craving for me this badly.
Asuka,
I'm going to cum now.
I want to see your face while doing it.
Asuka can really be a spoiled child sometimes.
These feelings of pleasure just won't stop.
It's coming.
I can't hold it back anymore.
I'm cumming!
I'm being filled... with Onii-sama's seed.
Your tongue, it's stirring my insides...
It feels good, my body is moving on its own.
I'm about to cum!
I'm about to cum, too.
I am yet to choose my bride.
This dream never ends.
It's the only thing that I have on my mind.
Oh previous one,
Masaya-sama has finally fulfilled his duty as the headmaster.
And it is an honor,
for me to be the bearer of the life-giver's child.