With this sweet scent,
and this intense fixation,
my dream for the night has just begun.
So this is a man's...
It feels good when I rub it like this, right?
It's lewd and warm...
And has a taste I don't hate at all.
It's starting to get really stiff.
How about this then?
Please, enjoy my hands.
It's starting to bulge.
You're about to cum, yes?
Please, squirt those manly fluids onto me.
With this...
Don't you want to penetrate a woman such as myself?
If this is a dream, I don't want to wake up just yet.
Just leave this to me.
It's opening my insides up as it pushes in.
Please, enjoy my body more.
I can feel it rubbing hard inside.
And it's getting even bigger.
Release it all... inside me!
Lots of your seed is inside me...
The seven impregnated woman who sneaked into the night
Part 01: A carnal visitor
It's been days since I came to this island.
I've been dreaming about sex all night.
And my partners are all girls who live here.
I'm probably just tired.
Lots of things happened, anyway.
The death of my father, whom I had
not been in contact with for a while,
and the appearance of my step-sister.
The letter provided me with this information,
so I came here to learn more about them.
Am I too early?
Good day, are you looking for something?
I'm actually waiting for someone.
Is that so?
Sorry for suddenly greeting you, it's just
that we don't get a lot of visitors.
Thank you for your concern.
What a beautiful woman.
Kuga Masaya-san, I presume?
Yes, that would be me.
Forgive me for calling you to such a far out place.
No, it's...
A-Are you the one who sent me the letter?
Yes.
I am Miyakura Yoshino.
Even though we just met,
Asuka still welcomed me home as a brother.
I was told that my father was the owner of this island,
as well as its only doctor.
A final will was left,
requesting me to inherit everything in his place.
Final will
What should I do now?
You pervert!
Pervert!
W-Wait, just calm down.
You were ogling at me, right?
Lecher!
You're mistaken!
I was just fascinated by the picturesque sea waves.
H-Hmph, I wonder.
You'll catch a cold if you don't dry yourself up quickly.
This is nothing.
That's not good.
You have to take care of your body.
Don't talk like some doctor.
I am a doctor, so I just can't let this go.
I-I get it already.
Well then, take care of your body, okay?
What a weirdo.
This sweet smell...
Who is it this time?
Ow!
Y-You?
I'm secretly visiting you.
It hurts!
You're a man, so you just have to bear with it.
It's supposed to feel good, right?
Since this is a dream, why don't I tease her a bit.
That's not good.
Not good at all.
I-It's my first time, so I can't help it!
Then, try to do as I say.
So, you do it like this?
There, it feels good.
Will it get stiff with this?
Will you do lewd things to women with this?
I want to insert it into you right away.
You... p-pervert!
Then, why don't I do it the perverted way?
What are you going to do?
This.
It feels hot and stiff.
For you to use my breasts like this...
I'm about to cum.
You can't cum just yet.
Hold it in!
Why?
I just said you can't!
Take a hint already!
I'm at my limit!
Wait!
I-I'm sorry.
You just did it all the way.
Hey, are you done already?
There's a reason why I need your cum inside me.
Please... do.
Something...
Something's coming...!
You really are a pervert.
What is this?
It feels tight!
It's pouring...
It's pouring inside me...
So, I'm going to get pregnant now?
Do you want to?
Sh-Shut up, I have my own reasons for this.
Then, let's do it some more.
I-Idiot...
Sto...
Don't fondle it...
Th-This is...
I can't stop this hot feeling inside of me,
especially when it hits me deeply...
Something's... coming...!
I haven't come yet.
I-Idiot, let me rest for a bit!
It feels completely different from earlier.
We're in a dream, so you have to feel hornier.
Getting myself horny with you as my partner...
Are you a sex fiend or something?
She doesn't want to be honest about it.
It's rubbing inside,
rubbing inside me.
Each time you penetrate me, I feel it in my entire body.
Show me more of your cute expression.
D-Don't look!
Don't look!
Y-You pervert!
My insides are getting stirred up.
I'm really moaning...
I can't stop it!
You're such a meanie.
Cum already, or else I'l...
I'll...
I won't stop until I cum, of course.
It's coming...
Something hot is coming...!
I'm cumming!
I'm going to cum too.
Your hot cum is filling me inside.
That felt good...
Eh?
Nothing, nothing!
Forget what I said!