Backside of the school!
Grandma's house!
The other world...
Oh, it's grandma!
Wow!
I can actually see it!
Amazing!
Hmm? Special training?
Yes. From now on you will be working while
disguised as a female high school student.
And in the case if you are ever captured, you'd
be tortured through many special methods.
To help you stand through such torture,
special training will start today.
Master! Something is hitting!
Senpai, if you suck my breast like that...
No... Senpai's penis...
Master's is gonna come in...
Wakaba, you're feeling too much!
You have to endure!
But... Master's feels really good!
What with that? Are you at your limit already?
No... I can't anymore...
To come with just that...
you definitely need more training!
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Some mysterious mirror!
That's a mirror that shows wherever you want to look.
There are all sorts of ways to have
fun depending on how you use it!
I can see...
Ena-chan down there..
It's like I can reach right out and touch it...
Kanou-san? Is something wrong?
Um, no... it's nothing...
What's going on?
It's so soft... it feels good!
This is amazing!
Huh? It's like someone's touching
me... What's happening?
Wow, it's getting wet...
My first time giving oral... is to Ena-chan's pussy!
This is the best!
Is it a prank from someone?
There's... nothing?
How's this?
Woah, it has like... an erotic taste!
Wow, its twitching...
Huh? Ena-chan?
Could it be... I made her cum!?
I'm amazing!
All the studying from porn is paying off!
Ayano...
Leave it to me!
Amazing... its really pretty and really erotic!
Huh? It's feeling weird down there...
am I getting my period?
I couldn't help but put it in...
Sorry, my stomach really hurts. May
I leave for the nurse's office?
Hmm?
Will you be okay alone?
Yes...
What's going on...
I'm not doing anything and yet it feels like
someone is licking and teasing that place...
It feels weird...
This is so good!
No! Somethings going in and out!
I don't want this...
Something like this... just isn't right...
Ayano's pussy is warm and feels really good!
This feeling is... really weird...
Shit... I'm gonna cum!
Don't!
No!!!
What is this... what's going on!?
No... I'm scared now...
From then on I teased Ayano every day with the mirror.
I put it inside her during class
and during break time as well.
Ayano, what's wrong?
It's nothing...
Do you have a fever or something?
Are you okay?
No...
My chest is... being licked or something...
At a time like this? And there...
I've always wanted to try something like anal...
Hey, stretch properly!
It's going in my butt...
No... I'll pee... stop!
It's really coming out!
It feels so good its scary...
If only I could talk to someone about it...
It's been a while since I came over to Ayano's, huh?
Recently, something strange has been happening to me...
Did she find out?
Is she gonna kill me because she
found out I've been fucking her?
It's something I can't say to my friends so..
B-But, why me?
Because Takaya is the person I can trust the most..
Ayano...
Great, she hasn't found out yet.
Well, we did grow up together after all!
Well, what happened?
Well, every day my breasts and also down
there feel like they're being touched...
It feels strange.
If this goes on...
I'll go crazy...
Well why don't I investigate!
But... um, it's my chest and those places
that are being touched, so...
Let's see...
To be able to see both your boobs and
your expression... it's really erotic!
It kinda felt just like this...
I see... so do you feel good right now, Ayano?
No, Takaya... not there...
What do I do? It really feels so good I could go crazy...
As expected, it's much better to be
able to see and touch everything!
I can't hold back anymore!
Ayano, could we have sex?
I'm scared... but I'd want Takaya to be my first so...
It's okay...
I'm going to do it... I'm having my first time with Takaya...
I'm going in...
Yeah...
Does it hurt?
No... it hurt much less than I thought it would...
That would probably be the case...
Huh? This feels... the same as those times...
Wow! This feels so much better than through the mirror!
Shit, I said it out loud.
That... that was nothing!
Hey, could it be that., the person
who did weird things to me...
Was that Takaya?
How did you kno...
So it was you?
Shit...
That was so cruel...
But...
It was Takaya instead of someone else or some monster...
I'm so glad..
Ayano...
Instead of doing it like that, doing it while
I can look at Ayano is so much better!
I can feel you with my whole body...
No... Takaya... I'm going to cum... I'll cum!
Ayano...
So you can do those kinds of things with this...
Yeah... but since we can do it like
this now... I guess I don't need it.
So you won't do it... anymore...
A-Ayano!
And so, even today, without caring about where we are...
Were having fun together.
Shouta-san! The tutor Yamashita-san is here!
Something like a tutor right now...
I'll teach you all kinds of things...
Put yourself together, you idiot!
A tutor huh...
I guess my parents don't plan to let me fail again...
If this is the case then it doesn't matter
how many times I fail the exam!
I'm gonna enjoy the school-free life as much as I want!
Well, if the tutor is a beauty then,
I might change my mind...Huh?
What was with that!? At least knock
before you go into someone's room!
I did! But you were listening to something
strange stuff like "Negi Negi Coconuts"
at a large volume so you didn't hear.
Well, what do you want?
I'm busy right now.
Did you live in the neighborhood?
What are you doing to my precious books!
I'm your tutor, Yamashita Konatsu!
Nice to meet you!
You're what!?
The Home-school Teacher
Katekyo no sensei
Shouta-san, what's with this?
The evaluation test I took earlier.
You can be dumb but not this dumb!
I'm shocked by just how incapable you are.
Damn... she's so full of herself
even though she's just a kid!
I might look like a kid but I skipped grades
and am a fourth year university student!
I'll be training you strictly until you pass the exam!
Lets start with solving these problems.
C'mon, hurry up and start!
This is hard...
Even middle school student wont get this wrong!
Listen up, right here you use this
equation... are you listening?
I'll be making sure you learn today as well!
Yes, yes...
We'll be reviewing the sections
you got wrong last time today!
Today we'll do the tests for English and Math section
C and Physics section One and Classical Literature!
You got it wrong again? How many
times do I have to teach you!?
Geez!
Geez! I want to get that kiddo to say something
like "I can't do this" or "I'm sorry"!
I know!
Huh? Practical technique for Health
and Physical Education?
That's right I'd be great if you
could help me with practice.
You'll know what I'm talking about
after you watch this DVD.
But something like technique for Health and Physical Ed...
Huh? Could it be that, you can't do it?
So there are things that Konatsu-chan can't do!
That's not it!
I might look like this but I do have stamina!
And there are people scouting for me in every sport!
I'll prepare for this until the next class, so don't worry!
Something like Technique for Health and physical
Ed... I guess new subjects are coming up recently.
I've got to study hard so I can teach that idiot properly!
There... Yes... Cumming again... Cumming... Cumming...
What is this?
Amazing... so good...
Could it be that they're having intercourse?
So this is how you do it?
My pussy... feels good...
I'm feeling... weird...
More...
Yes!
Yes... Amazing...
My boobs... and my pussy... feel good!
Well, how was it?
You cant, right?
I tried looking up some stuff myself, too, but there
were some stuff I didn't really understand.
Huh? I thought she'd be more embarrassed...
So please teach me, Shouta-san!
Eh... EH?
What, what are you talking about!?
So you wanted to laugh at me and
yet you can't even do this?
Is it okay? Actually doing it like this?
You're... not wearing a bra?
Well it's not like I need one...
Her tiny boobs are cute...
Wow, she's soaked already...
Damn, she looks really cute when she's excited...
More and more slutty juices are flowing out...
Makes me want to get her to make a naughtier face...
It's quite amazing if you look at the actual thing...
I'm supposed to lick this?
She did lick it in the DVD... what do I do?
Don't push yourself. You haven't done it before, right?
Please keep quite! I studied properly
for this, so don't worry!
This is...
Amazing, it feels really good! So when
she said shed study she actually did!
Doesn't feel like it s your first time!
So what's my score?
100 out of 100!
Konatsu...
She's too cute... I want to go in her right away...
But can I, really?
Shouta-san... please put it in..
Is it okay? Really?
What's wrongs Hurry and continue...
Um, let's stop around here...
Huh?
Konatsu... you're just doing this out of obduracy, right?
Because your pride doesn't allow
to say you don't know and stuff...
That's not...
It's once in a life time and you should be doing
it with someone you like and not just so easily...
I know that!
I like you! So I want you to continue!
It's not something like doing it easily!
If you don't want to then it's fine! I'll leave!
Wait! That's not it!
What's not...
I like you, too, Konatsu!
But you're smart and everything,
so I just wasn't sure you'd be happy with
an idiot like me for your first time...
Really?
I mean it!
I love you, Konatsu.
I love you too!
Here we go...
Yeah...
Konatsu, does it hurt?
I'm okay... so do what Shouta-san wan...
I never knew anything about such erotic things...
I want to learn more... more of these things!
I want to lots of things that feel good with Shouta-san!
I want to catch up with Konatsu,
too. So be sure to teach me!
Yes! leave it to me... Lets learn about
all kinds of things together!
Konatsu, cumming...
Shouta-san, I love you...
You made it!?
Yup, my number was up there.
Congratulations, Shouta-san! Even
though you were so dumb before!
Hey...
I've been studying, too.
Konatsu? Dude, that's SM you're looking
at... those are for perverts...
But it looks fun so I got really curious!
Well, lets go to my place.
Yes! Please teach me lots and lots!