Behind the school.
Grandma's house.
This shape...
It's Grandma!
Amazing!
I can see it!
Special training?
Yes.
For this mission, you're gonna pose as a school girl.
But, for a ninja like you, Wakaba.
You might get captured
and tortured in a special way.
So there's gonna be lessons to withstand that,
starting right now.
Master, something is poking me!
Senpai, you're sucking on my tits.
Huh... It's senpai's dick.
Master is coming in.
Wakaba, you're getting too horny!
Keep yourself in check!
But Master, it's feeling really good.
What, you're already this close?
Sorry!
I'm already...
If you're cumming like this,
then the lessons aren't enough yet!
Desires Bazooka
What a mysterious mirror!
This is a mirror that shows you any place that you want to see.
You can have fun in a lot of ways with it.
I can see it
Ena-chan's pussy.
It's like I can touch it.
Kano-san, what's the matter?
It's nothing.
How is this happening?
It's soft...
It feels great...
This is amazing!
What? It's like I'm being touched.
What is this?
Amazing it got wet.
It's my first time eating someone out,
and it's Ena-chan's pussy!
It's the best!
Is someone playing a prank on me?
There's... nothing?
How about this?
Wow... that's a lewd taste.
Amazing, it's twitching.
Ena-chan?
Did I... make her cum?
Wow, I'm amazing!
So, watching all that porn did pay off.
Ayano.
Leave it to me!
Amazing...
So pretty... so sexy...
Wh-What is this?
My pussy feels weird...
Is it my... period?
I just put it in without thinking...
Excuse me, my stomach hurts.
Can I go to the infirmary?
Are you okay going alone?
Yes.
What happened?
I didn't do anything.
My pussy...
It's like It's getting touched and licked.
It feels weird.
It feels great!
No! Something is going in and out.
What is this?
This is... weird!
Ayano's pussy is hot...
It feels too good.
Somehow... it feels weird.
This is bad, I'm gonna cum.
No!
No...
What is this?
I don't like this, it's scary.
From that day on, I had fun using the mirror on Ayano.
It didn't matter if it was during lessons or recess.
Ayano, what's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
You're hot, are you okay?
No!
It's like my breasts are being licked.
At such a place...
Moreover... in that part...
I was always interested in...
anal fucking!
Come on! Do your stretches properly.
It's going... into my ass.
Women Toilet
Pee is coming out.
No!
It's coming out, it's really coming out.
No...!
It feels too good, It's scary.
If I could talk to someone...
I haven't been to your house in a long time.
Recently... there's been something weird happening.
Did she find out?
If she finds out I put my dick in her, she s gonna kill me.
It's just... a topic that's hard to talk about to my friends.
Bu-Bu-But why me?
Because...
I'm more comfortable talking to you, Takaya.
Ayano...
Yes. She hasn't found out.
We-Well, we're childhood friends after all.
So, what's going on?
It feels like everyday,
my breasts and pussy
are being touched by someone.
There is this strange sensation.
If it stays like this...
I will go crazy.
Well, let me investigate a bit.
But, wh-what's being touched...
are my breasts...
and my pussy.
So...
Anyway, anyway...
Her tits and her facial expression...
Seeing it all is pretty hot!
I was feeling just like this.
Exactly...
Eh?!
Well, Ayano, are you feeling good now?
No, Takaya, that place...
What should I do?
It really feels so good that I'm gonna go crazy.
Really seeing and touching everything
is a lot better than the mirror.
I can't hold back anymore.
Ayano, can we have sex?
Yes. It's scary, but...
I always thought that having my first
time with Takaya would be okay.
It's fine.
I'm... doing it.
My first time with Takaya.
I'm putting it in.
Ok...
It doesn't hurt?
No. I thought it would, but it doesn't hurt at all.
Well, I guess not.
Huh? This feeling...
It's the same as that other feeling.
It feels a lot better than when I was using the mirror.
Eh?
Oh crap, I said it out loud.
It-It's nothing.
Hey, could it be that,
the one that did those weird things to me...
Was it you,Takaya?
How did you...?
So it was you.
This is bad.
That was cruel! Doing that...
But...
It was another human,
and not something like a ghost...
It was Takaya...
I'm glad.
Ayano.
It's better than before...
Doing it while seeing Ayano's face...
Feels a lot better.
My whole body... everything...
I can't anymore... Takaya...
l'm gonna cum... I'm cumming.
Ayano.
Wow, you can do that with this mirror?
Yes.
But now that we're together like this,
we don't need it anymore.
Huh?
We're not...
doing it anymore?
That...
A-Ayano!
Because of this,
wherever the place may be...
We are close friends.
Desires Bazooka
Shouta-san.
Your home tutor, Yamashita-san, is here.
The home tutor is late...
Onee-san will...
teach you... a... lot., of... things.
Give it your all, idiot!
A home tutor, huh?
My parents just won't let me slack off.
If it has come to this, then I won't fail the university
entrance exam a second or third time.
Life as a failure is just too enjoyable!
But if the home tutor is a beauty,
then it would be a different story.
Huh?
Wh-What?!
You can at least knock if you enter someone's room!
I did!
But you were listening to some weird "Leek,
leek, coconut" song at high volume.
So you didn't even notice, ain't it?
So, what do you want? I'm busy now.
Was this girl already living nearby?
Y-You!
What are you doing to my precious double-page spread!
I'm your home tutor, Yamashita Konatsu.
I look forwards working with you!
This brat?!
Shouta-san.
What is this?
That's the proficiency test that I took earlier.
There are limits to being stupid...
It's surprising that you can't even do this much.
Damn...
This brat is arrogant.
Look at this!
I've skipped grades, and I'm a 3rd year college student!
I'm gonna train you mercilessly until you pass.
First, you're gonna solve the problems
in these books on your own.
Come on, start already.
Th-This is difficult.
A middle schooler wouldn't even get this wrong.
Do you understand?
If you use this formula...
Are you listening?
The next day
Today, I'm gonna teach you a lot again.
Yes, yes.
And again on the next day
Today, we're gonna thoroughly review
everything you got wrong yesterday.
I'm going to test you in English, Mathematics
C, Physics 1 and Classic Literature.
You got it wrong again?
How many times do I have to teach you this?
Come on...
Come on!
Come on~
I want her to say to me "I can't do that either" or "I'm sorry."
That's It!
Huh?
A practical skill in health and body... education?
Yes, that's right.
I want you to help me with those exercises.
You'll understand the details if you watch this DVD.
Oh... But exercises for health and body...
Huh? Could it be that...
you can't do this?
Haha.
So, there is something this midget can't do.
You're wrong.
No matter how you look at it, I'm very fit.
People from different sport clubs, ask me to join all the time.
Don't worry, I will learn this to perfection until the next lesson.
Health and body exercises...
Recently, there seems to be a lot of new subjects.
To really teach this idiot a lesson,
I have to study this properly.
Good, good.
Please. I'm gonna cum again, I'm gonna cum.
I'm cumming.
Wh-What is this?
My nipples... feels good.
Could it be that, when you have sex...
This is what you do?
My pussy feels good...
My pussy...
feels weird.
This is good.
This is good, amazing, amazing.
My tits...
My pussy... This is good.
Now, how was it?
You couldn't do it?
Even though I studied this by myself,
there was a lot I didn't understand.
Wh-What?
I thought she'd be a lot more embarrassed.
So Shouta-san, please teach me about this.
Hu-Huh?
Wh-What are you saying?
Even though you made fun of me,
you can't even do this?
Is it okay? Doing this for real?
You... aren't using a bra?
I don't really need one.
Her breathing is cute.
Amazing it's already so wet.
Wow...
The aroused face she's making it's super cute.
Her lewd juice is flowing out rapidly.
I want to make her expression even more excited.
Seeing it for real, it looks so strong.
You can lick this?
She licked it in the DVD.
What should I do?
Hey, you don't have to,
if you don't want to.
Shut up.
I studied this properly, so there's no problem at all.
Th-Th-This...
Amazing it feels great.
She said she studied this... I guess she really did.
I can't believe this is your first time.
What score would you give me?
100 points!
Konatsu.
She's too cute.
I wanna stick it in fast.
But, is that okay?
Shouta-san.
Please put it in.
l-ls that really... okay?
Huh?
What's wrong? Hurry up...
Umm...
We should... stop at this point.
Huh?!
Konatsu, is it really just about us becoming one?
I don't know, but that's something my pride wouldn't forgive me.
That's just...
I'm saying this because,
this is something you should do with someone you like.
You can only do this once in your life...
If you just do it so easily like that...
I understand that!
That's because...
That's because I like you!
I really want to continue!
I'm not doing this easily!
If you don't want to, it's fine. I'm going home.
W-Wait, it's not like that.
What are you...
I-I like you too, Konatsu.
But you're so intelligent,
I'm just wondering if it's okay, to have
your first time with an idiot like me.
Really?
Yes, really.
I love you, Konatsu.
I love you too.
I'm going in.
Yes.
Konatsu, does it hurt?
It's okay,
so please do it however you like, Shouta-san.
Such indecent things...
I didn't know them at all.
More.
I wanna do a lot more things.
I wanna do a lot of things that feels good with Shouta-san.
I'm gonna do my best just like you Konatsu.
So please keep teaching me.
Yes.
You can leave that to me.
Together, we're gonna learn a lot of different things.
Konatsu, I'm cumming.
Shouta-san.
I love you.
Did you pass?
Yeah, I made it.
You finally made it, Shouta-san!
Even though you were such an idiot!
Hey.
I did some studying too.
K-Konatsu.
You are one of those S&M girls?
One of those perverts?
But, Im really curious and it looks fun.
So, let's go back to my house.
Yes.
Teach me a lot... a whole lot.