Uh, I'm late because of practice.
My new tutor's coming to my
house today.
I wonder what they're like.
A guy or a girl?
I hope they're good looking.
I hope they'll understand when I
explain my problem.
Well, I better get home quickly
before my tutor arrives.
I've got to move fast.
I'm home.
Welcome back. You're pretty late.
Your tutor's already upstairs in
your bedroom.
Okay.
I'll be going out to dinner with
my friends, so take care.
Got it, have fun!
Bye!
I'm so sorry, my practice ended kind of late.
Ah...
Nice to meet you. I've already
made myself at home.
Oh yes. Be my guest.
Um, I am Hanamura Milk.
Nice to meet you.
It's my pleasure.
Cool! He's good looking, and that's
what I was hoping for.
I'm sure I won't be studying that
hard anyway.
Then put your bag over there
and sit over here.
Right here?
Good. Take of your jacket.
Huh? Take off my jacket?
Yes. Hurry it up.
Okay.
Umm, I have a test next week.
Then unbutton your blouse and
show me your breasts.
What? What are you saying?
I can't do that.
Why would you ask me to do something like that?
Well, before we get started, I'd like to
become a little bit more acquainted with you.
But my breasts...
Forget it. I'll take off then.
I guess I'm not quite your type.
No, that's not it. I don't dislike you.
Besides, if you leave my mom will kill me!
So please don't mention anything
about leaving.
So you're going to cooperate then?
Umm, yes. I'll cooperate.
How's this?
Yes, that's better.
Now let's take off those panties too.
Oh, my!
Is this your method of getting
acquainted with me?
Yes, you're learning already.
Ye, yes.
Is this satisfying my tutor?
Milk-chan.
Yes.
Stir inside your pussy with this.
Are you serious?
Ok. I'm out of here.
Bu, but...
Fu fu fu...
It'll only get you into trouble
with your mom.
Here.
I'm starting to get horny.
Now, do it slowly.
Ye, yes.
Oh, my...
Slower.
Yes...
No, no... this is degrading.
What's your right hand doing?
Bring it up to your breast.
Now, I can spread open your
pussy like this.
No~!
No, no~!
It's slipping in.
No!
No, please!
No, no!
No!
It's going in so deep.
You're such a horny girl, Milk-chan.
Looking at your cunt got me
rock hard.
What have you done? Huh?
Oh my...
Please stop!
It's useless to cry for help.
I know that nobody's around.
Come on. Lick that dick.
Good, good.
You're getting to become a pro.
Yes, yes, yes...
Use your tongue.
Yes, yes.
Go down all the way.
Suck it harder.
Yes...
That's what I'm talking about.
More, more.
Swallow the whole thing.
Good, good, good.
It feels good.
Let's go on.
Great.
I'm starting to feel good too.
I can't hold it much longer.
Oh, that feels so good.
I can't hold it back.
I'm cumming! I'm cumming...
Okay, now it's my turn to do
some pleasing.
No, I don't want it!
Stop, please let me go! Stop it!
Stop!
You're already wet.
You don't have to be shy at this point.
No, stop! It's embarrassing.
My finger's going in.
This is embarrassing... No!
No, it's embarrassing!
Doesn't it feel good?
No~!
I think it's ready.
There!
No~!
No... No, no, no...
Do you feel it going in?
Doesn't it feel good?
No, no!
Don't say no.
It seems that you're enjoying it. See?
How does it feel going in?
No, no, no!
Come on, don't say that.
I'm taking it out.
No, don't!
Which one do you want, huh?
You're talking too much.
Right here. Right?
No, no, please!
No, no... I don't like this...
No, no...
No, please...
It's so tight...
No.
I'm going to fuck you harder.
No! No! Please... Stop it please!
You really want me to stop?
Huh? Should I stop?
No, no.
It feels good, doesn't it?
No, no...
Oh wow...
Oh my, I'm starting to like it.
No more... No... More...
No, please... No, no... more...
It's so tight.
You're doing good. Doing very good.
It's going in deep.
It's embarrassing.
Wow, it goes in so smoothly.
Embarrassing?
Please, no...
Feels so good.
I've never felt like this before.
I can't hold it.
Milk-chan, you're gushing already.
You're really into this, huh?
Tell me honestly.
It feels good...
Huh?
I can't hear you.
It feels good, so good...
Say it louder.
It feels so good. Don't stop.
Yes, yes. Please don't stop.
You should have said so.
Have you been holding this in
the whole time?
No...
Then, I'll grant you your wish.
This skirt's in the way.
I'll make it more interesting, there.
Please, no, no...
Wow, wow...
I see it clearly. Look for yourself.
No, no...
That's wonderful...
This is great.
Don't tighten that much, Milk-chan.
More, more...
What do you want me to do more of?
No, no... It's embarrassing, embarrassing.
My cock's hitting so deep.
No... More, more, more, more...
You're squirting now.
So embarrassing...
Bounce with me now.
Embarrassing, so embarrassing...
Doesn't it feel good?
No, no... It's embarrassing...
Wow, wow...
It feels good.
Feels good?
No, no...
Deeper, deeper...
I'm cumming...
I'm home.
Oh my, excuse me for not
having any tea.
Are you leaving already?
Yes.
How's my daughter doing?
She always has to do make up for tests,
even on the last one.
It's such a hassle.
But because you're here, I hope her grades
will improve, even a little.
Improvements in her grades will come
in matter of time.
She's a fast learner.
How wonderful. Very pleasing to hear.
Please take care of her tomorrow also.
Oh, my...
Is this what you want?
Good, good. Keep it up.
Good, move faster.
Oh my, wow...
It feels so good, wonderful...
Move your hips around more.
Feels good... Feels so good...
It's amazing!
Feels good.
What's the matter?
Aren't you enjoying this?
Yeah, it feels so good.
I'm so happy that you really worked for me.
Because you feel so good...
Oh God!
Wow...
Look below you.
It's embarrassing...
Feels so good...
Your mother will hear you from downstairs
if you keep screaming.
But, but... I can't stop in the middle...
I'll make it worse.
Do you feel it? Right?
It's embarrassing.
More, more, more...
No, no... I... Stop, stop!
Tighter.
No~!
Good.
How is it?
No.
It's good. It feels so good...
I'm cumming, cumming...
Give it to me...
Don't give up yet.
We're not finished. My lessons continue.
Okay.
Next, we have to study this part too.
No!
No, no, not that...
This is more gratifying isn't it?
I've never had this done before...
Wow, wow... this is great...
Please, please, more...
You're tightening... amazing, Milk-chan.
More, more, more...
Wow, your ass is getting tighter and tighter.
No, it's embarrassing...
Don't say that, it's embarrassing.
I'm embarrassed.
There!
I can't hold it anymore!
No more, I can't hold it!
I'm right with you baby.
It's so embarrassing, no...
More, more...
No, I can't bare it Milk-chan.
I'm going to cum.
Cum inside my ass...
Cum inside my ass!
Please hurry!
Cumming, cumming...
I'm busting a nut!
Here it comes! Here it comes!..
Cumming, cumming, cumming...
Time's up.
Please gather your tests from
the back row in order.
Whew.
Hey Mari. How did you do on the test?
Pretty bad?
I envy you, you look so stress-free.
Don't ask if you know already.
I studied so hard yesterday, but
it did no good.
Besides that, you look so happy.
Really?
Plus that confidence.
You looked so confident for this test,
not like your usual low scores.
You think you aced this test?
Kind of.
What?
I've got my ultimate weapon.
You want to know what that is?
Okay. Come to my house today.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Hey, Milk-chan.
You were early today. How was your test?
I have no clue.
What about you?
Huh? What is that?
I thought you did good on the test.
I never said that I did good on the test.
She is Mari-chan, my friend from school.
Mari-chan also wants to be tutored by you.
Is that all right?
Studying? Is he your tutor?
Oh, so you're a friend of Milk-chan.
Then starting today, the three of us
will have some real fun studying.
This is cool.
Now Mari-chan, let's start by
taking off your jacket.
What?