Ouch...
Huh? I was talking with a little girl just now.
My palm feels... delightful...
Please don't!
Am I dreaming? A girl?
Her ears are long though.
W-Wait—
You really can't... do that!
Whoa! I'm sorry!
I-It's alright.
My name is Lucie.
And you are the messiah that
Nol-sama brought here, right?
Messiah?
Right! We elves have been waiting
for your arrival so you can procreate with us!
Sukebe Elf
no Mori e
to the forest of lewd elves
Messiah, please impregnate all
of us elves in the whole village
Thanks for the hardwork.
Today was rough as well.
A little girl...
What a weird outfit.
Hey, you there!
Are you looking for your mom?
Want me to help you?
Y-You... You can see me?
Whoa! Is she some kind of tin foil hat kid?
Offering to help me with such generosity!
And that great potential to
notice my existence as well!
I found the right one!
You will come with me, to Alfhelm!
Wait, don't raise your voice suddenly!
Off you go!
Now I rememeber! That kid did something on me.
O Messiah, I beg of you.
May you bestow your semen upon me!
But... We only just met...
I am already done with all the
preparations for the ritual.
Your dick is entering me!
It's like I'm dreaming!
Lucie-san!
Don't mind me.
Please move as you please!
It can't be! It's only my first time
but I'm already feeling this much—
My breast!
Having it fondled while making a child feels good!
I'm having sex with an elf!
This is... a human's sexual intercourse...
After learning something that feels good,
my mind won't be able to think of anything else!
Sorry, I'm already coming!
Yes... Please come!
Give me your baby seed!
It's pouring... deep inside me!
Thank you very much.
To think that sex feels this good...
I have to tell this to everyone!
Lucie-san!
W-Wait a little!
Sorry! I didn't come enough yet!
Are you still not satisfied after coming once?
It's hitting me...
You're hitting me deep inside!
I'm mating... I'll get impregnated!
So intense!
If your keep penetrating me deep
with your cock, I'm gonna come!
I'm hitting something!
Shoot it deep inside me!
Knock me up!
That was a wonderful climax, Lucie!
And Messiah as well.
Ah! It's you!
I am Nol, the elder of this village!
Nol-sama...
You're of no age to be an elder.
Still trapped in the logic of how normal living things are,
you're still no more than a child.
You heeded our abrupt request,
gently making love with Lucie,
and even bringing her to climax!
Even my heart skipped a beat
and I'm feeling all tingly now!
In this world, we elves all lived with the tree of god,
and were all under the Holy Tree's divine protection.
Here in Alfhelm, the concept of
reproduction is almost non-existent.
When a child is needed, the Holy Tree grants us one.
But the power of the Holy Tree waned.
And we, it's unworthy children, have our lust
we supposedly lost being reawakened.
So that's why we elves
need to replenish our population.
Nol, you're bleeding...
No need to panic.
Make love and impregnate me
in any way you like to, Yuuichi!
We might look peaceful but
our lives are under a threat.
That's because of the nearby nation, Underdark!
And its dark elf inhabitants!
Because of their attacks, our
casualties have been increasing.
You have to make me pregnant!
Will your body be okay?
Petite elves like me can widen our holes up!
Our holes naturally gets molded by the shape of our first man's dick!
Look! My shallow vagina can take
all of your dick thrusting a lot!
Use it any way you want!
With something like this, I'm already...
It's pouring in me...
Deep inside me...
I'm counting on you for the prosperity of our tribe!
It's not just me,
There are a lot more elves who wants your semen!
This dick I called over for will take my first time...
So this is a human penis. What a horrifying thing!
O Messiah, forgive me for my late arrival.
I'm from the noble Hagerhelm clan,
my name is Firis Hagerhelm!
What's this, doing it together at the same night?
You're bleeding!
This is but a child's play for a woman
from the renowned house of Hagerhelm!
It's already decided that our household
will be the one who should produce a child first!
I'm sure it will start to feel good soon.
Lucie?!
The Messiah's dick is incredible!
Me too please, Messiah.
Not like I have any other choice.
If you lick me that much, my hips will go crazy!
That's not fair!
I was totally left out while you're
both doing it all day as well!
Jeez! What should I do?!
Your tongue is licking all of my creases inside!
It feels good!
It's always Lucie!
I'm sorry.
What's happening? It feels like my body is floating!
It's like I'm going crazy!
Firis-chan, are you feeling good?
You have a talent on copulation even
though it's just your first time.
I-I already get it!
Hurry up and yield your baby seeds to me!
Or else...
You're sure about it?
I said it's fine! Shoot it in my deepest part...
I'm gonna come too!
Impregnate me!
I love it! Amazing!
O Messiah... Give me your seed here too!
Your dick is inside!
Your dick is making my pussy sloppy!
We're making a baby!
Messiah, let's do it once more!
I want to make sure of getting pregnant!
That's not fair! You're only
paying attention on Firis-chan!
Ah, amazing!
Your dick is amazing!
You'll only come when I say so!
I'm already coming!
I'm coming, oh!
I'm coming too!
Shoot your semen in my womb again!
I got squeezed dry so bad yesterday...
I'd still feel clammy if I didn't wash my body.
A girl's voice?
Imbecile!
Wh-What are you saying!
She's a dark elf!
Even if it's a request from you, the Messiah,
How can I allow someone who's from
the enemy stay in our village?!
Even if you say that,
she won't let go of me.
This lowly Evelyn begs you, Elder Nol.
I was saved from the monsters by Yuuichi-san...
He's my master. Please let me stay with him...
Only this one time!
It's for the sake of gathering intelligence!
Wait... Evelyn!
I beg you, master.
Please let me thank you back for this monring!
This is the only thing I know to do.
So please feel free to use my mouth
and whole body as you please, master.
Are you fine with doing this?
Please don't worry about it.
I'm doing it of my free will and I wanted to.
Even just for once, I want to be of use for you.
I want to give my everything and serve you!
This is a human's...
Master's semen...
If I'm sprayed over with this...
I'm begging you, master.
Please take my first time!
Wait, Evelyn!
I'm connected with my master!
Master is entering me!
Oh no! I am so happy...
I'm coming... I'm coming!
Wow, what's this?
This is incredible! If the the light shines brilliant
when a dick is going inside me...
It's a magic to make me trust
nobody else except you, master!
Even when I'm reincarnated,
I can only do this with master!
It's something like an eternal vow!
It's like our bond, right? It's arousing me!
Yeah, I'm coming already!
I want it in my vagina, please!
I want to have your child, master!
I'm gonna come already!
Yes, please indulge yourself!
Take down your barrier, you damn elves!
We already know what you are hiding in there!
Relinquish the human stud!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization