You raised some annoying barrier as usual.
Misery
Delva
Elda
Elda the Warmaiden.
Misery the Dark Magician.
General Delva.
Hurry up and go! Call out for Nol!
Oh, dear Messiah...
Oh... Are you the Messiah?
Such a brave kid, but...
Isn't going against Misery
kind of imprudent!
It's gonna come through!
Oh my!
You came earlier than expected, Nol.
Meh, what a greenhorn.
You can't even hit Yuuichi with that attack.
This isn't good.
Misery, Elda, we're retreating.
Eh? We only just began—
We're saved... right?
Listen, foolish human!
Tonight is going to be the darkest of all.
Come and see us alone. And if you don't,
The village will be obliterated!
Sukebe Elf
no Mori e
to the forest of lewd elves
I'm not gonna lose from a mere human cock...
The Messiah's going alone to the dark elves?
Indeed. From what they said, they're determined
on taking the Messiah even if they
have to exterminate us elves for it.
I never intended to get you
mixed up on this dispute...
L-Listen... This is just my speculation but...
The dark elves could have been born
from the power of the Holy Tree
the same way we elves were.
With the power of the Holy Tree waned,
and our lust being reawakened...
I think they won't be a match
against the Messiah's dick!
Indeed, I can't think of any of
their possible weakness but that.
Are you serious about that?
Of course I am.
That's it!
I just had a great idea!
What is this?
This is a drug made from flower nectar... Oh yeah...
This is what humans would call an aphrodisiac.
Let's do it first without the drug for comparison.
It's too big so I'm a little worried if I can do this right.
Lucie-oneechan will pamper you like a good baby.
I heard from Nol-sama that you're younger than us.
I'm actually 1804 years old.
They sure are heavy.... Your tits.
They grew up just for this particular day...
So that they can be of service for your dick.
We're only about to begin.
If you somehow end up having sex with the dark elves tomorrow,
won't it be better if they're more captivated on you?
It's better to try it out than to explain.
Please give me the lots of your seed...
your floral garden essence!
Oh no! My nipples are getting stiff
just from it getting rubbed!
Forgive me... I already can't think
of anything else but having sex!
Yuuichi-kun... I'm...
I'm gonna make you feel good a lot more!
You see, I'm just sucking your dick,
but my pussy got dripping wet!
I should massage your dick...
I'll massage it for you!
I'm gonna come already!
You're gonna leak out?
No girl should be triumphant
against such an amazing dick!
Even the dark elves for sure...
Yo, you really came all by yourself!
I see that you have some balls.
Excuse me for calling you out of nowhere.
I am Delva, the General of the dark elves.
This is sudden but...
I want... you...
My country has the same crisis as the elves.
Our race is on the verge of extinction.
We need your baby seed.
I already said no.
Of course, we'll take you away
even if we have to force you!
Even so, I'm going back to the elven village!
Let's have a match, then!
You win if you can make me climax.
I'll let you go back to the village of those damn elves.
But...
If your cock can't satisfy my womb,
I'll be taking you away by force.
Do it, Elda.
So this is a man's cock...
You have such a puny cock, how awful!
You shouldn't underestimate me!
Here you go! Cry out with all your voice!
You're going to become our
exclusive semen tank!
Every day, every night, until your cock breaks off!
Are you getting off while being
squeezed and raped by a woman?
You're so cute!
Here! Here you go! Squirt
your quickshot in my pussy!
Come! Come! Ejaculate!
So this is a human's semen...
Hey! Did you hear that, Misery?
This guy moaned like a girl!
This guy isn't really that big of a deal!
It's now or never!
Yuuichi's PENIStrength
has increased!
Have you not given up on
my sure win condition yet?
Is it not taking effect by any chance?
What?! What did you do to me?
Your cock is so hot! No...
Your tearing my pussy!
Wait! My nipples are so stiff, this is really bad!
Cock! Your cock is incredible!
Your cock is too powerful!
No! I'll lose my strength if you come inside me now!
Shit! This is the best! Your cock is the best!
I lost...
I lost to a cock!
You pulled a fast one on Elda, didn't you?
Answer me, human!
I'm sorry!
What could this be?
It's slippery and has a good scent.
This isn't what it looks like!
Stop looking!
It feels so hot!
I need to get this over at once!
What have you just done, scoundrel!
Kill... me... Just kill me!
Being treated like this in front of my subordinates...
C-Coward!
I won't lose... I'm not gonna lose!
A-At least come inside me,
If I won't get impregnated, I would
have been raped for nothing!
Right... Shoot your baby seed into my womb!
You are begging for the semen
of a man you don't even know!
You scoundrel... Humiliating me up to this far!
Right... So this is the thing they call a penis!
This is what drives the elves crazy!
I'll admit my defeat for today!
But... Next time...
I'm going back to fight fair and square!
Please do!
It's pouring in!
It's gushing into me!
Shit! A mere penis... From just a mere penis!
Please don't attack the village anymore!
Making those two come back-to-back... I changed my opinion about you!
Misery...
Using drugs was a good idea.
It doesn't affect me though.
What are you planning to do to me?
What else will I do?
We're gonna do it as well!
Without the drugs.
We're having sex.
I'll give the highest level of pleasure
for you who fell into despair!
Come on, brave messiah of the elves!
This is... This is the so-called penis!
A weapon that only men have and women doesn't!
This is bad! It feels like I am
gonna be sucked dry to death!
I'm not letting you go!
Look, my pussy is getting penetrated by your cock!
Oh, fantastic! I am getting raped!
This is it! This is what I wanted all along!
I've been searching since forever
for a cock that will take my virginity!
It even reaches up to the places
that I haven't touched myself yet!
I love your cock!
It's like I won on something
and this sex is my prize!
I wanted to do something like this all this time!
Listen, I'll stop doing bad things!
Can I move back in the village again?
I'll pour my love on you everyday—
What's this?!
Did something happen?
How can this be?
My mana is getting sucked out. This can't be!
It's getting sapped!
My mana is getting drained!
I know that I should pull it out already...
I can't stop myself!
This is bad... I'm gradually
getting drained of my mana!
You're taking something more
important than my virginity...
And I even regret about the former as well...
But I want to be fucked by a dick!
More... Mess my insides up more!
I will endure anything that
you'll do, so keep moving!
I think I'm gonna come!
Hey, are you gonna come?
Pour everything into me!
I don't need anything else but you!
I want you to be mine!
I won't betray you!
Fall to the depths of hell together with me!
That's... I'm coming!
Cock...
Cock!
I never thought that he managed
to win against the three of us...
How dare him to humiliate me like this...
Lowly human!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization