Yue ni Hitozuma wa
Netorareta.
The Married Woman
is Inevitably Stolen.
Episode 2
Aoi-san, sit down right there.
Yes, mother.
Isn't it about two years already since you
got married into our Kotori household?
A Cuckoo Chick
Yes...
And yet, there isn't any sign of you conceiving.
Have I not been telling you about it?
It is a bride's duty to provide offspring
and keep the household intact.
As someone who has that same duty,
I see that I cannot just sit by waiting.
This is Ootori Itsugorou-sama
from our clan's main branch.
He will be staying here with us for a while.
Oh, I might be from the main branch,
but I'm just a fifth freeloader son.
This is my first time meeting Aoi-san.
Yes, it's been a while.
I'm the son, Seiichi.
I'm his wife, Aoi.
You'll be looking after Ootori-sama's needs.
Make sure not to show disrespect unto him.
Yes...
Hi, Aoi-san. Did I make you wait?
O-Ootori-sama...
U-Umm, please wait for a moment!
My mind isn't fully prepared yet...
And after all, isn't this kind of thing strange?
Aoi-san, we don't have the leisure
to stall this any longer.
Either conceive a child or let
the Kotori household die out.
You have to make a choice.
I understand...
That's it.
You're doing great.
To increase the chance of conception,
we have to mutually accept
each other's hearts and bodies.
Yes, I understand...
Ootori-sama...
That won't do, you have to relax.
Uh-huh...
Aoi-san...
Which one between me and
Seiichi-san has a bigger one?
That would be you, Ootori-sama.
If that's so, then I have to loosen
you up enough down here.
You are now well prepared.
That's enough, it's alright now.
Let's hurry up and finish this.
Bear with it for a little while.
You see, it'll hurt at the beginning
but you'll get used to it in no time.
Ootori-sama...
My body is somehow acting strangely.
The part where we're connected
feels so hot, and I don't understand why!
It seems like you're feeling fine now.
Alright, I'll start moving slowly.
Can you feel it, Aoi-san?
You and I have fused and become one.
I can't take it anymore! I'm coming!
Forgive me, Seiichi-san...
Ootori-sama, it's my first time to have it this way...
I usually am not like this!
I'm not as immodest as I am right now!
I understand, Aoi-san.
Ootori-sama, please don't stare too much.
I look shameful!
It should be alright now.
Ootori-sama...
Are you feeling good, Ootori-sama?
Yes, very good.
Aoi-san, I am about to pour
my baby seeds deep inside your pussy.
Loosen up your body and
let it feel more pleasure.
Let's love each other even just for this moment.
Will that be fine, Aoi-san?
Yes, Ootori-sama!
My voice is coming out on its own!
It's alright, let it out even more.
Let's feel good as much as we
want without holding back.
O-Okay!
Ootori-sama!
Make sure to get pregnant.
Ootori-sama, are you gonna
visit me again tomorrow?
Aoi-san, Seiichi-san knows nothing of this.
Shouldn't you make your own preparations?
Sleep with him once tomorrow.
Okay...
Aoi, what's the matter?
Seiichi-san... Today...
Welcome! Thank you for visiting us.
Congratulations, Seiichi-dono.
It's been a while, Aoi-san.
Ah, Itsugorou-sama!
Please take a look at our baby.
I feel that I've finally fully become
a bride of the Kotori household.
It's also thanks to you, Itsugorou-sama.
However...
Our mother told me to try having a baby boy next...
Then, one more time.
Yes...
The Married Woman
Gets Violated Twice
Hitozuma wa 2-do
Okasareru
Phew...
Doing it with my ex after so long sure fires me up.
Can I drop by from time to time?
Don't come here again!
The next time you do, I'll really call the cops.
Yeah, yeah... Got it.
That felt so good, Miho.
And so, what do you want me to do about it?
Sei-kun, I'm sorry.
Huh?
Can you watch a Hotman DVD
by yourself for a little while?
You see, mommy has something important
to talk about with this man next door.
Okay...
Th-Then, I'll leave it to you.
Make sure to delete that video.
O-Oh...
Y-You're quite huge, huh?
This thing is really huge...
Oh, gosh... It's that guy's fault that this happened!
I should've never let him
inside the house yesterday.
Th-This should be enough, right?
You have to leave as soon as you ejaculate.
M-Ma'am!
Huh? Wh-What?
Wait, stop! Get your hands off me!
Wait, you can't!
This can't be...
Why am I getting wet?
No, if he teases me at various
parts at the same time...
Wait... We can't!
I'm properly wearing a condom.
No, that's not the issue!
Didn't I tell you that we won't have sex?
I said wait!
You really have to wait for
a little while! I just came earlier!
No, this can't be...
Why am I feeling this good?
Huh? This can't be! Could it be...
Wait, pull it out for a moment!
The rubber got torn off!
This is bad!
M-Ma'am, I-I'm already about to come!
You can't!
Absolutely not inside!
Huh? It's coming!
Wh-What the hell are you doing?!
It's pouring inside me—!
Huh? Just wait for a moment...
No!
Coming! Coming! I'm coming—!
I'm gonna come—!
Huh? No way, again?
Huh? Looks like someone is here.
Yes? Oh...
S-Sei-kun...
Mommy is gonna have a talk
with our neighbor again.
Be a good boy and wait here, alright?
You absolutely must not go into our room.
Here...
Oh... thank you, thank you.
Phew...
The Neighborhood Association's
Head Inevitably...
Yue ni Chounaikaichou wa...
I think I drank a little too much.
Try not to drink too much as well, Shun.
You can't hold your liquor, after all.
Gotcha.
Alright, then...
I'll be excusing myself first.
You too, Mr. Chairman. Don't drink too much.
Yes, yes...
I'll take my leave after a cupful.
Oh, but I envy you for having
such a beautiful wife.
You're young newlyweds.
I'll bet that you're enjoying
yourselves each night.
My, oh my...
It seems like that won't be
the case for tonight, though.
It can't be helped,
I'll have to do it in your place instead.
Oh, the chairman finally left.
Gosh, Shun... Are you drunk?
What's the matter? Want to do it tonight?
It's been a while since we last did it,
so I feel so horny right now!
That feels good!
Shun, right there!
Shun, that feels great...
Hey, Shun... That's enough...
Hurry up and put it in!
It's my first dick in a while!
Huh? It's way bigger than usual!
Oh no, this feels good!
I'm coming! I'm gonna have
my first orgasm after so long!
I never had such amazing sex before...
Are you taking a shower?
Huh? Yeah...
I've been sweating in bed.
Oh, the chairman already went home earlier.
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization