Yue ni Hitozuma wa
Netorareta.
The Married Woman
is Inevitably Stolen.
Episode 1
Welcome!
Oh, Mr. Landlord!
Hello, I helped myself inside.
Hitozuma NTR Kissa
Wife Stealing Café
Please wait for a moment.
Oh, must be hard for you to work alone,
having your husband hospitalized.
Here, let me help you.
N-No need to bother yourself for me.
Oh, there's no need to hold back.
Th-Thank you...
You're the idol of our shopping district, ma'am.
I'll help you any way I can.
It's reassuring to hear that from you, Mr. Landlord.
Mr. Landlord, umm...
Yes?
There's one favor I'd want to ask you.
You see...
Would it be possible for you
to wait longer for our rent?
At least until he gets discharged...
I see...
Well, you're having a hard time...
Alright, then. I'll give you
another month, then.
Thank you! That's a huge help for us!
Anything's on the house for you today.
Isn't it going to be hard for you
doing all the work by yourself?
If it's alright, I'll take over your
husband's share of work instead.
Oh no, you don't have to go that far helping me...
Hello there!
Oh, Yamashita-san! Welcome.
Will it be the usual?
Yeah... By the way, why are you there, Take-san?
I'm helping out as her husband's proxy.
It might cause everyone inconvenience
until my husband comes back,
but I'll keep the shop open and hope
to be of service to everyone.
There's no need to worry.
I did promise to give my full cooperation, after all.
Am I right, ma'am?
Uhh... Y-Yes...
I see...
I'll help out too, just tell me
if there's anything I can do.
Uhh... Yes...
Th-Thank you.
She loves her husband,
so she took full responsibility for
this shop until he gets discharged.
Am I right, ma'am?
Uhh... Y-Yes...
How obliging.
I was so moved seeing that,
so I ended up saying that I'll do anything to help.
That's the very reason I'm here today.
I'm helping out in place of her husband.
I see...
Well, then. Keep it up, ma'am!
O-Okay...
Thank you...
Mr. Landlord... Stop...
How is it, ma'am?
Am I satisfying you well in place of your husband?
No way... You're cruel!
I never asked you for such a thing!
Is that so?
It seems that your body is getting off well, though.
I'm glad to be of help.
To think that you're this kind of man...
And here I thought that you're a good person!
Of course, I want to help you and your husband.
But won't it be fine for me to have
some collateral on your debt?
Don't you want to protect this place?
The truth is, I only came here
right after paying your husband a visit.
Didn't you make a promise to him?
That you are going to protect
this shop while he's away...
And besides, he asked me for the same thing.
He said that he'll do anything so
I should wait longer for the rent.
It's going to be alright.
We'll keep this a secret from him.
O-Of course, we are!
Heave-ho!
Please wait, we're in the shop right now!
Isn't that a good thing?
No!
You're saying that,
but you're dripping wet and slippery down here.
Th-That's because of what you did earlier!
You're so sloppy inside!
It feels very good!
I'll push it even deeper!
You're clasping me so tightly! This is the best!
Alright, I'll start moving now!
There isn't any customer right now,
so it should be fine to let your voice out.
If you take my breasts out...
That's good to hear!
You're finally starting to moan in pleasure, huh?
Y-Your wrong...
How am I doing compared to your husband?
I'm pretty confident of myself, you know.
Doesn't my cock feel good?
There's no way...
This is bad! Mr. Landlord, wait...
Feel free to come anytime, ma'am!
It keeps on squeezing me like it's
telling me to hurry up and come!
You're wrong!
Your place down here badly wants to have more.
Does it mean that you never had enough yet?
That's not true!
M-Mr. Landlord, a customer...
Hey!
Please wait a little longer!
I am about to come!
H-Hurry up, or else...
I understand.
I'll come inside just like this!
Th-That would be...
Can't I?
Someone might find out what
we did if I shoot it outside!
Alright.
I-It's okay...
So hurry... Hurry up and come!
Welcome!
Huh? Take-san, why are you...
I'm working here as a temporary shopkeeper.
I see... And where is the madam?
I heard that her husband has been hospitalized.
She's having a break right now.
We'll come again.
Keep at it!
Yes, thank you for coming.
I'll be waiting for your next visit.
We can finally catch our breath.
Aren't you tired already, ma'am?
Isn't it about time for your break?
Y-You're right...
I think I'm a bit tired.
Welcome!
Huh? Are you by yourself, Take-san?
Is the madam away?
She's in the middle of something right now.
Her mouth... I mean hands, are full at the moment.
That's too bad.
I wanted to drink her coffee right now.
I'll bet that you're here for the lady, not the coffee.
Well, damn you're right!
I'll drop by again, then.
Yeah, sorry for the inconvenience.
It'll take a while before your
husband gets discharged.
It's going to be okay. I'll come
here every day to help, ma'am.
O-Okay...
That will be a huge help, Mr. Landlord...
Alright then! Let's toast for
Minami-san, our new coworker!
Cheers!
Thank you for having a welcome party
even when I'm only a part-timer.
Don't mind it, Minami-san.
That's right, the manager just
wanted a reason to drink.
He closes the shop down on any little
reason he sees for a drinking party.
Not all the time.
Minami-san
Can't Hold
Her Liquor
Minami-san
Can't Hold
Her Liquor
Minami-san
Can't Hold
Her Liquor
Minami-san, are you gonna keep this job for a while?
Yes.
I still have lots to learn but I'll do my best.
Manager, we laid Minami-san
down to sleep in the room.
I see...
You can both go home now.
Okay!
She's carefree and out cold.
Minami-san, I'll borrow your
smartphone for a bit.
I'll call your husband so he can
come and pick you up here.
These are amazing!
Daichi-san...
My boobs...
Feel tight...
Oh, just hold on.
I'm gonna unbutton your shirt.
Whoa, they're incredible!
M-Minami-san, your tits are too huge!
You only got hired on the spot at your interview
thanks to these bumpers.
That's why you should at least
let me taste them a little.
Minami-san, your nipples got hard.
Me too...
My package here got hard as well.
I-It's starting to feel tight so I'll take my pants off.
What is this thing?
Minami-san, your tits sure are soft.
You can just keep on sleeping.
I-I always wanted to try having a titjob!
You don't mind, do you?
M-My self-control already ran out!
This is bad...
It feels good!
I'm gonna come!
So bitter!
What was that?
O-Oh... It's something to help you sober up.
Seems that your husband's taking some time,
so you can keep sleeping just like that.
Okay...
Let's take these off to help you feel comfier.
I'm taking your pants off.
Oh... Your panties are all soaked up!
Shall we take them off as well?
Incoming call
Daichi-san
Mobile
Slide to Answer
Alright, I'm putting it in.
Huh?
Mr. Manager...
H-Huh?
Why...
You shouldn't put it inside me...
Daichi-san
Missed Call
It's alright.
It looks like your husband will be late.
That's why we should make each
other feel good while waiting.
Incoming call
Daichi-san
Mobile
Slide to Answer
My phone... It's Daichi-san...
Hello, Ryouko?
Oh, are you Minami-san's husband?
This is Koitami, her manager, speaking.
We held a welcome party for your wife earlier
and she got a little drunk.
Yes, she's now sleeping soundly in one of our rooms.
Nah... Don't worry about it.
Mr. Manager?
I'm sorry, I'm in the middle of
stocking up our inventory.
This is quite a strenuous job.
P-Please, wait for a moment.
I'll get this done in no time!
I'm gonna come, ma'am.
I'm sorry for calling when you're busy.
Umm...
Mr. Manager?
Hello... Can you hear me there?
I wonder if the call got cut off...
Mic test... Can you hear me?
I'll be on my way for now.
Oh... Yes, sure. You're just about to go right now?
Ah, yes. I'm sorry.
By the way, how long will it
take for you to get here?
About thirty minutes, I guess.
I'll be able to go for another
round of restocking, then.
Nah... That's totally fine with me.
Right... Yes.
Alright, we'll see you later.
Excuse me! It's me, Minami.
Huh, it's locked...
Oh... Hi there.
We have been waiting for you.
Oh... Is that you, Mr. Manager?
I'm sorry that my wife caused you trouble.
Oh no, that's nothing...
She's such a good drinking companion.
I'm looking forward to her drinking with us again.
Huh? It's you, Daichi-san!
So, you came to pick me up.
Thank you!
Yeah, shall we go home?
Alright then, we'll be excusing ourselves now.
I hope that you'll take care of
my wife next time as well.
Yes, it will be my pleasure.
That felt great, Daichi-san...
Let's do it one more time!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization