Snow Night Stories
Episode 1 - Thief
Shizuka?
You know, l would like to receive a bit of your time.
lt is quite cold tonight.
lt is snowing out front, my lord.
Oh please, will you warm my body with yours?
Lord?
lt maybe due to the cold.
But my energy is drained. Forgive me.
l will not!
You do not know for how long l have been
waiting for be with you tonight.
But, but you are...
lf you must insist, then try to make me in the mood.
What should l do?
Remember last time we were in bed,
and you told me a love story.
By listening to your stories, you can put me in the mood.
l will warm you as much as you desire.
But, if it's dull...
As a punishment for making me sleepy...
You will strip off your clothes,
and l'll leave you out in the snow
Would you still like to try?
Yes, l shall.
Hmm...
Here's tonight's love story.
ln a village far, far away, there lived
a couple who were very different in age.
lt sure is hot today.
Oh, wait!
We need to finish before there's still light.
lt's okay, forget about work.
The husband was so infatuated by his young wife.
That he could not help himself.
W, Wait...
lt's sweaty down there...
lt's sweaty.
lt's not just sweat.
My face is all sticky with your wet juices.
Don't do that.
l can't hold it any longer!
Yes...
Yes!
Good, so good...
Cumming!
What?!
But, due to the age difference,
her young body could not be satisfied by the husband.
When the market fair comes, the husband would
travel across the mountain.
To the neighboring town to sell their goods.
She has come to know that during market fair days, he would stay in town.
During these times, the wife has trouble
falling asleep by herself.
W, Who's there?
Don't make a sound. l know your husband's gone.
Give me your money.
Are you deaf? l said give me your money...
l, l don't have any money.
Don't lie to me.
Just hand it over.
My husband keeps all the money with him wherever he goes.
And l don't have any money, l swear.
You're lying. Tell me where you're hiding it.
l told you, my husband has it.
What are you doing?
Since you don't have any money,
l'll take you instead!
No, please stop! Please stop!
No, please stop, stop!
lf you resist, l'll kill you.
M, Mr. Thief...
lf you say that you'll take my body in exchange,
how much is it worth it for each shot?
One coin, for one shot.
Touch me down there.
Touch me there.
Yes...
l can't wait any more.
Here we go.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes...
More, more...
Yes!
lt has been a while since the thief has had fresh meat.
He repeatedly penetrated the wife with his boiling heat.
And he continued to take her until the morning.
The wife also forgot that he was a thief.
And started to want him because of what her
husband couldn't provide her
l'm going to cum!
Cumming!
l'm cumming, cumming...
l'm cumming!
l, l can't go anymore.
Are you done?
Yeah, that was plenty.
Well then...
What are you doing?
Well, you came five times.
So that's five coins.
Pay up, or l'll bite it off!
What are you doing? Please don't!
Then what happened?
Did the wife bite off his penis?
What makes you think that way?
The thief came to steal because he had no money, right?
He couldn't pay five coins.
Well now lord, l am sure it is normal to think that way.
What? Are you saying that it's not?
Well, it really did happen.
Damn it, l am getting frustrated.
Would you like to hear the rest of the story?
Then please, warm my body.
Only after that, will l...
For a female, your affections run deeply.
Lord...
Yes...
Yes, yes, yes...
Oh lord...
Y, yes...
Going to...Shizu...
Please give it to me!
lt's so hot...
What is it, Shizu?
l would like to be warmed some more.
You want to go again?
Oh lord...