Oh lord, please be more gentle...
Shizu, you are completely exposed.
Oh lord, please forgive me...
This is most embarrassing.
lt hurts...
Good...
C, Cumming...
So tell me something lord, did your wife speak
nonsense to you again today?
Those nights, especially, you come to me and
take me relentlessly.
Oh, she is from a noble family
No matter how much she curses at me, she
cannot go against me.
Shizu, are you mocking me?
l would never do such a thing. l simply
remembered a folk-tale.
Oh yes, then do, tell me.
Well then, l will tell you.
Here's tonight's love story.
Snow Night Stories
Episode 2 - Warrior Groper
There was a time during the war era.
A castle on a small island was being overtaken.
Without saying, it was a custom of the world.
But the failed family and followers of the country
were each killed.
Go after Princess Ogi. Find her as soon as possible!
l cannot allow it princess.
Please, you must resist.
Are you telling me to abandon them?
Are you going to waste the lives of the solders, who
sacrificed themselves so that you can escape?
lf you don't eat something, your body won't hold up.
l know this!
lt's good.
Shingo, please protect me.
Promise me that you'll never leave my side.
Of course, princess.
There she is! l see her!
Let's grab her, quickly!
Come on, let's go! Get her!
Don't let them get away.
Faster, they're getting away, come on!
They're over there! Hurry up!
Shingo!
Let's go back, princess.
You must be Princess Ogi.
Prepare yourself!
Servant, fall back!
Kill them!
Shingo!
Hurry, let's get this done.
Hey, it's a women.
Wait, don't kill her.
Oh, there you go!
Put me down! l said put me down!
Be quiet! Stop moving around, okay?
l know.
How dare you!
Stand down!
Your strong spirit is good, but it will end right now.
No, stop it!
Stop it right now!
lf you move around, it'll just hurt more!
Why can't you just lie still?
l can see the princess is still a virgin.
This is so good...
Tasty.
l can't hold it any longer.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
l'll make you a women right now.
l can't hold it either.
Someone!
Hey!
lt's useless to scream.
Here, lick my penis.
lnsolent fools.
Hey, don't use your teeth.
lf you bite it, l'll break your neck!
l'm going to cum!
Oh yeah, me too!
l'm cumming!
You peons! l'll kill all of you!
Help me!
Wait!
Princess Ogi?
Princess Ogi!
Shingo?
What's the matter?
Why do you look like that?
You're asking me what's the matter?
You, if you...
Because you didn't hurry and save me, this is
what happened to me!
Oh no, Princess Ogi!
The only thing left for me now is death.
Princess Ogi...
What a poor princess, indeed.
What happened after that?
Princess Ogi accepted Shingo's love for her,
and left the noble family
They began lives of their own in a far away land.
Shingo, isn't breakfast ready yet?
Yes, it's almost ready.
No matter what he does, he's so slow.
l can kind of understand Shingo's feelings.
But you my lord, has someone like me.
You sly fox...