Will you not be returning to your wife tonight?
l will not!
You are being childish again, my lord.
l do believe she dislikes you.
You, Shizu, were the first women to walk down that
male and female path.
She talks nonsense of you and
it was becoming frustrating to me.
So without thinking, l raised my hand at her
Your hand?
You know, you do not need to be concerned about this.
This time, l am sure that she has
definitely drawn the last straw.
And tell me, how is your wife?
She said she's going to return to her parents.
Oh lord.
l think you should go back to her tonight,
and make amends with her.
Are you telling me to apologize to her?
My lord, your wife is from a well respected, noble family.
lf you continue being stubborn, something may happen that you may never be able to take back.
What is that suppose to mean?
lt means that, you don't realize how much one's
means to you until they are gone.
There was a story about that.
Oh really? What kind of story?
Well then, let me tell you.
That will be tonight's love story.
Snow Night Stories
Episode 3 - Love Shamed Bride
A famous, well respected, feudal clan lord first laid
eyes on a princess from a clan in a dying country
And decided to take her for his bride.
l shall now make an announcement.
She has now arrived!
Oh! She's here!
Oh, she's pretty, like an angel.
lt's hard to believe her beauty could be something of this world.
l'm growing weary of waiting, princess!
What an unbelievable beauty
Chiho...
Lord...
Oh, that's, that's...
Your sweet juice is dripping down.
Oh lord, l'm embarrassed.
So pretty.
Chiho, are you ready for me?
Yes.
Oh, lord, be gentle...
Lord...
That good, so good, Chiho, Chiho!
l'm going to...
Chiho...
Chiho, l promise you that l'll make you very happy
Yes, lord, l promise l'll stay by your side as long as l live.
Chiho!
How is this, Chiho?
ls this not pretty?
Oh yes, lord. lt's so beautiful, l can't believe it
absolutely captivates me.
All of this is just for you.
Here, please, take this in your hands.
Yes!
Would you like to try it on?
Oh yes!
l would like to see also!
Why don't you hurry up, and go put it on.
May l ask you something?
After l try this kimono on,
would it be possible to walk outside in it?
What?
Who, who is it that you want to show it to?
l've told you before, that you only need
to dress nicely for me!
Yes, immediately.
Servant, please take this kimono from me.
You can change right here.
But lord, you understand there are people everywhere.
l don't care!
l'm sorry lord, please, l'll be right back, don't worry, l'll
be right back, l'm sorry please...
lf you go against me, then l'll undress you!
Chiho...
Lord, please stop...
Lord...
No, not in this place.
Wait!
You both, stay here and watch.
That's an order!
Please stop, l beg you.
Oh lord, l don't like to do it here!
No, please stop, people are watching!
So tell me, what don't you like?
We are a married couple, after all!
You belong only to... only to me.
You belong only to me!
No, please, lord...
Please stop...
You are pretty, Chiho.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
From your fingertips to the tip
of the toes of your feet...
Everything, everything is mine!
Please, please stop...
Well now, l'll give you my lewd saliva.
No, please stop...
l'm putting it in, Chiho...
That's good, that's good, Chiho!
lt hurts...
No, please stop already, it hurts, it hurts!
Please, no more...
Even though it's a little tight, l'm about to cum!
No...
Chiho, Chiho, l'm about to cum...
Chiho...
Chiho!
Chiho, Chiho!
Look, the hairpin l have ordered has come.
Wow...
What do you think?
Do you like it?
Yes.
Here, l'll put it in for you.
lt is pretty.
l must say you look so beautiful, Chiho!
Yes!
How is it? How's the hairpin the lord gave me?
Shinzaburo, l would like to share some of my
happiness with you. Would that be okay?
Thank you, but l'm happy as it is.
l haven't seen you look so happy
since the first time you came here.
There's a look of real joy in your eyes when l see you.
l love you.
l also, my lord.
Chiho...
Please stop, l don't like this.
But you know that l really adore you.
You are beautiful, Chiho.
Oh, that's such impurity please stop...
My lord, that's an impure area, it's obscene, no!
There's no obscene areas on your body.
No, no...
Everything, everything is all mine!
You are so pretty, Chiho...
Now, it looks like it's going to be your turn.
No, no...
No...
Now, lick my asshole!
l can't...
Lick it!
Oh yes, good, that feels so good!
Rub my penis at the same time!
Good, good, Chiho!
Now open your mouth!
Amazing...
Chiho, l'm, l'm...
Chiho, it's so good!
Good!
l'm about to cum!
Chiho!
The anniversary of Chiho's father's death had come.
And the feudal lord gave Chiho permission to visit his grave.
Father...
l can't take it anymore.
Lady Chiho.
Who is it?
Shinzaburo...
You have to be careful.
lf someone sees you here, you won't be let off easily.
l'm worried about your well being, and l just can't
simply stand by and do nothing anymore.
Please, come and run away with me,
and we'll get out of here right now!
l don't understand, what are you saying, Shinzaburo?
Lady Chiho...
From now on, everyday, things you don't want to do
are going to be forced upon you.
lndeed, he is a bad husband.
But at times, he shows me great kindness, you know
Surely, you're not telling me that
you still want to go back to a man like that?
Lady Chiho!
Let's hurry before someone else comes and sees us here.
Why, why have you left me?
Chiho...
l will never do anything that you do not like any more.
So please, please come back to me!
Chiho...
Chiho!
The two had ran off and disappeared.
He has lost his love, and realized for the first time, how precious she really was.
Lord?
Forgive me. Actually tonight, l will go to my wife.
Yes...