Toya..
It's hitting the top.
It's so rough...
A big, hot dick is pushing into me.
It's so good.
It's rubbing inside me.
And reaching so deep...
It's pouring into me.
How does this look?
The quality of the scenario and illustrations is about equal; that's sisters for you.
Rumi's scenario is really starting to get some life in it again.
Thank you very much.
I won't allow selling this in a region under police jurisdiction.
I'm still not sure about this game.
I suppose you're right.
I'll be sure to bring back Rumi.
As a producer...
this is also part of my job.
Okay!
I'm counting on you!
All right, then I'm done with work for today.
It's delicious!
I'd glad to hear that you like it.
I do.
This shop is one of my favorites.
Is it really okay for you to eat so much with your recording session coming up?
Leave it to me.
I'll make short work of this ramen.
Your dick is really hard, Toya-kun.
The juices are flowing from my pussy.
I don't want to stop.
My pussy is quivering.
What?!
Kanzaka-san...
What are you doing?
I'm in the middle of recording.
As the producer, I just thought I'd give you a helping hand.
Huh?
Help?
You certainly are amazingly talented,
but sooner or later you'll lose it.
There's a sure-fix for that, though.
What is it?
That would be...
real experience.
Real experience?
Stop it.
Just what are you after?
We're in the middle of recording, so don't forget about the microphone.
What?
Now, show me your true self.
No!
Save me, Director!
Director!
You can hear me, right?
Help me!
This is nice, Kanzaka-san.
This is some great acting, Akiho-chan.
I've been waiting for this.
No way.
You've got really cute boobs.
Don't say that.
Please... stop that.
Why?
We're getting some great material here.
Right, Director?
It's got really great feeling.
Keep it going for the rest of the scene.
For the rest of the scene?
Shinizu Miko...
Loses her virginity?!
Stop!
This can't be happening!
You protest, but look at how erect your nipple is.
It hurts!
You're more sensitive than I thought you'd be.
That's not true.
I never knew you were like this.
Hey, what're we paying you for? Get to work.
Don't touch me there!
What shouldn't I do?
Don't touch me...
You're getting wet.
No!
Don't...
Don't look at me there!
Your boobs are nothing special. , but what about here?
What's this?
This is also nothing special.
Don't get so close to it.
Hey, now... You're a virgin, but you're already this wet?
You're really perverted.
I'm just sensitive.
That's good thing.
No.
You have to be more saturated with wet, so you will make game users throughout Japan penis hard.
If you lick me down there...
Don't do it.
You're going to have something hard put in you, so you need to be wet enough.
Don't do that!
Oh...
I didn't expect it to be so tight.
It hurts.
Pull it out!
That's good.
You're giving a nice, natural, performance.
You're making good progress Kanzaka-san, keep it up.
No!
Th-This is strange.
Such naughty juices are spilling out of you.
Wait...
If you keep doing that...
Master is having so much fun.
It's so frustrating...
that master is doing things like that with another woman.
He's making her so happy.
My nipples are getting hard.
I want Master to torment me.
I'm already so wet.
Hurry up, Master.
Come and torment me.
Good.
It should be fine if you're this wet.
What are you going to do?
Here.
That hurts!
Come on, make some nice sounds for us.
No.
Don't!
That hurts!
I'm begging you, stop.
Fantastic.
I got a perfect recording of her virginity being taken.
No way.
My virginity was taken by a microphone...
Master, are you trying to bring up her?
Now then, let's get serious.
No! No!
Stop it!
That's some nice acting.
It's like hardcore reality.
It's not acting.
So big!
You can't put that inside me.
No!
It hurts!
Even though your virginity was taken by a microphone, your pussy's still tight.
T-Take it out.
I beg you.
Quit joking, we're just getting started.
It hurts.
Even though you are not an adult, the juice keeps coming out.
You have a really nice voice, but you need to try harder.
Don't cum inside me.
There's no line like that in the script.
Next up is a blow job scene.
Suck off that microphone.
No.
Hey now,
we're not playing around here.
Rather, it's a sales war.
That's not it.
T-That's not it.
Hey! Suck it more or we can't finish.
This is getting more and more weird.
No.
You're a real natural.
I'm going crazy.
She's fantastic.
Akiho-chan, hurry up and become Master's sex slave.
I'm going to cum.
Cum?!
Then when I finish, let's be sure to record you as I cum inside.
No!
No.
You can't.
Don't cum inside me!
This is really good stuff.
But none of our girls would ask the guy not to cum inside her.
I can feel it.
Semen is going inside me...
Soon enough, you won't be able to live without my dick.
This is my new sex slave.
Okay.
Rumi is in the living room.
That's right.
Let her go to the toilet just once.
Understood.
I'm going back to the office.
Take this.
What is it?
It's what you asked for.
You're a quick worker.
Then maybe I should go to one more place before I go to the office.
Take care.
Good job, Kanzaka-san.
There was a great, natural feel, to the lines this time, too.
The scenario of Pay Back Miko-chu is done?
I'm looking forward to it.
These are...
I'm sure the Manager will be surprised to see these pictures.
N-No...
What do you want?
Is that true?!
So, my sister's okay?
Yeah, she is fine, she also said that she wants to meet you at the comiket.
Comiket?
Yeah.
She's eager to see you.
The original artist, Sakurada Tongai who never showed up, will now have her debut.
You're producing some nice scenarios that'll really attract male buyers, it'd be a shame if they were never released.
N-Not at all.
I'll wait, so take time to think about it.
Okay.
So everyone, look at the debut of Tsurumiku's brand new product.
This is the booth for Pay Back Miko-chu.
We're distributing free trial DVDs.
It's a new studio, so who're the staff?
Scenario written by Katagiri Hinoka.
Original illustrations by Sakurada Tongai.
The heroine's voice actress is Fujinomori Akiho.
The theme song is by Planets.
Hey, did Katagiri Hinoka break up with her old development team?
If Sakurada Tongai's involved, then I have feeling it could be good.
Fujinomori Akiho is really good!
Planets' songs are pretty good, too.
Since you're all here, why don't you give this a go?
W-What is that?
This is an artificial vagina we're developing.
We'll be doing some field trials with it here today.
Shizuna... why are you here?
I have to expose my pussy in front of Shinzuna and a bunch of otaku.
Hey, can I try it?
Ah, yes.
Let me switch it on.
Shinzuna?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry, Izumi.
Why, Shizuna?
Now, go ahead.
It looks just like a real pussy.
Not that I've seen one in person.
It's really dirty when he wiggles it back and forth like that.
Can I put a finger in?
O-Of course. Use it as you like.
It's getting wet!
Yes.
Pressure, tilt, and temperature sensors work in harmony to detect stimulation,
then ammonia, saline and a special lotion are combined within
to produce a realistic emulation of the substances formed by actual vaginas.
A-Amazing.
It even secretes an odor.
No!
Don't play with my pussy!
W-Wait.
What are you doing?
It's even making noises...
And as I move my finger, it's getting even wetter.
This sex machine, Woman Hole, is breaking the industry's traditional production concepts.
Hey, you've had your fill, let me try.
I want to try it with my dick.
Y-You can't.
Of course you can't.
We can't have you doing that for free.
You have to buy Pay Back Miko-chu first realease limited edition pre-order volume for ten thousand yen.
Oh, okay! I'll buy it!
Thank you for buying.
Okay, here goes.
No!
I don't want to be fucked by those otaku!
It went in really easily.
Now, start moving.
Okay.
It's good.
Pull it out!
I'm going to cum.
Make sure to cum a lot inside, or she won't be satisfied.
Okay!
W-Wait.
What are you saying?
S-Stop it.
Not...
Not inside me!
I-I'm cuming.
Good, feel free to.
Okay.
No!
Holy shit.
It even urinates?
I'm up next.
Give me one!
Me too!
Thank you for buying.
I want to try, too!
And me!
Reserve one copy and you get five minutes of play.
You want 10 minutes? That's two copies.
And if you want 15, it's three copies.
This artificial vagina is incredible!
Stop already!
I want three!
I'll take four.
This is the end of our trial.
Hey, I still haven't had a go!
Hey!
What's your problem?!
I want you to try this now.
Who's that?
It's Pay Back Miko-chu cosplay.
This is the mystery "S" Sakurada Tongai-sensei, who has never before made a public appearance.
She is so cute and yet so sexy.
Hey, Kanzaka-san, what about my sister?
Right.
Rumi was working on the scenario 'til morning and she fell asleep.
I see.
Now, greet all of your fans, Tongai-sensei.
It's a pleasure to meet all of you. I'm Sakurada Tongai.
Please buy Tsurumiku's debut "Pay Back Miko-chu."
She is so cute~!
So cute!
Please buy-
What are you doing?!
Let's start the dark training of Tongai-sensei.
If you want a 5 minute hand job, then please reserve one copy of Pay Back Miko-chu.
If you want a blow job, that'll be two reservations.
If you want to use her pussy, it'll be three.
No!
Of course, you're not limited to using hands, dicks are fine too.
I want one!
I want two.
No...
I'll take three!
Stop it.
I'll be selling reservation tickets here.
Help me, Director!
I'm sorry, Yumi-chan.
No way.
No!
Stop it.
No...
Stop!
Hey, isn't this illegal?
You seem quite concerned, sir.
Let's ask our heroine.
No...
I have naked Rumi here.
Do you know what that means?
No!
It hurts.
It still isn't all in yet.
Here I go.
It hurts!
Take it out.
She looks like she's in pain.
Tongai-sensei is just shy, that's why she's so embarrassed.
Right, Sensei?
I'll show them all Rumi naked.
You can't do that.
Then accept it.
Wow.
Tongai-sensei's pussy is getting wet!
Don't be so rough.
As you can see, her pussy is hungry for cock.
No. Don't say that.
No!
Stop.
No.
Don't cum inside me!
I can feel it.
Your semen is flowing into my pussy!
So that's what it's like when they cum inside...
I understand.
You're such a slut, Tongai-sensei.
I'll stick it in from behind.
I've got 10 minutes of fun with your mouth. Let's enjoy it together!
No way.
I'm going to cum.
Me too.
No.
Please do it outside.
Cum outside.
I'm next.
I'll join in.
Stop it.
This is amazing, Kanzaka-san.
Today alone we've sold fifty thousand!
1 year later
Hey, it's me.
So what's up with Memory?
Ah, I see.
As I'd expect of you, Takatsuki.
From now on, for SPC...
actually, for me. do your best.
My Father is planning to introduce you to everyone at the press conference as the next president, Master.
Oh, I see.
Congratulations, Master.
Hurry up so we can switch places, Shizuna.
Please, jam your dick in me again, Master.
No.
One sex slave can have sex with the master for the whole day.
Right?
I didn't know you girls made an agreement like that.
I have everything that I want.
Money, women, status, prestige and power.
I'm cuming, Master.
Master!
I still have a lot more for you slaves.
Of course.
We can't live without you, Master!