Hurry... Up...
I'm kinda... Starting to feel good...
So... Rough... Your hot, thick dick... Pulling me apart...
This feels great!
It’s rubbing my insides!
It’s pushing all the way into me!
My insides... Are throbbing!
How was that cut?
As expected from you two sisters.
It fits perfectly with the scriptwriter’s and original author’s vision.
Rumi’s script was accepted and praised.
Thank you so much!
Unfortunately, we can’t do anything about it until we hear from the police.
In the present situation, we can’t let anyone know about this game.
I guess you’re right.
I promise I’ll bring Rumi back.
I am the producer after all.
It’s my job.
Thanks!
I really appreciate your help!
Well, I guess I’ll call it quits for today.
Subbed by SubDESU-H
Yume-Kui
– Erotic Game Production –
Kuzuha Yumi
Ramen
Yummy!
I’m glad you like it.
Yes!
I’ll add this place to my list of favorites.
It’s almost recording time.
Are you sure you’re okay eating so much?
You can trust me!
The ramen will help my performance.
Your dick... It’s so thick...
And naughty juice is dripping from my pussy...
It... Won’t... Stop...
My pussy... It’s throbbing.
What?
Kanzaka-san, what are you...? We’re in the middle of the recording session!
Just thought I’d give you a little help as your producer.
Wait... "Help” me?
I’ll admit, you are a genius voice actress.
In time, you’ll be a star.
But there’s one thing that’s holding you back.
What is it?
It is-
Real-life experience.
Real-life experience?
Stop it, please!
Wh-What are you planning to do?
We’re recording. Don’t forget the mic.
What?
Now. Show me your dedication.
No! Director, please help me!
Director! Director! You can hear me, can’t you? Help me!
Very nice, Kanzaka-san.
Akiko-chan, that acting is superb!
Hear that?
You can’t...
You’ve got cute boobs.
Don’t say...
No... Stop it... Please...
Why? You’re sounding a lot better now.
Right, director?
It really does sound great. Keep it up and let’s go for the final scene.
Eh...
The final... Scene...
It’s when she... Loses her virginity?
No! This can’t be happening!
Your mouth says no, but your nipples are really hard!
Ouch!
You’re more sensitive than I thought.
That’s not it... I’m shocked that you're that kind of person!
Come on, cry better and do your job right!
No! Not there!
Why not?
Don’t... Don’t touch...
You’re wet now.
No... No!
D-Don’t! No!
Don’t look! No!
Your boobs seem small, so how about down here?
Oh, it’s pretty small down here too.
Don’t look so closely.
Easy, easy. For a virgin, you’re awfully wet already.
You must have a really dirty mind.
I’m just sensitive, that’s all!
I’m sure you are.
No!
Get wetter and hornier and give every boy in Japan playing this game an instant hard-on.
My pussy... Don’t lick it...
It’s... Dirty...
A thicker thing will come in soon.
I have to get it ready.
Don’t touch it!
Wow, it’s tighter than it looks.
That hurts!
Don’t use your fingers!
Very nice.
That’s as authentic a voice as you can make.
Very nice, Kanzaka-san. I’m recording this.
No!
Not this... This is too weird!
You say you don’t like it, but you’re overflowing!
Well that’s... Because... I can’t help it.
Darling Master... I hope you’re... Enjoying yourself.
This is frustrating!
My Master is with... Another woman...
Like the way... The way we are...
My nipples are so firm.
I wish Master would tease them.
I’m so wet.
Master... Hurry.
Please tease my pussy for me.
Good.
If you’re that wet, you should be okay to go.
Eh?
What are you planning to do?
Well...
Ouch!
Come on, make some good noises for me.
No... Don’t... That hurts!
Please, stop this!
Okay, good. Got the sound of the hymen breaking perfectly.
N-No way...
I lost my virginity to a microphone?
Master... Are you leaving me for her?
Now, time for the real thing.
Eh? No! Stop it!
Great acting.
You get full points for your realism.
It’s not acting!
So big...
It won’t fit!
No!
That hurts!
Ah, even though her virginity was taken by a mic, she’s still a little tight.
T-Take it out. Please.
Stop joking.
The good stuff starts here.
It hurts!
You’re dripping enough juice for a big girl.
You’ve got a great crying voice so far.
But let’s keep going.
Not so... That...
Those lines aren’t in the script, are they?
We’re at the fellatio scene now.
Suck on the mic.
No.
Come on, this isn’t child’s play.
Though... You ARE a child.
No... I’m not!
See there? Suck harder. You’ve got good technique.
I can’t... Breathe...
You really are a genius actor.
I’m losing... My mind...
Beautiful. This girl is wonderful!
Akiko-chan, hurry. Become Master’s slave with me!
I’m about to cum.
“Cum”?
Well then, let’s record the cumming inside part last of all.
No... Don’t... Not inside!
Great acting.
But...!
There is no heroine who can stop a man from cumming inside her with that line.
It’s coming...
Semen... Coming inside...
I’ll make it so that you won't be able to live without my dick!
I’ve got a new sex slave.
Yes, Master.
Rumi’s in the living room.
So then...
Let’s put her in the bathroom on the first floor.
Understood, Master.
I’m going back to the office before going home.
Take this.
What is it?
What you asked for.
Oh? You work fast.
Then I’ll do another job before going back to the office.
Have a nice day, Master.
Kanzaka-san, good work.
I got some great recordings that time!
TL Note: The sign is some sort of mall: Possibly "Studio Department"
Huh? The job I asked for is already finished?
I can’t wait to see it.
What’s this...?
If your boss sees these, he’ll probably be shocked.
Y-You wouldn't...
Wh-What do you want from me?
A-Are you serious?
So onee-chan is doing well?
Yeah. You could say she’s doing well, but she wants to see you again at the comic mart, Yumi.
At the comic mart?
Well, it’s a bit difficult for her to see you right away.
Probably why she doesn’t want her work shown.
But let’s make a great game, Sakurada Tongai.
You’re really good at writing stories that boys would like.
It’s a shame you don’t let others see them.
W-Well, that’s... Not true.
I’ve prepared things. So think about it.
Okay.
Now, everyone, step right up!
Schools Brand’s newest project.
Two-Milk’s debut product!
“Pay Up, Miko-chi”!
We’re handing out free trial DVDs!
It’s a new brand, but the staff is all first-rate.
The story is by Katagiri Hiroka.
The pictures are by Sakurada Tongai.
The heroine VA is Fujinomori Akiko.
And Planets sings the theme song.
Hey, wasn’t the Katagiri Hiroka team disbanded?
If Sakurada Tongai is also involved I guess they got back together.
I really do love Fujinomori Akiko.
And Planets makes great music.
Gentlemen, while I have you all assembled here, go ahead and give this a test run as well.
Wh-What is this thing?
I-It’s our newly released m-masturbation sleeve.
We’re going to test it out on location today.
Eh? Shizuna? What are you doing here?
I-I’m going to have my ass and pussy violated by a bunch of porn geeks in front of Shizuna?!
Um... Can I test it out?
S-Sure.
Then I’ll turn on the switch.
Sh-Shizuna?
I’m sorry! I’m sorry, Izumi.
Shizuna... Why?
Well, touch it.
Wow! It feels like a real pussy.
Though I’ve never seen the real thing.
It’s wiggling around too. Awesome!
C-Can I put my finger in it?
Of... Of course you can. Use it however you want!
It’s wet?
Yes...
It has pressure and heat sensors in it, plus there's ammonia, lotion,
and other fluids inside that it can secrete when these sensors are engaged.
It feels like real love-juice is coming out of it.
Awesome!
It even smells!
N-No! Don’t smell my pussy!
W-Wait, what are you doing?
It... It also makes noises.
And it’s moving and getting wetter!
It’s a special sex machine that increases in intensity when stimulation increases!
Dude, awesome...
Hey, you’ve had enough. Give me a chance.
Hey! I wanna test my dick.
No way. Of course there’s absolutely no way.
Naturally, we cannot allow that for free.
You’ll have to buy invitation tickets to the release of “Pay Up, Miko-chi”’ for 10,000 yen.
I’ll buy one! Me!
Thank you for your patronage.
Then, here I go.
No!
I don’t want some geek’s dick in me!
It slid in all the way inside.
Well, move all you want.
I will!
Wow, this feels good!
Take out your dick!
I’m gonna cum.
Yes, cum inside as much as you want. The machine likes it that way.
I will!
W-Wait, what are you saying?
No, stop!
Not inside... Not inside!
I-I’m cumming...
Then cum until it’s all gone.
I will!
No!!
A-Awesome!
She even cums?
My turn next.
Thank you for your patronage.
I’ll buy one too!
Me too!
Each ticket purchase gets you five minutes.
If you want ten minutes, then buy two tickets.
If you want fifteen minutes, then buy three.
This is awesome!
I love this machine!
Just... Just stop it!
I’ll take three!
Give me four!
Well, the sleeve's location test is over.
But I didn’t get a chance to test it!
Hey!
What the fuck!
I’d like the rest of you to test this one.
Who’s that?
She’s dressed up as Pay-Up Miko!
She is the mysterious artist who has never before made a public appearance.
She is Sakurada Tongai.
Such a hot chick like this is into porn games?
Um, Kanzaka-san... Where’s my sister?
Apparently, she was working on the story until morning,
so she was going to take a nap before coming here.
Oh, really...
Well, Tongai-sensei, greet your fans.
Eh? Um! Hello, everyone, I’m Sakurada Tongai.
Please be sure to buy my new work, “Pay-Up, Miko-chi”.
She’s so cute!
If you’ll please...
What are you doing?
Well, now we’re going to have a hand shaking session.
Those who would like five minutes with her hand, you need to buy a ticket.
If you would like five minutes of mouth-time, buy two.
And if you would like her pussy, then buy three.
Naturally, you may shake hands with your dick if you wish.
Oh! I’ll take one!
I’ll take two.
And I’ll take three!
Stop it! Please stop it!
Okay! We’re selling the tickets over here.
Boss...
Please help me!
I’m sorry, Yumi-chan...
You can’t...
No! Stop it!
Don’t... No!
Hey, isn’t this a crime?
What a concerned customer you are.
Then let’s ask her directly.
No...
I have Rumi tied up in the back.
You understand the meaning of this, I assume.
No! That hurts!
That’s because I’m not lubed.
Here we go.
That hurts!
Um, I think you’re hurting her.
Tongai-sensei is just shy, that’s all.
Right, sensei?
I’m gonna throw a buck-naked Rumi into this crowd.
Don't do that...
Then accept it.
Awesome...
Tongai-sensei’s pussy... It’s gotten all wet.
You can’t...
Not so... So fast...
As you can see, Tongai-sensei’s dirty pussy wants your hard dicks.
No... Don’t look at me...
No... Stop...
No...
Please, just stop it!
It’s cumming... Cumming in my pussy!
This is... You can’t...
I understand. So you’re a slut, eh?
I’ll go from behind.
Here. I bought ten minutes with your mouth. Two at once should be fine.
No way...
I’m gonna cum already!
M-Me too!
No... Stop!
I-I’m losing my mind, nee-chan...
I’m up next.
I’ll join you!
Stop...
Th-This is amazing, Kanzaka-san!
Just today, we sold 50,000 tickets!
-1 year later-
Hi. It's me.
And, how’s Memories going?
Ah, I see.
Takatsuki, you are the one.
Work hard for SPC... I mean, for me, that is.
Father wants to introduce you to his associates with hopes of promoting you, Master.
I see.
Congratulations, Master!
Shizuna... Hurry up and switch with me...
Please.
Master, I want your dick.
Just once more, please put it in Akiko’s pussy, I beg you.
No, you don’t!
I get to have sex with Master all day!
We decided that-
I had no idea you girls fought so much over me.
Anything I want, I can get.
Money. Women. Power. Fame.
And authority.
I’m cumming.
Master!
I have much more work yet for you sex slaves.
Of course we’ll do it!
All of us...
We can't live without you, Master!