Sailor Kids here!
Die, Sailor Kids!
Green!
Blue!
Red!
Wonderful!
Do your best, Sailor Kids! Justice will definitely win!
Nee-chan! That hurts! Let go!
Hey! Don't act like a wimp when the Sailor Kids are in a fix!
Hey, Mutsuki. Go pick up the Sailor Kids tape for me!
Get it yourself.
You won't grant your big sister a favour?
SHOOT!!
Please wait!
Over here!
Don't just stand and watch! Save me!
Save you?
I want you to get that thing away from me!
This guy?
Hurry up and do it!
Sorry.
Go over there.
What's so scary about-
Thank you. I'm saved thanks to you.
N- No. It's not really a big deal.
You're a good person! I want us to be friends!
You have to tell me your name!
I- I'm Mutsuki. Sakamoto Mutsuki.
My name is Yunna.
Yunna?
That's right. But since everyone calls me Yunyun, so you should too.
Yunyun...
Yunyun
Paradise
You got lost?
Aiya. That's right.
I just moved here today.
That dog started chasing me then. After I ran away, I didn't know where I was.
I see.
Then let's go to the police box.
It's near my house, so I'll show you the way.
I'm in your care. Mutsuki, you're a good person!
H- Hey, Yunyun...
Yes?
Um, well...
What is it?
It- It's nothing...
This is my house.
The police box from here is...
Aiya!
What's wrong?
My house is over there!
Over here?
So we're next-door neighbours.
Yeah.
That's great! Being your neighbour makes me so happy!
I got it!
Thank you for everything today. I'll give you my thanks later.
You don't have to pay me back.
All right, Mutsuki! See you later!
Yunyun, huh...
Onii-chan!
Yayoi, I'm home.
Um. You see... Well, Mama made dinner since you weren't home.
Mama!
Mutsuki... Mama thought to make dinner, but...
Mama tried her best, but it didn't go too well.
I understand.
It's all right. Mama, you just sit here.
Okay.
Bro! You're back, aren't ya?
Hazuki! What are you wearing?!
Hm? This?
'Cause every time I squat my butt rips it apart.
A girl shouldn't loiter around like that!
Who cares?
Welcome back, Mutsuki. You got that tape?
I put it there.
Awesome!
Hey, Mutsuki! This Genki Sentai Sailor Kids is the TV series!
I asked for the film, you know!
They're all the same.
They're completely different!
Onii-chan, I'm hungry.
Hey, bro. Get me a new one.
I'm beat!
Yunyun!
So this is your room, huh?
What's wrong, coming at this hour?
I came to pay you back.
You don't have to pay me back.
No! If you don't let me pay you back, it'd bother me.
I get it! I get it, so be more quiet!
So you accept?
Y- Yeah.
Yay!
Yunyun, what are you doing?
This is my thanks.
Th- Thanks?
I'm giving myself to you.
Th- You can't do that!
Why not?
B- Because...
Because mama will scold us.
Then it'll be fine if she doesn't find out!
Yunyun, this is...
You don't want to do it with me?
That's not it...
Then there's no problem.
Mutsuki, your heart is beating fast.
But...
My heart is beating fast, too. We're the same.
Yeah.
Mutsuki.
Yunyun, that's...
Mutsuki... You're sensitive.
Yunyun, stop it.
This is totally weird.
Mutsuki, I'm doing more good stuff for you.
What are you doing?
Gosh!
Y- Yunyun! Hold on!
Mutsuki, yours is really stiff.
W- Well...
I'm taking it off.
I can't do anything if I don't.
I see.
Looks like I'll be doing it with Yunyun from here.
Yunyun!
Hey, Mutsuki.
It's your turn this time.
My turn?
Mutsuki, touch me.
Mutsuki, how is it?
It's soft.
And...
Don't stop. Harder. Do it even harder.
Mutsuki, you meanie!
Mutsuki, down there, too.
D- Down?
This. Spot. Here.
Mutsuki, touch it.
Mutsuki! Inside! Touch inside, too!
Yunyun, you're incredibly wet.
You made me wet.
Really?
I got really excited when I was licking yours.
And then, it...
Got really wet.
And warm.
Mutsuki, stir inside.
More!
L- Like this?
Yes. Yes, that's great.
Mutsuki, you can take off my clothes.
Okay.
Soon, you'll put yours here...
It'll go into my dirty place. Can you see?
Mutsuki, you can touch.
Gently!
More!
Like this?
Stir it harder!
Yu-
Yunyun!
Huh?
No. Not there.
Here.
Yeah.
It went in...
Mutsuki is inside my dirty place...
There's plenty of you inside me.
Yunyun...
Mutsuki, move.
Yunyun!
Mutsuki, how is it?
It feels... It feels really good.
Me too! It feels good!
It feels good!
Mutsuki!
Yunyun!
Yunyun! I... I can't...
It's okay. You can come.
I'm coming with you!
Mutsuki!
C- Co- Come!
Yunyun!
Mutsuki, I love you.
Hey! How long do you intend to sleep?
I'm coming in!
I'm awake! I'm awake! That's enough! Just wait downstairs!
What's with the yelling? Hurry up and fix us breakfast!
Was... that a dream?
Good morning!
Yunyun...
All right! Keep it down!
Okay. Well then, let me introduce a transfer student to everyone.
A transfer student?
Looking forward to see her!
Come in!
Cute!
She's the new transfer student-
Yunyun!
Mutsuki!
Yay!
Yunyun!
Mutsuki! Mutsuki! Mutsuki!
Ending up in the same class is like a dream!
Okay, Mutsuki. Open wide!
Yunyun, don't do stuff like that again.
Stuff like what?
Like hugging me so suddenly.
Why not?
Because... it's embarrassing.
You and I are lovers, so there's nothing to be embarrassed about!
Lovers?! Yunyun!
You don't want to be my lover?
Th- That's not the issue!
Hey, you two!
Do you not know what this place is?
This place belongs to the granddaughter of the board chairman, Inukai Sachiko-sama!
It's not a place for pipsqueaks like you.
Pipsqueak?!
Um, I'm sorry!
An honest mistake! She's also a new transfer student and...
Go elsewhere.
No!
We should eat here with everybody!
Keeping this lovely place to yourself is unfair!
Yunyun, let's go somewhere else.
I think this place is good!
Miss pipsqueak, it would be a good idea to listen to your boyfriend.
Who would listen to a middle-aged woman like you?!
Middle...
...aged...
...woman?
I'd feel bad for the middle-aged; you're an old hag!
O- Old...
...hag...
Don't say selfish things. Let's go somewhere else, okay?
I didn't say anything selfish! Why are you on this old hag's side?
Yunyun!
Mu-
Mutsuki, you...
...idiot!
I'm- I'm sorry!
Yunyun!
Mizumaru.
Investigate those two, please. Be quick about it.
Yes, Miss.
Yunyun, are you still angry?
I'm not angry.
Yunyun, where are you going?
I'm obviously going home.
This is the wrong way, though.
I have something to do. It has nothing to do with you.
And, you want to get lost again?
I have to go home and fix dinner. Just finish what you have to do.
Sorry. I said too much.
You don't have to apologise.
It- It was my fault.
It was my fault during lunch, too.
I knew I was selfish, yet I...
Yunyun...
No one... No one would love a girl like me.
But... But just to you... Just for the person I love...
I wanted you to love me.
Yunyun, I'm sorry.
I didn't think you were that serious about your feelings.
You wouldn't have done that if you didn't love me.
Goodbye, Mutsuki!
Wait!
I don't know if I love you or simply just like you, but...
I definitely don't want to see you sad.
I want us to be together if possible.
And if it turns out that my feelings are love...
I like you, Yunyun.
Really?
Really.
Then show me proof.
Proof?
Right away, right here... do it.
D- Do it?
I want you to show me your feelings right now.
N- No way! This place is no good!
What's wrong? Are you still sad?
That's not it.
This time, I'll kiss you.
Yunyun...
Slow down a bit!
St- Stop it. If you do any more...
I'll come!
Mutsuki, this time you touch me.
You got so...
Yunyun.
I can't wait any longer, Mutsuki.
Mutsuki!
Yunyun! Yunyun!
My pussy... My pussy feels great.
My dirty place is soaked!
Tell me! Tell me you love me!
I love you, Yunyun.
More! Tell me more!
I love you so very much!
Fill me... Fill me with your love!
Yunyun!
Mutsuki!
With Yunyun, I...
Yunyun...
You called?
I've come again!
Yunyun!
Mutsuki!
Presented by Killer Maid
http://www.killer-maid.net/
Translator:
Dark Master Schmidt
ohima nara asonde yo
Let's play if you're free,
naishoubanashi shiyou yo
whispering secrets to each other.
Timer:
Dark Master Schmidt
kuyokuyo shitte itte atte
Talking about our worries.
Typesetter:
Dark Master Schmidt
hajimaranai
Don't start now!
koukai nanka sasenai
I won't make you regret it.
Quality Checker:
Dark Master Schmidt
asobi nara makashite yo
Leave the playing to me.
koi no nazo toki nanka
The mystery of love or something like that.
Encoder:
Dark Master Schmidt
asameshi mae
Just before breakfast!
futari de suriru shiyou
Let's do something thrilling together...
dare ni mo iwanai
without telling anyone about it.
dakara yuuwaku shite ne
So let's give in to our desires.
yuuki dashite
Have courage.
genki ni EVERY DAY
In full spirits every day!
daiji na mono ha hitotsu
There's only one important thing.
suteki ni ai o
Keep this wonderful love...
kanjite mama
always in you.