Volume  5
Yuuwaku
Temptation
All done!
Here, look.
See? Aren't you so very cute?
When you're like this,
you look just like a girl, Akira.
Do you want to be even cuter?
Then, let's try some
other clothes. Okay?
A prettier ribbon
would be better, Sis!
Yes, yes, I understand.
Really! You messed up
at the same place again!
Well, I don't like the piano...
Don't talk back to me!
When I was your age, I could play!
So, there's no reason why
you can't play it too, Akira!
Now, again!
Just relax.
See, you can do it. Good boy.
Sis!
Akira, stop that!
I said quit it!
Sis!
I told you to stop...
Hey, Akira, did you know?
White lilies are the
symbol of Mary's virginity.
What is "virginity"?
I guess you wouldn't know yet, Akira.
It means that
you aren't dirtied by anything.
That's like you, Sis.
Sis!
So, what's a girls' school like?
What's it like?
It's fun. But why?
I thought if there were only girls,
then it'd be really annoying.
No, it's not like that at all.
You've grown, Akira.
I'm almost taller than you now.
Are you happy?
I don't know.
Sister...
S-Sis!
I won't... tell anyone.
Chapter Two
#LAMONAE @ RIZON presents...
Ripping etc. by Robink
Script meddling by ics-
Special thanks: CharlieB & kurochocho
Give it to me...
I'm... I'm coming.
I'm coming!
No one is here to take your call.
Please leave your name,
number and message at the tone.
Amemiya, who are you
sleeping with tonight?
What are you thinking about?
Is it your sister again?
You're still such a spoiled little boy.
But I like that part of you, too.
So thirsty...
Sorry I'm so late!
Are you mad?
I said I'm sorry!
You aren't going to say you won't
lend me your notes, are you?
That'd be too cruel!
I'm begging you! Please help me!
This is the library, you know.
Thank you!
Now that test the day after
tomorrow will be a breeze!
The rental fee is,
you owe me a meal.
Sure! That's cheap!
Hey, what is it?
Weren't you wearing
that outfit yesterday?
Huh?
Oh, so that's it...
Boy, do you check up on things!
But I DID change my underwear.
The person I was
with last night wasn't him.
Not Amemiya?
It was a guy from work.
Is that so?
What's with that face?
It's okay. Who cares?
But, Yoshiko, you were saying
how much you liked Amemiya.
He's sleeping around, too!
It doesn't bother you,
even though you like him?
I understand what you're
trying to say, Kaname...
...but it doesn't mean anything even
if you say "I love you" to him.
To me, he's the ultimate sex friend.
With him, that's enough for me.
It's good to worry
about others and all, but...
The other day, at the
harbor park, I saw Tatsuro...
Huh? Don't tell me
you already knew?!
What are you waiting for?
Don't you care?
I didn't know anything.
Like a fool,
I just believed that he loved me.
Just steal him back!
It's okay. I don't want him anymore.
Kaname!
Yes, this is Leona.
How is it over there?
What? It's already that chilly?
How awful! Don't catch a cold!
Well, we can't just
chat on an international call.
I know it's sudden,
but I want you to go to Rome...
though it'll delay your
homecoming even further.
I'm so sorry. I'll fax you the details.
Well, talk to you later.
Say, Amemiya...
You know my friend,
Kaname, don't you?
Yeah.
She's being cheated on.
It's pretty sad.
Kaname is just too straight-laced.
She's the type who thinks you can't
have sex unless you love each other.
Makes you laugh, doesn't it?
And you're different?
It depends on who it is.
What about you, Amemiya?
Sex doesn't need a reason.
That's true.
And so, Amemiya,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Can we make
it your place tonight?
Why?
Because...
it's always been somewhere else!
I want to see your place.
All right?
Wait! Weren't you taking me home?
If you please...
What is this?! You jerk!
Message number one.
This is Leona.
Because of a sudden
schedule change...
your sister's
homecoming will be delayed.
It was to going be
next week, but I'm sorry.
End of message.
Sis, how long are you
going to leave me by myself?
Sis...
I won't... tell anyone.
S... Sis...
I won't tell anyone.
In exchange,
you'll do whatever I say.
Understand?
That's it. You're a good boy.
All done. Now open your eyes.
See?
You're so cute! Just like a girl.
How do you feel, Akira?
It doesn't seem like me.
Doesn't it bring back memories?
When we were little,
we used to play like this a lot.
Did you forget?
I remember.
Akira, you were really cute back then.
But you're even cuter now.
And you're very beautiful.
I look like her.
I wish I had a wig.
Sis...
Akira, you'd look so nice if
you had your ears pierced.
Should I pierce them for you?
T-That's okay!
S-Stop it, Sis!
You're not supposed to move.
You're my plaything now.
Why don't we change
the look of your hair, too?
A white lily...
White looks good on you, Akira.
You once said a white lily
is a symbol of virginity.
That's right.
I understand the meaning now.
Are you trying to say that
you've become an adult?
Akira, look this way.
You're so very beautiful.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give you my first kiss.
After all, you're so beautiful,
Akira. I really love you.
Let's play from now on.
But, this is a secret
just between the two of us.
Promise!
Sis...
Really, can you believe that attitude?
All I said was that I
wanted to see his place.
Then he pushes me in a taxi,
and all of a sudden, it's "See ya!"
Even though it's purely physical...
I think he should be able to
grant me a little favor like that!
Amemiya called later or anything?
Like he would!
He's never contacted me!
Not even once.
Not even once?
He wouldn't dream
of doing such a thing.
He's never had the ability to be
tactful or to care about anyone!
Like he would!
He's never contacted me! Not even once.
He's never had the ability to be
tactful or to care about anyone!
No one is here to take your call.
Please leave your name and number...
I want to see him.
Amemiya!
Wait!
I've thought only of you since then.
I've missed you this whole time.
I like you...
I love you, so...
I told you,
I don't feel anything for you.
If you want to get laid, then say so.
I didn't mean that!
It's so nice!
It seems simple dresses
look better on you, Akira.
Sis...
What?
Let's stop all this.
You've made a plaything
of me for a whole year!
Shame on you!
What are you saying?
Toys are something you play
with until you're bored of them.
But...
You're getting so beautiful that
you're afraid of yourself, aren't you?
I'm afraid, but it's
not because I'm beautiful.
I'm afraid, because I look more
and more like you every day!
That makes me happy.
Play with me more.
You can't be bored with me yet...
Screw me.
I won't say "I love you" anymore.
Just your body is fine!
I don't need your heart, so...
You don't need my heart?
I don't need it.
Come in.
I just want to feel your presence.
It doesn't have to be your heart.
Your body is enough.
I want you to have sex
with me for a long time.
Until it ends,
you'll be mine and mine alone.
Please...
I want it...
So... so good...
I'm...
going to come...
I'm coming!
Amemiya...
That girl... looks like Amemiya...
No one is here to take your call.
Please leave your name, number
and message at the tone.
Akira, how have you been?
Sis!
Sis, it's me!
Oh, so you were home!
S-Sorry!
Listen. It seems I may be
home sometime in December.
I'll be able to see you soon, Akira.
Really?!
His sister?
I can't wait to see you, Sis!
Sis!?
That person...
My soul is hers alone.
... is coming home.
Part 3
That person...
It seems your sister's
homecoming is on Christmas Eve.
... is coming home.
Sister!
Soon, I'll be able
to hear you call my name.
Volume 6
Yuuwaku
Temptation
AKIRA
Chapter 3