All done.
You look very beautiful
Do you like it? Yes.
Akira seems like a girl. Yes.
Would you like to wear a new dress? Yes.
I have one that would look nice on you
I would another beautiful one
Ok Akira
Not like that. You keep making a mistake with the same note!
I try, but I just can't do it
I don't want to hear excuses
I could do it at your age
So you must learn play it, Akira
Try again.
Good Akira.
See? You play better.
Little sister!
Akira, stop!
Little sister
I said shut up.
I wanna play with you
Why are you so mean?
What a nice flower Akira
Did you know that the White Lily is the symbol of purity?
Well...
Purity is a thing
Which has not been touched by anyone
Then...
One like you
Sister!
Would you tell me about the girl's school?
It's just like the other school
Why do you ask?
So there is no difference?
No difference
Akira
Do you know that you are growing?
I know. You are nearly as tall as me.
Are you happy?
I don't know.
Little sister...
Be quiet
I will not tell anyone.
Countdown:
Akira Complex
Chapter 2
I want it.
If you would like to leave a message
Begin speaking after the tone.
Who are you making
love with tonight?
What're you thinking?
Your sister again?
You can't really
forget her.
Empty...
Sorry Kanape if I am late
Unfortunately I gotta hitchhike
You don't believe me?
Listen, I have a favor to ask you. Can you lend me your history notes?
I need them for the test
I'll be in trouble if you don't let me, please.
All right.
Thank you!
You are a true friend.
Just don't raise your voice.
Ok, I don't know how to thank you
Do you have any ideas?
Well, one of these nights you can buy me dinner.
All right.
I promise.
Out of my curiosity. You're wearing the same dress as yesterday. Aren't you?
Shit. You don't miss anything.
Yesterday I met a guy
And the same night I made love with him.
I thought you were with Akira.
When I find an occasion like that, I don't pass it up.
I see.
Why do you look like that?
Are you surprised?
He has sex with other people
So...
Listen...
I must tell you something
Yesterday, at the park I saw Tetsuro there.
Well
He was having sex with someone.
What?! I tell you a thing like that and you don't even react!
I think
That sounds absurd.
I thought he loved me.
Remember, don't ever trust men.
However you did the right thing to tell me this Yoshiko.
I'm sorry.
Hi. I'm Leonard.
How are you?
What?
Isn't it cold today?
Well, you should dress warmer
With your job as a model, you can't allow yourself to suffer.
Oh, I wanted to tell you
That for the moment you'll have to delay your return because they want you to do a modeling Job in Rome
Yes, I'll send you all the information by fax
All right. See you later.
Well.. Akira.
Do you know my friend Kanape?
Yes, I know her.
I met her yesterday
She is very depressed
Because her boyfriend cheated on her
She's so sad
She says that she can't have sex
Unless she falls in love.
She is a strange girl, isn't she?
Are you any different?
Well I can have sex with someone
Without any problem
Well. I don't need a reson to make love.
Right.
Well now it's time to think
About what we should do after dinner
I wanna ask you something
Why don't we stay at your home tonight?
Why?
We've had sex in so many places
But one time
I'd like to do it in your home.
What are you doing?
Aren't you coming? No.
I hate you Akira!
First message.
Hi, this is Leonard
I called to tell you that because of a lot work
Your sister will be home a little late.
Sorry for the trouble.
End message.
Sister...
I must wait again to see you, why?
I don't tell this to anyone
I don't tell this to anyone.
Sister...
You must promise to do all that I ask of you
Do you promise?
Nice, Akira.
And now open your eyes.
Let me see
They are very nice
You look like a girl.
I like you dressed like that.
I... I don't recognize myself.
What are you saying?
When you were little we always played.
Have you forgotten this?
No, little sister.
When you were little, you were very beautiful.
And now that you are grown
I like you even more
Now I am like you, right?
I still haven't finished.
What are you planning to do?
I want only to make two little pierces on your lobes
for putting the earrings on your ears.
I'm afraid that will hurt me.
Come one Akira, stop complaining.
And to make you more beautiful, one last touch.
A white lily.
Now you are perfect.
I remember that one day, you told me that a white lily is a symbol of purity.
Yes, it's true.
Now I understand the meaning.
Sure, Akira
Akira
Now turn around
You are so beautiful
I want to give you a kiss
This is the first kiss I give you
But from now on
I'll give you many more
and we can play funny games
It will be our little secret.
Little sister..
You know... I asked him to take me
To his home. I've never been there.
He asked me to call a taxi and go out alone.
It ruined my night
I don't understand his reaction. I don't ask him anything unreasonable, right?
Call to make an excuse?
Nah.. A guy like him does not do thing like that
He never explains himself?
Well
You have to understand he is a guy who is
Empty. Without a heart.
Nah.. A guy like him doesn not do thing like that
Well
You have to understand he is a guy who is
Empty. Without a heart.
This is an answering machine
If you would like to leave a message, begin speaking after the tone.
I must see you
Akira
I need to speak with you!
I wanna tell you that
Ever since we made love
I love you, Akira
You know that I don't want to hear these things
I go with women to have sex.
But I didn't come here to talk to you about sex!
See how nice you look in that dress?
Akira, it looks very good on you.
Yes.
I'm grown up.
I don't like wearing this dress anymore.
Even if only as a game
Why do you say this?
Well, I'm not bored yet.
I...
I don't like seems similar to you
Which should not be so sad.
What are you saying Akira?
I want to continue playing with you until you want it.
It's me!
Please let me come in!
I promise I will never say
Are you sure you won't break that promise?
Yes.
Ok, come in.
It is not important
That you don't love me.
I just need your body
To feel inside of me
When I make love with you, I feel an incredible snesation. Take me.
I like it
Yes!
More!
It was so good.
The girl in the photo looks like you.
This is an answering machine
Jf you would like to leave a message
Begin speaking after the tone.
Hi Akira, it's me.
Sister!
Sister, how are you?
I'm fine, and you?
I'm fine too.
I wanted to tell you
That I'm coming back in a few weeks.
Nice, I'll wait for you.
What? Your sister?
I also want
To stay with you, little sister.
Kanape
Did you know that Yoshiko is having a party at her home on Xmas?
I didn't know.
Yes, it seems she is inviting
Lots of people
There will be lots of boys
Your coming, right?
No, sorry.
No? Why not?
Maybe she already has a date with some boy
No..
Probably not.
Your sister should be
Coming back on Xmas.
Akira..
I would like so much to stay with you.
My heart is only for one person.
PRESENTED BY HENTAI-FANTASIA @ IRC.ANIVERSE.COM