Hentai-Fantasia presents
Countdown
Akira Complex
Volume 3
A special "Momo" for a Merry Xmas.
I'm going to organize a beautiful party at my home before Xmas.
I have invited a lot of people.
Obviously, I wish you can come too, Kanape.
Did you hear me? I was telling you that you can't miss my party.
Well... I...
Do you have any appointment?
You hope that Akira will invite you...
Well You really fall in love with him.
Yes, it's true. I love him...
Kanape...
Don't make any illusions.
Akira has promised that he will spend Xmas with you?
No, but I hope anyways...
I know him very well.
Kanape...
Because I spent it with him before. Akira is not a guy you can count on.
He's do dry and egoistic. If you want he invited you... you rather to spend Xmas alone.
I know...
But it's not important...
Do you love hime ultil this point?
Kanape... I admire you.
But surely I don't envy you.
Take this.
Thanks.
Then tomorrow... will come back our sister?
Yes...
Will she arrive at the airport at 16?
Yes, of course.
So... on Xmas eve you'll stay with her.
Akira, you are so beautiful... I like you so much.
Sister...
I wish to see you soon.
Sister!
Akira...
It's Kanape.
Tomorrow is Xmas eve... I wish to spend it with you...
No, I can't.
I need to see you...
Just only few minutes...
Is it possible?
No.
Sister...
You're so dry and egoistic... A-ki-ra...
Passenger travelling from paris with flight number az-708 are boarding at the gates 6.
Sister!
I'm happy to see you.
Sister...
Hi... Akira.
I see you good.
Merry Xmas.
Finally... I see you again. I thought about you so much while I was out.
You couldn't even imagine how much I miss you.
Sister...
Oh... this is your brother...
Then you were right when you talked about him. He's really nice as you told me.
Akira...
This is my personal assistant. Is my make-up artist.
Asu Chijajacha. Nice to meet you Akira.
Should we have a glass for the wine?
Kanape.
What are you doing here?
I thought that you should be alone.
Listen, why don't you come to my party?
Really?
Did he asked you a thing like this? Do tou remember the name of that photographer?
I think it's luis.
Yes, it's right. I remember that he tried with all the girls... he was a pervert.
Yes.
One time with an excuse he touched my tits.
Well, you lost up on some occasions, because he liked you. It could be your fortune. He's the most famous photographer of Paris.
If to become a model require to have sex with a ugly guy, then I give up!
You kept it the same.
Sister... look...
Yes...
You have put some fresh flowers, it's a sweet thought.
White lilies.
I think that you have a lot of things to tell. Meanwhile I'll go to prepare dinner.
No, wait. I wanna help you.
Well Akira... don't be so sad.
I like this holidays so much, it's a nice chance to know new people. Don't you think so?
Are you bored Kanape?
What?
You are here alone, and don't want to talk with anyone.
I'm sorry.
I know who are you thinking.
Kanape... It's a waste of time to suffer a lot for a guy like that.
I was not thinking about him.
But... today is Xmas, we must enjoy! Come on!
Look! There are so many nice guys, there is only the embarassment of choice.
Do you remember that famous italian make-up gay?
He made lots of nice compliments to all the models.
Yes it's true.
That was funny.
And then we caught hime repeating the same things to all the models. I remember how many laughs we did taht day. I think taht he confided his secret to me that he does make-up for women only because it's his job but his trust of passion was to do make-up to himself.
Really?
Sure. Well with his face is hard to have any changes on it.
Instead if we do make-up to Akira...
He'll become more beautiful.
That's right, Akira.
Then, we can try to do make-up to Akira.
Akira, we'll make you become beautiful. You have some features so delicate.
No... don't...
Come on.
Don't be so shy.
But...
Akira...
Sister...
Why...?
Why do you do this?
It had to be our little secret.
You had promise.
Wow! Akira you are so beautiful!
Why don't we try to make him to wear a dress... what do you think?
Sister, do you remember the promise?
Akira.
Wear this dress.
Sister...
What are you doing?
I am leaving...
Kanape...
Sorry...
I miss you so much Akira...
You look so nice Akira!
It's incredible you really look like a woman.
Well you don't see him with the wig yet. Now I show you.
I wear it myself.
Oh my god, you are like your sister.
You're beautiful... Akira.
Sister...
Why don't you have to respect our promise?
Eh? What's promise you are talking about?
Leave me!
Open this door! Open!
Akira, what are you doing?
You didn't keep our promise...
...because it's not important to you.
Leave me.
You never ever loved anybody.
Akira...
On the contrary... I have always loved you more than anything else.
Please...
Sorry...
Akira! Wait!
Sister, I have always believed in you.
You were my idol.
I thought you loved me.
I always loved you.
But...
I was wrong.
Sister...
Akira...
Akira.
I believed to stay with you...
Now that I'm here...
...the rest doesn't interest me. Amamija.
My name.
Use my name.
My real name is Akira.
From now on... I want that you call me so.
A-ki-ra.
I love you.
I'll call you that.
Akira...
Yes...
Visit us: #Hentai-Fantasia at irc.aniverse.com