Model Planet for Tourists
18th Master Planned City
Also known as...
Famous Trick History
Hooligan Boy
Kaede! Water the storefront, will you?
Kaede!
Yes!
You're becoming such a babe! Have
you got a man in your life right now?
Stop it, Gen-san. Are you
drunk already?
Yo! Kaede-chan!
Bye-bye!
Goodbye!
Kaede!
Boss!
It's only Mai.
Not here in the street.
Then, let's go get a hotel room.
No! Stop!
No?! What, no?
Your body's saying something different.
We interrupt this program,
so that we may bring you
this important emergency
announcement.
Before daybreak today,
an unidentified giant creature appeared in the 808th district.
Currently, this creature is
heading toward E-D-O,
in the direction of Edo castle.
According to the announcement by the magistrate's office,
the culprit is demanding
the position of shogun.
What the hell is that?!
Also, if he doesn't get his wish granted
What the hell?!
A terrorist attack by bomb
has been promised.
There is still no word from Shogunate personnel.
To the common populace!
Now is the time for you to surrender
to this super genius!
And now for the second
phase of my plan.
Kaede! You are so hot!
No!
How about this!
No, please. Forgive me!
No! Not yet!
It's cold!
Don't you like it because it's so cold?
Oh, my God!
What?!
Boss, there's kinda some big trouble.
Kuma!
You idiot!
You interrupted me at a very
important moment!
This one is very fresh!
A fresh one, you idiot!
The big trouble will be your medical
bill about ten seconds from now!
Now! Prepare yourself!
Stop! Please, wait a second!
Fuck you! Since I know
you're also gay,
you should've been more
considerate of my situation!
How do you know about that?!
Kuma! I already know
that you're doing it
with Sakichi of the Comet
Terraced Houses!
And furthermore, I heard that your
body has been transformed
for cybernetic orgasms, or whatever,
by those visiting Europeans!
How embarrassing! He promised me
that it would be our little secret.
Are you a school girl or something?
What?!
Boss!
Kaede!
What's happening?!
Boss! Help me!
Kaede!
What the hell was that?!
That's it! It's the one!
That thing has been kidnapping
every young girl around here!
What the hell?!
What?!
Boss! It seems like that
thing is the culprit
who's been kidnapping young girls!
That bastard! And on top of that,
it took my prey as well!
Kuma! Are you ready to arrest it?!
Red alert! Red alert! Everyone take
first degree battle positions!
From now on, all gates of
the castle will be closed!
Activating barrier generator!
Deploying headquarter
defensive blockades!
The fifth guard line barrier
is about to be broken!
It's continuing! It's closing in!
Panic, everybody. Go panic!
You can't do a thing about it!
Damn, that was a terrible experience!
Kuma, where are you?
Hey, Kuma? Where did you go?!
Hey, this isn't too bad.
Moron! What are you doing?
Just kidding, boss. The mere sight of
a woman's thighs doesn't arouse me.
What do you mean, "mere?"
Boss, don't be so hard on me!
Hey, Kuma! How long
are you going to rest?
We must start hunting now!
As you can see, I couldn't move
even if I wanted to.
Oh, I understand perfectly.
I feel sorry for you.
This is...
Didn't you say just recently
that you'd like me to
introduce you to a promising
young man?
Wow! Thank you!
What an idiot!
Stop fooling around, Boss. Let's go!
You got it! What?
Switch the castle tower to complete
armored condition!
Open all cannons!
Interlock all cannons!
Prepare for automatic shooting!
The target is about to come
into cannon range!
Fire!
Did we get it?
No, Sir! It's still alive!
No sign of any damage!
What's that?
Hey! You punk! Give Kaede back!
Damn it! One more time!
Right on!
Anyway boss, are you sure there's
something we can do?
Why do you say that
at a time like this?
Don't you know?
See the teacup that thing is holding?
It's full of nitroglycerin.
Say what?!
Kaede is...
Kaede is being attacked!
What?! Hey, she's mine!
Oh, you're awake!
A kid?
Kid? So, I'm a kid...
No! Please...
Please, don't look.
Kaede!
Oh, I see. You two have
a relationship.
In that case, let me show
you some more.
No, not that!
Kaede...
Hey, he kinda has a cute face.
Wow! Looks delicious!
Kuma! You're finally awake!
You're so noisy, Mr. Mechanical Man!
I've reset your dangerous body.
So, please be quiet.
Now, it's your turn.
Thank you for waiting.
Do you know what this is?
You'll find out very soon.
Oh! You're already wet.
You are so naughty.
You're just a kid!
Not again.
For those who aren't educated,
it's all the same!
Why the hell does age matter?
My mind more than compensates
for it! And look at this!
Very appropriate for a ruler.
Look at this Thing which utilizes
most of the biotechnology
of the visiting Europeans!
Biotechnology? I want it too!
What?
I can't hear you!
Please, I...
That's it. Being true to oneself
is always best.
Please, hurry...
Big sister, this is great.
What the?!
Oh, damn! I forgot about
the inner moat!
Ouch! I've been buried way
too many times today.
Kaede! Are you okay?
Yeah, did you come to save me?
I guess. Oh, yeah!
Oh! It's mine now!
This is the super-sized one, baby!
That might be worse than torture!
It hurts!
Pain!