Yuuwaku - Temptation
#LAMONAE @ RIZON presents...
Ripping etc. by Robink
Script meddling by ics-
Special thanks: feadraug & kurochocho
Volume  3
I want it!
Sometimes these
things really do happen.
Akemi...
Akemi.
What is it?
You tell me.
Oh, I was just thinking.
That we've come so far?
Is it "marriage blues"?
No, it's not that.
Look, isn't this sofa cute?
Which carpet should we get?
Well, let's see...
Here, I want a bed like this.
And these...
What do you think of them?
Or do you think this pattern is cuter?
Hey, which one do you like?
Or would you prefer another color?
Akemi...
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine.
Can we try to get
something more conservative?
I have to sleep on
them too, you know.
You're right.
The wedding is next week.
Kunihiko...
Don't worry about a thing.
Honey, it's me!
Kunihiko's parents are here.
Please shut the door.
She's still getting dressed.
Oh, sorry.
Just look at you.
You're so beautiful, Akemi.
Y-Yeah...
I received your letter.
Miss Jun!
What did it mean?
W-What do you mean?
It was about you.
Of course I'd show up...
...after getting that letter.
Mom!
Things are going to get lonelier now.
Why're you here?
Well, until later.
Hey, Akemi, did you get
a good night's sleep?
Yes, I slept really well.
Really?
Is that how it works?
You didn't get restless because
you were nervous or anything?
Yeah, really.
I was so busy with preparations
I got really tired. I fell sound asleep.
For real?
I still can't believe you're
getting married, and before I do!
Hey, his friends will be at
the post-reception party, right?
Are you shooting for that "Oh, we
met at my friend's wedding" thing?
Leave me alone!
You don't have to analyze it!
That's your aim though!
Then I'll be sure to throw
you the bouquet, Yohko!
Make sure you catch it!
Oh, quit teasing me!
Father...
It starts at 10:30, right? Then we've
only got ten minutes to get ready.
Yuki?
Nice to see you again, Yoshimi.
Congratulations.
Would you wait out
in the hall, Yoshimi?
But the time...
Yuki!
Akemi...
I'll see you later.
Yuki...
It's time for the ceremony.
That's right.
You were never late for anything.
Professor...
What was with that letter?
I...
I can't help it.
I can't forget a girl's body.
After all, I have a body like this...
And if I'm a girl,
I can come see you anytime...
Professor! Please don't!
It's time for the ceremony.
That's why I'm going to test you,
to see if you can forget about me.
Professor, my father
will come to get me.
Don't worry.
Yoshimi is just outside the door.
Akemi! You're twenty minutes late!
Everyone's waiting.
Your face is red.
Do you have a fever or something?
No!
I'm about to walk down
the virgin road, you know...
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry. Could you go on ahead?
I'll be right along.
I'll be waiting.
Akemi, that was quite
a lousy explanation.
You're terrible. You're the one who...
Really?
I have to go.
Akemi...
But...
No!
Why? Even when
you're as wet as this?
That's because you're...
N-No...
You want me to take
you from behind, Akemi?
Akemi, I'm going to fill you up!
No! Stop!
Not inside me, please! No!
Not inside!
No! It's hot!
Go out there like this.
All right...
And do you, Kunihiko,
promise to love her forever?
I do.
Akemi Takase, do you take
this man to be your husband...
...to be faithful to him
in prosperous times...
...hard times, sad times,
and happy times?
I do.
A Planet Designed for Tourism
The 18th Version of This Regulated City
Also known as
A Play on History
Hooligan Boy
Kaede!
Water the storefront, will you?
Okay!
You're becoming such a babe!
Have you got a man in your life?
Stop it, Mr. Gen.
Are you drunk already?
Yo! Kaede!
Take care!
Sure thing!
Kaede...
B-Boss!
Don't be so distant.
You can call me Mai!
N-Not here in the street.
Then let's go get a room.
No! Stop!
Stop? Stop what?
Your body's saying
something different.
We interrupt this program to bring
you an important emergency report.
Before daybreak today...
...an unidentified giant creature
appeared on the outskirts of the city.
This creature is heading toward
E-D-O, in the direction of Edo castle.
A magistrate-office announcement...
...states the culprit
is demanding the position of shogun.
What the hell is that?!
Also, if his demands aren't met...
What is that?
...a terrorist bombing
has been promised.
There is still no word
from shogunate personnel.
To the common populace, now is
the time to yield to this super genius.
And now for
the second phase of my plan.
Kaede... you're so hot.
No!
How about this?
Oh, please. Forgive me!
Not... yet.
It's cold!
The cold feels good, doesn't it?
Terrible news!
What?
Boss,
there's kinda some big trouble.
Kuma!
You idiot!
You interrupted me at a crucial
moment! She was ripe for the picking!
Your repair bill about ten seconds
from now will be big trouble.
So prepare yourself...
Stop! Please, wait a second!
Fuck you!
Since I know you're gay too, you
should've been more considerate!
H-How do you know about that?
Kuma, I know that you're doing it...
...with Sakichi of
the Comet tenement houses!
And I heard
your body was transformed...
...with cybernetic organisms and
such by those visiting Europeans!
How awful! He promised me
that it would be our little secret.
Are you a high-school
girl or something?
What?
Boss.
K-Kaede!
What's this?
Kaede!
Boss! Help me!
What the hell was that?
That's it! That's one of them!
They've been kidnapping
every young girl around here!
What the hell?
What?
Boss! It seems like that thing
is the culprit kidnapping the girls.
Those cheeky crackpots!
They won't get away with this...
I won't give up,
not after they took my prey!
Kuma! Get ready to arrest them!
Red alert! Red alert!
Everyone take
level-one battle positions!
All castle gates will be closed!
Activating barrier generator.
Deploying defense blockades.
The fifth line is about to be broken!
It's still advancing!
Go panic, everybody.
You can't do a thing about it.
Damn, that really sucked!
Huh? Kuma, where are you?
Hey, Kuma? Where did you go?
Hey, this isn't too bad.
M-Moron! What are you doing?
Just kidding, boss. A mere
woman's crotch doesn't arouse me...
What do you mean, "mere"?
Boss, that was mean.
Hey, Kuma! How long
are you gonna lay around?
We've got to get on the case!
As you can see,
I can't move if I wanted to.
Oh, I see...
That's too bad.
Who's he?
He said he'd like to be introduced
to a promising male companion.
Wow! Thank you!
He really went all out...
Stop fooling around, boss. Let's go!
You got it!
Huh?
Switch the castle tower
to fully armored mode!
Open all cannons and interlock them!
Prepare for automated barrage!
The target is about
to come into cannon range!
Fire!
We got it?
No, sir! It's still alive!
No sign of any damage!
What's that?
Hey, punk! Give Kaede back!
Damn it! One more time!
Right on!
By the way, boss,
is it okay to be this reckless?
Why do you say
that at a time like this?
Don't you know?
See the teacup
that thing is holding?
It's full of nitroglycerin.
Say what?
Kaede is...
Kaede is being violated!
What? Hey, she's mine!
Oh, you're awake.
You're a kid?
So I'm a kid, am I?
No! Please...
Please, don't look.
Kaede!
Oh, I see.
You two have a relationship.
In that case, I think
I'll show you some more.
No, not that!
Kaede...
Hey, he kinda has a cute face.
Wow! I could go for that!
Kuma... so you're finally awake?
You're so noisy, Mr. Mechanical Man.
I've reset your dangerous body.
So please be quiet.
Now it's your turn.
Thanks for waiting.
Do you know what this is?
You'll find out,
and you'll find it irresistible.
Oh! You're already wet.
You're so naughty.
Why you... You're just a brat.
Not that again.
It's all the same to the uncultured.
What the hell does age matter?
My mind more than
compensates for it!
And look at this!
This thing utilizes most
of the biotechnology of the...
...visiting Europeans!
Now this is the schlong of a ruler!
Biotechnology?
I want it too.
What?
I can't hear you!
Please, I...
That's it. Being true
to oneself is always best.
Hurry...
This is great!
What the?
Oh, damn! I forgot
about the inner moat!
Ouch! I've been buried
way too many times today.
Kaede! Are you okay?
Boss, did you come to save me?
I guess. Oh, yeah!
Oh! It's mine now.
This is the supersized one, baby!
Oh, ouch... That might
be worse than torture.
It hurts!
Pain!!
Writhing in agony, year after year,
he makes my heart flutter.
Cut the Gordian knot
in two, you eloquent tomboy.
Overpreparedness and sudden
impulse, we're the children of Edo.
Point blank, we never miss a shot.
Make me dizzy.
Beat a retreat as fast as you can.
We won't fall anytime soon.
We get immediate results.
We're very hard to deal with.
Peaceful times, a rosy future,
today's another beautiful day.
It's perfect!
All right...
What say, what say, flowery Edo
is a kaleidoscope of dreams.
The perfect woman, a playful
woman, the choice is yours.
What say, what say,
if you work out a plan...
... you can love
as much as you like.
Let's go party
in the balmy weather.
Roaring business,
ceremonial occasions.
Shut the doors and mind the fire.
Reward good
and punish evil in all things.
The women sure show off.
It's an outrageous celebration.
You'll have good luck in the spring.
Keep yourself
and your life in order.
Today's another healthy day.
It's perfect!
All right...
It's hard work to make animation based on an original story, isn't it?
For now, buy a single winner for "Go Go Z" for 5,000 yen,
and an additional 1,000 yen on 2, 6, 8, 13, 17.
What I want most is a small house with a big garden.
I'll plant fragrant olive, gardenia, and sweet daphne!
This was my first experience
singing an ending song.
I'll never forget the recording.
Then they took me to Ebisu.
If you pronounce them, "Sawaguchi Yasuko"
and "Kawaguchi Jasco" are very similar.
I feel like I ran a hundred-meter
dash. Once it starts, it never stops
and my stomach made noises
during my acting.
Since I've done this series,
I use my pen name for NOK.
I'm a different person from Mr. Masao Mochizuki at KSS.
(I guess...)
Staff, voice actors and actresses...
Good job! The customer who
bought this... thank you very,
very much. Hee hee...