Volume  4
Yuuwaku
Temptation
Thirsty...
I can't wait...
Please... I want it...
Hurry...
Don't tease me...
I'm going to explode.
I can't hold back!
Akira!
No! Don't stop!
Why? You're so cruel!
How could you stop
in the middle like that!?
I told you not to say my name.
What's the big deal?
What difference does
it make if I say your name!?
My name and my
body don't belong to me.
Huh?
I won't let anyone
but her defile them.
What the hell does
that mean!? You're insane!
Idiot!
After all, it's only our
bodies that are connecting.
Chapter One
#LAMONAE @ RIZON presents...
Ripping etc. by Robink
Script meddling by ics-
Special thanks: CharlieB & kurochocho
What? Class is cancelled?
Damn! I came all the way
here in this heat for nothing!
Kaname.
Tatsuro!
They cancelled fourth period.
Seriously? That's the
only reason I'm here today!
Me too!
Huh? That guy...
What's wrong?
See that guy?
That's Yoshiko's boyfriend.
Oh? But, that's
not Yoshiko with him now.
I think she said
his name was Amemiya.
That's strange.
It's none of our business, though.
Let's go to the cafeteria.
I'll buy you lunch.
Oh! I wish I could,
but I have to go to the clubroom.
Oh, all right.
Sorry, Tatsuro.
No big deal. Don't apologize.
Anyways, I'm glad
that you like the earrings.
They look really good on you.
Thank you.
What?
Sir...
Oh, sir!
Amemiya, sir!
Hey! You!
Aren't you dating Yoshiko?
I am. What's it to you?
What were you
doing in the clubroom?
What do you mean?
Were you watching?
Couldn't you
figure it out for yourself?
I wasn't watching! Why would I?!
Then, I'll tell you.
I was having sex with another man.
That's disgusting!
What is?
Don't you feel sorry for Yoshiko?
Why should I?
What do you mean?
Can't you see it?
Yoshiko loves you.
Is that so?
Why would you want anyone else?
Either a girl, or a guy?
That guy says he loves me, too.
What difference does it make
whether it's a girl or a guy?
A hole is a hole.
That's terrible!
You can still screw girls
after you've screwed a guy.
That's too terrible!
Why are you getting
so worked up over this?
Do you have feelings for me?
Don't kid yourself!
Who could have feelings for you?!
If you want me
to screw you, just let me know.
I'll give you the ride of your life.
All I feel for you is pity.
You've never really
loved anyone, have you?!
There is someone.
Someone I truly love.
Amemiya!
Yoshiko!
I'm so glad I ran into you!
What's wrong, Kaname?
Oh, nothing...
Oh! You and Tatsuro are
having problems, aren't you?
Don't try to steal my Amemiya
just to get even with him.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Tatsuro and I are doing just fine.
In fact, he just gave me these.
Oh, those are really cute!
Well, it's too hot
out here, so we'll get going.
See you later, Kaname!
Remember, we're still on for Friday!
Yosh-
Amemiya, sorry about yesterday.
I can be such a bitch sometimes.
If you'll forgive me,
I won't ever do it again, okay?
You shouldn't be
with a guy like him...
Yoshiko!
Sis...
It's already been a year since
we said goodbye to each other.
I know that work keeps you busy.
But...
Couldn't you call me, at least?
A single postcard is not enough.
And it's all about you.
What about me?
Dear Akira...
Why can't you say
those words to me?
No one is here to take your call.
Leave your name and number
at the sound of the tone...
...and we'll get back to you
as soon as possible.
It's Leona.
Come to my office tomorrow.
I have something for you from
your sister. I'll be expecting you.
Sis...
Hey, that new
bistro is pretty good!
The food is amazing!
They've been written
up in all the magazines!
I can't believe I ate so much!
Hey, look at that guy.
That's Amemiya, isn't it?
He's gorgeous!
He looks like a movie star!
Oh! I should ask him out!
You can't just snatch him like that.
But he did it with one of my
classmates and she can't stop bragging.
And he looks like he really
knows how to kiss!
Oh, I would love to kiss Amemiya!
What's with you today?
You're acting funny.
It's because your kisses
are so wonderful, Tatsuro.
I really like you.
I love you.
My friend was talking about that
Amemiya. She said he's pretty kinky.
Kinky?
He goes both ways. He does
it with guys and girls.
We know about
Yoshiko and that other girl...
...but there are
probably a lot of others, too.
Probably.
But, do you think
Yoshiko knows this?
Who knows?
We are talking
about Yoshiko, though.
Maybe she doesn't care at all.
Of course she cares!
Why are you getting mad at me?
Why am I so sensitive?
That's strange.
Why am I concerned with that guy?
Tatsuro, do you really love me?
W-What are you talking about?
Answer the question!
I love you.
Hey, you really are
acting funny today.
It's nothing. Hold me tight.
That guy doesn't
have anything to do with us.
When it's your sister, you always
get here on time, don't you?
When did you get back to Japan?
Yesterday.
Here. From your sister.
So, don't you want to know how
she's doing over there?
Is she well?
Of course she is!
At this moment, she's the top
Japanese model in the business.
Does she ask about me?
She's always worried about you.
She picked that out herself
during one of her rare breaks.
Go ahead. See how it looks on you.
Whenever she's interviewed
she mentions your name...
Even though it is a strange name,
she says she likes it.
I don't think she'll be coming
home any time soon, though.
Is that so...
It looks good on you.
Your sister has good taste.
She's one of the top
models in Paris and Milan.
This is a critical time for her.
You understand, don't you?
It's her dream.
Yes, your sister's dream.
I know how badly
you want to see her...
...but you'll have
to be patient a little longer.
I, however, can't wait anymore.
I love both of you...
She's very beautiful...
As are you...
My sister's dream... I understand.
But, let me share in the dream!
I want to be part of her dream.
Having to live without her is unfair.
Huh? What do you want
to know about Amemiya?
What kind of guy is he?
What do you mean?
What's he like when he's
alone with you? Is he nice?
Not at all!
If he gets mad, he won't even
talk to me when we're on a date.
It's kind of cute, though.
He's always looking in a mirror
and that narcissism is kind of a turn-on.
So, he is pretty self-centered.
But, hey Yoshiko, haven't you
heard what people say about him?
That he goes both ways?
Yeah...
I've heard that one before.
But, who cares if it's true?
It just means he's
that much better at sex.
Yoshiko!
Kaname, you're adorable!
Sexual prowess is
an important thing, you know.
I love it when we walk down
the street and other girls get jealous.
Does that ever happen
when you're with Tatsuro?
Hey now!
Yes or no?
It doesn't happen, but he loves me.
That's so like you.
Speaking of which, there is one
thing that really ticks Amemiya off.
What's that?
Calling him by his first name.
Calling him Akira.
That's bizarre.
Isn't it?
He gets mad and says,
"That name belongs to her!"
"Her"?
It's probably some problem
he had with an old girlfriend.
He hasn't been able to forget
about her or something.
Doesn't he say
anything more than that?
I've never asked for more than that.
Why spoil the fun?
That's just not right! It's weird!
You're the one getting all worked
up and you're calling me weird?
I'm... worked up because
I care about you, Yoshiko!
If you keep this up, you're going
to end up with a broken heart.
You've got to be
serious about this!
What gives you the right
to say something like that?
Nothing, really, but...
Then, why does it matter?
We're not hurting anyone, are we?
But do you really love him?
You really are weird, Kaname!
Could it be that you've got the
hots for Amemiya yourself?
That just isn't possible.
Oh, no! I was supposed to
meet Yuko and the girls!
I'm sorry, Kaname!
Pay my tab, would you?
Later!
I could never fall for a guy like that.
Why would I when I have Tatsuro?
Tatsuro loves me so much.
Anyways, I'm relieved
that you like the earrings.
They look really good on you.
Come up to my place
and get out of the rain.
No.
Then, I'll get in touch with you later.
Hey, screw me.
Why?
My boyfriend has
been cheating on me.
So?
So...
I want to do it with the
most disgusting guy I know.
I see.
Please, kiss me.
Please.
Please...
I can't wait anymore.
Hurry!
You're driving me crazy!
You want it that bad?
Then, I'll give it to you!
I like you...
I do like you!
I think I love you...
I care nothing for you.
I'm gonna come!
Oh!
Amemiya...
I love you.
I want to kiss you.
I want you to fall in love with me.
There is only one person I truly love.
But, she's the one
person I can't have.
Sister, my soul is so thirsty.
No one is here to take your call.
Leave your name...
Amemiya, who are
you sleeping with tonight?
Part 2
Memories
Secrets
Sex doesn't need a reason.