Brought to you by #Hentai-Fantasia@irc.aniverse.com
Empty.
I want you!
Come on...
...and take me
What are you waiting for? I'm not resisting!
Let's go!
More!
Akiraaaaaa!!!
Well, what are you doing?
Why did you stop?
Please go on
You can't leave me now
I told you not to call me by my name
Why can't I use your name?
Tell me!
So?
My name and my body are not yours
Except for one person.. no one may use my name
What?
What the hell are you talking about?!
You're weird
You're crazy!
They can only have my body.
Countdown:
Akira Complex
What?
There's no lesson?
Damn
I came here for nothing
Hi, Kanape
Oh, hello Tetsuro
There is no class today?
Damn
I came here for this lesson
Me too.
Hey
Is that?
What?
Isn't that Yoshiko's Boyfriend?
Ah yes?
Well, if she catches him now...
I think she will not be happpy about this
This is not good
It's none of our business.
Listen, do you want to go get something to eat?
Ok.
However, I must spend some time in the arena
All right.
I'll be quick!
Don't worry, there are no problems
You know...
...those earrings...
...are very nice.
Thank you.
Hey, may I ask you something?
Are you Yoshiko's boyfriend?
Yey, so?
What were you doing earlier in that room?
Hey, you have saw me, Then you know what I was doing.
I heard you having sex with a girl
You're wrong
I was having sex with a boy.
But are you?
Is this really important?
I feel sorry for Yoshiko
Why?
Because she loves you...
...and instead of returning her love, you betray her with other girls and boy
Well, yes.
It's wrong to trick someone that loves you
That's an arrogant behavior.
When I made the decision to do this, it's not important with who
Men.. Women.. It doesn't matter.
I don't see any difference.
I hate you!
Your opinion doesn't matter.
But aren't you ashamed?
Why should I be?
If you want, I can make love with you too.
What are you saying you filthy pig!?
Really? Well if you change your mind...
...you know where to find me.
You...
...only care about yourself
You don't know what true love is!
There is a person that I love more than myself.
Akira?
Yoshiko!
Akira! I finally found you.
Well, is there something wrong?
Ehm...
...no!
Why are you here with my boyfriend?
Don't get any strange ideas
By the way, do you like these earrings?
They are so beuatiful
Kanape, do me a favor...
...get ready for the party on friday.
Hey, Yoshiko
Well, time to go.
I am sorry my love...
...for the things I said to you yesterday. I said some really stupid things!
Poor Yoshiko
She really dosn't know him.
Little sister
It's been over a year since you left
Your job as a model takes you so far away from home
My life is empty without you
You don't know how much I miss you
Sometimes I get your postcards
But they're never enouch.
Dear Akira. I'm fine.
Why don't you...
...call me?
This is the answering machine
Please leave your message after hearing the tone.
Hello, I'm Leon.
Please come by my office tomorrow.
I have a present from your sister.
Little sister...
Listen, yesterday I met someone on the metro.
Is he good looking?
Uhmm... he's gorgeous!
I'm going out with him today.
Hey girls, that's him coming now
But It's Akira.
Yes, it is him.
He is very handsome
Ah, how I wish I knew him
One of my friends met him at a party. And they made love that same night!
Lucky girl
Yeah
And he is such a good lover.
Why is that?
Today you look different
Maybe it's the feeling I get...
...when I kiss you.
I love you.
Do you know Yoshiko's boyfriend?
He has all the girls falling in love with him.
Really?
It seems that he likes men and women.
He is bisexual.
He probably has sex with Yoshiko and other girls.
He also has sex with guys.
Do you think Yoshiko knows about all this?
Well
Of course.
Maybe she knows and decided to say nothing.
But what's are you saying?
It's strange that he didn't get caught.
I must ask you something..
Tetsuro
You love me, right?
Why you asking this question?
Reply me now!
Yes, I love you.
You're strange today, what's wrong?
Nothing
Please give me a big hug
I must get these thoughts out of my head.
Your sister is the only one you think ok.
When did you return?
Yesterday
This is the present you got from her.
She found time in her busy schedule to buy it.
How is she?
She's fine.
Out of all the Japanese models,
she is the best!
Doesn't she ever talk about me?
Yes, she talks about you a lot whenever she is asked.
She always talks about you
She says that has a brother
with a handsome name.
I think
She will return late, now that...
...she is so busy with her work.
That tie that she got for you...
...looks is nice on you.
She knows what your preferences are
As I was saying
She is always full of commitments.
I know..
However, these sacrificies are necessary.
It could be important for her
Modeling career that she loves so much.
Didn't you think?
Cheer up
This is always been her dream.
I'm here to help you
I like you so much.
She is carrying out her dreams
While I'm suffering.
Waiting she comes back to me.
Sister, I miss you so much.
Then, what were you asking me?
What type of guy is Akira?
Is he your original boyfriend?
Why do you ask?
You know, he is strange
Well, when he doesn't feel good
You can't talk to him
He is always looking himself at the mirror
Do you know what I think?
I think...
...he's a conceded jerk.
Conceded jerk?
Yes.
I'm not interested. In fact, this maybe the reason that he's such a good lover.
What are you saying?
I'm serious!
I like the idea of being with a boy that others desire.
When I go out with him
I catch others eating him with their eyes because he is such a cute guy
I don't know if you understand me. Does it happen to you and Tetsuro?
Why are you asking?
Answer me.
No... it's doesn't happen
That's because he doesn't cheat on me.
Oh, you are not happy?
A guy like him make me bored.
Ah, I remember now. There is one think that make Akira upset.
What?
He doesn't like to be called
Akira.
And why?
He said that his name belongs to another person.
To who?
Maybe to an ex-girlfriend that he can't forgot.
Aren't you curious to know who?
If I ask too many questions
I risk loosing him.
No! You have to know!
Be quiet. I'm not interested in finding out if he was faithful.
He shouldn't have all these secrets.
He knows that you are weak, that you are afraid of loosing him
and for this why he take advantage of you.
How can you put up with this?
These are my problems.
I.. I.. want only..
I don't need your advice.
I don't need your help.
Yes, but this is not love.
Oh Kanape
You make laugh.
Don't you love for Akira?
It's not that.
Oh no! I forgot that I had an appoinment with Yuko!
Can you pay, Kanape?
I have to go, bye.
It's not possible that I like Akira
and be with Tetsuro
He loves me.
I'm sure of this.
You know...
...there earrings...
...are very nice.
Are you sure you don't want to come with me?
No I don't want to.
I wish to see you as soon as possible.
I want stay with you.
Why?
I now understand that I don't love my boyfriend anymore
And so?
So, you were right, I changed my mind. I want make love with you.
Kiss me
Please
Take me
I'm yours. I want you.
Please
I can't resist anymore.
Do you want it badly?
Then take it.
I like you
I'm crazy for you.
You can only have my body.
I like you
I like you so much.
I want kiss you.
I would want you to love me.
I only love one person
and she is the only one who I call.
Little Sister
My earth is too empty.