It's the same old story.
Some princess in some kingdom gets herself kidnapped by some monster...
"To whomsoever rescues our princess, we shall grant a royal fortune."
"And furthermore, he shall become her husband and heir to the kingdom."
But I don't care!
All I want is a little stimulation!
Once again, a stupid human comes to die!
What a fool!
Come on, looks like I'll have some fun for a change!
Hey, hey!
Isn't there anyone else who's stronger?
Here I go!
Man, he wasn't even good.
That didn't give me a bit of stimulation.
But hey, this princess isn't a bad-looking mama!
Mr. Hero, at last we can see the town.
Indeed, we can. We should be able to reach the castle by tomorrow.
Princess, we should spend the night there.
Welcome to our inn. You look tired.
Are you getting a room?
Hey, dude.
Yes?
Do you have a room for two?!
Huh?! Oh, yes, we have prepared two single rooms for you.
I said the two of us!
Oh, of course, of course...
That's right, we only have one room left.
What? Only one room?!
I guess we've got no choice.
Oh, sure, thanks.
This bed is quite big for this room.
Is that so?
Yes, although, it's still smaller than mine.
Oh gee, thanks.
By the way...
We only have one bed.
That means you'll sleep on the floor, yes?
Floor...
Man, am I gonna fuck this bitch over or what?
Please!
Stop!
Please stop! It's my first time.
Please!
Stop!
Please! Stop...
Please!
I can't hold it anymore.
I don't think I can take this any longer.
Princess, what are you doing?
Princess?!
Who are you calling that?
You'd better call me Queen!
Hit me more!
Good morning, Sir!
Did you enjoy yourself last night?
Princess, this way, Ma'am.
Yes!
Please, use my back!
Thank you.
Oh! I love this stimulation!
My Queen!
What? I'm just the Princess.
Oh, yes, you're right!
Shall we go?
Mr. Hero, what's the matter?
Nothing! Nothing is wrong, My Queen.
You just said it again!
I'm the Princess.
I guess there's nothing wrong with
succeeding the king and ruling a kingdom some day.
A life without wondering if
I'll live through the day,
and a little special stimulation every night.
I'm a man who craves stimulation.