Temptation
Episode 3
I want it!
Sometimes these things
really do happen.
Akemi...
Akemi!
What is it?
What is what?
Oh, I was just thinking.
That we've come so far?
Is it wedding jitters?
No, it's not that.
Look, don't you just love this sofa?!
Which carpet should we get?
Well, let's see...
Here, I want a bed like this.
I love these and...
How do you like these?
Or do you think this pattern is cuter?
Which one do you think is cuter?
Or would you prefer another color?
Akemi...
Are you tired?
No, I'm fine.
Can we try to get something
more conservative?
I have to sleep on them too,
you know.
You're right.
The wedding is next week.
Kunihiko-chan...
Don't worry about a thing.
Honey, it's me!
Kunihiko-kun's parents are here.
Please, shut the door!
She's still getting dressed.
Oh, sorry.
Just look at you. You're
so beautiful, Akemi.
Yes...
I received your letter.
Jun-san!
What's that mean?
What's what mean?
It was about you.
Since I received that letter from you,
I couldn't stay home.
Mom!
I am going to miss you, and more.
Why?
Well, until later.
Hey, Akemi, did you get a good
night's sleep last night?
Yes, I slept really well.
Really?
Is that how it is?
You didn't get restless because
you were nervous or something?
Yeah, I thought for sure
you would be.
Oh, no, I was so busy with all the
preparations that I got really tired.
Then I fell sound asleep.
So that's really how it was?
I still can't believe you're getting
married, and before I do!
Hey, his friends will be at the
post-reception party, right?
Are you shooting for that "Oh, we met
at my friend's wedding" thing?
Leave me alone! You don't have
to analyze it!
Oh, but you are hoping for that!
Then I'll be sure to throw you
the bouquet!
Make sure you catch it!
Quit teasing me!
Father...
It starts at 10:30, right? Then I've
only got ten minutes for this.
Yuki-san?
Nice to see you again, Yoshimi-san.
Congratulations.
Would you wait for me down
the hall, Yoshimi-san?
But the time...
Yuki-san!
Akemi...
I'll see you later.
Yuki-sensei...
It's time for the ceremony.
That's right. You're never
late for anything.
Sensei...
What was that letter?
I am...
I can't help it.
I can't forget a girl's body.
That's because a body like this...
And if I'm a girl, I can come
see you anytime...
Sensei! Please don't! It's time
for the ceremony.
That's why I'm going to test you,
to see if you can forget about me.
Sensei, my father will come to get me.
Don't worry. Yoshimi-san is
just outside the door.
Akemi! You're twenty minutes late!
Everyone's waiting!
Your face is red. Do you have
a fever or something.
No!
You know, I'm going to walk
down the Virgin Road so...
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry. Would you wait for me
out there? I'll be right along.
I'll wait.
Akemi, that was quite
a lousy explanation.
You're not nice. You're the one...
Yes?
I have to go.
Akemi...
But...
No!
Why? Even when you're as wet as this?
But sensei...
No!
You want me to take you
from behind, Akemi?
Akemi, I'll come a lot for you!
No! Stop!
No! Outside, please! No!
Outside!
No! It's hot!
Go there like this.
Yes...
Do you promise to love her forever?
Yes!
Takase Akemi-san, do you take this
man to be your husband,
to be truthful to him and protect him
in prosperous times,
hard times, sad times,
and happy times?
Yes!