Volume  6
Yuuwaku
Temptation
Kaname!
Have you heard about
Yoshiko's Christmas event?
No, I haven't.
Yoshiko's having a party at
her apartment on Christmas Eve!
There's supposed to be
a lot of fine guys there!
Kaname, you come too!
I think I'll have to decline.
Why?
Don't tell me you've already got
a date with some guy on that night!
There's no way that... could happen.
It seems that your sister's
homecoming will be on Christmas Eve.
Amemiya, about Christmas Eve...
My soul is hers alone.
Chapter  Three
#LAMONAE @ RIZON presents...
Ripping etc. by Robink
Script meddling by ics-
Special thanks: CharlieB & kurochocho
Wow! This winter break is
full of fun events!
Anyway, you have to come to
the Christmas party, okay?
Hey, are you listening, Kaname?
Excuse me, "Come to the party
on Christmas Eve", is what I said.
I'm not going.
Do you already
have something planned?
Like meeting up with Amemiya?
So the rumors were true.
I wasn't really trying
to hide anything, but...
Kaname, do you have a minute?
Are you spending
Christmas Eve night with him?
No, there's no way.
But you're thinking,
"Maybe there's a chance."
Kaname, I think you already know...
...he's not the kind of person who
can understand your feelings.
No matter how long you wait...
...there's no way he's ever
going to say, "I love you."
Is that still okay with you?
It's still okay.
You're seriously in love with him.
Yeah...
Kaname, you're so strong!
I kind of envy you.
Here you are.
Thank you.
It's finally tomorrow, isn't it?
Yes.
Narita Airport, 4:00pm.
Is that so?
It sounds as though it'll be
a wonderful Christmas Eve.
You're so very beautiful.
I love you, Akira.
Sis...
...I so want to see you.
Sis!?
Amemiya?
It's Kaname.
Um, I want to see you
tomorrow, on Christmas Eve.
See me and then what?
It's okay if you'll just see me.
It's enough if you'll just be with me.
I can't see you.
Sister...
In a little while, she'll call my name.
Akira...
Sis!
Welcome back, Sis!
I'm home, Akira.
And...
...Merry Christmas.
I finally get to see you!
I haven't forgotten you,
not even for a day, Akira.
Let me get a good look at you.
Sis...
So this is your beloved brother?
Makes sense. He is as
cute as you've always bragged he was.
This is my makeup artist and personal
assistant from abroad, Chihaya Aso.
Nice to meet you, Akira.
Hey, should I buy
some wine glasses, too?
Kaname!
What are you doing?
So, you are alone today.
Hey, come on over to the party.
What?! For real?
That cameraman back then,
what was his name again?
Wasn't it Louis?
Yes, yes!
The way he acted, he'd go after
anything female, even a dog!
That's true.
He put his hands on my hips!
Well, wasn't that an honor?
After all, he is the number one
fashion photographer in Paris.
Even I have a right to choose!
It's all just the
same as the day I left.
Just for you, Sis.
Oh?
Then, those flowers.
Are they for me, too?
Yes. They are.
Um, I want to start on dinner, so...
Chihaya, I'll help you.
Akira, you can just relax, okay?
Merry Christmas...
Hey, hanging out here is boring.
After all, it is Christmas...
...so let's go somewhere together.
Hey, aren't you a bit depressing?
Huh?
You're thinking it'd have been better
if you hadn't come, aren't you?
That's not it.
Then, don't just sit there and mope!
Kaname, I know it might not be possible
to not think about him, but...
I'm not.
Really?
Then we have to liven things up!
After all, it's Christmas Eve!
Let's see, that guy and
that one are free, okay?
And then this one here!
This Italian transvestite makeup
guy was weird, wasn't he?
Wasn't he the one who used the
same compliments on every model?
I thought so!
And this transvestite was doing
it because it was his job...
...but he said it
was definitely more fun...
...to put makeup on
himself than on the models.
Really? Is that true?
But with that face...
...it made no difference
whether he did or not, did it?
Speaking of which, Akira is so
beautiful, I'm sure if we made him up...
...it'd turn out great!
Hey, why don't we make up Akira?
Well, Akira, why don't you
have her do it for you?
Your skin's so beautiful, Akira.
You're sure to look good!
I... I don't want to...
Your sister would like to see.
You'll show me, won't you?
B-But...
Akira...
Sis, why?
This is our special secret, just
between you and me, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Wow! Akira, you're so beautiful!
Since he's this beautiful, it makes
you want to dress him up, too!
Sis, what about your promise?
Akira, why don't you try this on?
Sis!
What's wrong?
I'm going home.
Kaname!
Sorry.
What am I doing?
You look wonderful, Akira!
If you said that you were a girl now,
people would believe you!
Why don't you use that wig over there?
You'll be even more surprised.
I'll do it myself.
No way!
You look exactly like your sister!
You're stunning, Akira.
Sister...
Why did you break your promise?
What promise?
That hurts!
Open up! Akira, open it, please!
Akira, what are you doing?!
Sister, the only one you love is yourself.
Because you don't love anyone else,
it doesn't bother you to hurt others.
Akira...
I've loved you all this time.
No!
Akira, stop...
Please...
Akira, wait!
She was seeing herself in me.
I saw perfection in her.
She's unrestrained and selfish,
and she casually hurts people.
But, she's more
beautiful than anything else.
Sister...
Amemiya?
I'm so glad I got to see you tonight.
You don't have to say anything.
Just being with you is enough.
Call me by my name.
My name. Call me "Akira".
Then, look only at me...
Akira...
...I love you!
I love you.
You are waiting for...
... something to begin.
Standing in the dark...
... like a scene that's
waiting for the rain.
You just don't know...
... what you want to do.
Have you ever thought...
... I might be your dream?
I will be sweet all the time.
I'll be very sweet...
... always and just right.
Just right are we two.
You're the only
one who makes me feel that...
Akira...
... there is nothing to be afraid of.
You're the only one
who makes me feel that...
... here in this
world I was born to love.
I believe in you.
You don't have
to be waiting anymore.
Did you know you can start it?
When you find what you
really want to do someday...
... you will find a way, surely you will.
So good...
Akira...
Akira!
You're the only one
who makes me feel that...
...there is nothing to be afraid of.
You're the only one
who makes me feel that...
...here in this
world I was born to love
I believe in you.
You don't have
to be waiting anymore...
...'cuz you know you can start it.
When you find what you
really want to do someday...
...you will find a way,
surely you will.
Akira...