Yuuwaku - Temptation
#LAMONAE @ RIZON presents...
Ripping etc. by Robink
Script meddling by ics-
Special thanks: feadraug & kurochocho
Volume  2
CRIMSON
I was 28 years old and a virgin
when I acquired this homunculus.
Its vocal speaker and
visual sensors were broken.
Until I came across these
"hands" that were just like hers...
...my penis was never erect.
That's of course assuming that
my actions with this sex doll...
...count as my first time.
Do you want to be unbound?
You're so beautiful.
Probably more so than she was...
The sensation of her sweet fingers...
...still cuts painfully
into me even now.
I guess this is all that's the same.
Although after twenty-odd years...
...I can't even remember her face.
What color were her eyes?
What color are your eyes?
Can't you even shed tears
with those broken eyes?
Now I wonder...
And the more I wonder,
the more I want to see.
You can't see anyway,
so you won't miss one.
It's so pretty!
Is this how pretty eyes can look
when they don't see unclean things?
It's so absorbing.
She smiled.
Tears of blood didn't make her cry.
Since that day, the unseeing eye...
...has been watching me.
Damn it!
Stop!
Don't look at me!
Damn it...
She never would look at me.
Even though I wanted her to...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to cause
trouble or make you cry!
I was a bad boy.
Hey...
I'll be a good boy. I will...
So don't cry!
You can punish me. I'll be good!
Come on, punish me...
Her fingers unsteadily
grope for my neck...
...and there's a moment of delight.
To this day, I can still feel...
...fingers digging into my throat.
Deeper they go,
millimeter by millimeter.
And yet...
...that's the one and only love
I remember her giving me.
Mommy, this time...
This time, take me with you...
There's something I've lost.
Oh, how I pine for it...
But the thing
I was unable to regain...
...is love.
Yes...
These are the hands.
-The second time she sheds tears-
CRIMSON
A spring morning.
Early light slowly dyes the sky...
...and purple clouds
stretch over the mountains.
A summer night.
Never... Never mind moonlit nights.
On moonless nights, the lights of
fireflies cross through the darkness.
It would be as strange to see just
one or two as it would be to see rain.
An autumn evening. The setting
sun tints the tips of the mountains.
Ravens fly in groups of two,
three, four, to their abodes.
A wavering line of wild geese
vanishes into the distance.
The sun's journey ends, and only the
sounds of wind and insects remain.
A winter morning.
The ground is covered in snow...
...and a frost only serves
to add to the cold.
The fire must be tended to so that
it will continue its blessing of heat.
But as the sun
brings greater warmth...
...the neglected fire
becomes nothing but ash.
I'm so unlucky.
The time is January,
March, April, May...
That's all for this week.
We'll discuss the meaning Monday.
Be sure to be ready for it.
Anyone who has a home visit set for
today, be sure to go straight home.
You'll get this then, Miss Takase.
Not now, Professor?
No. I'd say about 4:00.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go, Akemi.
Wait up!
You're so slow, Akemi.
What happened?
She took my pencil.
Wait, I'm coming too!
She's not visiting you.
What about club?
Don't worry about it.
I got the kiss today!
Perfect for a Saturday.
And what if Professor Watanabe
asks what it means?
Oh, I don't know what I'd do...
No problem.
It means, "Wear lipstick today."
Then what about the heart?
It means,
"Something hot will happen."
Just be sure not to say
it means S-E-X, Akemi.
You know what?
Today I got the girl mark.
That's a toughie. What personalized
meaning could that have for you?
Personalized?
It could mean an older girl
who likes you will talk to you.
There's nobody like that.
You never know, Akemi.
You're pretty cute.
I've got it! Maybe it means
you have nothing to do with men.
No way!
Catch.
You might be
seeking it unconsciously.
Here she goes again.
In other words, a hidden instinct.
A craving in your subconscious.
In a nutshell,
it's a hidden devilishness.
The hell you say?
The fun never ends with you here.
The first time I noticed this
devilishness hidden in her heart was...
Yes, one night this past winter,
at the tennis club training camp.
I didn't know that!
What? Details!
Shii, Hiroko, and Nat were in a bath.
Kana!
With me and Akemi.
We all decided to bathe
Akemi like she was Cleopatra.
She resisted a bit at first...
No no no! Stop talking!
But you didn't really mind!
I did!
Her maids' expression of love...
...caused the queen
to lose the will to resist!
But I did resist!
Nope, now open
the door within your heart!
I was so surprised by that
I couldn't even speak!
That tickles!
That makes sense. Subconscious
craving and acceptance.
Talk about deep.
Wow, you girls will say just
about anything about a person!
Sweetest
Lips
Are you sure you wouldn't
rather just buy some cakes?
No, I'm making these for her.
Don't worry.
I won't screw up doughnuts.
Mom, I dropped
the dough on the floor!
This is why I was concerned.
Hi, ma'am!
Hi. Is this a good time?
Ma'am!
You're early. It's only 2:30.
The first half went
faster than I expected.
Oh, where's your mother?
Sorry, she's out buying tea cakes...
You didn't have to go to such
trouble. It's just a home visit.
That's what I said too,
but she was like, "Even so..."
Please wait in
the living room for a bit.
Oh my.
The doughnuts didn't
work out? That's too bad.
I wish I could've tried your cooking.
Don't look in there!
Oh, why don't you show me your
bedroom instead of the living room?
Sure, this way.
Did you burn yourself?
I said not to look!
It's upstairs. Let's go.
My, what a cute bottom you have.
Oh no! What did you see, ma'am?
Sorry, I couldn't help myself.
That miniskirt looks cute on you.
Please Knock
Here you go, before I forget.
Thanks.
What did it land on?
Um...
Wow, that's cute!
And fluffy!
Do you hug this while you sleep?
N-No, I don't!
Well, if it were up to me,
I'd hug you while I sleep...
Oh no, I can't push away!
No, ma'am... Stop...
Sorry. I'm just the type
who can't bear to wait.
Now let's get rid of some clothes.
It's good to be alive!
You're all mine!
No! Stop that, ma'am!
You're nice and sensitive.
But we're just getting started.
You're so cute, Akemi...
Still so nice and smooth.
Did the girl mark mean her?
No, don't bite it!
I'd say you're ready,
judging by how sticky you are...
M-Ma'am...
W-W-What is that?
"What is it?"
Haven't you ever seen your dad's?
It looks like the top
of a Persian palace.
I've heard it described
many ways, but that one's a first.
W-Why do you have one?
Do you like Arabian Nights?
Then this is a magic carpet!
I'm going to fly you through the sky...
No! Don't do this!
I've always watched you,
Akemi. I love you.
Mom... H-Help me...
Oh?
Whoops,
her professor's already here.
Huh?
Akemi?
Hello. Don't mind us.
Looks like you're stiffer
than Akemi was, ma'am.
P-Professor...
B-But that's...
I know what you're going
to say. Everybody says it.
Look, don't worry.
The way to be with women all the
time without suspicion is to be one.
So I just had to become a woman...
...even if only for
the sake of appearance.
I was always teased that I looked
too feminine, so I hate men.
I heard your husband has
to work far away from home.
That must be lonely for you.
You want it, don't you?
It's amazing!
Please, I want it from behind...
Hurry...
Hurry and do me!
That's wonderful! Keep going!
It really is great...
It's hitting so deep!
I can't hold back!
That's okay!
Come, come inside me!
School is now over.
Those students still inside
the building, proceed to your homes.
Staff Room
All right, understood.
Yes, I'll tell her.
No problem. Goodbye.
Professor Watanabe.
Yes?
Mrs. Takase just called.
She wants to discuss course loads.
Thank you for telling me.
They've really been
eager beavers lately.
I'll say.
You carry a burning
dream in your heart...
... as you set out down
the sunset-lit street.
Your umbrella is small, so some
days you're going to get soaked...
... but please, don't let that stop you.
Goodbye, my girl friend.
Here's a shout out for you.
I know...
I just know that tomorrow...
... will be on our side.