Temptation
Episode 1
Stay, why don't you stay with me?
I dream of a blue moon
Why, as you were in my dream
It's only a dream!
With someone you love
Where is my love?
More...
Take my breath, breath that can voice my feelings
Uh, oh, I've only got twenty minutes.
Where is your love?
Softly...
The nakedness of my bare skin
What the...
Well, I guess they're not shy.
But...
Two girls!
Uh, oh, I'm thinking about it.
Excuse me.
Coming through.
Yes!
Oh, no! She saw me! She saw me!
What were you doing just now?
What?
Well...
I guess we're even.
I was watching you.
You were?
Gee, don't you hate these awkward silences?
I'm Nakatani Jun, very nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm on vacation. Alone.
What about you?
Business?
Yes, I'm a kitchen coordinator.
But I'm just getting started.
You coordinate kitchens?
Yes, I use ergonomics to coordinate blueprints
of more efficient kitchens for my clients.
Oh, and we carry Italian-made kitchens too!
Ergonomics...
You poor thing, how awful, you must work so late.
Well, I would've gotten a hotel room,
but my fiancé's son is in bed with fever.
And I couldn't just leave him alone.
Fiancé! Sounds like you're already married!
We've been engaged for two months, but we haven't set the date yet.
I'm just happy to be with him.
Really? Well, you sure don't look like a housewife.
Mind your own business.
Ladies and Gentlemen, your attention please.
We have just entered the expressway, and will be turning off the lights.
Your fiancé must be away quite a bit.
Well, you looked awfully interested back there.
No, no... Not at all!
I was just shocked.
So, how are you feeling?
How... what?!
So young and healthy...
You shouldn't waste your talents.
You mean you want to do it?! Here?!
It'll be such a thrill!
You... what?
My goodness!
You've done this before, haven't you?
Where are you staying?
I haven't decided yet, but
I have a friend in town.
Why don't you stay with me?
We could be very good friends by tomorrow morning.
Yes!
Kunihiko-kun! Let me in! I forgot my key!
Chizuru-san? Welcome home!
It's open. Come on in!
Sorry I didn't come to the door.
Don't worry about it.
But how are you feeling?
How's your fever?
I'm fine.
It was just a little one.
It's no big deal.
Really! You should take better care of yourself.
Well, I'm glad you're better now.
I was worried about you.
Who's she?
Hello there, I'm Nakatani Jun, but you may call me Jun.
We got acquainted on the bus.
Glad to meet you, I'm Kunihiko.
You're cute, and so polite.
I like that in a man.
Do you still feel hot?
Ouch!
Let's go upstairs now.
Ow! That hurts!
He doesn't call you mama?
He's an adult. I'm only eight years older than he is.
But I know you must have felt it.
What?
He was mentally undressing you down there.
He looks appetizing, but he's not quite ready yet.
You felt it, too?
Such tight, smooth skin, so skimpily dressed...
It makes me hungry.
You think I have the same hunger?
Anyway, shouldn't you take a shower?
No thanks.
Okay, but we smell a little funny.
That's the smell of love.
He might be the dessert, but
I want my main course now!
Woman!
No... no...!
I can't...
Move... right?
Make it good and loud, so he'll hear you downstairs.
No!
There's a stain from last night.
This feels so good! You're so wet!
You're just saying that...
Yes! And so tight too!
A body like yours can't possibly be satisfied by one middle-aged man.
So, just how many men have you been with since you got engaged?
No... I haven't...
Liar!
Two... three... f...
I'm gonna come...
Coming...
Oh, Chizuru-san!
What are you up to?
Kunihiko-kun?
You're all red. Has your temperature gone up?
Well...
Don't worry. You can sweat that fever away.
Or for faster relief, you can transfer all that heat to me.
Come on.
Chizuru-san... I... I...
Can't! No... I'm coming!
Oh, my!
You would've burst if you held that any longer!
So cute!
Look at this. I've wanted you so much since...
Chizuru-san...
This is much tighter! So good!
You've been burning the candle at both ends! How naughty!
Maybe I should quit now?
Not now!
Just kidding.
Coming!
Chizuru-san!
And now, Kunihiko-kun...
What?
I think you need a booster shot.
What?!
Don't worry, this won't hurt a bit.
Well... I mean, wait a minute!
No! Stop!
Pain!
Oww!
How are you, Jun-san?
I can't believe I really caught it!
You feel even hotter.
You're welcome to stay in my bed.
Oh, no...