Yuuwaku - Temptation
#LAMONAE @ RIZON presents...
Ripping etc. by Robink
Script meddling by ics-
Special thanks: feadraug & kurochocho
Volume  1
Uh-oh, I've only got twenty minutes.
Huh?
No way... This is in public...
And...
It's two girls!
Uh-oh, I keep thinking about it.
Excuse me.
Coming through.
R-Right!
Oh no...
She saw me... She saw me...
What were you doing just now?
What?
Well...
I guess we're even.
You watched me earlier.
Oh, you're...
Hello.
Isn't it awkward to sit next
to someone in silence?
I'm Jun Nakatani,
and it's very nice to meet you.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm on vacation alone.
What about you?
Business?
Yes, I'm a kitchen coordinator.
But I'm just getting started.
A kitchen coordinator?
Yes, I use ergonomics
to coordinate blueprints...
...of more efficient
kitchens for my clients.
We also deal in
Italian-made kitchens.
Ergonomics, huh?
Anyways, it must be awful
to have to work so late.
I would've gotten a hotel room...
...but my live-in boyfriend's
son is in bed with a fever.
I couldn't just leave him alone.
No way! Sounds like
you're already married!
We're not married yet,
but we will be two months from now.
He'll be away until then,
so I have to make sure I'm around.
Really? Well, you sure
don't look like a housewife.
Well, excuse me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
your attention please.
We've just entered the highway and
will be turning off the interior lights.
Your boyfriend must be busy a lot...
...because you looked
awfully interested before.
N-Not at all! I was just shocked.
So how'd you like watching us?
How did I...
You're still so young...
It's such a waste.
You mean you want to do it? Here?
It'll be such a thrill.
You've got a...
My goodness...
You've done
this before, haven't you?
Silly...
Hey, where are you staying?
I haven't decided.
With a friend, maybe.
Why don't you stay with me?
We could take our
time tonight, you know?
Yes?
Kunihiko, it's me. I forgot my key.
Chizuru? Welcome home!
It's open. Come on in!
Sorry I didn't come to the door.
It's all right. I see
you're still feeling weak though.
Well? How's your fever?
I'm fine.
It was just a light one.
The nurse was exaggerating.
Really... You should take
better care of yourself.
Anyway, I'm relieved.
I was worried about you.
Who's this?
Hello there, I'm Jun Nakatani,
but you can call me Jun.
We met each other on the bus.
Glad to meet you. I'm Kunihiko.
You're cute, and so polite.
I like that in a man.
How's your "temperature"?
Ouch!
Let's go upstairs now.
Ow! That hurts!
So he refers to you by your
first name, rather than "mother"?
I don't really mind.
I'm only eight years older than him.
But you felt it, didn't you?
What?
He really likes you, you know?
It was both cute and pathetic
how he kept glancing at you.
I thought so. You noticed it too?
His smooth skin,
the way his pajamas cling...
It makes me hungry.
Maybe it's time for a snack.
By the way, how about a shower?
No thanks.
Really? But we smell a little funny.
The smell of passion turns me on.
He might be the dessert,
but I want my main course now.
Ma'am...
No...
Wait...
I can't...
Can't move, can you?
Make it nice and loud
so he'll hear you downstairs.
No!
There's a stain from last night.
No way...
Wow! You're so wet...
You're just saying that...
And so tight too!
A body like yours can't possibly be
satisfied by one middle-aged man.
Tell me, how many men
have you had inside you?
No... I haven't...
Liar!
Two... three...
I'm gonna come...
Coming...
Oh, Chizuru!
What are you doing?
Kunihiko?
Your face is red.
Is that your fever again?
Well...
Don't worry.
You can sweat that fever away.
Or maybe you'll get better faster
if you transfer all that heat to another.
Come on...
Chizuru... I... I...
I can't...
No... I'm coming!
Oh my!
You were really pent up.
So cute...
Look at this.
I've wanted you so much since...
Chizuru...
This is much tighter! So good!
You've been burning the candle
at both ends. How naughty.
Maybe I should stop.
Not yet...
Just kidding.
Now come!
C-Chizuru!
And now, Kunihiko...
It's time for your booster shot.
Don't worry. This won't hurt a bit.
Well... I mean, wait a minute!
W-Wait...
N-No!
Pain!!
Ow!
How are you, Jun?
I can't believe I really caught it...
Your fever's getting even worse...
I wonder if my
"booster shot" would help.
Oh no...
It's the same old story.
Some princess in some kingdom
gets kidnapped by some monster.
To whomever rescues our princess,
we shall grant a royal fortune.
And further, he shall become her
husband and heir to the kingdom.
But I don't care about that.
All I want is a little stimulation.
Once again,
a stupid human comes to die.
What a fool!
Looks like I'll have
some fun for a change!
Come on, come on!
Isn't there
anyone else who's stronger?
Here I come!
Man, even he wasn't any good.
That didn't give me
a bit of stimulation.
But hey, this princess
isn't bad-looking at all!
Mr. Hero, at last
we can see the town.
Town, huh?
We should reach
the castle by tomorrow.
Princess, we should
spend the night here.
You look tired, honored traveler.
Would you like a room?
Hey, gramps.
Y-Yes?
Do you... have a room... for two?
Huh? Yes, we have two
single rooms prepared for you.
I said the two of us! Understand?
Oh, of course...
We only have one room
open today, I'm afraid.
What? Only one room?
I see. I guess we've got no choice.
No, I suppose you don't.
Oh, this bed is
quite big for this room.
I-Is that so?
Yes, although it's still
smaller than mine.
Well, hey...
By the way...
We only have one bed.
That means you'll
sleep on the floor, yes?
The floor?
Man, is this bitch frigid or what?
Please!
S-Stop!
Stop! It's my first time.
Please!
Stop!
Please! Stop...
Please!
I... I can't take it anymore...
I don't know what's what any longer!
Princess, what are you doing?
Princess?
Whoever do you mean?
Call me "Queen"!
Hit me more!
Good morning.
Did you enjoy yourself last night?
This way, Princess.
Okay.
Please, use my back.
Thank you.
Oh! I love
this stimulation! My queen!
What? I'm just the princess.
Of course you are!
Well, shall we go?
Mr. Hero, is something the matter?
Nothing!
Nothing is wrong, my queen.
You just said it again!
I'm the princess.
I guess becoming
the king won't be so bad.
A life without wondering
if I'll live through the day...
...and a little special
stimulation every night.
I'm a man who seeks stimulation.
The billions of stars shine
through distant light years...
... to reach us here
as shimmering lights.
Let's set off
on our journey tonight...
... relying on the blue
guide board of the Pleiades.
No one knows what
shape dreams may take...
... but let's go search for a place
that gives off dizzying light.
Keep on dreaming anyway.
Time's highway.
A far-off klaxon gives me courage.
Keep on dreaming any day.
We'll meet up someday.
I love
the capriciousness of tomorrow.