The century draws to an end.
All over the Earth,
demons, ghosts, goblins, and monsters of all
kinds began to escape from their prisons.
They attacked humans.
The number of casualties increased rapidly.
At long last, a group of
hunters called Raiatto,
specializing in exterminating monsters,
appeared from some secret land.
The stage was set for a fierce battle
between the hunted and the hunters.
Demon Hunters
Part 1
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Tamesuu | Edit: Collectr | Timing: v1touch |Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
Kamiya Detective Agency
Miss, a spirit called an
incubus has possessed you.
It makes people lustful
and drains their vitality.
A woman who has been possessed
will crave semen until she dies.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
There is a way to exorcise it.
Well then...
No! Don't stop.
Very well.
Take me.
I'll handle everything.
You'll be better off if you stop right there.
Who are you?
What are you doing here!?
There, there, no need to get angry.
I just have some business
with that lady over there.
Business? This woman has
been possessed by a spirit!
I have to exorcise it as quickly as possible!
You haven't done your research, detective.
What?
Miss, you've been involved with
thirteen men in the past few months.
I'm telling you, it's because of the incubus!
Each of those men met an unnatural death.
Doesn't that sound a little suspicious?
Are you serious?
Incubi, especially those from
the higher echelons,
take the shape of humans
and steal others' vitality.
In other words, they're vampires.
What are you talking about?
What he's talking about...
is this!
Damn!
Geez.
What?
You're fast.
And it looks like you're not
just an average person.
But whatever.
How about it? Do you want to embrace me?
That sounds interesting.
I'll show you pleasure like
you've never tasted before.
It'll melt your body and your soul.
You...
Sorry about that.
I'm bad at kissing.
You're an interesting man.
Now I want to know more about you.
I'm honored.
I wonder what kind of heart that body holds.
I'll tear it out and see for myself.
I'm glad you want to play,
but this will be your opponent.
A familiar?
What an interesting thing you have there.
It is, isn't it? But I'm not giving her up.
Oh, Master!
Now, it's your turn to shine, Ilia.
Wh-What do you mean?
I'll take good care of you, little lady.
Ilia.
Yes?
Go take advantage of her hospitality.
You could at least avoid getting caught.
Here I go.
No...
Your name was llia-chan, right?
I'll make you feel good real soon.
Not there!
No!
How about we move on to the main course?
Come here. Don't be afraid.
No...
Stop!
It looks like you're about to cum.
How about your ass?
No, not there!
Don't stick your finger in!
Oh? But it looks like you're really enjoying it.
Should I put it in and let you finish?
This girl is done.
Now it's your turn.
Is it now? I guess that's
all Ilia was capable of.
Maybe it's time I got rid of her.
Either way, it's not like
Ilia is my, only servant.
I don't want that to happen!
No!
What is that girl?
That burned!
There are all kinds of beings in the
world that you don't know about.
Now it's time for me to do my job.
Are you all right, Ilia?
Yes.
Damn it!
Shit!
M-Master, I-I'm...
Follow me!
Wait for me!
Blood.
I need blood!
She's over there?
Oh, no! I've been pulling
you around everywhere.
I really don't mind.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What was that?
B-Blood?
S-Sir! There's a h-head!
Now that I've run this far away...
You won't get any further.
What?
Who are you?
I am Garuard, a Magic Knight.
You might not guess it from my name,
but my job involves nightly inquiries
regarding demons.
A Magic Knight?
I'm having a really bad day today.
Travel between our Demon Realm
and this world is forbidden.
I'll let you off if you return to
the Demon Realm peacefully.
Otherwise...
I guess I have no chance
against a Magic Knight.
Then will you be returning
to the Demon Realm?
Yes.
But the way I look right now...
I'll take that attack as your answer.
You've got a lot of fight in you.
But it's all useless against me.
I'll deliver your punishment.
Hold it!
Sorry, but she's my prey.
Could you leave her to me?
Prey? Are you one of the Raiatto?
Well, something like that.
It's my professional duty to get rid of her.
And besides, a normal Raiatto can't
handle a demon of her level.
Don't worry.
I'm not quite normal.
Fine, then.
Great, then it's settled.
Hey, Sis!
Let's continue where we left off.
However, Ilia might be a bit late.
This time, you'll face her.
Her name is Kusuka.
Take good care of her.
What?
Is he the one I should defeat?
He's a little too much for you.
That's who you'll be facing, over there.
Just her?
Ilia should be enough for this one.
Whoa, girl, you're hot.
Where do you work?
She's kind of lost right now.
That knucklehead.
Damn you.
Don't underestimate me!
You're really weak.
And slow on top of that.
I'm going to seal you!
What is this thing?
How could this...
Wow, great job, Kusuka.
You're always on top of your game.
Just what are you people?
We're just what we appear to be.
Our job is to seal demons.
I see.
But for what purpose?
Figure that out on your own.
Well, I'll tell you this much.
There's no point in just killing.
That's fine by me.
You don't seem to be my foes.
That's true enough, Magic Knight.
Call me Garuard.
Recently, demons of her level have
become much more numerous.
Have you heard the rumor that
the gate's been opened?
Gate?
Do you mean the gate to the Demon Realm?
Yes.
No, I haven't heard anything like that.
And if the gate really is open,
this would be just the tip of the iceberg.
Are you searching for the gate?
I am, if it's already open.
I see.
It's true that there are a lot
of demons in this city.
The key to the gate may be hidden here.
Once opened, the gate can't be closed.
That would be a problem,
both for this world and for yours.
I agree completely.
I'll let you know if I learn anything.
Come to think of it, I haven't
heard your name yet.
My name?
My name is Mitsurugi.
Mitsurugi-san, is it?
Mitsurugi-san, I'd like to hear
more about you some time.
If the opportunity presents itself.
Now then...
Give me that stone, Kusuka.
What's wrong?
I don't want to.
You always work us like slaves.
If you want it, take it yourself.
Hand it over.
No.
Girls that act like this need to be punished.
Huh?
W-Wait a second.
Now be good and hand over the stone.
N-No!
That spell won’t work on me.
Then I guess I have no choice.
S-Stop. Stop!
No!
You wet yourself.
Wh-What are you doing?
I already told you. It's your punishment.
Is the stone... around here?
No!
If you won't give it to me,
I'll just have to take it out.
Get ready, Kusuka.
Damn it, my consciousness is...
Let's get started.
Wh-What's happening?
Preparations.
Now get me ready too.
Is this the time to be embarrassed?
You're the one who'll be
hurt if you don't do this.
And besides,
you really want it soon, don't you?
Good girl.
This is too embarrassing.
Naughty girls need to be punished.
I'll get it back real soon.
It's... reaching so deep.
Oh, no. It's coming! out It's coming out!
That's right It'll come out soon.
S-Stop!
Stop it!
I-I'm gonna cum! I'm cumming!
Why did you do that?
This stone would be useless
to you if you kept it.
Well, no matter.
It's time for you to return to your seal.
Wait.
What is it?
I want to be outside a little longer.
Please.
You should have asked at the outset.
But...
What are you two doing?
Ilia!
I can't believe it! I was
looking all over for you.
Serves you right. It's because you're so slow.
How can you say that, Kusuka?
I was trying my hardest!
Oh, yeah?
Please tell her something, Master.
W-Well...
Master doesn't like dumb girls.
I'm not dumb!
Then what were you doing all this time?
I was lost in the city.
What did I tell you?
What was that?
What? Take this!
I thought I had to turn at
the convenience store.
They tire me out.
Right, right.
SEE YOU NEXT STORY
Damon Hunters
Part 1
aoi hikari hashirinuke
Outrun the blue light
hametsu no tobira hiraku toki
when the gates of destruction open
hikari no honoo kanashimi no kaze
A flame of light, a wind of despair
dareka ga kimi wo yondeiru
Someone is calling you
mou zankan yobisamase mune no oku kara
Zankan! waken in the depths of your heart
mou zankan dokiharae mugen no chikara wo
Zankan! Wield your limitless power
harukana jikai wa toki wo koe
A far-off meeting surpasses time
in no kagayaki ga kakeru keru
The brilliance is missing from the shadow
yami wo kirisake muteki no yaiba Mitsurugi
Pierce through the darkness, invincible blade Mitsurugi
kuroki arashi fukiarete
A black wind blows violently
hijou no sadame semaru toki
as the appointed time draws near
inochi wo iyasu daichi no inori
The foremost prayer is to spare life
dareka ga kimi wo motomete iru
Someone is seeking you
mou zankan tachiagare yuuki wo daite
Zankan! Stand up, and embrace courage
mou zankan sora wo kake imawashii uwa donaru
Zankan! Fly in the sky, and shout obscenely
mesameyou tamashii toki wo koe
Surpass time, awakened soul,
ashita no kidou mamoru tame
to protect the path tomorrow takes
yami ni kirameku seigi no/yaiba Mitsurugi
The justice that shines in the darkness,
invincible blade Mitsurugi
mou zankan yobisamase mune no oku kara
Zankan! Awaken in the depths of your heart
mou zankan dokiharae mugen no chikara wo
Zankan! Wield your limitless power
harukana jikai wa toki wo koe
A far-off meeting surpasses time
in no kagayaki ga kakeru keru
The brilliance is missing from the shadow
yami wo kirisake muteki no yaiba Mitsurugi
Pierce through the darkness, invincible blade Mitsurugi