Shit Where is it?
Up above?
Sintering light!
Damon Hunters
Part 2
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Translation: Tamesuu | Edit: Collectr | Timing: v1touch |Typeset & Encode: ShocWave | QC: Brush
All systems green.
Checking status of brainwaves,
body, and psychological state.
Brainwaves normal.
Bodily functions normal.
Psychological state normal.
No abnormalities detected.
Commencing download.
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
0...
Download complete.
Miss Iwama, how do you feel?
I feel great. Well done, Adams.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'll be back in a bit, so watch over me.
Yes, ma'am.
What network should I play in today?
I hope there are some cute girls there.
But before that...
You, hiding over there, who are you?
Oh, you noticed.
You found me so easily.
I'd expect no less from Iwama Mitsune-san,
CEO of the Saishisumu Company.
Where did you connect from?
How did you get into my network?
I apologize for forcing my way in.
Who are you?
Please don't get so upset.
I just wanted to ask you for a favor.
A favor?
Yes.
This network is incredibly well made.
I've spied on many networks,
but this is the first time I've seen something
so complete and beautiful.
So what?
This network would serve perfectly
as a pipeline to the Demon Realm.
How about it?
Will you let me build a gate here?
I was wondering what this was all about.
You don't believe me, do you?
Don't take me for an idiot.
I made this network.
I wouldn't sell it, no matter
how much you gave me.
And what's that about a Demon Realm?
Who the hell are you?
That I cannot tell you.
Then I guess we can't talk.
Get out of here.
You won't reconsider?
Stop blabbering.
This world is mine!
"Mine."
How very human to think like that.
You leave me no choice.
Miss Iwama.
There is a system error.
If you leave now, I don't mind
letting you off easy.
Now go!
Leave?
It's too late for that now.
Too late?
That's right.
It's too late.
What are you talking about?
Hurry up and get out of my network!
Your network?
No, now it's my network.
What’s going on?
What did I just tell you?
Adams, delete the system.
Erase the virus.
That won't work.
You should hurry and run away before
your network disappears completely.
What in the world is going on?
Adams, bring me back to normal.
That’s impossible.
Please give up, Miss Mitsune.
Will you allow me to build the gate?
I'm not asking to do it free of charge.
What the hell?
In exchange, I'll give you
the greatest pleasure.
No!
What is all this? No!
It hurts... Stop!
Stop?
Don't you always do the
same thing to others?
It hurts!
S-Sto–
I can't believe I had so much
trouble with that thing.
It's pathetic.
Shit.
You should have called me,
since you're injured.
Shiori?
I told you not to come out on your own.
Opening the seal by yourself
is a breach of contract.
Oh? I don't remember making
a contract with you.
My master is and always
will be Kaname-sama.
The same goes for you, Mitsurugi.
I'm your master right now!
That's right. He told me to listen to you.
At least for the time being.
Don't push it!
Why are you always like that?
What do you mean?
You only call us when you're
facing a weak enemy.
Whenever it actually gets dangerous,
you always do it alone.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I don't want anyone getting in my
way when I'm fighting seriously.
So what would happen if you lost?
You were seriously injured.
Your body isn't yours alone, you know.
Every time you get injured,
Kaname-sama also...
So that's what this is all about.
No! What are you doing?
Stop it, Mitsurugi!
Aren't you supposed to listen to me?
No...
You can really run your mouth,
but you're lagging behind down here.
No.
Spread your legs.
No, not that.
Here I go.
It hurts!
So rough... I'll break.
Shiori...
N-No! This is too embarrassing!
Wait, please.
I understand how you feel, Shiori.
But I have my own way of doing things.
I'll protect Kaname-sama.
There will definitely come a time
when I'll rely on all of you.
Until then...
No...
All you girls have to do is believe in me.
Now I understand how you feel.
I'll believe in you. And so will the others.
That's right.
Wha–
Y-You two! When did you...
They came out of their seals
at the same time I did.
Seriously. Our master always needs
to have everything his own way.
Master, I'll try my hardest from now on.
"Trying your hardest" is
meaningless in your case.
What do you mean by that?
I mean just what I said.
You should start off by
learning how to assist us.
You brats!
Are you saying I can only
pull half my weight?
More like a quarter.
What do you mean by that?
Go back into your seals already!
Honestly...
Well, I'll tell you this much.
There's no point in just killing.
Recently, demons of her level have
become much more numerous.
Have you heard the rumor that
the gate's been opened?
It's true that demons have
recently been appearing often.
And they're all in such a small area.
It's as if they're being
drawn in by something.
What...
exactly...
is going on!?
Acid?
Well, I'll tell you this much:
There's no point in just killing.
You've got it all wrong!
This is my duty.
I wonder what this is all leading up to.
I'm gonna cum.
Huh?
No.
Why?
Why did you stop?
Hey!
More, please. Give me more!
Don't stop. I want more, more!
So how about it?
Will you grant me that favor?
If you do, this pleasure will be
yours for the rest of your life.
I'll do it. I'll do anything you ask.
So please...
Thank you.
Well then,
I'll open the gate to the Demon Realm.
So the gate has opened again.
Mitsurugi, this is how I do things.
This is my mission.
You damned fools!
Kaname, have you noticed it?
Yes.
The gate has been opened.
Things are about to get nasty.
How many centuries has it been
since you became my master?
It has been a while.
And all this time, you haven't grown.
You haven't had the choice
of ending your life.
You've kept sealing demons.
I can step down once the
next master appears.
Isn't that right?
Yeah.
I understand, Mitsurugi.
Our mission is to seal demons.
If we kill them, the balance with the
Demon Realm will be disturbed.
Both worlds will be ruined.
The battle that is about to begin
will be beyond vicious.
It's all right.
I'm not alone.
Shiori and the others are with me.
And so are you, Mitsurugi.
You are my master.
I serve you.
I protect you.
I fight alongside you.
Let's fight, Mitsurugi, as all the
masters before me have.
Good morning, Shiori.
Kaname-sama.
Yes, the gate has opened.
It's been opened.
Then we should seal it right away!
Dummy! Don't make it sound so simple.
We don't even know where it is.
What's with you?
Quit it, you two.
You can't help but fight
whenever you see each other.
Let’s leave it at that.
As Kusuka said, the first
challenge is finding the gate.
We can't allow demons to get any
closer to people than they are.
Mitsurugi and I will give it our all,
so lend me your strength.
We will, Kaname-sama.
Good.
Let's head out.
Damon Hunters
Part 2
aoi hikari hashirinuke
Outrun the blue light
hametsu no tobira hiraku toki
when the gates of destruction open
hikari no honoo kanashimi no kaze
A flame of light, a wind of despair
dareka ga kimi wo yondeiru
Someone is calling you
mou zankan yobisamase mune no oku kara
Zankan! Awaken in the depths of your heart
mou zankan dokiharae mugen no chikara wo
Zankan! Wield your limitless power
harukana jikai wa toki wo koe
A far-off meeting surpasses time
in no kagayaki ga kakeru keru
The brilliance is missing from the shadow
yami wo kirisake muteki no yaiba Mitsurugi
Pierce through the darkness, invincible blade Mitsurugi
kuroki arashi fukiarete
A black wind blows violently
hijou no sadame semaru toki
as the appointed time draws near
inochi wo iyasu daichi no inori
The foremost prayer is to spare life
dareka ga kimi wo motomete iru
Someone is seeking you
mou zankan tachiagare yuuki wo daite
Zankan! Stand up, and embrace courage
mou zankan sora wo kake imawashii uwa donaru
Zankan! Fly in the sky, and shout obscenely
mesameyou tamashii toki wo koe
Surpass time, awakened soul,
ashita no kidou mamoru tame
to protect the path tomorrow takes
yami ni kirameku seigi no yaiba Mitsurugi
The justice that shines in the darkness,
invincible blade Mitsurugi
mou zankan yobisamase mune no oku kara
Zankan! Awaken in the depths of your heart
mou zankan dokiharae mugen no chikara wo
Zankan! Wield your limitless power
harukana jikai wa toki wo koe
A far-off meeting surpasses time
in no kagayaki ga kakeru keru
The brilliance is missing from the shadow
yami wo kirisake muteki no yaiba Mitsurugi
Pierce through the darkness, invincible blade Mitsurugi
What was that just now?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I just had the feeling that
something was approaching.
Oh, no!
is it something scary?
It's all right.
I'm here with you.
Now calm down and continue.
Okay.
Good.
That's all you have to do.
Just stay like that.
You're my precious link
connected to the gate.
Just stay like that a little longer.