Adult Toys
Today after school, the three of
us are playing together again.
Translation Snake | Timing: v1 touch^Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by erobeat | httpV/www eraeeit.net | #erobeat @ ircr.rizon.net
Suzuno! How's this? Good?
Lick me, too!
Yes...
Your fellatio has been getting better and better recently.
Suzuno can do it if she tries.
You two much be so in love.
I'm pulling out the vibrator, Okay?
I'll take the one behind.
I know, I know.
They're going in...
It's... it's amazing...
No...
Hamura-kun's and Inogashira-kun's are...
rubbing inside!
Suzuno's butt feels really, really good!
Suzuno you're so cute! You're really feeling
it from being praised by Kouta, right?
That's... that's not...
No... no more!
Amazing!
Suzuno... Cumming!
N-No!
There's so much of both of you guy's semen...
Let's play together tomorrow as well.
Of course.
Let's try this tomorrow!
Huh? What is that?
Its been a month since then, and
my life has been dramatic.
It seems that I have started to
attract many Spirits of lust...
I get frequently violated by them in all kinds of places.
I think... I'm going to go crazy...
No... not my butt as well..
It feels too good!
My senses are controlled, and I'm bombarded
by intense pleasure non-stop.
I am raped until the spirit is satisfied and passes on.
When I tried asking help from a psychic at school....
That's the first time I've met anyone
with a problem that serious.
I'll try to look up some countermeasures,
but for now you'll have to help them pass
on like that Good luck with that.
The spirit today seemed to have been a
person with extremely strong desires.
I was violated for the whole day,
and when everything ended,
it was already midnight.
It's seems like the spirits have
different kinds of attachments.
For the most part, they'll pass on
if I satisfy them with regular sex.
But occasionally there are also spirits who
like gangbang that come in groups,
and I'm raped continuously until all of them are satisfied.
It's a lot of trouble.
How many more of you are there!?
Cumming...
I'm cumming!
Let me... go already..
If this goes on, my body won't hold.
With quite a bit of money, I tried
buying some so-called amulets.
So you have appeared!
It doesn't work'?
No! Even though it cost me 50,000 yen!
It'd be great if something is done about this already.
Extermination of ghosts?
Oh, I forgot...
Um...
Where am I?
Thank goodness, you're awake.
Here.
You were lying unconscious in front of my house,
So I thought I'd bring you back to rest at least
But why did you faint in the middle of the road?
Me? On the road?
Ouch...
Huh?
Um... strange... I can't... remember anything...
Your Memory
Even your name?
Nope.
Or your address and stuff?
Oh dear...
Um... err... then...
Have you also forgotten that I'm your boyfriend? Err...
Huh? You're my...
Shoot, I said it.
Um, err...
Miku • XXX-School Student's Crazy Sex -
Your name is Miku, and...
you've been, err, dating me for about half a year.
I'm sorry... even after hearing my own
name, I can't remember a thing.
Even though a boyfriend is such an important person...
Bam!
It's fine!
As long as we work hard together until Miku remembers...
For now, I'll just make sure you're
not hurt anywhere else, so...
Take off your clothes.
Eh?
Stop!
Ah... Crap!
Um, so, we've been going out so we've
seen each other already, so...
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Huh?
Was it like that?
It was, it was!
Though I am lying...
Although it's embarrassing, I'd hurt him
if I'm unwilling because I forgot.
and I guess its normal if we were dating each other...
But I don't remember so it's the same as the first time!
Looks like you're fine here.
Um...
C'mon, Miku-chan!
Hmm? Is this place slightly swollen?
That place... it's not... swollen so...
It's fine...
Heh, I know.
Then, why are you doing this?
If we do it like usual, maybe you'll
remember something, right?
We do this, all the time?
That's right, stuff like this, or this!
You cant press my nipples like that!
No!
Are you still not remembering anything?
No... I'm sorry...
Then... then let's do other stuff, too!
Maybe this will do.
Eh? What's this? It's so embarrassing!
Hey, Miku, don't take them off!
You're always really happy with these on!
Let's work hard together so you remember!
No, you can't.. I was licked so much...
they've become... sensitive...
C'mon, show me here, too.
No!
You can't!
Don't resist.
Chance!
No!
Amazing, Miku.
Although you have no memory
you remember to feel good!
Even your butt hole is soaked.
No!
There.
What are you doing?
It's fine, don't worry.
No... not like this...
C'mon, you loved this, right?
I'll put it in now.
Amazing, it's going in.
Is it that good?
See? Only three more.
Its completely inside Miku!
No... no!
Still not remembering..
Oh dear...
Guess it won't work unless it's mine, huh?
Geez, there's no helping it then.
No, that's...
No, you can't!
There, all the way in!
It's... rubbing... inside...
Yes...
I'm gonna cum!
I'll give it to you inside!
No! You can't!
Ah... I came so hard...
Looks like we still need to do more, huh?
I said it's finel
C'mon, don't feel restrained in front of your boyfriend.
No... Ouch!
Oh, that's right...
I... I remember now...
My name... isn't Miku or anything..
Huh? So you remember?
I... don't have a boyfriend!
Someone... I don't., know... has their penis... inside...
Even though... this is wrong...
Ah, sorry about that!
It feels so good, I can't stop!
No! Take it out!
A stranger's penis... feels good!
No... a stranger's penis... is making me go crazy!
My butt., it's going out!
So cruel... something like this...
I m sorry!
I really didn't mean to do this!
You were just so cute, I couldn't help but use
those toys I bought but never used before.
Um, so my memory is back... and you did help me...
I'll be back to thank you properly.
Um, so err, can I get your name?
My name is...
You can't!
Huh? Why? Not my name, either?
I'll see you.
That's because... I can Impossibly say
that a stranger's feels better.