Orgasm Rocket
Translation: Snake | Timing: v1 touch | Typeset & Encode: ShocWave
Presented by Erobeat | http://www.erobeat.net | #erobeat @ irc.rizon.net
Yes!
Amazing, Takano-kun!
I've never felt this good before!
You re able to... make me... feel this good, so...
Have more confidence... in yourself!
Yes!
Takano-kun's penis!
Thanks to your help, manager, I've
been able to do my best recently.
Thank you very much.
Great to know!
Takano-kun's been a little off recently,
so it's nice to have you back.
But, getting you to do that much... sorry about it.
It's fine! I felt really good, too.
Besides, it's my also my job to keep track
of you guys' health and mental states.
I am the manager, after all.
Taking applications! Apply Now!!
I'm really not the type to be captain...
If I'm going to end up as trouble for everyone else...
I should really quit.
You're doing fine as captain!
I'm sure everyone appreciates your work!
I've always been looking at... how hard you work so...
You shouldn't have to worry about things all alone!
You can tell me anything!
Captain's is... coming in!
Deep inside...
As captain, I'm really not proficient enough!
That's not true!
It's because that captain is here,
that everyone can work as one...
Let out all your troubles... along with your penis-milk!
Cumming!
I'll take care of all your worries!
I feel really refreshed now thanks to you, manager.
Thanks.
Great.
Aun Hospital
Is your foot alright?
Yeah...
I'll visit you every day until Ookawa-kun
gets well, so cheer up!
Manager... I haven't done it in a while... this is kinda bad...
I'll cum right away!
It's fine...
It's coming in!
Hot stuff is coming right away!
Let out more hot stuff inside!
Itou-kun lacks stamina...
So we'll be doing special training at lunch every day!
More! Move around more roughly!
Sports Equipment Storage
No... no...
Manager... it seems like this position
is the easiest to move in.
I see... be sure to find the best position
for yourself, Takehara-kun!
Club activities! I wonder if anyone will be there already!
Don't joke around! That's completely your fault!
What did you say!? Are you starting a fight!?
Stop it! What if you get hurt!
Manager...
Don't stop us! This guy won't
understand with just words!
What!?
Don't get too full of yourself!
Geez! You two are always fighting!
If you really hate each other like that,
why don't you have a match right now, and
the loser will listen to what the winner says!
The person who makes the manager
cum more times will win, alright?
I know.
I won't lose to you!
Not my nipples...
I'm cumming from my nipples!
One point for me to start with.
Damn, like I'd lose!
My pussy...
I just came!
I'll go crazy...
We're even now.
Amazing... she's soaked...
Here we go.
It's going in my butt... too...
Who's was that?
I guess it was the two of us at once, so it doesn't count.
I'm cumming again... cumming from my butt...
Coming from my pussy...
You're pretty good.
You, too...
No... I'm going to cum again!
Both sides feel good...
No... it's so good!
It feels good because the two
of you are doing it together!
I'm cumming again... I'll cum again and again!
Both of you feel so good!
I didn't know you were this good. Sorry about earlier.
No, I was the one amazed by your ability.
Let's work harder together from now on.
Hey, what are you guys doing in an empty classroom?
In addition to being lectured, the
three of us got suspended.
Oh and, all of us don't actually have club activities.
That movie was really interesting.
Yeah, it was fun.
Um, um... ﻿
I don't want to go home ye-
No.
You should go home and study. Don't
you have exams next week?
Here, we're at your house.
See you! I'll text you!
I had to bring my courage up to say that...
Huh?
You went that far and nothing!?
Yeah... even though I tried...
I would start doing it right after dating each other!
But that's... actually I think that's how it should be.
But you've been together for half a year already, right?
More accurately, six months and twelve days...
You don't have to be that accurate...
I wonder if it would be better if I were
sexy and bimbo-ish like Yuna...
Who are you calling a bimbo!
Then, why don't you just make the approach?
Huh? How do I...
Alright, let's go to my house so I can teach you about it!
But., the exam...
I've got books and videos, too, so it'll be fine!
Girls with Tough Measures
Yes, he's fast asleep.
Well I guess he wakes up at 8 every day.
If it's someone like your guy, you can
just assault him during his sleep.
So Tomokazu-san sleeps in his underwear...
Here we go...
Woah, it looks just like the ones in the videos!
It's delicate, so be sure to treat it gently.
It's really soft... so it really is a vital point for guys...
This... I think this is what I should do...
Woah, it's hot!
After taking it in, you can try sucking on it with your lips,
or wrapping around it with your
tongue and lick the back side.
Apparently it feels good.
Tomokazu-san's penis... is getting really hard!
Hey, what are you doing!
You can't do this, hey...
Yuki...
It's Tomokazu-san's fault!
You completely get my hints but you never make a move!
That's because...
Listen up. I can understand if
you don't find me attractive...
But I can't hold back anymore!
I'll do everything, so please stay still!
Or else, I'll crush this!
Yes...
Push hard!
Tomokazu-san looks like he feels really good!
I want to be connected with him already...
What would it feel like?
But, what if Tomokazu-san doesn't want
to do it with someone like me?
What do I do??
But.. I don't want to stop here!
Hey, Yuki... not somewhere like that...
Yuki...
Sorry, Yuki.
I really treasured you,
so I thought I'd hold back and wait until
I can take proper responsibility...
I actually really want to do it with you...
There's no way I could fine you unattractive.
But I ended up stressing you to
do stuff like this... I'm sorry.
Tomokazu-san...
I... Did these things...
You won't hate me for this... right?
Of course I won't! You surprised me a bit but...
It’s not like I don't like these types of things.
So it's fine if I go on and do it for you, right?
Yeah...
If it hurts then bear the pain!
Ouch... it's inside!
So much of Tomokazu-san inside...
It hurts... but...
Start moving your hips after you put
it in! Here, just like in this video!
Yuki... it hurts, doesn't it?
Don't push yourself.
It hurts... but...
I'm finally connected with Tomokazu-san!
I don't want to separate yet!
I'm really happy right now...
Because... I really love Tomokazu-san...
Yuki...
You can't!
So rough!
No, don't move it!
I'm... gonna...
Sorry, Yuki... if it does happen, I'll take responsibility.
It's fine... let it out... inside!
Amazing! Tomokazu-san s is flowing inside me...
Hot stuff is flowing out...
Tomokazu-san!
We'll be doing it every day from now on, get it?
Y-Yes...
We're making up for the times we didn't do it before!
Prepare yourself.
By the way... where did you learn stuff like that?
The butt... and stuff... from videos?
Videos, and books of course, I read
them carefully and studied hard.
And in the end I tried it with a friend.
Well she was a girl so it is a little different...
A friend... and more importantly a girl
did those kinds of things with me!
And it felt good...
This is like... a whole new world...