Is it okay now?
Yes...
ZERO SUM GAME
Congratulations for being number
one on the first week.
Thank you.
Oh, it's Zero Sum.
Keith, you guys are so popular.
Your album is selling like crazy.
Hey, isn't Keith the singer
one of your underclassmen?
Back from my high school.
Romance?
Yes! You're so popular, I bet
the girls never leave you alone.
They still send you tickets right?
Would you ask one for me, please?
Hmm... I guess I'll give them a call,
since it's been a while.
Really! I'm so happy! Thank you!
Hey...
Love won't mean a thing unless
you're loved by the one you love.
Hey, cut that out.
Here, I'll do it Yuuka.
It tickles...
Enjoy the delight of traveling
Cover yourself with the
delightful voice
The hair violently swaying
Oh! You should stay away from me
It's not your fault
for my heart tormenting
How far
All of us
Did we travel?
I don't remember
the words I believed in
Please forgive everything
To live is to always be yourself
Recollect the precious memories
All of us
Shove everything
If we do that
It will be all right
In my room there will be the memories
and the values that we share
Since the beginning when I met you
I felt compassionate about you
Job well done!
Whew.
Mr. Saeki, someone came to see you.
Who is it?
He said you'll know
Yazaki from Minami high school.
Hey Saeki.
Big bro!
She is...
Hi, nice to meet you.
I am Tokano Yuuka.
I was being shallow, Big bro.
I didn't know you had a cute girlfriend.
Haha... Oh yeah, why don't you
line up for a picture?
Don't be shy Yuuka.
Yea.
There, stand next to him.
It's natural looking right?
Saeki, the hand is too much.
Move it!
Big bro, don't worry.
It's not like you're gonna lose her.
I was just...
Now, congratulations on the success
of the national tour, cheers!
Cheers!
Is it ok to join your after party?
The more people there are,
the more excitement we have.
Thanks.
Here Big bro, drink up!
Great!
Hahaha...
Haha...
Huh?
Hey, don't you think
you're drinking too much?
Really?
Big bro, do you remember
the math teacher with the wig?
Yea, the barcode right?
Haha, I do remember!
Excuse me, where's the restroom?
It's out the door, to your right.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Why thank you.
Sorry to bother you guys.
Hey, who was that girl?
Isn't she one of our fans
who followed us here?
Hmm...
Yea, I'm not the guy
who dislike music or anything.
Shall we eat?
Umm... is it this way?
Huh?
No! What are you gonna do?
Hey, aren't you one of our fans?
No, I'm not like that.
Come on, isn't this what you came for?
No, somebody help me!
Shut the hell up.
Huh?
You have to be nicer to girls.
Yea, no fair, you get all the fun.
See you later!
Nice job today!
Hey Keith.
Huh?
Where is Kimihiko and the others?
I don't know. Maybe they're in
the middle of their fun.
Man, I told them not to put their
hands on the fans.
Nothing I can do.
Keith, the taxi's here.
Then see you later.
Take care of this guy, will you?
Are you okay?
Where's Yuuka?
She left earlier.
Yuuka...
Stop it!
Isn't it an honor to fuck with
the Zero Sum band?
No!
Wow, you have a sexy body.
It's worth fucking.
No!
Hey, hey, stick your ass out more.
Stop it...
I can't hold it any longer.
Let me go to the restroom.
Oh yeah, you were still trying to go.
Then why don't you piss right here
while I'm fucking you.
Aaah...
Come on.
No...
No~!
No, no...
No!
I'm cumming... No~!
I won't let that bitch have Yazaki.
What are you looking at?
Excuse me.
Big bro...
I have always loved you, and only you.
Even if you didn't love me back.
Hehehe...
Yazaki...
Hi, this is Tomoko. I can't answer
the phone so leave a message!
This is Yazaki.
Please call me after you hear this.
What happened to you?
You've been gone for a week and
don't even pick up your phone.
Hello?
Huh? Sorry, I've been sick for a while.
Hmm, I see. Putting that aside...
Huh?
What happened?
Heh?
With Yazaki!
Didn't you have dinner at the hotel
for your anniversary?
Yea...
It wasn't just a dinner right?
Confess!
Sorry, I don't want to talk about it
now...
Hey.
I wanted to talk with you...
What! Isn't that Keith from Zero Sum?
How did you meet him Yuuka?
I've heard.
My band members did some
awful things to you.
I know it's not to be excused.
Forget it...
I just want to forget it
like nothing happened.
So please don't tell Yazaki about it.
If it's okay with you...
Are you free right now?
Huh?
Can you hang around a little more?
Isn't that Keith?
Keith from Zero Sum?
Yea, that's him.
He sure looks bold.
Pretty soon he'll be in the headlines.
Something like "A New Lover!"
So jealous of a celebrity boyfriend.
But having celebrity lovers must
be really stressful I bet.
Concerned?
Umm...
This is my normal face.
Is it okay if I go with you?
If I bring a date, the girls
leave me alone, so it helps me.
The pasta is delicious here.
Eat up!
What...
Sure...
Man, it's good!
Hehe...
You finally laughed.
Thank you for today.
I'll invite you another time.
Huh?
Yazaki...
Yuuka!
I was worried,
I couldn't get a hold of you.
I'm glad I got to see you.
Yazaki...
I'll forget about that day.
What's the matter?
Want me to stop?
No, it's nothing.
Let's continue.
Yuuka.
Great...
No, no...
Why don't you take a piss
while I'm fucking!
Stop it...
No~!
No, no~!
Yuuka?
Sorry, I...
No, I'm sorry.
I got a little too excited.
No...
Let's take it slowly.
We'r e together forever.
Oh yea, today at school...
Huh?
Nothing...
I love you, Yazaki.
I love it...
I love your cock Keith.
Bitch, you got my dick dirty
with your pussy juice, so clean it.
Hey, call me again.
Can't help this...
Hey, it's her. Do you know her?
Keith came to pick her up again.
The English major right?
Are they together?
Look, he's here again.
But don't the fans of Zero Sum
have something to say?
Those girls are so scary.
But I still envy it.
I love you, Yuuka.
Me too, Yazaki.
Good, good!
Yuuka...
Me, me too Yazaki!
What are you playing d umb for?
Huh?
I'm Keith.
Where's Yazaki?
Silly, how can Yazaki be here?
I'm your boyfriend, Yuuka.
No, I...
That's why we're making love like this.
Right guys?
Hahaha...
It's useless trying to run.
No, let go of me!
I forgot about you guys.
Impossible.
Your body still remembers.
See, your ass is moving along.
Keith...
You wanted to fuck Keith right?
I was just...
We'll fuck for him.
Stop it! No, no...
Yazaki...
Yes...
It's Yazaki.
We need to talk.
When I'm done with work,
I'm thinking of coming over if it's okay.
Okay.
If I talk with Yazaki,
he will understand.
Is this paper true?
Yea.
Keith stopped by my campus one day
and had some tea.
How many times did you two meet?
Umm... three, four, maybe five times...
Hmm...
I wonder why Keith would ask you out.
My band members did some
awful thing to you.
I can't say the truth.
At first it was a surprise.
You know how my friends are fans of
Zero Sum.
So the next time we met,
I went with my friends.
Then why didn't you tell me about it?
Because, I didn't want you
to be worried.
All right, I believe what you're saying.
I'm going home today.
Yazaki, sorry I...
Good night.
Yazaki...
Sorry...
Sorry, Sorry...
Don't go away, Yazaki!
You're famous and handsome and
all the girls fall for you.
I got a little excited, but Yazaki is
the most important person...
...and I don't want him to suffer.
But I still...
Huh? What ar e you laughing for?
I'm just imagining Big bro going crazy
after he hears about you being used.
It's funny thinking about it.
Tears.
That's why bitches ar e sneaky.
Big bro, how many times
did you hold her?
I wonder how his tongue, his fingers
touched all over her body.
This spot, Yazaki's cock has been
sliding
and pumping his love juice inside.
Big bro...
I only want it once.
I want Big bro to hold me.
I want to touch his skin.
I want him to fuck me here and
spill all his love juice in me!
Hey!
Nakano, Nakano, next is Nakano.
Don't worry. If you don't say anything,
we'll keep our mouths shut.
I feel sorry for Big bro for
being played by a slut like her.
I love Yazaki...
Big bro, I...
...love you always!
You...
...I love you?