Yes?
Hey there, Takumi-Kun!
Good day!
Woah!
Takumi-Kun?
And I'm, Sex chan!
We've brought a new license just for you!
Even if you say that...
Takumi-Kun, You're too slow on the uptake.
They're our anti-population decline mascots!
Don't you think they're cute?
Ena-san?
This time,
I've brought you a Sex Tool License!
We've also brought you an entire set of adult toys.
Adult toys?
That's right. As long as you have this license.
No...!
I'm being raped by these tentacles!
I'm being stirred up deeply inside.
I'm going to cum with these things inside of me!
That hurts!
No anal please!
I'm going to break.
My asshole, and my pussy are going to break!
That Sex Tool License is the best!
No, that's way beyond what you can call as "adult toys".
Who cares?
I have no other role here than to be the one to give you these.
Also,
I have other weird licenses here,
like this Fellatio license, or this Tittyfuck license....
Just Think of it as some kind of a reward, and enjoy yourself with them.
Other than those, there is just one more
license left for us to give you.
One last license?
What kind is it?
That's a secret for now.
compulsory child-making
Page 2 ~Completely cummed inside~
Hey Takumi!
It'll get dark soon if you don't move faster.
Don't you even want to help me a little bit here?
Oh, but men are happy and consider it courteous
to carry heavy things for women.
I think the rule was called...ladies first?
You're quite far from its meaning.
The theme sounds the same though.
Okay, okay, move first before complaining.
Besides, it helps train the muscles too, right?
Damn, what a bitch.
That's not what you call a boy and girl going out together.
It seems as if they're already newlyweds!
It can't be helped.
Onii-chan and the others already did it.
But, how do I put it...
If feels as if something is pricking deep inside my heart.
Yeah, I also feel a bit fuzzy about it
Oh yeah!
We don't have to just sit by and watch!
Because Takumi and his thing doesn't really belong to her!
Sara-san?
Hey, Sara,
what's with that outfit?
I heard from Himari,
that you like these things. Am I wrong?
Well, I don't hate it, but...
If you're still not satisfied with this, then...
Hey what are you doing Sara?
There, this would arouse you, right?
Your perverted self!
Geez, you really are helpless, aren't you?
Your thing got hard so quickly.
We kind of went overboard last time,
The tip is starting to drip with lewd liquids~nya.
And it's already this twitchy.
I never thought that this perverted thing of yours
Lovely?
It's my own expression!
So it works better here, huh?
Hey are you okay?
I'm fine, no problem.
It's your first blowjob, and you're already very good at it.
Of course I am.
I researched, and researched everything about it.
My thing even reaches your throat...
Try to think of it as the womb.
Think of it as the spot to be filled quickly later.
It's sucking me in!
Here, does this feel good~nya?
It's coming out.
Come on, let it out.
Now cum, I'm going for the tip again.
How is it?
With my technique, you'll soon be...
What's this?
I was surprised.
So men also pee uncontrollably like that.
I can't hold on any longer.
I'm about to cum.
I'm cumming.
Sa-Sara, I'm letting it out.
Drink it Sara.
I'm cumming...!
I-It's coming out!
No one just bursts out wildly like that you fool!
That's amazing, Sara-san.
She really did a cosplay sex.
My thing down here is like this now too.
What should I do?
I didn't want it to turn out like this...
So? How does the sensation of my carnal
lust creeping slowly inside you feel?
Just what are you planning to do with this?
Thanks to my special masochistic training, you
are now a hundred times more sensitive!
How did it become like this?
As long as you are unable to resist the urge to do it,
you will forever be stained by my carnal lust!
Oh no, it's getting deep inside.
What's wrong?
Keep your horny ass moving!
And forever swear your wet and wild loyalty,
to your supreme ruler and master!
Still persistent, eh?
How about this then!
This is too much.
It's getting deep inside me.
When fucked like this, it's only a matter
of time before breaking down,
even for a champion of love.
It's hitting my womb.
Oh no, I'm going to cum while being penetrated deep inside.
His cum will be poured in me...
I'm cumming!
No, he really came inside...
We're not finished yet!
True hell starts from here.
There, there!
Don't, I'm going to break.
I'm going to break!
Submit to your master!
I'm cumming!
I won't resist anymore,
so please violate me more with your cock!
Goodgirl.
Fall down!
Into the never ending realm of dreams!
It's being sucked in...
It's pouring in.
Lots of semen is being poured inside me.
Oh no...
Lots of it is coming out.
It was an agreement.
I lost, so you can do whatever you want to my body.
But you're already this wet.
You just want to be done, don't you?
Shut up! Just do it!
I will, and I'll push it in deeply for you.
It's at my very inside...
You want it done intensely, right?
And you're the pervert who already
has his cock twitching wildly inside!
Here, take this!
It's wet to the core.
I never thought you'd get really horny like this.
Shut up, and don't say I'm horny.
You make it sound like I'm some nymphomaniac!
I'm going to cum inside.
That's not what we agreed on!
I'm cumming inside!
He's cumming deep inside me...
I sure came a lot.
I'm not yet satisfied with this.
Let's ramp up the intensity!
Let me go.
Let's end this already.
My pussy is tingling and I'm getting very sensitive.
I'm camming.
Look, and you just came by yourself.
Don't stop and keep it up.
Do it more like this!
Oh no!
I'm about to cum.
Take this!
Don't, any more of this and I'll really be pregnant!
I'm cumming!
It's coming out.
It's coming out inside me.
Now I'm going to get pregnant for real.
His hot semen is...
That was quite good.
With you cumming like this, it's definite that I'll get pregnant.
Please, I also want Onii-chan's stiff and hot cock in me!
I wish he would take notice of me that way too.
This is embarrassing Onii-chan.
I can't hold on anymore, Himari.
No...
I'm going to totally check you up.
What?
Your virgin pussy is twitching a lot.
No!
Onii-chan, don't look!
Himari, your thing looks very beautiful.
No!
Onii-chan, don't do this!
Wow, it's really wet.
My fingers are getting sucked in and it won't let go!
Your nipples are also becoming hard.
No, something's coming.
No, no, no!
No...
Bad Himari.
You shouldn't just pee like that.
This is your punishment then.
Himari, you look very horny.
I can't hold it back any longer!
I'll release your punishment in your mouth!
I'm about to cum.
I'm camming.
I'm going to cum inside your mouth Himari.
Be sure to drink it all.
You drank It all?
Good girl, Himari.
This is your reward then.
I'm inserting it in now.
It's in.
It's wrapping me tight.
Onii-chan is thrusting inside me.
Oh no...l'm having sex with Onii-chan.
And we're doing it in this embarrassing position.
I'm about to cum!
I'm starting to feel weird
No...!
It's coming out, it's all coming out in me.
His semen is coming out inside my womb.
And I came.
I came, while he came inside.
Everyone's getting really horny, eh?
Things are rolling along smoothly.
We're going by train today tor our shopping?
But we usually do it at the station, right?
It just feels embarrassing to do It at our local place.
Do this I mean.
Today I'll be your special comfort station.
Do whatever you please, Takumi.
Saki-nee?
Let's do it here, okay?
Right now? Right at this spot?
But you already did it with Rin in front of many people, right?
That's because my license was approved
at that time so I had no choice.
Then use your license to do me too then.
What?
If you don't I'll just be treated as a train pervert.
A-Alright already.
So, how does it feel with me?
It feels better due to the shaking of the vibrators, right?
Wow...
Saki-nee, it feels really good.
You're already this stiff..
Everyone's looking at us, so I feel very weird.
It's alright.
Why don't we show it to them then?
What the cock of a teenage boy looks like.
I'm sure it's going to be a rare unforgettable sight one
which they will not have a chance to see again!
The tip of my cock feels tingly, I'm about to...
It's okay, let It out.
Use my boobs as your onahole, and cum!
Spray it all over my face!
The people around here feel grateful for us.
You can insert it in now.
Inside my wet pussy.
It's completely A-ok.
Yes!
It's thick and stiff!
Your cock has completely gone inside!
Everyone's looking at me.
They're looking at my boobs, and my pussy.
All of them can see our sex clearly!
Saki-nee, they're taking pictures.
It's alright.
We're going to show them more of our sex!
This would feel a lot better if we just enjoy it, you know?
It's thrusting wildly in me.
Rub it in me more!
This position...
Everyone can see it clearly.
Saki-nee.
I'm going to cum inside.
Everyone's taking pictures of us.
Of our embarrassing sight.
We're going to become their masturbating material.
I've become really perverted.
I feel excited at each flash.
I feel like cumming.
My pussy feels like it's going to flutter.
Please cum.
Cum inside my pussy.
I'm cumming!
Wow, there's a lot of semen in me.
Oh, he sure came a lot there.
At this rate, in no time they'll..
8 months later
So this is the last license, huh?
Pregnant Sex License
Takumi Ibuki
Is it really okay for me to use this?
It's okay.
I've been holding out for a long time anyway.
My body line has changed so I feel embarrassed.
Really?
You look really beautiful as you are now Rin.
Thank you.
My breasts have grown so much, they're now more sensitive.
And they're also like this now.
It's hot.
You look very horny when drenched in your own milk.
No, please don't say such weird things.
My breasts are bulging and they feel tingly.
Please give me your milk, Takumi.
You can cum this way.
Sorry I came a lot.
Lots of it came out...
It's been a long time so I feel really aroused.
It's thick, and hard.
No, don't squeeze my breasts!
We'll have to get milk from that as soon as possible.
It's coming out.
Wow, your insides are trying to squeeze my cock.
It feels so good I just can't stop.
I'm about to cum.
Oh no, if you keep on thrusting intensely like that..
I'm cumming.
I'm cumming!
Please give it to me.
Please pour all of your semen into my womb.
I'm cumming again.
It's flowing in.
It's trying to get into my womb.
You came a lot...
Lots and lots of it...
Oh, you've started already?
I see.
So the last license was the Pregnant Sex License.
The room reeks of her boob's scent.
It feels very horny.
That's just not good.
Because that license isn't just restricted to Rin, you know?
Look, my boobs have already grown this big too.
I've held on to not having sex until the 4th month.
My nether regions are already itching for it.
I want to have sex.
I won't be able to handle you all at the same time!
Everyone's bearing your child, Takumi.
So it's your responsibility and obligation to make us all feel good.
You got that right!
That's still part of our anti population decline strategy anyway.
Because your sex license,
needs to be used no matter what!