No! No!
No!
Zoku Gosenzo San'e
Episode 2: Furnace
So you're saying both of those girls...
They both lost their memory.
And both had fang marks on their necks.
Could it be...
It's highly unlikely that there are other
vampires like Beth at the school.
But if it's true, then as commissioner,
and as a member of the Hiraga family,
I can't turn my back on this.
And you want me to investigate this?
We still have no solid proof.
Incidents continue to happen.
And we mustn't draw attention to ourselves.
Good point, but if a westerner like me investigates,
won't I draw attention to the case?
I've already set things in motion.
Well, we'll be back!
Have a nice day.
Bye.
Wait a minute.
What?
What are you...
Wh-What the hell was that for?
A-Ayumi!
See? Jennifer just threw herself at me!
It was a goodbye kiss.
"Goodbye"?
Yes. Sakura-san gave me a new assignment.
It's a pretty serious job,
so I'm done taking care of you.
But that's so sudden!
Are you going back to America?
See you again.
I see. Take care.
Oh, Gen! One more please!
Oh Gen, I love you. Kiss me, my sweetheart!
Um, there are people watching.
So I'd cut it out if I were you.
Ah, it's just an American custom. It's no big deal.
Looked like a big deal to me.
Then you get one too!
Bye.
You're wearing lipstick.
So are you, Ayumi.
It's not really a big deal.
Like she says, a kiss is just customary.
And besides, we've already...
Whatever!
Hey!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Oh, thank you.
Did you get in a fight?
I just said "Good morning" to Ayumi-chan,
but she ignored me.
She had a handkerchief up to her
mouth, and her face was red, too.
Did you make her cry?
That's not it at all.
Then what is it?
It doesn't matter.
I guess not.
You look pale.
I'm a bit lightheaded again.
I've felt this way all morning.
Should I take you to the infirmary?
Nope.
But if you kiss me, I might get better.
Don't tease me!
But it's no big deal. It's just a custom.
Did you see that?
Is that American woman your lover?
Lover? N-No, she's not!
You're panicking.
Listen, just because we kissed doesn't mean...
Doesn't mean anything, right?
That's what you said, at least.
Though while we're on the subject, apparently you did
something even more impressive with Ayumi-chan.
Don't worry. If I breathe some outside air, I'll feel better.
Hey! What did you mean by...
I'm skipping first period. Tell me what I missed.
I'm done taking care of you.
So she's really going back.
Ayumi!
Hey, hey, did you hear?
Hear what?
A female student from another class
was found naked and unconscious.
Really?
That makes two of them now!
The one two days ago was on the swim team,
and the one yesterday was on the track and field team.
People are saying it might be a child molester.
Yuck...
Sorry! I was running a bit late.
From today on, I'll be your temporary English teacher.
I'm Jennifer Collins. Nice to meet you.
No way.
What are you doing here?
Um...
What's this?
Skipping first period is bad.
Though I don't blame you.
If I were sitting out here in this nice,
warm sun, I'd be in the mood, too.
Um, I wasn't...
You can't hold yourself back, can you?
Don't worry. You can relax.
Making your body feel good...
is my job as a doctor.
S-Sensei...
What?
Um... please kiss me.
"If we confess our sins, He is faithful.
And just to forgive us our sins and
purify us from all unrightness."
Translated into Japanese,
"Moshi watashi-tachi ga jibun no
tsumi o kokuhaku suru nara,
kami wa shinjitsu ni tadashiku sono tsumi o yurushi,
subete no fui kara watashi-tachi o kiyome tamau."
In this passage, do you see how the author is revealing
the main character's struggle with evil?
S-Sensei, don't–
Silly. This is just right.
You're so cute.
What about this? Does it feel good?
Oh, my. Look how wet you are.
Oh, no. This is embarrassing.
Why don't you lick it?
See?
Is it good?
S-Sensei!
What's wrong?
Yoshino-san?
No! Get away!
But...
I'm okay.
It'll go away soon.
Yoshino-san...
This morning, I went to the homes of
the two girls who'd been assaulted.
But neither could recall anything
that had happened to them.
That's too bad.
Just in case, I left them with a purification serum.
Purification serum?
In layman's terms, it's a substance that
suppresses vampire symptoms.
It can't defeat an actual vampire,
but it does help people who were
attacked by a vampire recently.
Take this vial with you.
Not only to protect Gen, but to protect
everyone at this school.
So you believe that the cause of this is...
Yes, probably.
The being that was left alive all those years ago.
To think that it still serves a purpose
after all these years.
You gonna have lunch?
Yeah.
Me too.
Oh.
What do you mean, "Oh"?
Wanna eat together?
Outside.
Okay.
It really surprised me that Jennifer's
our new English teacher.
She didn't tell me anything about that.
Hey, Gen!
Sorry to interrupt your lunchtime,
but can you show me around the school?
Right now?
Yup.
Well...
It won't take long. Please?
I guess so.
Sorry, Ayumi!
What the hell is her problem!?
Me!
That was nice!
What are you investigating?
Nothing much.
I'm just directionally challenged, so I'm drawing a map.
Is this related to what happened yesterday?
"Happened"?
I mean,
the girl from the swim team who was attacked.
This doesn't concern you, Gen.
Okay?
Oh dear, were you looking at my butt?
I wasn't!
I know you were.
During class, you were staring
at my butt the whole time.
I wasn't! Everyone else was looking at it, but I wasn't!
First the swim team, then the track team.
I wonder if it's related to the rumor.
Gen!
Come here a minute.
But that's the girls' shower room!
No one's here.
Why do I need to go in there?
Never mind. Just come in.
What the hell...
Oh, dear. What kind of savage comes into
a shower room with his clothes on?
Let's fuck.
Gen! Gen!
Yes! Yes! More! More! Harder!
Make your tongue stiffer. Yes.
That's why you were staring at my butt.
This is what you wanted, isn't it?
I knew it all along.
You pretended you didn't care, but
you really wanted me all along.
Right? Isn't that right?
Well, now I'm yours. Do what you want.
Mess me up!
More! Lick me harder! Lick me deeper!
Oh, yes!! Gen! Gen!
You're good! You're really good!
Sorry, can you get that?
Thanks.
I've seen this.
Work it. Work it, Gen!
Work it harder! Yes. More of that!
Fuck me, Gen.
Yes! Fuck. Fuck me, Gen!
Fuck me. Oh! Yes! Fuck me. Yes!
Baby, fuck me! Yeah!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
You're my baby!
I apologize.
Can you make it home by yourself?
I'll be fine. I'm used to it.
I think you'd better have a doctor see you again.
Okay. Thank you for your help.
Excuse me.
Yoshino!
Oh.
There you are. I was looking for you.
Did you faint again?
Yeah. She said I should go home for the day.
I see.
You were looking for me?
Oh, yeah.
This belongs to you, right?
Gen, thanks for lunch.
It was yummy.
That bread!
It was my lunch.
It stopped working, so I threw it away.
Really?
If you like, you can keep it.
But it's a souvenir from your trip to America.
Did I say that?
Yeah, you did. You know, Gen was there.
I remember Gen saying he used to have the same pen.
Wait a minute...
These initials...
Hi, Ayumi!
Jennifer...
Where's Gen?
He's just cleaning up.
He'll be out here soon.
I'd better get going.
Take care of yourself.
Ayumi, I have something to talk to you about.
Shirakura Yoshino has left early due to dizziness.
And also, Itoh?
Does anyone know where Itoh Ayumi is?
Hiraga-kun, do you know where she is?
No. Even I don't know.
At the end of lunch period, I saw
her walking towards the pool...
with that new gaijin-sensei.
With Jennifer?
Class is finally over, huh.
I see, Ayumi did...
But she's not the type of girl to skip class.
I'm gonna go look for her.
I appreciate it, Hiraga-kun.
Sensei! A girl is unconscious in the bathroom!
A girl?
I-It can't be...
Sorry, let me through, please.
Mitsuko-sensei.
It wasn't Ayumi.
Bye-bye.
Maybe she's at home.
I hope she is.
All the students have gone home.
Good work.
Are you the only one here?
Yes. I sent Mitsuko-sensei home.
She looked tired,
and I didn't want to involve her
too deeply in this case anyway.
How is she doing?
I injected her with a purification
serum, and she's settled down.
Her parents should arrive shortly to take her home.
Then I guess it's all settled.
Not everything. Ayumi-san is missing.
Ayumi is missing?
Do you have any ideas?
I don't.
She didn't come home.
Oh, no.
What should we do?
I fear she's been attacked by some strange man.
That's not it.
That must be it!
Stay calm.
Hiraga-kun...
Don't worry.
I asked her friends to call me if they found anything.
You don't need to worry.
Please don't go.
Sensei?
I'm scared. Stay here just a bit longer.
Sensei...
Okay.
What's that?
I bought it at a toy shop.
We'd better have some weapons on our side.
I injected the tips with that "purification serum" of yours.
It may not stop the vampire, but it'll at least weaken it.
I see.
My top priority is protecting you.
I'm gonna go patrol the grounds.
Be careful.
If there really is a vampire out there...
then why did it target this school?
This feeling... It's exactly like the schools in America.
What if Ayumi comes back?
She'll probably get mad and run away.
Then I should leave.
Please don't.
Stay here a bit longer.
Is that so? I knew it.
Yes. I understand, Mistress.
No. That is fine. Do not worry.
Yes. I will speak to you later.
Well, then...
So our adversary is a snake.
I'm going back to school.
It just doesn't feel right.
Hiraga-kun.
Thank you.
I'm sure Ayumi will come back.
I suppose this will work.
If I'm going to school, I'll need to wear a uniform.
I wonder if it already left the school.
Maybe I should leave.
S-Someone's behind me!
A girl?
You damn vampire...
Jennifer! Are you okay?
Gen, you saved me!
Are you hurt?
No.
A naked girl. What's she doing here?
Oh, my God!
It... can't be!
Ayumi!?
Next time, on Zoku Gosenzou San'e:
Possessed.