You damn vampire...
Jennifer! Are you okay?
You saved me!
Are you hurt?
No.
A naked girl. What's she doing here?
Oh, my God!
It... can't be!
Zoku Gosenzo San'e
Gen!
Grandma.
I thought you were supposed to be at home.
Now isn't the time for that!
The vampire's identity is actually...
Itoh-san?
Episode 3: Possessed
Why Ayumi?
Vampires often have limitless superpowers.
"Superpowers"?
For example, possessing those who've been bitten.
Moving objects with telekinesis.
It only hurts the first time.
Jesus!
You belong to me now.
I wonder if she's still nearby.
Perhaps the vampire that attacked
Ayumi is still in this school?
Possibly. At least we can assume the
vampire would need to stay nearby,
in order to manipulate the victims.
Okay. I'll go find that bitch.
I'm coming with you!
Gen, don't.
It's too dangerous for you. Just go home.
But there's a bunch of women here!
What kind of man would I be if I just went home?
But...
I'll protect everyone! Jennifer, Ayumi,
and you, Grandma.
Gen...
Gen, you're a stud. A man's gotta be like that.
Very well.
Take this with you.
Grandma.
Proceed with extreme caution.
I will.
I still don't believe it. A vampire in this school?
Schools make good lairs for vampires.
Why's that?
There are plenty of places to hide,
and plenty of victims to bite.
Victims...
Are you scared?
O-Of course I'm not scared!
So that's all we know for now, Itoh-sensei.
She's asleep at the moment. So don't worry.
Yes. she'll be fine. Jennifer vill take her home later.
Goodbye.
About lunch today...
What were you saying to Ayumi by the pool today?
Did I do that?
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
I was with you during lunch.
It was after you left
One of the girls in my class saw you.
Ayumi and I were together?
Yes, you were.
Don't you remember?
Maybe she mistook me for someone else?
Is that possible?
The pool, huh?
What?
I thought I just saw something move.
Vampire...
Oh, just the wind?
No. When I checked the campus earlier, it was locked.
Ayumi!
It's the real Ayumi. No mistaking it.
Then what about the other one?
Itoh-san...
Oh, no.
Who are you?
Liz.
Liz?
What do you want?
Don't...
No!
N-No. Stop it.
I'm begging you.
Gen, hurry up!
What's wrong?
Something just jumped out.
I'm gonna chase it. Gen, go back without me.
Grandma!
I'll be fine.
But if Beth hadn't come, I probably
wouldn't have made it.
It was too close.
Beth! Why are you here?
I asked her to come.
But...
My duty is to protect the Mistress and Gen-sama.
Beth...
More importantly, Gen, you must help Itoh-san.
Oh, that's right!
Shit. She got away.
I guess it disguised itself as Ayumi.
Some vampires have the ability to take on
the appearance of a different person.
That means she wanted to distract us,
so she could end up alone with Sakura-san.
And we fell for it.
So you're saying that Grandma was the
one the vampire wanted all along?
Liz tasted my blood like she was
trying to discern something.
Then she smiled.
Liz? Is that the vampire's name?
I'm not sure what her smile meant,
but there's no mistake: I was her target.
Liz? Sounds like a name I've heard before.
Chemistry Lab
Gen-sama, what are you doing?
I thought I'd make a barricade.
But even if you do that...
Is it futile?
It won't hold back a vampire.
I see.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
As long as we're all here,
she won't materialize into this room.
Why is that?
Vampires are actually quite insecure.
Really?
The reason they change forms and hide in
the dark is not just to attack humans.
It's because they are outcasts.
Well then, everyone. Let's all take a little rest here.
Should we have a midnight snack?
We can't fight on empty stomachs.
Wow!
The epitome of the Japanese warrior:
"Never eat, never sleep!"
That's backwards.
Yum!
Eat as much as you want.
Beth.
Yes?
It seemed a little strange at first, but you
look really cute in that school uniform.
Oh, my.
Oh, crap.
What are you doing?
I love you.
Gen, I love you.
Hey.
I love you.
Ayumi...
S-Stop it.
Gen...
Ayumi.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go wash my face.
Looks like he's really wiped.
What are you doing?
Looking at the moon.
The moon?
The moon appears with the night
and disappears with the morning.
Its form is ever-changing.
We're quite similar.
You used the word "outcast" back there.
But even an outcast can cast
sparkling light on many people...
just like that full moon.
Long ago, my Mistress told me that.
My grandma did?
It's quite odd.
Now I finally believe it wholeheartedly.
Well then, I'll be off.
I explained everything to her mother.
When you get there, please contact us.
Come on, Gen.
Yeah.
Be careful.
As I feared, Liz is too powerful.
We must finish this tonight.
Yes.
Beth,
you always seem to suffer on my behalf.
Not at all, Mistress.
Protecting both you and Gen-sama is my privilege.
I do not consider it a burden.
If l am of help to you, then I can
atone for the evil in my past.
Beth...
But more importantly, Mistress...
are you sure it is entirely wise to destroy Liz?
I know you want to use vampire genes
to help cure Gen-sama's body.
Yes, I had thought of that at first.
But luckily, Gen's condition is improving.
I think his current medication is sufficient.
I don't wish to take the risk of letting Liz live.
Mistress, is that what you truly feel?
I believe you feel the opposite.
The opposite?
To use the vampire's powers to restore
Gen-sama's immortal body to normal.
To completely resurrect–
Beth!
I have only one wish: to let Gen lead a normal life.
That is all.
Yes, Mistress.
I apologize.
I wonder if Ayumi was shut up in there during the day.
But that doesn't make sense.
Why not?
Vampires can't walk around in broad daylight, can they?
Which means that someone else
must have taken Ayumi there.
Could it be... Jennifer? No way.
Well then, I'm going back to the classroom.
What?
Did you hear something?
No, not "hear".
I can't "hear" anything.
The noises outside have no sound.
It seems as though we are trapped in here.
What did you say?
Perhaps it would be easier to
understand if I lowered the barrier.
Is this Liz's doing?
Most likely.
We must contact Jennifer at once!
No answer.
Oh, no!
What's the reason for trapping us in here?
Um, so that we couldn't run away if we were attacked?
That's not it. It's to prevent us from getting in the way.
But that means, Liz's true target is...
Gen's in danger!
Jennifer.
Are you... Liz?
I've been waiting.
For your blood.
I want...
your blood.
Stop it! Cut that out!
Didn't you say you wanted my blood!?
J-Jennifer!
Stop it! Snap out of it!
Jennifer!
Beth!
Mistress...
Hurry! While there's still time!
Beth!
You stay here.
No. I'm coming... too.
Liz!
Gen!
Gen! Wake up!
Good. He wasn't bitten.
You want blood!? Then take mine!
Grandma.
I can't die anyway...
even if you cut me to pieces.
I won't let you lay a finger on Gen!
Don't hinder me!
With this man by my side, I have no need of you!
Grandma!
Die!
Y-You...
Is she dead?
"Destroyed" is a better word.
Vampires do not die.
Beth...
This was for the best. This was...
Good morning!
Long time no see. Are you okay now?
Yup.
That's good.
Morning.
Oh, Yoshino.
I haven't seen you in three days, Ayumi-chan.
What happened? I was worried about you.
I guess I was just exhausted.
I should probably take up skipping class like you.
You should.
Hey, I was just joking. Don't take me seriously.
Oh, crap. We're late!
Let's go.
Gen, hurry!
Y-Yeah.
Don't tell me...
Next time, on Zoku Gosenzou San'e:
Remnants of a Dream.