I-Ikumi?!
It's just a dream...
Zoku Tsuma Netori
Wife Stealing: The Sequel
Ikumi and Shizuka
See, I had a fight with my girlfriend...
You came?
I didn't.
Okay! Come on, let's go!
Good morning, Akagi-sensei!
Oh... Shizuka-chan. Good morning.
Onii-san, you look down lately.
Did you have a fight with onee-chan?
I'm alright.
Hurry up and go back to your room.
The chime is about to ring.
Okay—!
Good morning.
U-Umm...
Yasuno-sensei!
Yes?
The truth is, I need to tell you about something...
Sunohara-sensei is in that DVD?
That can't be... Is lust messing up with your head?
I'd rather think that's the case,
but she really looks like her.
Well...
That video was from a secret club where I frequent
which I happened to get my hands on...
But to say that your wife, I mean...
Sunohara-sensei is coming in there...
That's why I want to see it for myself.
I understand.
This is a key card for that club.
Please take good care of it.
Umm... Who is today's harlot?
Are you a fan of Ikumi-san, sir?
Ikumi?
That's the harlot on the stage right now.
Is this woman really Ikumi?
I can't believe it!
But the man before certainly said "Ikumi"...
More, lick me more!
Lick me deep inside!
Your finger went inside!
Good, keep stirring my asshole! It feels good!
W-Wow...
Keep teasing my asshole!
I want lots of lots of cocks!
Give me a cock! Give me a cock right here!
Come a lot!
How amazing, even though you're married!
Are you not ashamed of your
asshole twitching like that?
Take this!
Here comes a fat one!
I can't believe it!
She hated it so much when
I touched her butt hole a little...
Yet here she is now, willingly taking a man inside it...
I'm filled with cocks! There's so many!
Both of my asshole and pussy
are filled with cocks!
It's churning up deep inside me!
Come right here with all of your force!
There are so many cocks!
Make your cocks come!
Keep those cocks coming!
Coming, coming, coming!
I'm coming from my asshole!
I'm coming—!
That's hot...
Gentlemen, is there anyone here
brave enough to join in the show?
How about the newcomer
right there, care to join?
Huh?
Hey, Mister Newcomer! Do it.
I'll take the offer if you keep dilly-dallying!
Uh, no...
I'm sorry!
What, you're going home?
Hey! Let me do it, then!
Me too, me too!
Welcome home, darling!
You got home late, huh?
Uhh... Ikumi? Why?
What's the matter? The bath is ready.
You already had dinner, right?
That woman is still there
when I went out of the show.
I went straight home afterwards
so I can't think of any way for her to outrun me.
Jeez, so it was another woman.
Well, of course, it was.
There's no way that Ikumi will do that.
It's a little disappointing, though.
If a strict P.E. Teacher like Ikumi
has been secretly doing that...
That would be quite hot...
Huh?
What are you grinning at?
What's up?
It's nothing.
Yeah, it ended up to be another woman.
Is that so? That's good to know.
I've been worried to death if something
strange has been happening
in the place where I usually go to!
I'm sorry for the trouble.
And about that, Yasuno-sensei...
Isn't it unfair that you get to go to
such a good place all by yourself?
Let me join that club as well!
Even if you tell me that...
Right? Won't it be alright?
Aren't we both men of culture?
Well, it can't be helped.
You already know the place,
so this might be some sort of fate.
I'll talk with the guys in the club about it.
Really? Oh, I'm glad...
Oh yeah, there's this harlot
sex slave that I saw there.
She looks just like Ikumi.
I was thinking about doing stuff
that I couldn't do to my wife to her instead!
Oops, lunch break is almost over.
Let's have a better talk about that next time.
I'll leave it up to you, Yasuno-sensei.
Alright!
That's so good! I want more of it, please!
So, did you do it just as I told you?
Yes, we've told him that she's Ikumi
just as you instructed, Shirou-sama.
He totally fell for it.
And then? Did he participate in the play?
No, I asked him to join in
but he got startled and ended up running away.
Alright, always keep an eye
on your posture.
Go faster little by little.
Okay!
Okay, last five minutes! Keep your pep up!
Just one more push!
What's the matter, Ikumi-sensei?
Oh, Shizuka?
I'm sorry, something urgent came.
I'll be going now so take care of the rest, alright?
I wonder what's up with onee-chan...
You may all go too when you're done!
Okay!
Oh... Just as I expected from a female slave.
You sure come fast when I call you.
Or is it because you're starting
to enjoy this as well?
Stop that nonsense, I was in
the middle of club activities!
Hurry up and get this done.
Well, don't talk like that.
You'll be taking care of those who
always jerk off from watching you.
They'll be here soon.
Oh, they're here!
Ikumi-sensei!
Don't they feel heavier right
after you get out of the water?
Hey, you shouldn't make fun of adults!
Wh-Why?
Don't worry, they are the master's underlings.
They know it for a long time now.
Sensei, when we see you strictly teaching P.E. lessons
it's hard to keep ourselves from laughing.
The same goes for us trying not to pitch a tent!
We always jerked off thinking about your tits!
But it turned out that the same
teacher was a perverted slut!
That's how it is, sensei.
You won't go home until you satisfy all of us!
Hey, look! She even has
piercings on her nipples!
Yasuno-sensei also said that
her pussy has one as well!
Pretty crazy, huh?
You really are a pervert to be
coming like this at our school!
Alright! Sensei, everything's ready!
N-No way! Anything but doing
that in front of my students!
What are you saying after all this time?
If you don't want them to see
that, then do your best.
Hey!
No! Stop!
Wow, Ikumi-sensei's asshole is twitching!
I can't get enough of that!
Y-You three, don't look there!
Stop!
Here, here you go!
Isn't your asshole twitching from craving this?
Just how miserable do I look
right now in front of my students?
Here, gulp this down!
No—!
I-I'm begging you! Don't watch this!
The fluid is getting soaked up deep inside me!
Let your students see how their teacher cries
while being given an enema!
Let's see...
Face this way, sensei.
You still make that intimidating face, sensei!
This amount won't be enough for you, sensei!
It's flowing deep inside me!
That would be the first shot!
That same sensei who's a prodigy in sports
is looking good here now, twitching her asshole.
Try your best to endure it, sensei!
Look, here's the second shot!
No, stop pouring any more inside me!
Why are you talking spooked like that, sensei?
Your students will laugh at you
if you keep acting timid like that!
It feels intense!
Here's the third shot!
Don't! I can't take it anymore!
It'll come out if you don't shut
your asshole tighter, sensei!
This will be the last one!
I-It won't go inside anymore!
You got pumped full in front of your students!
Your belly is bulging like you're pregnant!
This is excruciating! It feels
like my belly is gonna burst!
I can't get enough of seeing her
holding it in desperately!
I can't take it anymore!
Hey there, kids!
Show those swollen penises
of yours to your teacher!
Look, sensei! Seeing you
naughtily getting an enema
made your students unable to hold their lusts in!
Take responsibility as a teacher!
What kind of stupidity are
you saying? I'm a teacher!
I can't ever do something like that!
You act so mighty for a sow teacher
who's belly is bulging with an enema!
Even though you always gobble
on my cock like it's delicious!
Stop pressing there!
That's gross!
Shut that asshole tightly! It'll spill out!
It hurts!
Come on, sensei. Please suck this.
Looking at me like that just makes me more excited.
No, stop that!
Stop!
Here, come on! Please suck this!
Do your best, sensei!
There you go! Gobble it up, sensei!
Sensei, are you planning to make a place
of learning like this classroom
filled with the smell of your shit?
That's right! You have to do your best, sensei!
This is bad! I need to quickly make
them come or it'll all spill out!
Having his tongue wiggle
in my bowel feels too much!
I can't hold it in anymore, it'll come out!
Let me go to the toilet already!
No, you can't! You haven't made
even one of us come yet!
S-Sensei... That feels great!
O-Oh... Sensei, it's coming out!
Oh... That felt great...
Okay, I'm next!
Ohh... You only got two down?
It'll all leak out if you don't hurry up!
Are you fine with your students seeing
you splatter your poop everywhere?
I can't take it anymore!
Let me go to the toilet already!
What a helpless teacher you are!
I'll plug you up with this so try
to hold it in a little longer!
I can't, I can't! It's gonna come out!
It's gonna come out—!
It hurts!
Sensei, here's the last one!
Please... Hurry up and come!
Mine's smaller than Master Shirou's,
but don't you feel it more when
you squeeze tightly on it?
Not in my ass...
Something hot is pounding in it!
My belly is getting stirred up inside!
Akio-kun, hurry!
Hurry up and come in my mouth!
That's incredible, sensei!
I'm about to come!
It's so hot! It feels hot!
I can't take this anymore!
I can't anymore!
I'm coming—!
No... It won't stop!
Please... Stop looking!
That's a P.E. teacher for you!
Ikumi-sensei's shit stinks!
I got an unbearably hard boner now!
Please take responsibility, sensei!
Stop looking...
Sensei, how do our cocks feel?
We can't... We shouldn't be
doing something like this!
Your asshole is squishy and
it feels so good, sensei!
Ohh... It's squeezing me like crazy!
No... Don't say that!
Look, here are the cocks that went inside you!
Your stench got blended with
ours. Don't they smell good?
They have an unbearable smell!
Here you go! Come, you slutty teacher!
Have an orgasm in front of us!
Yes, it's good! I can't take it
anymore, it feels good!
Here, take this, slutty teacher!
Let us see how you climax!
It feels good in my asshole too!
Shoot it out, shoot it out! I'm gonna come!
Everyone will shower you
with cum, slutty teacher!
I'm coming!
No matter how lofty you try to be,
you just lose your head in the end!
Looks like they roughed her up good...
That's the youngsters for you.
They tend to overdo stuff.
Take Ikumi to the stage tonight.
Your training is about to end.
You're up for the next stage.
Onee-chan! Is she not home?
Both of them should already be home...
There's no one at the staff room anymore.
It can't be helped.
Those two have been acting
kind of weird lately.
Onii-san looks down and onee-chan
has been sneaking off to somewhere.
They're definitely hiding something!
Nothing seems unusual in here...
I'm already invading their privacy here, for sure...
What...
Huh? Something's left playing on the TV?
Onii-san was watching some lewd stuff.
I can watch a little bit, right?
R-Right, I'm just checking to make sure!
You can break me!
Is that onee-chan?!
Hey, I got my hands on something good!
What's that?
You see, this was said to be
filmed from an S & M club.
This should be the real thing!
The woman here is rumored
to be from our neighborhood!
Huh?! Then it could be a woman we know?
Damn, that makes me so excited!
Then, let's check it out in the
audiovisual room after school!
Okay!
I have to do something!
If anyone sees that, onee-chan will...
Sensei, seems that last night's
performance was quite intense, huh?
You... This is the women's toilet, you know!
Classes are about to start
so nobody will come there!
Show me that huge anal rotor instead!
Should we really have to watch it here right now?
I'll have to return it today so it can't be helped!
Alright, alright...
More importantly, if the woman
here is someone we know,
let's copy and share it with everyone.
Okay!
Sounds great, let's watch it already!
H-Hey, you three! What are you doing here?!
I'll confiscate that!
You think you can bring
this stuff on the campus?
What are you doing? Stop that, Sunohara!
Let go!
No!
Should I make this bitch shut up?
No... Stop! Let me go!
What are you doing?
School hours have ended long ago!
You should hurry up and go home now!
Don't rush and trip yourselves over!
Thank you, Mr. Janitor...
What did just happen here?
Uhh... No, it's nothing important.
The boys brought a lewd DVD here on campus,
so I was only reprimanding them.
So those three were planning to watch this, huh?
You can't!
I'll hand this over to a teacher!
I will never let anyone have this DVD!
We'll be having some fun from now on.
Wh-What is this?!
Take it off! Take this off me!
Oh? Are you awake?
I'm watching the DVD that you confiscated
and don't want to hand over right now!
This isn't something that you'll want
people to see, that's for sure!
Come on, take a look! Your sister is so bold!
No! Stop!
Shizuka... You rubbed yourself while
watching this DVD, right?
Th-There's no way that I did such a thing!
Don't lie!
While watching cruel stuff done to your sister,
your pussy got dripping wet, am I right?
That's because you love rubbing your pussy.
Which one between this and your beloved
senpai's uniform makes you hornier?
I know everything about you! Look at this!
You sisters both make such good performances.
Then, how about I show these two videos
at the school's morning assembly?
If that happens, both of you won't have
any face to show in this neighborhood!
Wh-What do you want me to do?!
You know it already.
You will undergo through the
same things your sister did.
I'll train you to become a full-fledged woman
on par with your sister with my own hands!
No, I'm begging you! Spare me!
I won't get tired of this!
Hey, Shizuka! You see...
I've been aiming for you all this time!
I dream about you in my sleep and
I fantasize about you when I'm awake!
I've been sniffing your indoor shoes
as I wait for this day to come!
No! Pervert! Let me go!
Who would want that with you!
Let me out of here! No—!
Shut up!
Today is the day that I'm gonna carefully check
every nook and cranny of your body!
Don't worry, we have a lot of time until morning!
I'll make sure to talk to your dorm mother as well.
No one's gonna come here
no matter how much you cry!
This place is my realm when the night comes!
Alright, where should I start your physical exam?
Oh yeah, starting from the mouth is the right way.
So tasty!
Your drool tastes delicious, Shizuka!
How does your armpit smell?
Don't! Not right there!
Hmm, it tastes so sour!
It has a nice flavor!
Your breasts are soft! They're the best!
No more!
Let me go...
Oh, what's this?
Aren't you bushy down here? Haven't you taken good care of yourself down here?
I see... That's because you're
still a child. Right, Shizuka?
But you're about to become a woman today!
Taking good care of your coochie
is a proper etiquette!
No—!
I need to have a taste of your
crotch hair before we shave it.
No... Stop!
I can't get enough of this!
The older sister smells like a pickled seaweed,
but the younger sister reeks of
a cheesy stench down here!
You're both sisters,
yet your pussies smell so different!
No... Don't say that!
I can't get enough of this smell!
Stop!
Please let me go! Stop doing that!
No more!
I don't want this!
I don't want this—!
Just stay still.
Your clit will get chopped off
if you try to struggle.
That's it, that's it. Just stay put like that.
This will be over soon.
Alright... Look, it's now squeaky clean!
Let's see...
You have quite a pretty pussy.
But you've been rubbing it too much!
Just look at how big your clit has become!
No—!
It grew even bigger! Is this your first time
to be touched by another person?
Oh, it's pussy juice!
Your pussy juice is dripping out!
Are you feeling good from this?
No more...
No, I'm begging you!
Stop it already!
No... What? What is this feeling?
What's happening...
No! I can't take it anymore!
I'm going crazy—!
I-It's coming... It's coming, it's coming out!
I-It's coming out!
You had a huge orgasm. Am I right, Shizuka?
That's a good reaction.
Shizuka, we've only just begun.
You have a huge potential.
From now on, I'll open up your body
and train you to become a female
slave on par with your sister!
A SakuraCircle Project
Translated by: Tennouji
Special thanks to: Anime Holics Organization
Support the group by sharing the releases
and and giving it proper credits.
http://sakuracircle.animeholics.org