Episode 4: Remnants of a Dream
It's been more than half a year since Beth bit me.
But I didn't know traces of the bite were still inside me.
And this is what it looks like...
Yes.
I took this sample from my blood three days ago.
And this is a sample from the victims in this recent case.
They look very similar.
Yes. This is probably the common vampire gene factor.
Anyone who has this can be controlled.
And that is how Liz was able to possess you,
even though it was Beth who bit you.
That's correct.
I have never heard of this before.
This is scientifically very significant.
If Liz had lived longer, we could
have taken more samples.
What a shame.
Don't say that!
We couldn't risk putting any more lives in danger!
Ah, you're right.
I was starting to become a mad scientist there.
But anyway, without your purification serum,
it would have been difficult to collect this data.
Though it did contaminate the data a little.
You still got results.
Yes. I tested my own blood.
This is the sample from three days ago,
and this is the sample from today.
You can see the difference.
Looks like this will be useful.
Yes. I intend to carefully study the difference.
So everything is settled, or at least I hope so.
Gen-sama. What are you doing here?
Is something the matter?
Gen-sama?
Gen-sama, your eyes... It can't be!
No!
Gen-sama...
Please forgive me, Gen-sama.
You mustn't!
No.
Gen-sama...
Gen-sama, please forgive me.
That was Beth's voice.
Beth!
Gen...
Zoku Gosenzo San'e
I thought he was getting better.
In fact, he was getting worse.
His genes were even stronger than I imagined.
Was everything I did to this point futile?
Don't give up yet!
Have faith in the power of Gen's life force!
Gen...
You did nothing wrong.
Please forgive me. It's all my fault.
My...
I came here to take my son home.
Gen...
I wonder if I should visit him.
Wait! Yoshino-san!
Liz is alive. Hiraga-kun's live in danger.
What's this?
A girl named Shirakura Yoshino gave it to me.
What could it mean?
Since she knows the name "Liz," I doubt it's a prank.
I wonder how much she knows?
And how she knows Gen is in danger.
I suppose we'll have to ask her directly.
It's difficult enough to keep up with Gen.
And now Liz as well?
Things just aren't going our way, are they?
What a big house.
Gen's grandma is the school commissioner.
So he's a rich boy, huh.
Makes me nervous.
Is this your first time here too?
I've been once before.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Oh, jeez.
And what else could I do? So I carried him to the toilet.
Let's stop talking about that.
Okay, okay.
To preserve your good name, I'll end the story here.
But I wanna hear more!
For the last time, no.
Say, Gen, you're so cute when you're mad.
But I'm glad to see you looking well.
That's right.
We were really worried about you.
Do you need to be hospitalized again?
I'm not sure.
Yes, well, if Gen keeps being so nasty to women,
he might have to be hospitalized again.
What's that supposed to mean?
Never mind. I promise I'll take good care of you.
Oh, that's from when you were hospitalized.
Yeah. I took that with my doctors.
Dr. Kimble and Dr. Casey.
And also...
The other one was...
Um, I think it was Elizabeth.
Yes, yes. Elizabeth Bartley!
And the other doctors called her Liz.
"Liz"?
Um, well...
Yoshino.
Excuse me.
Gen-sama, it is time for your medicine.
Ah yes, we've excited him too much.
He needs to take his medicine and rest. Right?
Okay.
The rest of us can go to the other room
and continue our conversation.
Again? Don't tell them gross stories!
You two... I'm glad you came to visit.
But with you here, it's like we're back in the classroom.
It feels strange.
The real commissioner is on sabbatical.
I see. So you're related to Gen's grandmother.
Itoh-san, how have you been feeling lately?
Any more fainting spells?
I'm all better.
I see.
But your symptoms could return at any time.
So you mustn't grow complacent.
We just received some effective medicine.
Is that it?
Yup. My colleague from Howard U sent it.
It's good stuff.
I never thought I'd get medicine
when visiting a sick friend.
It is kind of funny, isn't it?
I feel a bit tired.
There's a bit of a sedative in there.
Don't worry, you can sleep a little if you want.
What about you, Yoshino?
I'm fine, thanks.
Besides, I want to talk to you.
About Liz, right?
Yes.
Are you okay with telling us about it here?
Liz sleeps most of the day.
Though she sometimes wakes up a little to spy on me.
"Spy"?
Not right now. So we can still talk.
I see.
The first thing I want to clarify is this:
Liz is the same Elizabeth Bartley who
worked at Howard U with me, right?
Yes.
She seemed normal enough... though not really.
Yes. She isn't human.
She's a vampire.
How do you know that?
I witnessed her attacking someone.
Right in front of you?
Yes, exactly.
And you couldn't stop her from doing that?
I'm sorry. I wasn't blaming you.
I was just wondering what actually happened.
Liz is a bad person.
She was violent and selfish.
She never listened to anything I said to her.
I told her to stop over and over again.
But... then she kept doing so many
horrible things! Even to you, Sensei!
Yoshino-san...
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry, Sensei!
You don't need to apologize.
Liz told me she was born with both
vampire and human genes.
This means that she's not a complete vampire.
She needs a certain kind of blood to sustain her.
And so she went after Gen.
Yes.
Back at the hospital, she said, "At last I've found him!"
I begged her, over and over again,
to stop hurting people.
And whenever I did, Liz always said, "Okay, I'll stop."
But I couldn't believe it.
And at this rate, Hiraga-kun's life will be in danger.
Beth...
Will I die?
Why do you ask that?
I don't want to die.
I want to live a long life... just like Grandma.
Gen-sama...
Thank you, Yoshino-san.
Your story has helped us a great deal.
But there is still one thing you're not telling us.
I suspect you're hiding it specifically from me.
But may I ask you directly?
Yes.
Where is Liz right now?
Well...
Um...
If we're going to protect Gen from Liz,
we need to strike first.
Yes.
You know where she's hiding, don't you?
W-Well, I...
That is the most important piece of information.
Tell us! Where is Liz right now!?
Well... Well, um...
Sakurako-sensei, this girl has a weak constitution.
I don't think we should...
I know.
I'm tired too.
Sorry for pushing you like that.
The rain has become heavy.
You should stay here tonight.
I'll prepare a room immediately.
Let's continue this conversation tomorrow.
Dear Grandma,
Yesterday, something very sad...
Gen!
I just found out that Elizabeth Bartley
left Tokyo University two months ago.
Currently, they don't know where she is.
So the university is no help.
Liz and Yoshino-san sure have a peculiar relationship.
Why do you suppose Yoshino-san knows what Liz
is thinking and what happened in her past?
Don't you think Liz just told her those things?
I thought at first that Yoshino-san was being used.
But thinking of it from Liz's point of view,
why would she confide in someone
as fragile as Yoshino-san?
You've got a good point there.
It sounds almost like they've been
friends for a very long time.
No, perhaps more than friends.
Gen.
Gen...
I love you. I've always loved you.
You never noticed, though.
But I always looked only at you.
When you were happy.
When you, were sad.
No matter the situation, your eyes were always gentle.
I loved your eyes.
I know that you prefer Ayumi-chan and Jennifer-san.
But...
For tonight please be mine.
Please...
I thought so.
The moment I saw you,
I knew that wasn't the first time.
Gen?
When I was in the hospital,
you were always by my side.
You noticed?
I just remembered, Elizabeth Bartley.
No, Liz. You are Liz, aren't you?
No, I'm not. I'm Yoshino!
Please believe me. I'm not Liz. I'm Yoshino!
Please. Make love to me.
When you make love to me, I can remain myself.
Yoshino...
Please!
More. Kiss me more.
Gen!
You're beautiful. I always dreamed of doing this to you.
Of giving my whole self to you.
Great! I love you, Gen.
I can't wait anymore. Come. Hurry, inside of me.
I want you to complete me!
I feel it. Your strong life force.
Inside of me... Lots...
Yes!
More! Give me more, Gen! More!
Amazing...
No, Gen...
Not there. No.
That tickles.
It's embarrassing.
No. Stop. No, don't stop.
I should have noticed it sooner!
Yoshino's dark aura.
The countless patients who have lost their energy.
The answer was right there in front of me!
Gen. Do you love me?
Is that why you're doing this to me?
No, not that
Don't. Not that.
It's embarrassing.
Wow!
That's amazing, Gen! I feel like I'm losing my mind!
Very good. Nice eyes.
I was waiting for those eyes to emerge.
No. Don't!
Stop it now! Stop!
Don't do that, Liz! How cruel! You're so cruel, Liz.
Not now. No! Stop it!
No!
Gen! Gen!
Open up! Hurry!
Gen! Yoshino!
What's going on?
Mistress, Gen-sama is...
Gen!
Gen! Gen...
I win.
How dare you!
You bitch. You're my own kind.
You traitor!
Don't hinder me!
I'm still in the middle of a meal.
Stop it!
Yoshino!
Why are you there?
When one of us is in the forefront, the other is asleep!
We both agreed to that rule!
The one who broke the rule first was you, Liz!
You stole my body all the time and did horrible things.
You placed the whole school in danger.
And in order to regain the energy you kept depleting,
I ended up killing so many trees.
The only reason I was able to last as long as I did
was because I believed you were my one true friend.
But in the end, you betrayed me.
You promised you wouldn't touch Gen!
You're wrong, Yoshino. I didn't betray you.
I did all of this for both of us!
If our body is complete, there will be nothing to fear.
We can live in peace!
I've had enough!
W-Wait!
Gen, please forgive me.
I couldn't protect you.
You are Yoshino-san, correct?
You are, right?
We can find a way for you to coexist with us.
Just like Beth.
Okay? Yoshino-san...
It's no use, Sensei. Liz is still alive in my heart.
When night falls again, she might wake up.
Before that happens...
I must end things.
The sun... is so hot.
S-Stop that!
Farewell, Gen.
Yoshino!
How dare you! You think you can...
E-Energy...
If only I can find energy...
Gen-sama!
Gen!
It's a horrible fever!
Gen! Why so sudden?
As I feared. It's just as I feared.
Liz's vampire genes have merged with Gen's DNA.
His body was unprepared for such a drastic change.
He's rejecting it.
Then if this keeps up, will Gen...
Will he become immortal like you?
Yes. Most likely.
But I must not let that happen.
That's right! The purification serum.
I might be able to reverse the vampire genes.
Jennifer, bring me the medicine at once!
Okay!
Mistress, do you think that will really save Gen-sama?
In the best case scenario, he will
be able to live a normal life.
But what about the worst case scenario?
We will not be able to let him live.
Oh, no!
That's the only way for him!
I don't want Gen to undergo the same fate as me.
If the alternative is living with my curse,
dying right now is much easier.
Gen... You must be in pain, you poor thing.
Everything will get better soon.
Better...
No, Grandma.
I would rather live with you forever.
I don't want to die now.
Gen!
Didn't we promise?
That we'd be together forever.
That's what I want.
For Grandma...
to...
Gen!
E-Energy...
Gen-sama!
No way...
Do you really have no regrets?
Of course not
Didn't I promise you?
We'll be together forever.