Zoku Gosenzo San'e
Gen-sama!
We're ba–
Beth! How are you doing!?
Welcome back...
Oh, my God! Hey, Beth!
Come on, wake up!
Hey, Beth!
Grandma.
Welcome back, Gen.
Episode 1: Spring Dawn
I've been gone for so many months,
but nothing's changed.
It must feel very relaxing.
Unlike the schools in the big
city, the air nere is delicious.
And it's quiet.
But in a place like this, it's difficult
to imagine anything ever changing.
Who are you?
I'm a student here.
Have we met before?
Have we?
You just got here, didn't you?
Yeah, well...
The entrance is this way.
Your eyes are as distant as ever, I see.
Hey! Wait!
Well you see, yeah, yeah.
Gen!
Yo.
What the hell! You came back today?
You could've at least told me you were coming!
Coming here was a last minute decision.
Is everything okay now? You know, your body...
Yeah. It took longer than I thought, though.
Oh.
That's good.
Long time no see!
Aw, don't say that.
Wanna come over after school?
I'd love to spend some time catching up.
Jennifer's coming to pick me up.
Jennifer?
She's researching my illness.
Didn't you know?
Of course I knew that.
I just didn't know she was in Japan.
She came here with me this morning.
Then I'm coming home with you. Okay?
I guess it's okay.
Oh, you're...
Oh. So we're in the same class.
We met at the front gate a few minutes ago.
I was wondering why she was absent last period.
Do you two know each other?
Of course we know each other.
I only missed school for a little while.
Oh, now I get it.
I thought you were a new transfer student.
A new student?
I just transferred to this school a month ago.
My name's Yoshino.
I'm Hiraga Gen. Nice to meet you.
Is that an original pen from Howard University?
Have you been there?
It's only sold on the Howard campus.
I bought it when I was on vacation earlier.
I had one of those too, but I lost it in America.
Oh, really?
It had my initials engraved in it. I really liked it a lot.
Boring.
Jennifer is coming to pick you up, right?
Yes.
If you don't feel well,
you should get some medicine from her.
Don't worry about it, Grandma.
Gen, you need to call me Sakurako-sensei here.
S-Sorry, Sakurako-sensei.
I'll check in later.
Have a safe trip home.
Thanks.
Hiraga-kun?
Long time no see.
Mi-Mitsuko-sensei!
Then, will you show me?
Is it all better?
Yes. My symptoms are gone.
Oh.
So what was the cause?
Well, it was in my genes.
Something inherited...
S-Sensei?
Stay still. I'm going to help you.
Why did you leave?
Why did I leave?
Everyone was worried about you.
Especially my daughter, Ayumi.
She talked about you all the time.
Ayumi did?
Oh. Oh, no.
Sensei...
Sensei... don't.
S-Sensei!
Gen? Gen! Where are you?
Gen?
What?
Oh, you were in here the whole time?
Yeah.
Jennifer's here to pick you up.
Oh. Okay. Well, Mitsuko-sensei...
Goodbye. Take care.
You suck!
Hey!
How was it, living a celebrity's life in America?
Oh, well, I had a hot and lovely night life.
When Gen was recovering from his
illness, he was with me every night.
That's not what I was asking about.
P-Please excuse my clumsiness!
Oh, excuse me.
That was just a joke.
So what were the results of Gen's analysis?
Well...
After analyzing him at the research
center at Howard University,
I discovered that there was a mismatched
gene in his 22nd chromosome.
How that mutated gene will affect Gen's body...
we're still researching that.
How are you researching it?
Twice a day, we shoot radiation
directly into his bone marrow.
This inhibits further growth of the
strange matter in his blood cells.
We've tried this treatment for a month.
Then we've run current through the sympathetic
nerves to weaken them.
That must have been difficult.
Yes. But Gen has been trying his
hardest to control it himself.
Beth...
Is something wrong?
Gen-sama...
I missed you the whole time you were gone.
Beth...
Can we return to the way we were before?
But back then...
I had a blood disease.
Is that all it was?
Was that the extent of your feelings for me?
It's not like that.
Even a little while would suffice.
If you care for me in even the slightest way,
then please...
Please make love to me.
Beth...
Gen-sama...
Beth!
B-Beth...
Wow, this feels great.
Better than when Jennifer does it?
No! Sorry! I didn't mean that.
There are things you'd probably rather not talk about.
Gen-sama!
And then, yeah.
You heard?
I knew it!
There's something going on between those two.
Really?
Yeah, right!
No need to worry.
Just a normal fainting spell.
Ayumi, listen...
I think you're under a misapprehension.
Nothing wrong has happened
between Hiraga-kun and me.
For starters, I'm your mother.
And I know how you feel about him.
Why would I betray you like that?
Hiraga-kun hasn't been back in Japan for very long.
Of course he's going to be a bit distant.
So being moody about it won't help anything.
That's true, but...
You two have just begun.
Wait until he settles back into his old life.
Now, you have class, don't you?
I'll watch over this girl.
But you know, if you beat around the bush too long,
someone else might steal him from you.
Are you awake?
Why am I...
You fainted during recess.
When you fell, you must have hit something.
It's not a serious injury.
Are you okay?
Yes. May I return to the classroom?
Wouldn't you like to rest a little longer?
But my class...
You don't look like the type of person who skips class.
Very well. You may go.
Thanks.
Is someone there?
Hey, someone's there, right?
Just come out.
Come on...
Itoh-sensei!
Come right away. A student has fainted!
Are you hurt anywhere?
Do you feel nauseous?
No, I don't.
What are you doing here? What happened?
I'm not sure.
You're not sure?
I don't... remember anything.
Was it really a bite mark from a vampire?
Yes. There's no mistaking it.
Don't tell me you think Beth did it?
Not at all.
Are you sure?
She would have no reason to.
No "reason" to?
If you see this, you'll understand.
Beth...
By using this device to fulfill her energy needs,
Beth is able to live as normal a life as the rest of us.
I see. So that's what you were talking about.
How long have you had this device?
This device has been in the family for a long time.
Probably as far back as the Heian era.
The Heian era?
But it's almost like Western magic.
Both Western magic and Eastern sorcery
are more similar than one might think.
When their motives are the same, that is.
I researched both and discovered the best mix.
However, unfortunately,
the Hiraga family has since fallen victim to a cruel fate.
So your eternally youthful body and
Gen's illness are from that?
That's correct.
That's why I have asked you to help research
this problem with modern methods.
Is Gen's illness really under control?
For now, it's totally suppressed.
But what if...
You needn't worry.
Modern medicine will cure him completely.
I pray you're right.
Yo! You big stud!
Good for you. Happy about it?
Don't tease me!
Just know that I'm rooting for you, with all my heart.
I like that! Sounds like fun.
Nothing.
Why don't you give up?
How can I?
The teacher told me to assemble the research materials.
Still, it's not your fault if they're not there.
But that teacher's scary when he's mad.
Damn.
It's nice that you're back.
But you seem kind of distant.
Really?
When Americans reconnect,
don't they hug each other really tight?
But I'm Japanese.
I'm sure you hug Jennifer all the time.
Yeah, but she always initiates it.
Then maybe I should try initiating something.
Ayumi...
You're okay with it right?
When you were in America...
Huh?
You forgot about me, didn't you?
No, I didn’t.
I thought about you every day.
I never forgot you.
<•>
Huh? Where's Etsuko?
Isn't she on the athletic field?
She wasn't there.
Then maybe she's in the shower or the bathroom.
I'm gonna go look.
Hey, what's going on?
No! No!
No!
Next time, on Zoku Gosenzou San'e:
Furnace.