And now to set it up.
Alright, stew prep done.
The only thing remaining is...
Potatoes and my dear.
There they are.
Hey!
Over here, Fumi-kun!
Look, look! I harvested lots of big potatoes today.
You sure are a real work horse.
Whoa, I've got to open the place now!
Need a ride?
Righty-o! Gallop away, Silver!
Off we go!
Giddy up! Oh wait, I forgot to slap the thingy.
Ah well, just forget it.
Welcome!
One draft beer over here, please, Lea-san.
Coming right up!
Lea-san's looking gorgeous as usual, boss.
Such a waste for her to be with a human.
I'm really impressed at how you managed
to snag a typically stubborn centaur.
Human and demi-human couples
are already quite rare, you know.
Lea-san, deafr beer here, too, please.
Just how the hell did you do it?
I never wanted to remember.
No, that's...
I'm Lea, from Germany.
I may be a demi-human, but I hope that
I can get along well with everyone.
This my first time ever seeing a centaur.
Can I take a pic?
Me too!
So they really exist.
So creepy!
Isn't that body inconvenient for you?
Hey, you freak!
S-Stop.
Please stop.
Can I have a look?
Hey there, Nanafumi, check this out!
What the hell did you just do?!
We don't allow this stuff here.
Quit doing this stupid stuff already.
My dear customer.
Stupid potato.
Umm... I...
Hey.
Hey, kid, do you really love demi-humans that much?
Actually, we kinda love humans, too.
Especially guys like you.
You okay?
I'm fine. Sorry to make you worry.
Sorry about the fuss, everyone.
This may not suffice as an apology,
but all drinks tonight are on me!
You're getting carried away with that again!
It's all on me, so just drink up!
Goodness...
Thank you very much.
Damn, I'm totally red-zoned now.
Maybe I should issue charge fees next time.
Whaddya think, Lea?
Thank you for today.
I've fallen in love you all over again.
You don't have to worry about that.
It's the husband's duty to protect his wife.
Also, centaur boobs are the best.
Jeez.
Then, I have to be a good wife as well.
This is a good kiss.
Lea-san seems surprisingly passionate today.
Fumi-kun, your dick's gotten so lively already.
Stahp.
Your centaur handjob technique is just far too incredible.
You sure do love this, Fumi-kun.
Just cum whenever you want to.
I'm not gonna cum just yet!
Your boobs...
The only thing I see here are lethal weapons.
Perfect for being a cook!
Idiot.
Not there...
My nipples are too sensitive.
You did love it so much here when we first did it.
No... please don't say that...
Now then,
lemme do a check up of this horsie here.
Your horsey-pussy is so beautiful and erotic as always.
(Umanko, uma=horse + manko=pussy)
Stupid Fumi-kun.
Don't compliment me by saying such embarrassing things.
You say that, but I can see that you're
already horny down there.
Centaurs do have such honest bodies.
Whoa, it's wet already.
It feels as if it's going to burn me.
Don't play with the tip.
I'm the most sensitive down there.
Oh? Giving up already?
Your body's always been just as sensitive as it is sturdy.
However,
I'm still using only two fingers.
That's...
Here comes the third.
Stop. Stop!
I can't take it all!
And here's the fourth.
Fourth finger incoming!
Fumi-kun, it really won't fit.
Please stop!
Here I go.
My much awaited...
...first fist!
No!
She's cumming hard.
I'll move it, then.
Here we go.
Your love juices are gushing out.
I'm feeling weak...
The sounds it makes as I slide in and out is very erotic.
Oh?
Found the entrance to your womb.
I'm very sensitive down there.
Shall I stop fisting, then?
Please, just keep doing it.
I-I like it.
I love being fucked by something very big and thick.
It's coming.
Something big's coming!
That was quite the powerful orgasm.
I might just enjoy this more in the future.
I'm pulling out, then.
No, don't pull it out just yet...
The floor's all soaked with your love juices.
Don't say that, please.
I wanna take a short break, too.
I won't... let you!
It recovered so quickly!
Centaurs sure have lots of HP!
The smell of work.
That's are heating up.
Wow...
Such incredible mouth control.
It makes all that practice from the ground up worthwhile.
It truly is my very own exclusive custom-made blowjob!
Lea, I'm about to cum.
Here I come.
Drink it all.
Not just yet.
Thanks for the meal.
I wanted to drink a bit more, but you can't run dry just yet.
You should cum the rest inside me, okay?
My libido's off the charts!
I just came earlier, so my tip's quite sensitive.
Jeez, stop teasing me.
I want it now.
Man, you're one horny centaur.
Amazing.
All that slimy flesh is sucking me in.
Your pussy feels so good that I just can't get enough!
I'm happy.
Just keep pounding away.
Keep fucking your special exclusive Lea pussy.
It's pulsating hard.
My womb feels amazing.
It's stretching out as it craves for your cum.
I'm going to cum soon.
I'll squirt every last bit.
Cum.
Fill my womb.
Impregnate me!
I'm cumming.
That felt fantastic.
Lemme see...
Whoa, I sure came a lot.
It just keeps on overflowing.
Such a waste, it's going to spill.
Hey, Fumi-kun.
What?
You never thought you'd get married
to a demi-human like me, right?
Yeah.
I'm still astonished that things turned out this way.
Same for me.
But now, I can't imagine a life without you.
Damn, our married couple aura's just too sweet!
Hey, no teasing!
Then, let's do something even more
in tune with married couples.
Huh?
Let's do it again, okay?
We'll definitely return!
Thank you  vary much.
Mr. Fumi, the adventurer.
This may not be a sufficient token of my appreciation,
but if you're currently looking for a place to stay,
please come otfer to our placed.
Man, she's really one gorgeous busty lady.
Immaculate from top to bottom.
Mr. Adventurer!
Would you mind sharing a meal while you grace
us with one or two of your adventure stories?
Wh-Whoah!!
Wait, I'm not really trying to fap to you or anything.
Anyway, please don't look!
It seems you've built it up from all of your perilous travels.
I can provide comfort with this rather
sturdy half-woman, half-horse body.
What will it be, sir?
Oh yes.
This one, too...
What exquisite handplay!
Your licking of my nipples feels nice, too.
If you keep playing with both tips,
I'll...!
That's three days' worth of cum.
Being given a handjob and a nipple-suck simultaneously
by this centaur babe is the best.
I'm glad that you like it.
I'll be sure to cleanly suck all remaining cum.
How beautiful.
So this is the renowned horsey-pussy
of a thoroughbred centaur.
An adventurer always cherishes the
exploration of the unknown.
As such, I definitely should explore this myself!
No way.
I can't stop it!
Such a mellow scent.
Perfect for this festive catch that I have.
I can't hold back any longer.
H-Here I go.
I'll di into some interspecies fucking.
Okay, please do...!
I'm... I'm cumming.
That's good. Just keep on caressing the tip carefully.
Oh yeah!
This armpit blowjob also feels great.
Oh crap.
Sex with a centaur is so addicting.
Will you be able to comfort me again sometime?
Of course. I'll always be waiting.
And thus, our role-playing ended.
Oh man!
I want to fuck a demi-human!
Let's go catch some in the sea!
Are you insane?
I'm still sane, you blue-balled jerk!
It's my first time out in the sea after a long time!
Don't you know about those humanoid forgs?
Entertaining those military police rumors again?
They're called forgs exactly because they
don't closely resemble humans.
I bet you're thinking of "those" things with that.
Like if us delivery men happen to have a relatively
harmless type of manta forg for a very long time,
that we eventually did "it".
Whoa, I could totally dig that.
Oh wait!
What I'm talking about,
are the ones from continents swept up
by the mystic sea a long time ago.
Those who thrived while hiding from humanity,
and those who eventually acclimated to the Mist,
that they soon obtained a forg's characteristics.
You know, they might be living in some secluded
paradise deep beneath the sea!
That's quite an elaborate shitty rumor.
Besides, how in the world are you going to find one?
Even if you can penetrate the Mist that deeply,
you'd be unable to see anything at all.
And that is why today,
I've decided to use this!
A Spine?
That's top quality equipment you've got there.
Don't tell me you got that thing solely for that purpose?
Alright!
I'm off.
Just you wait.
I'll return with a legend that will spread like wildfire
and help explain what I want easie-
I don't fucking care.
A shelter from three-hundred years ago.
From what I've heard, this is that weird place.
Well, considering the acquired coordinates...
Just kidding.
Hey, octopus, I've got no business with-
What?!
A girl?!
Wait, don't tell me this is the humanoid
forg I've been hearing about?
She's leaning more on the demi side of things, though..
That is... actually better!
Even if it is a forg, I can't just leave a girl here.
I'll take responsibility...
...and fuck her.
Her loli lips feel so soft,
and her petite tongue is also something else.
Is this a nipple?
Wait, a sucker?
It's actually quite stiff...
Whoa, it's actually a sucker nipple?
It's sucking my fingers!
Can she feel pleasure while she's unconscious?
She maybe small, but she's far more
sensitive than a normal human.
Guess I have to tram her well while I still can.
It's so wet!
She's so aroused, that she's even sopping wet down here.
I definitely need to teach her a few things now.
Oh, you're awake.
That's a nice expression.
This guy here is more aroused than ever!
Man, it reeks down here.
Though it's actually pleasurable for me.
Guess I should start fucking your loosened up hole already.
Don't break down on me now.
Well then, for this forg-tan's virgin pussy...
I'm digging in!
Wow, oh crap. What the hell is this?
It's as if her cervix is another sucker!
Amazing!
It's writing around me.
Oh? Loving how my thing's roughly
bumping up against your womb?
That's good.
If you really love it that much,
then I've got no choice but to pump all my human cum inside!
I'll directly cum inside!
That was great.
Whoa.
The insides were also pulled out.
Looks like I don't need to tie you up anymore.
Well? How does it feel to be raped so
much that your insides spilled out?
It's become a really fine fuck hole.
I'll be using you from now on,
as my personal onahole.
Your tentadejob's getting quite good already.
Here, I'm going to cum.
Drink up!
Breastfeeding your kids while sucking something on your own...
You're such a perverted mom.
What happens if they try to imitate you?
No? a bad deal for me, though.
A human-forg hybrid.
A new breed of humans acclimated to the Mist.
There was no need to search for paradise.
I simply needed to conjure up my own!
That's right.
If there isn't one, then I'll just make one.
My own personal paradise.
A legion only I can command!
Kuku-chan, the demi-human girl of killer whale descent.
Today, with his hopeless human, Haru,
they've decided to take a bath together.
I'm going to give you my special bath treatment today!
Hey, don't tell me that you've been
wasting this much everyday?
Oh! It was purely instinctual on my part!
I-I'm not!
Whoa! Haru's such a pervert!
Why is your dick completely stiff right now?
That's because you're always going
around walking naked every day!
It seems she's willing to take responsibility
and attempted to quell this dick's desires.
Guess I'll have to give you my special service.
Here we have Kuku-chan giving a hearty
blowjob with her petite mouth.
That's good. Use lots of your fluidvs like before,
while vigorously sucking on the tip.
Oh crap, I'm gonna cum.
I'm cumming in your mouth.
Here I go!
She carefully cleans and licks every last drop.
It seems she loves blowjobs because
Haru compliments her a lot.
No...!
Please don't push your tongue in like that.
Here we have Kuku-chan getting a big, fat, adult
tongue plunged into her flight loli hole.
While her hole gets more and more loose,
her sticky secretions start flowing,
and she orgasms several times.
Looks like it's loosened up quite enough.
With this...
No, please don't stare at it.
Surrounded by her completely white crotch,
her salmon pink loll hole awaits him.
It's primed and ready.
I'm ready now, so...
Try to relax.
This dick's about to fuck you.
Her still immature opening is being
pried open without restraint,
with an erect penis that's sixteen centimeters
long, and four centimeters wide.
Kuku's loli hole is only about six centimeters deep.
Taking only the uppenhalf of his penis,
her cervix and entrance are enveloped
in such intense stimulation
as she's completely violated.
Kuku, I'm about to cum.
I'm going to cum into your womb!
Even as the penis starts ejaculating,
Kuku-chan is still in the throes of her own orgasm.
Perhaps due to the sheer pleasure
of getting directly impregnated,
she unwittingly urinates all over.
Wow, so much came out.
Now it's a lot sticker than before we took a bath.
Let's just go again.