Ahh... I want a girlfriend.
You said it.
It'd be nice to have one, I mean we are in
co-ed school.
But you're different, you have Akaishi.
Ehh? Are you talking about her?
I don't really know other girls besides her.
It's just happens that I've know her since kindergarten.
She's not different from my other male friends.
Uh-waahh.
Got you.
Se-Setsuna... That's dangerous.
The girls are at the gymnasium aren't they?
So what are you doing here at the sports ground?
I thought I couldn't let feel lonely the crybaby Gin-chan.
Just how old do you think we are!?
You two look just like a couple, Shiraha-san.
I'm sorry for the troubles my useless husband caused.
Who's calling you husband?!
Who want to marry your in the first place?
Ohh?
If I'd have to marry, It would have to be with
a girl with feminine charms like Tomoe-chan.
What was that?!
I won't let anyone else have her!
Tomoe is my bride you got that!
W-what?
You're in to that?!
W-well, you certainly fail in comparison
when it comes to feminine charms.
And just who do you think
you are comparing me with Tomoe, huh?
Ahh... It's starting.
Later.
Yeah.
I kinda feel like hitting you right now, Akashi.
Huh? Why?
Yes? What is it? Gin-chan?
Are you still at the classroom?
Yeah, I'm about to attend club activities right now.
Could you do me a favor and take my
gym uniform with you when you go home?
We have gym tomorrow but I kinda forgot and left it there.
Uwah... it stinks of sweat.
Shut up!
Jezz. It can't be helped.
I feel great today.
It's so good when my body performs when I need it.
Is the most happiest moment.
Tomorrow, I'm gonna show off in front of Gin-chan.
To Gin-chan.
I always get so riley when Gin-chan crosses my mind.
My body feels all tingly.
No no.
But it'd be bad if I did that at school.
Kuroki-sensei has the keys, it'd be bad to keep him waiting.
B-but, right now, I'm the only one inside the locker room.
If I do it now. It'll just be quick.
Just a little bit.
I can't believe I'm getting off with Gin-chan's smell of sweat.
Am I a pervert?
During that time at gym class, I was so close to him.
My heart was pounding that entire time.
Gin-chan. I love you. I love you!
Gin-chan.
Ehh? K-Kuroki-sensei?
Nooo.
L-let me go.
Isn't this the girls locker room!?
It's fine.
The other students have already went home anyways.
I've always liked you Shiraha-san.
Eh?
W-what are you saying?
I've been wathing you for a while now.
You like Akaishi-kun right?
I even have proof of that.
D-did you take a picture?
Wh-where did you hide the camera?
I'll make sure to report you!
That's fine with me.
I have relatives at the police station,
you'll only waste your time.
And I could also upload the
video at the schools hidden website.
If you're planning on telling other people about this,
you better make sure you have the resolution.
What's he saying, It's just unreasonable.
He's the one who committed a crime,
he's more at risk than I am.
Do I run away?
And say it to the police.
Maybe I should consult with the other teachers first.
But they might just shrug it of as a lie.
But what if Gin-chan finds out?
If word breaks out at school.
And Gin-chan starts avoiding me.
I could report it in secret?
There are surveillance camera right?
I'm scared.
Why did it have to be me?
How far will the truth get me.
Right now.
For me, the most important thing is.
It sure fan having you around.
Let's get along like best friends ok?
Yeah, let's.
Hey, I've been meaning to tell this.
Akaishi-kun really doesn't realize how you feel.
It's alright! It's fine the way thins are right now.
Right now, I'm fine with just being with near him.
I don't think I'll be able to handle it,
if our current relationship gets tarnished.
Please.
If Gin-chan finds out about this.
I don't think I'll be able to live anymore.
Yes, that will do.
Cross your arms and put them behind your head.
Make sure to stay still.
You taste just like the water on the pool.
It makes me excited.
I love seeing you swimming at
the pool while wearing your swimsuit.
I can't get enough of the softness of your skin
and the texture of your swimsuit.
I-I don't want this.
He's licking me through my swimsuit. It feels gross.
No! Not there.
You're drenched inside your swimsuit.
That's reminds me,
you were playing with yourself just while a go.
This is quite something.
It just keep oozing out.
No!
It looks tasty.
Please sto...
Noo... Don't suck it so hard.
It hurts.
It tastes like pool water,
with a hint of saltiness.
Why did you do that.
Well then, take off your swimsuit.
Eh?!
And... could you try waring that gym uniform?
Ohh, that's good.
A girl wearing a guy's clothes is arousing.
We can't be doing this.
Please don't involve Gin-chan in this!
It's alright. There won't be any traces
of evidence left after it goes tb the laundry.
And besides, I know you can't get enought of his smell right?
Even in this situation,
I can't help but react to Gin-chan's smell.
You're a virgin right?
It won't do if you're scared of having sex.
I'll make sure to loosen you up nicely.
I'm gentleman after all.
Noo... I'm scared.
You're wet but, your pussy still won't open up.
I'll need to loosen you up more,
mine's on the larger side you see.
He's slowly rubbing my insides with his fingers.
It's disgusting!
It's like another creature went in,
like a worm crawling inside me.
You're too stiff... you need to relax more.
Kyaa!! Se-sensei...
Th-that's... It hurts.
It's alright, I'll make sure to do it more gently this time.
Noo... Not there.
It's like my body's sensitivity is gathering at one place.
Noo... I'm scared.
My body... Is springing up.
Looks like you've relaced a bit.
And you've loosened up.
If I keep it up, you'll open up eventually.
I-I can't anymore.
Any further that this.
Huh?
Look, this thing's gonna enter your pussy.
Try touching it.
Noo. It's too big. It's impossible.
It will be fine, my dick is already slippery.
Ahh, it feels good just rubbing it.
Stop.
Don't rub your dick on me.
I never imagined this.
At this rate I'll end up cumming too soon.
Noo.
My thing feels hot.
Sensei... stop it.
Your love juice keep oozing out, it won't stop.
No.
S-stop... do it slowly.
Noo... save me... Gin-chan... save me.
I'll let it out, Shiraha-san.
I'm gonna spray my semen on your beautiful skin!
No.
I've always thought giving my first time to Gin-chan
would've been fine.
But that would never happen I guess.
But, I never thought, that would end p.
In the worst appearance imaginable.
I'm being started so lewdly by this man.
I never imagined this would happen.
I'm putting it in.
My Shiraha-san.
The precios first time that I've held on to,
I never thought it will be taken away like this.
But if I endure this, I'll be able to protect
what's most important to me.
This is nothing.
That was supposed to be.
Kuroki-sensei's vicious gaze.
He's touching all over with his sweaty hands
and his thing is pressing onto me.
This is so revolting, I just want to cry.
I'm gonna keep my eyes closed.
Hurry up and finish it please!
Wouldn't it be better if you enjoyed this moment?
After all, I'm giving you your precious first time experience.
It's alright, the head is the thickest part and it's already in.
I've loosened you up quit a bit, so it shouldn't be that painful.
I'm gonna go in little by little inside your pussy as I spread your entrance.
It will ease you, if you take a deep breath and cling to me.
It's so tight.
You're gonna make it harder for me to penetrate if you strain yourself.
I'll be all inside in just a few moments.
Your entrance have loosened up quite a bit.
I'm gonna go forward a bit more.
It's gonna be even more cramped from here on.
If you feel pain from pushing it in, I'll momentarily thrust back and forth.
It's gonna be painful but, adjust your breathing accordingly.
I'll play with your breasts until the pain subsides,
so just focus your attention on this for now.
You might feel some prickling pain on your nipples but.
While I touch your nipples, I'll make sure to feel you good.
Noo.
It's a good pussy, it's nice and tight.
It's still unrefined though.
By the way, who long are you planning on keeping your eyes closed?
Don't you want to see where we're joined together?
Look my dick is inside nice and snug right?
Noo.
Noo! I don't want this!
Pull out... please pull out.
It's alright, no need to be so afraid.
I've only just put it in but, I can already move inside smoothly.
Your pussy is getting used to my dick.
All that's left is for you to feel good as well.
That's impossible.
I'll never feel good from something disgusting.
Noo... noo... don't push it in my narrow place, it's scary.
He's hitting my deepest spot and pushing it even further.
He keeps grinding it inside me.
His tongue is so slimy. He's locking me all over up to my throat.
Sensei... he's defiling me while taking my first time.
He's so rough kissing me while playing with my nipples.
He's slowly thrusting his dick back and forth and caressing my insides.
This is bad, he's gonna keep going like this.
Sensei... please.
I don't mind even if it hurts.
Please finish quickly.
This is troubling.
It's like I'm raping, forcing myself on a girl
unaccustomed to sex and making her cry, I don't want that.
Eh? What's he saying now at this late hour.
So, why don't you try moving at your own pace, Shiraha-san?
It's inside you again.
I'm gonna support your hips.
Try moving now.
No.
If I move to fast, the stimulation will be too strong,
my body won't be able to cope up!
You don't have to rush.
I-I'm alright.
Oh, your doing your best.
I like diligent girls like you.
Well... but you know.
It's gonna take some time doing it like this.
N-No way.
It can't be helped.
You we're doing your best and all.
I think it's time we move on to the finish.
Since you're the one who suggested it.
No matter what happen, I'll never stop.
M-My inside.
You're piercing it.
My belly's gonna break.
No.
I-It's coming out.
Noo.
Woah, were you feeling too good that you had to take a leak?
Seeing you peeing like this makes me excited, Shiraha-san.
Well a man's gotta impregnate girls.
I want us to come together but I've just put it in so
I'll make it last a bit more.
I'll rub your clitoris as well.
Noo.
I'm gonna ejaculate soon.
Let's come together, Shiraha-san!
Noo! Noo! I'm scared!
It's coming out.
To your deepest part.
It's over.
Noo!
Please let me go.
Hurry up and get started getting used to my dick.
I'll only let you off after I cum inside five more times.
You're a tough girl, Shiraha-san. I know you'll be fine.
My head has gone blank.
The only thought that crossed my mind was to
hurry home and wash the gym uniform.