I Always Loved You 2
You saved me!
Thanks, Setsuna.
You better be thankful!
Now you owe me one.
Wow you're stingy.
Just like me though, your gym clothes really smell like sweat.
Oh, do they?
No.
S-Stop it.
S-Sorry.
I wanted to stay home today, but
I didn't want to worry Gin-chan.
I'm not cute and big-breasted like Tomoe.
Even though I'm not even girly at all
why did it have to be me?
Tomorrow's Saturday.
At the least, please stop doing this at school.
It's scary to think what would happen if someone saw us.
More than anything, I don't want the place
where I spend time with Gin-chan
to become a place of trauma and bad memories.
Alright, would you keep your Saturday open for me?
I won't do anything to you on schooldays.
Thank you.
Even though this didn't solve anything
I felt completely relieved.
Why'd I buy a new set of underwear just for today?
Shiraha-san, I'm done with the bath.
I-I think I'll freshen up too.
No. There's no need for that.
P-Please wait. I might smell like sweat.
I'm not emotionally ready.
You smell sweet.
Girls your age have a special smell.
It's a different smell from when you're
fresh out of the pool. I like it.
White panties really suit you.
You're cute, Shiraha-san.
You're doing that?!
You've got a healthy-looking, beautiful
complexion and a white brassiere
and small, cute nipples.
It's a very inviting set of features.
No!
Kuroki-sensei's fingers and words
even though I don't like them, they're
making me feel like a girl.
I can feel it inside me!
I'm being made into a girl, in body and mind!
Shiraha-san.
You're making a very lewd face right now.
I-I'm not! It's not lewd!
My nipples are tingling. They're swelling and hardening!
I'm undressing you now.
P-Please wait! Please, don't look at me!
Your body really learns quickly.
It's just like swimming. Your body knows
what to do before your mind does.
It knows that doing this will make you feel good.
Next you'll understand what you really want.
He's licking me though my thin panties with his hot tongue!
You're rubbing through the cloth!
No!
Your breath's become rough, I'm guessing
you want me inside you now.
N-No, I don't!
You're so wet inside your panties.
This isn't just my saliva, you know.
I'm putting it in, Shiraha-san.
Relax.
Don't struggle. You know this by now, don't you?
It's really tight!
But my body's getting used to Kuroki-sensei inside me!
You've gotten the hang of it.
Your body's gripping me inside.
I didn't understand it the first time
but now that I can gather my thoughts.
My body's enjoying the feeling of a penis inside me!
I'll be gentle, so there's nothing to worry
about. There's nothing to be scared of.
He's being gentle, but he's keeping up an unrelenting tempo!
Your body's started responding, hasn't it?
Hang in there, Shiraha-san. There's more to come.
I-I can't, sensei.
P-Please stop this!
You're already about to cum, aren't you?
You're like this after only two times?
You've really caught my eye.
No!
Don't try to run. Cum while I watch, Shiraha-san.
You came really hard.
Cum some more while you're at it! Come on, come on!
Thanks to your last orgasm, I know
how to pleasure you better now.
What's this!? I feel it in my womb!
I can feel the crevices of my womb.
It feels tingly and warm inside!
Good girl, good girl.
Did you feel it rubbing your deepest spot just now?
I don't really remember what happened after that.
I'll give you plenty of semen inside.
Sensei!
Your... it feels so good!
Shiraha-san, I'm gonna cum.
I'm cumming too!
Well done. You're cute, Shiraha-san.
Sensei, more.
In grade school, I couldn't swim.
I was afraid of the water.
But playing with Gin-chan made it
fun, and I came to like swimming.
I felt so light in the water. It was such a nice feeling.
However.
When I'd lose control of my body.
I'd drown
so wet
so sensitive.
I'm putting it in.
You're cute.
Good girl.
So sexy.
Good.
Cute.
I'm putting it in.
Amazing.
Y-You're wrong!
I'm...
Try saying that again.
N-Nevermind.
Sensei, please stop! It's ticklish!
Your whole body's becoming sensitive.
It still wants more, doesn't it?
Come on. Say it properly, and I'll give you a reward.
The inside of my body, my heart, and my womb
they all feel like a ball of warmth.
When Kuroki-sensei touches me, I can feel them respond.
Like that.
If he rubs me any more inside, I'm going to lose it!
No!
Inside.
He's teasing my shallow spot. What is this feeling?
Now I'm throbbing inside!
If this keeps up, I'll end up really wanting it!
I want it. I want him deeper in me.
I can't say that!
I don't want that!
But I do! I want more!
I can't say that!
I-I have.
Why don't you just put the blame on me?
You're not in the wrong.
It couldn't be helped. You were just forced into this, right?
If nobody finds out, there's no problem.
I just couldn't resist. You've got such
a beautiful and lewd body.
You haven't done anything wrong.
Sensei!
Please. I want more.
Nicely done, well said.
There's... Great!
That's so... so intense!
No!
It's leaking! Something's leaking out!
That's fine. It's called squirting.
I can't control this throbbing feeing or my breathing.
To think that my own body and
heart won't even listen to me!
But that doesn't feel bad, somehow.
Shiraha-san, you're cute.
No!
He's holding me tight, so I can't run away.
He's holding me tight and thrusting
so rapidly my mind is going blank!
Trying to resist is futile!
That's good. You're the best, Shiraha-san.
You're so enticing. I just can't get enough.
I'm... I'm cumming! Sensei, I'm cumming!
No! I'm going to break!
I'm... My pussy's going to break!
You're the type who hangs in there and toughs it
out, so you like this, don't you? I'll work you hard!
Yes, that's so good, I'm going crazy.
I feel it! I feel it inside me!
I'm going to cum inside. Shall we climax together?!
If you do me so hard
I'm going to cum again!
Amazing.
I'm still hard. Shall we keep going?
Y-Yes.
I drowned and sunk.
You really hung in there, Shiraha-san. Well done.
You really are cute. Good girl. That's good.
Kuroki-sensei's body and words seized and seduced me.
And in those "depths".
I fell into a deep sleep.
Translator: hanime.tv
Timing: hanime.tv
QA: christophersenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч