I've Always Loved You 02
You're a lifesaver. Thanks so much, Setsuna!
Yeah, be thankful.
You owe me one now.
Damn, you're petty.
You know how smelly your gym clothes are, don't you?
What'd you say?!
No.
Stop!
S-Sorry.
I really wanted to stay home today, but...
I didn't want to make Kin-chan worry about me.
I'm not like Tomoe... I'm not cute and I don't have big boobs.
I don't have a shred of girlishness in me...
So why... why someone like me?
Tomorrow's Saturday, huh?
Please at least don't do this at school anymore.
I'm scared what'll happen if somebody finds out.
More than anything, I didn't want to dirty the place where
Kin-chan and I were able to be together with bad memories.
Then how about you leave Saturday open?
I won't do anything to you when there's school.
Oh, thank you.
Even though this barely changed
the situation I was in, I felt relieved.
I really didn't want to come here at all, but
I still bought new underwear. I hate myself!
Shiraha-san, I'm done with my shower.
O-Oh, then I'll take mine now...
Nope, you're good as you are.
P-Please wait. I might be covered in sweat
and I'm still not emotionally ready...
You smell sweet. It's a smell that girls your age give off.
It's different but just as good a smell
as when you get out of the pool.
White underwear looks good on you.
You're cute, Shiraha-san.
Th-That's...
Such a healthy color. A white bra on top of porcelain skin.
And then you have these fun-sized breasts.
Together, they're quite the tantalizing combination.
No!
Even if I don't want to, my body is getting
aroused by his words and his fingers!
My insides are shaking.
My mind and body are both being turned into a girl's!
Shiraha-san... your face is really lewd now.
N-No, it's not!
It's not lewd at all!
I can tell without even looking, my nipples
are tingling and so erect right now.
I'm taking these off now.
P-Please wait! P-Please don't look!
Your body really is a fast learner.
It's the same when you swim. Your
body reacts faster than your mind does.
And it feels good like this.
It's time for your mind to understand too.
His hot tongue is moving against my thin panties.
No, stop rubbing your tongue against me like that!
No!
Your breathing's gotten pretty rough.
Does that mean you want me in you now?
N-No, it doesn't!
But look how wet it is under your panties.
This isn't saliva, is it?
I'm gonna put it in, Shiraha-san.
Loosen up.
It'll be better if you don't tense up so much.
You should know that by now.
It feels different, but it's still really tight!
But my insides... my insides remember the shape of his dick.
You're sucking me in.
Is your body starting to like this?
The first time we did this, I didn't
know what was going on at all, but...
Now that I've loosened up a little, my body's...
My body's starting to savor the taste of his dick!
I'll move gently, okay?
See? Nothing to be scared of.
This might be more gentle, but the steady
rhythm of his dick hitting my inside is...
Looks like your body's starting to react to me little by little.
Keep it up, Shiraha-san!
I'm gonna keep going.
Stop... Sensei!
Stop! Please stop this!
Oh, are you ready to cum?
That makes me happy.
Looks like you really like doing it with me now.
No!
Don't run away. Cum in front of me, Shiraha-san!
You came with everything you had, huh?
Keep it up! Keep cumming!
Come on! Come on!!
Now that you've cum, it looks like your
insides are becoming more attuned.
What's going on? It's echoing against my womb!
It's hitting so hard, I can tell what shape my
womb is! It's making my stomach so hot!
There there, good girl.
Can you tell that I'm rubbing against your womb?
I can't really remember what happened after that.
I'll be sure to load you up with lots of my cum.
Sensei...
Sensei, your dick feels good... It feels so good!
Shiraha-san, I'm gonna cum.
I-I'm gonna cum too!
Good job hanging in there. You're so cute, Shiraha-san.
Sensei... more...
When I was in elementary school, I couldn't swim at all.
I was scared of the water.
But after playing with Kin-chan, I started
having fun and swimming suddenly became fun.
Being in the water made me feel all
light and fluffy... It really felt great.
But the second I couldn't control my own body, I drowned.
You're so...
Sensitive here...
So cute...
Good girl...
How impressive...
You're...
I'm putting it in...
You're so wet...
W-Wait, that's not what it sounded like.
I-I...
Try saying it a little louder.
I-I didn't say anything!
Sensei, stop!
That tickles!
Are you sure your entire body hasn't become sensitive?
That wasn't nearly enough for you, was it?
Come on, say it right and I'll give you a reward.
It felt like my entire body... my
heart and my womb were on fire!
When Kuroki-sensei touches me,
those feelings only get stronger!
N-Not there...
If he touches me any deeper inside, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna lose my mind!
No! No!!
No!!
My insides are...
He's rubbing me so hard inside!
What's going on? I can feel myself throbbing deep inside!
No! If this keeps going on, I'm
going to break... I'm gonna lose it!
I want it! I want it deeper!
No! I can't say that!
I don't want that!
I want to do it more! I want to do it so much more!
But I can't. I have... I have...
You can just blame it all on me.
It's not your fault.
You were blackmailed and had no choice
but to listen to what I told you to do, right?
It's okay as long as we don't get caught.
You just have such a beautiful, tempting
body that I can't help but play with it.
You're not doing anything wrong.
Sen... sei...
Please... more... I want more...
Good girl.
You said it perfectly.
That...
That feels so good!
That's so... So rough...
No!
I'm gonna pee! I'm gonna pee myself!
It's okay, you're just squirting.
I can't calm my heart or my breath.
Why won't my body or my mind listen to me?
But for some reason... I don't really mind.
Shiraha-san, you're so cute.
No!
I'm stuck on him! I can't run away!
He's holding me so tightly and shoving it in
me so quickly that my mind can't keep up!
How am I supposed to resist this?!
Very good. You're so beautiful, Shiraha-san!
I want to mess you up so bad!
I-I'm cumming!
Sensei, I'm cumming!
Stop! I'm gonna break!
My pussy's gonna break!
You're a hard worker, so you like this, don't you?
You like me screwing you hard without
any breaks in between, don't you?!
Yes, I like it! I like it so much, I'm losing my mind!
I can feel it, I can feel it reverberating deep inside me!
I'm gonna cum inside you!
How about you cum with me too, Shiraha-san?
Don't be so rough!
I'm gonna cum!
So good...
Look, I'm still hard.
Y-Yes...
I drowned and sank to the bottom.
You really hung in there, Shiraha-san.
It was really good.
You really are cute.
– Kuroda-sensei's body and words
grabbed me and dragged me down.
– Good girl.
– Kuroda-sensei's body and words grabbed me and dragged me down.
And at the bottom of the water, I fell into a deep sleep.
translator: hikarucon
timing: hyakupercent
typesetting: hyakupercent
editor: braden
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч