Damn, I want a girlfriend.
I know, right?
I thought going to a coed school would
make this easier, but I guess not.
But I thought you had a girl, Akaishi.
Huh? Oh wait you're talking about her?
She doesn't count as a girl.
We might have known each other since kindergarten,
but she's basically the same as a bro to me.
I've always loved you
Operation Tackle is a success!
S-Setsuna?! That was dangerous!
Aren't the girls supposed to be in the
gymnasium? Why are you out here?!
I thought it'd be bad if I left a little
crybaby like you all by himself.
That was years ago!
You guys... you're like an old married couple.
I'm so sorry for the trouble my useless husband is causing you.
Who the hell is?!
I'd never marry her.
Really?
If I were gonna get married to anyone,
Akaishi-kun?
it'd have to be a more feminine kind
of girl like Tomoya-chan you know?
What'd you say?
I'm not giving her over to you, Kin-chan!
She's gonna be my wife!
Wh-What?! So you're one of those?
Hm, well thinking about it, you'd go well
together because opposites do attract.
A-Are you trying to say that we wouldn't look good together?
Oh that's the bell.
Later!
Yep.
I wanna hit you so hard right now.
Huh? Why?
Yes? What, Kin-chan?
You still in the classroom?
Yeah. Just about to go to practice.
Think you could wash my gym clothes for
me and give them to me tomorrow?
We have gym tomorrow and I forgot
to bring them home with me.
Ew, that's gonna smell.
Shut up.
Geez, that guy's a mess.
Man I felt great today.
It's the best feeling when your body
moves exactly as you want it to.
I'm gonna brag about this to Kin-chan tomorrow.
Kin-chan...
Whenever I think about Kin-chan when I'm in a certain mood,
my body just starts to get so hot.
No, I can't. I'm at school right now.
Kuroki-sensei's waiting on me too right now to lock up.
Akaishi
But right now I'm the only one in here.
I should be able to cum really quickly.
Just a little bit...
I love the smell of his sweat.
Am I some kind of pervert?
My heart always goes crazy when we're
next to each other after gym.
Kin-chan... I love you.
I love you!
Kin-chan!
Kuroki-sensei?
No!
Please let go of me!
This is the girl's locker room!
I don't see a problem. Everybody's gone by now.
I've loved you for so long, Shiraha-san.
Wh-What are you talking about?!
I've been watching you forever.
Akaishi
You like Akaish-kun, right?
I even have video proof.
You filmed me in secret?!
Wh-Where's the camera?!
I'm gonna report you to the cops!
Do what you want, but I have friends
there, so I doubt it'd go too far.
Also I can upload the video to the school's
underground website whenever I want.
You should ready yourself for having everyone
in the school see what you just did.
What's he saying?
This is messed up.
He's the one committing a crime. He's
in a worse position than I am for sure!
I'm gonna run for it.
Should I go to the police? Or should I go to another teacher?
They probably wouldn't believe me.
If that video gets out though and Kin-chan sees
it.. and the entire school sees it, then...
What if Kin-chan starts to hate me?
Maybe I could report him without him knowing.
Are there any other secret cameras?
I'm so scared. Why is this happening to me?!
How much of what he's saying the truth?!
Right now, the most important thing to me is...
It's always so much fun hanging out with you.
Let's keep it up, bestie.
Yeah, let's do it!
Want me to tell him for you?
Akaishi-kun doesn't seem to notice
your feelings one bit, Setsuna.
It's fine just the way it is now.
As long as we're together forever, I'll be happy.
If our relationship fell through, I don't
think I'd be able to continue living.
Please...
If Kin-chan finds out, I won't be able to keep living.
Yep, good choice.
Put your hands on your head and keep them there.
You still taste like the pool.
Really turns me on.
I love seeing you in a swimsuit Shiraha-san.
The softness of your skin and the feel of your swimsuit on it...
I can't get enough of it!
No... His warm touch on me feels so disgusting.
No, not there!
Your swimsuit's drenched.
Oh, right, you were enjoying yourself
just a little while ago, weren't you?
This is amazing.
It just keeps getting wetter.
No...
Looks tasty.
Please stop...
No! Please stop sucking it!
It hurts!
The pool water mixing in really gives it a salty taste.
Why are you doing this?
Okay, time to take off your swimsuit.
And how about you put on that gym uniform over there?
Akaishi
Oh, that's good. So good.
Nothing hotter than a girl wearing a guy's shirt.
This isn't good. I don't want to involve Kin-chan in this.
Don't worry. As long as you wash it, he'll never know.
And you just love his smell, don't you?
Even though I'm in this situation, my
body's reacting to Kin-chan's smell.
You're a virgin, right?
It'd be bad if you were scared of sex.
So I'll loosen you up a bit.
I'm a nice guy after all.
No! I'm scared!
You're pretty wet, but still too tight.
Gotta stretch you out some more!
I'm kind of big, you see?
He's twirling his fingers inside of me.
It feels disgusting!
It's like some unknown life form is squirming inside of me!
You're still too tense.
Just relax.
S-Sensei, it still really hurts down there, so please...
Don't worry, I'll be more gentle.
No! Stop!
It's like my entire body's sensitivity is focusing down there now.
No! I'm scared!
My body arched itself.
Looks like you're more relaxed now. Definitely looser now.
I'm gonna spread you out even more now.
N-No more. Please, no more...
Look, this is gonna go inside you.
Try touching it.
What? It's so big. There's no way.
Don't worry. I'll lube it up.
Oh shit, just doing it like this feels so good!
No, stop rubbing your dick.
This is even better than I imagined.
I'm gonna cum real quick, okay?
Huh? No!
It's hot! Sen... sei... Stop...
Your love juices just keep pouring out, huh?
Please stop this!
Save me... Kin-chan!
I'm gonna cum, Shiraha-san!
I'm gonna cum all over your pretty skin!
No!
I always thought that Kin-chan would be my first.
But I guess I only thought of that as a dream.
But...
I never thought that my first time would be like this.
I never thought that there was a guy who
was looking at me with lustful eyes.
Here I go. You're mine, Shiraha-san.
I never really cared too much about my first time,
so as long as I grit my teeth and bear it...
If I can protect my relationship with Kin-chan, then...
Then this is nothing!
Or at least it should be...
But Kuroki-sensei's passionate eyes,
his shaking sweaty hands, the thing he's pushing into me...
It makes me want to burst into tears. It makes me feel so sick!!
I'm gonna shut my eyes so just hurry up and end this already!
You don't have to be like that.
You should enjoy your first time.
It's okay. The biggest part is inside now.
I've loosened you up a lot, so it shouldn't hurt as much.
I'm gonna go slowly, opening you up wider as I go.
Take deep breaths. It'll be easier for you if you hold on to me.
You're pretty tight.
It's useless if you try to make it tighter now.
I've already made it so that I can move inside you.
Looks like you've loosened up more.
I'm gonna go deeper now.
I can't seem to go past here.
It'll hurt if I go any deeper, so I'm just gonna keep moving here.
Looks like it's still rough for you. Catch
your breath and try to breathe.
I'll keep moving until the pain goes
away, so focus here until then.
Your nipples might still be hurting a little bit, but
soon enough, you'll feel pleasure from them same as your pussy.
No!
Your pussy's so tight! It's great!
It's still not completely ready though.
By the way, are you really so hellbent on keeping
your eyes closed the entire time?
This is your first time, how about you take
a look at what a dick in a pussy looks like.
See how your pussy's gobbling my dick up?
No!
No!!
Stop this already!
Take it out! Please take it out!
It's fine, you don't have to be so scared.
It's a lot easier to move it inside you now than it was before.
Your body's adapting to me.
All that's left are your emotions!
No. There's no way I'd ever like something this disgusting.
No... No! I don't want it going any deeper! I'm scared!
It's going even deeper and pushing against me even more.
It keeps rubbing me inside.
His tongue's also going so deep inside
me, making me practically drink it.
He took all of my first times now!
Even though he's being so rough with my nippies and mouth,
his dick is moving so gently, like it's petting me.
No! This won't ever end if this keeps up.
Sensei, please...
I don't care if it hurts, please just hurry up and finish.
Oh boy.
I'm not a fan of fucking a girl who's not even used to
sex so hard that she'll start to cry. That's like rape.
This IS rape.
So how about you move the way you want to?
It's inside again, huh?
I'll hold your hips for you, so try moving around a bit.
No! If I move, the pleasure's just too
much and my body can't handle it!
Don't overdo it.
I'm fine.
Oh, you're really trying.
I love girls with energy like you.
But I don't think this is speeding things up too much.
No... you're kidding!
Guess I've got no choice.
I'll respect your efforts and help you
get to the finish line a bit faster.
You're the one who told me to, so I won't
stop no matter how much you beg me to.
I-It's so deep!
You're thrusting so deep! You're gonna break my stomach!
Oh god, no...
No...
Geez, was it so good that you couldn't hold it in anymore?
That really turns me on though.
Alright I think it's time I planted my seed.
I'd love to cum with you, but I don't think
that'll happen with just my dick.
I'll rub your clit for you.
No!
I'm gonna cum!
Let's do it together, Shiraha-san!
No!
I'm scared!
It's coming out.
It's going inside your womb!
It's over...
No, please stop.
I want you to get used to my dick as quickly as possible.
After we do it five times, I'll let you go.
You've got spunk, so I'm sure you'll be fine.
My head was blank and could only focus on one thing...
that I had to go home and wash the
gym clothes as soon as I could
translator: hikarucon
timing: hybrio21
typesetting: hybrio21
hentaisenpai
quality control: hentaisenpai
softsub: торрент иваниваныч