kkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkkk
Gentle Summer
The classroom where the summer's evening sun shine
Hey, did you hear that Monami and Hiroki from our class had sex?
Well, unlike you, she feels more like an adult.
I dont wanna hear that coming from YOU.
As far as I know, being your childhood friend and all. You havent even had one girlfriend yet...
That goes for both of us, right? (Laugh)
That's right, all this time you've never had a boyfriend.
That's rude...
Don't compare me to the likes of you!
Having sex is not that hard, really!
Oh-ho... So, why don't you show me that amazing technique of yours?
Of course it should be no problem, right?
Well sure!
See if I care if you regret it later!
Get it now? This should be enough, right?
Let's go home.
Oi, wait!
Did you think you could get away with just fellatio?
Come on now, stick out your ass!
No, stop it!
Until now, how many guys have you done it with?
Hey, it feels nice, doesn't it?
Don't say... mean things...
Alright, I'm coming. I'll be sure to release everything inside!
Noo~, don't come!
No! No!!
Before when I saw your penis...
...my heart was actually beating really fast.
It gets this big...
Fheels ghood?
Natsumi... it's warm, and feels gooood!
Oishii~ (tastes good)
I cant let you come just yet.
This time... let me feel it gently.
I'm a bit scared...
It feels good...
Amazing...
Yu-chan's... is really warm...
Does it feel good inside of me?
I can't let you come just yet.
I'm comi-, coming!
To do something like THIS in the classroom...
It makes your heart beat, right?
Hey... watch my pussy...
To be watched masturbating...
It's embarresing but...
...it feels good.
I'm soaking wet all over.
Oh noo, in such a embarresing situation...
To be watched by Yu-chan...
To think you would be so nasty, I had no idea.
Mou~ Baka!
It's touching... all the way inside.
Noo~ I can't... I'm coming! I'm gonna come!
What, don't you try and satisfy yourself only. You will not come until I do!
Please! I can't hold it any longer...
Let me come!
Mou~
You're such a teaser!
Hey, do me this way too!
I can't stand it much longer...
Hey, why dont you try on your own and move your hips.
Yada~, you meanie~!
Not like that! That way it'll go soft.
Push it further in, all the way in!
Ahh! I'm coming! I'll release inside of you.
I'm coming, I'm coming!
Fill me up with lots of cum!
I too... came... a lot...
Made by your friendly neighbour, Anon. Sorry for the english!