My name is
Jun Kitano.
I'm a porn manga artist, my forte
is expressing all the nasty details.
This is my cute fiance, Miyuki,
who used to be my assistant.
We have finally
become man and wife.
Actually, tonight is our
very first night together.
Darling!
[ Jun & Miyuki Kitano ]
Honey!
Darling...
Honey...
Darling!
You were so beautiful
in that wedding dress...
Can I see you in
the dress again?
It might inspire me to
come up with a story.
Sure, I'll do anything
for you, Darling,
How do I
look, Darling?
You're so
beautiful, Honey!
What's the
matter, Darling?
I'm so
happy, Honey.
Me too,
Darling...
But, um,
I'm a virgin...
I know, we've never
actually went all the way...
Please be gentle.
Darling...
No, you're getting my
panties wet, Darling.
Okay, then I'll take
them off for you, Honey.
It feels good when I
lick you here, doesn't it?
Darling...
Please,
I want Darling...
It's going to
hurt a little.
It's okay, I want
to be with Darling.
I love you,
Miyuki.
You can move
your hip.
I'm so happy, Miyuki.
I'm so happy!
Oh Darling!
I love you Darling!
This is it...
Oh Honey...
How about here?
Darling,
wake up.
You have a
visitor, Darling.
A visitor?
Good morning, Mr. Kitano.
Do I know you?
I'm sorry to bother
you so early.
My name is Sonoko Mifuji,
I'm from Aranami publishing.
The chief editor from
Aranami publishing?
Yes.
I know I don't have
an appointment...
...but I came here today
to offer you a job.
Here you go.
What kind of job are
you talking about?
Well, I'd like you to
draw a manga anthology.
Seriously?
Yes, we'd like you to create
something that would span many...
...different genres and be a masterpiece
of twenty-first century culture.
That's awesome!
We can pay off the
mortgage with this, Darling!
I can't believe it, this is a great
opportunity for a manga artist!
There's one thing, you need
to finish the job in 30 days.
What?
You have 30 days.
30 days?
So, what
do you say?
I understand that
you're a fast worker.
Are you out
of your mind?
Did you come here
to make fun of me?
Darling...
Who could draw an
anthology in a month?
I've just become a chief editor recently,
so I don't know much about it, but...
...is it that hard?
Of course it is!
It may not look like it, but
making a manga is a lot of work.
It takes time and effort,
putting sweat, blood and tears...
Porn is...
...the spirit of man!
Yes, the
spirit of man!
Sure I love drawing
pussies and penises...
...but it's not all
that easy, you know!
I was just told to ask
you to finish it in a month...
I used to be an
assistant, so I know that...
...it's almost impossible to
draw a manga in a month.
But my boss will fire me if I don't
bring back something in a month...
He said I'd have
to become his toy...
So if Darling doesn't
take this job...
...I'll have to do what
he tells me to do.
What a jerk!
Either I take this job or
you become his sex slave...
Darling, can't
you help her?
I went to ask every porn manga
artist I could think of, but...
They all rejected,
didn't they?
It's almost
physically impossible...
But I know
Darling can do it!
Other people may not be able
to, but I know my Darling can!
Well, if I use
Hyper Erection Mode...
...I may be able to
make it happen...
Hyper Erection Mode?
What is that?
Let me explain what
Hyper Erection Mode is!
When I maintain an erection for a long
period of time, I'll have unlimited stamina...
...and I can finish a job ten
times faster than normal!
I didn't know such
a technique existed...
However, to maintain
an erection for a month...
...it requires Honey's complete
devotion to my erection.
I will do anything
for you, Darling...
...and I mean anything.
Are you sure, Honey?
Yes, Darling.
I will take that job!
R-Really?
A porn manga
artist never lies!
I don't know how
to thank you!
What about me?
I will fax you
the schedule later.
Okay.
This is a great
opportunity for you, Darling.
Thank you, you're the
one who convinced her.
Say, why don't I buy
you new clothes?
Really?
Yay!
This is my
favorite boutique.
Hello Miyuki!
Hello.
Hi Miyuki!
Do you shop
here too, Kozue?
That's right, what do
you think of this one?
Um...
How do I look?
That will look great
on you, Kozue.
Kozue, don't tease
my Darling like that.
Kozue told me that
you've gotten married.
So is this
your husband?
N-Nice to
meet you.
Nice to
meet you too.
He's buying me
new clothes today.
I'm jealous,
what about me?
Uh, sure.
What a
sweet husband!
Minori!
Yes?
Could you find something
cute for Miyuki and Kozue?
What pretty sisters!
Well, actually...
Huh?
They aren't sisters.
I'm Minori's brother.
B-Brother?
That's right, he's
my twin brother.
I see...
Well, come
this way.
A Chinese dress...
Miyuki will look
great in this...
She could be a
martial artist...
A sexy martial artist
who's sent to spy...
This is a
great plot!
What's the
matter?
You look
really serious.
Sexy Agent,
code name 001919...
Huh?
We'll take
this dress too.
Okay...
Darling?
Jun?
Miyuki,
are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready!
Oh yeah, that's it...
Activate,
Hyper Erection Mode!
The setting is a
bustling street.
The sexy secret agent, Miyuki,
is being chased by officers...
It's a dead end.
I'm telling you, I'm just a
waitress at a Chinese restaurant!
Whether you're just a waitress
or not, that's for me to find out...
Foolish woman...
You came to?
Sexy Agent 001919...
...or would you rather be
called Madam Orgasm?
Where am I?
If you're a spy,
you should know.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
The general that you were
trying to seduce is already dead.
I wasn't trying to seduce
him, I really loved him!
Oh, I'm sure...
You loved him with this!
I love what the secret
organization, MMK, made you into!
Let go!
Let go of me!
If you hand me the microchip
you stole, I'll spare your life.
I told you...
...I'm just a waitre-
You really think
you can fool me?
I'm always up for
doing it the hard way.
Go away,
you pervert!
I also train and sell
sex slaves on the side...
A girl with your face and
body can make fortune.
W-What are
you doing?
There's only one place where a
woman can hide a valuable thing...
You are sick!
This drug was secretly
invented by our organization.
It will make you so horny
that you'll slide off your chair.
I'm a trained spy,
drugs won't work on me!
We'll see
about that.
It's cold...
Let me investigate your secret
space with this special camera.
No, stop it...
I-I'm getting hot...
How do you
like our drug?
Is this it?
Oh no,
the microchip!
Why don't you
just give it to me?
Don't underestimate the
4,000-year history of China!
It won't be easy to
overpower my trained pussy!
Impressive...
...but I don't think even your
pussy is a match for my baton.
Don't underestimate the
amount of semen I can produce.
I will wash everything
out of you with my come!
It's so tight, I can feel
the 4,000-year history...
It's so hot...
I feel like
I'm melting!
Oh no, I'm
getting loose...
I can't hold it...
What's the matter, your
body is betraying you, isn't it?
I don't want to,
but my body is...
I'm getting hot too.
I'm coming...
I'm coming soon!
I'm coming!
You are going to be
my private sex slave...
I'll tell you anything if I
can be your sex slave...
Darling, you can do
it, I have faith in you!
Please Master, punish me!
Good morning, Darling.
I cooked you breakfast, you've
got more work to do today!
Wow, this is
some breakfast...
By the way, can you go get me
"S&M Fun Fun" at the bookstore?
Um, sure...
What's the matter?
Well, I don't like
the bookstore.
What do
you mean?
The owner,
Watanabe...
He always
stares at me...
And when he
gives me change...
...he holds my hand
with his sweaty hands.
Okay I'll go with you today, and
tell him not to molest my Honey.
I had no idea Miyuki's
husband was a porn manga artist.
Nice to meet you.
This week's S&M Fun
Fun is really good.
It has special features on female
teachers, stewardesses, nurses, and...
...all sorts of
costumes...
I like the nurse
costume the best myself.
I can use this...
Use what?
Let's go get a
nurse's uniform!
Miyuki in a
nurse's uniform?
I'm so jealous!
Come in.
Doctor.
You have a patient.
Honey...
Oh yes, that's it...
Activate,
Hyper Erection Mode!
Today is a training
day for new nurses.
But of course, it's not
ordinary training.
Today's your first day
here, right, Miyuki?
That's right, how
about you, Minori?
It's my
second day.
Don't worry, you'll
catch up soon enough.
Miss Miyuki and
Miss Minori, right?
A new intern, Doctor Watanabe,
is also joining us today.
Pleased to
meet you.
Likewise.
Please begin,
Doctor Watanabe.
Yes.
Miss Miyuki, please take
your underwear off, and...
...get on the table and open
your legs as wide as you can.
But...
This is a gynecology clinic, every
patient must take her underwear off.
I know, but...
Please do as
the Doctor says.
Okay...
So how does it feel
to be a patient?
I'm a little nervous...
Doctor, please
start with palpation.
Yes.
D-Doctor...
I'll check to see if there's
any sign of swelling.
Miyuki, your nipples...
They seem to be stiff.
Let me massage them.
Miss Minori, would you
cleanse her genital area?
Yes, Doctor.
How does
everything look?
The labia seem to be normal and
soft, nothing abnormal is found.
The inside of her vagina
looks pink and healthy.
I feel embarrassed...
Now you understand how
a patient feels, Miss Miyuki?
Yes, Doctor.
Let's try something else
to make her comfortable.
Yes.
Doctor, there's some translucent
liquid coming out of her vagina.
It's kind of sticky and smells a little bit
like ammonia, but I don't think it's urine.
That's not good...
Please
examine inside.
It's twitching inside,
appears to be very healthy.
It also looks like it
wants a man, Doctor.
Please don't say
such things, Minori.
Would you like me to insert
my penis in your vagina?
What?
As a doctor, I have to do my
best to address the patient's needs.
B-But Doctor Watanabe!
Don't worry, it's going
to make you feel good.
Miss Minori, would you
cleanse my instrument?
Yes, Doctor.
Minori...
I will now insert my penis
into the patient's vagina.
Yes, Doctor.
How does it feel?
I-It feels so good...
Doctor, please
examine me too.
Doctor Watanabe, looks
like you can use some help.
Let me lend you
my instrument...
Yes, Doctor...
I'm coming...
I'm coming!
How was
today's training?
It was
very useful...
I will teach you how to use
a female condom tomorrow.
Yes, Doctor.
I'm relieved...
It seems like you can finish
it in a month at this rate.
But it gets harder to
come up with ideas later on...
But with your
Hyper Erection Mode...
I might have to ask you to help
me with it later, Miss Mifuji.
Help you
with it?
Darling!
I'm kidding, Honey!
But you
know what...
It might not
be a bad idea...
What are you
talking about?
19 days and 20 hours
until the deadline...