I'm all the patients idol, beautiful angel.
I love patients who are victims of street accidents, staying at the Hospital
and patients who can't move their body.
Everyday I'm having sex with all patients in the hospital.
Bakunyuu BOMB #1
Nurse - Tachibana Kaoru
W
You're patient who was carried in here yesterday
that got a broken leg in a street accident, right?
Can you move your index finger?
Yes.
If you need something,
use this nurse call switch...
No..bra?
Press this switch and call me here, okay?
Ah..Yes...
Did you call me?
What is it?
Did your stomach hurt?
No, that's not it.
I want to piss on the toilet, If you would help me with it.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize it.
Please wait a moment.
Miss Nurse...
Eh..It's strange..
You're still don't know the other way to use this penis, right?
This penis look's like a childs one.
Miss Nurse, what are you doing?
Of course, I'm playing with your penis.
That's not it, I want you to help me piss.
It's really gonna come out...
With this long size, It's a pity to be like this.
Miss Nurse, my piss gonna come out...
Please stop it.
Then, before you take out your piss,
I'll let your penis be an adult one.
Ah..my piss..!!
Because you came out like this,
I had drink your piss.
I'm sorry...
She's pulling out her nipples.
Now I'll teach you how to use your penis like an adult,
beside using it to piss.
How perverted I am...
I forgot to put on my panties,
when I masturbated a while ago.
Masturbate..? Miss Nurse?
Good..Good...
What a hard and hot penis!
You can't, but I want it in.
Good! Come inside!
Miss Nurse!
What is it?
I'm sorry..I'll put in right now.
Don't rush yourself.
Here it this, now put it inside of me.
Yes, Miss Nurse!
It's big!
Let your hips move!
Yes...
It's good!
It feels good..It feels good...
Good...
Is that possible that you're cumming inside of me?
I think so...
Miss Nurse's pussy is slowly taking in my penis.
It's getting big inside of me.
It's hitting my womb!
It's good..amazing!
It feels good..It feels..good!!
Good..It's good!
I can feel you move.
Your pussy is getting tighter...
It feels...amazingly..good...
I feel it, I'm feeling it deep inside of me!
Miss Nurse, I can't hold it anymore.
Can I cum inside?
It's okay, let it out.
I want you cumming inside of it.
Together..together...
It's hitting so deep!
I'm cumming!
Good!
That's it!!
How do you feel being an adult?
From today, I'll be your nurse for this.
So please enjoy your time in here.
Miss Nurse, I'm sorry as always.
It's for you to get healthy, right?
Look, It's getting healthy.
I'm gonna cum soon...
It feels so good...
The taste, amount, and temperature, doesn't have any problem.
It's really in good condition.
It still can go on.
Everyone, It's time to take your temperature!
You're having so much fever on your body.
Then, I'll measure it right now.
Your fever is quite high, isn't it?
I'll measure it with this thermometer.
I'll look at your heartbeat too.
You're getting better, aren't you?
Your temperature is getting high,
quickly..quickly...
I'm feeling it!
Good...
It's hot..hot!!
No~!
38 degrees, right?
Well, I'd better tell the doctor
to get you some vitamins.
Your measurement hasn't started yet, okay?
You leave me no choice.
It hurts!
Miss Nurse's breasts are so big~!
No, my breast gonna come out!
Amazing, gold milk..It's gold milk breasts..amazing!
I'll measure Miss Nurse's pussy too.
Amazing, I'm gonna piss myself!
No~ I feel so strange!
No~!!
Let's ..go in!
It hurts!
Feels good..It feels good...
No...!
The taste of your piss is going inside of me...
I'll measure the temperature of your ass.
It's tight..It's tight in there!
I'll make it even more tight.
Tight..It's really tight!!
Down here is also tight.
Miss Nurse, I'm gonna cum soon!
I can't hold it anymore!
Good...
It's good...
My piss is gonna come out too...
Miss Nurse!!
It's okay, the two of you are in good condition.
If you hurt yourself or you get sick,
please stay at Yamane Sougou Hospital!
I'll take the responsible for nursing you!