What should I do?
My skin is throbbing.
Don’t touch me there!
Oh there… yes, there!
A holy goddess is finished once she’s like this.
I want more semen!
In my mouth, in my ass and in my pussy!
I want to be filled up!
Skuld wants it too.
Skuld wants it!
The insects are swirling around inside of my intestines.
Harder, harder… dig deeper into me!
Original story by
Rune
Shinshou
「I will give everything to you」
Ikusa Otome
Original story by
Rune
Original Animation Video
Chapter Two  「Heroic Death of the Fallen Goddess」
Valkyrie
And then, the holy tower was breached.
Rook and his demon army continued to shame the now homeless angels.
No!
Don’t look!
Please, I’m scared!
Please, have mercy!
That hurts!
I’m being ripped! I’m being ripped apart!
The prized sorcerer army in Midgard was no match for the demon king’s prized army
Bested by the demon king’s minions, Elisa, commanding officer of the sorcerers, was punished.
Stop it at once!
Do you understand what you are doing?
No… stop it!
Oh my, oh my, how pretty.
So my counterpart, the commanding officer of the sorcerer army, still hasn't known a man.
If we give them the proper “bait,” they will swear loyalty to us.
Don’t touch me there!
Please, I beg of you, unhand me!
No…
I can’t take this…
I don’t mind. That girl belongs to you.
Do as you wish.
No, stop it!
That hurts!
No…
Oh, Elisa, I did not know you were a masochist.
Does getting fucked by Rook arouse you?
Yes… this feels great…
More, more, burrow in deeper!
I love this. I love sucking cock!
Oh no, something’s happening to me.
I’m losing my mind!
Oh no, I’m losing...
Losing…
In my pussy… and in my ass, a man’s semen is flowing!
It feels so good!
It’s inside!
I can feel it inside. Spray more into me!
Amazing!
I’m cumming… cumming!
Me too.
Me too!
Yes! Go in deeper!
Mess up my uterus!
My pussy feels good!
My pussy feels so good!
Mess up Skuld inside!
Give me more cock!
Skuld… again…
I’m cumming!
Your asshole is throbbing – it really wants it.
Don’t worry, we'll soothe it soon.
With Rook’s cock.
I don’t wish for that at all.
I just… want the war to…
Don’t bother trying to talk.
Once a woman tastes a cock, there’s no turning back.
You’re lying.
That can’t be…
That is what all virgins say. But you'll soon learn otherwise.
Right, Rook?
That must have been tough for you.
I will put you at ease now.
No
Stop it, please have mercy!
Don’t worry, we'll break your hymen more later.
Don’t! It’s too big…I will break!
Help me!
You pretend to protest, but your asshole is sucking me in.
Your rectum wants me and is moving on its own.
That hurts… hurts…
My asshole is tearing!
Don’t worry. It only hurts at the beginning.
Just look at them.
Oh yes! My ass and my pussy both feel great!
I’m so happy!
Just like them, you will come to wiggle your ass and beg for it.
You will scream for more.
No…
It’s swirling inside me!
Inside my rectum, there are insects and a cock…
It's probably starting to feel good about now. Right, Valkyrie?
I'm going to get killed.
What’s happening? I feel hot…
It feels like my asshole is tearing...
I don’t like it, but why…?
This feels great.
Yes, that feels great!
It feels so good!
Rub me more with your cock!
Make my asshole nasty!
There, look at those naughty eyes. It must feel very good.
Now, make me feel good too.
Be more delicate.
Trace a circle around my pussy with your tongue.
And suck on my clitoris too.
That’s right.  Very good.
I feel something inside of me…
Oh my? Looks like the insect matches with you well.
I’ve never seen them mutate so quickly.
In time I really will make the three of them pregnant.
That reminds me, how is the insect we slipped into Skuld?
What should I do?
My insides are swirling. Skuld is feeling strange.
Don’t worry.
You will feel very good soon.
Just surrender your body to it.
Freya-sama, Skuld will surrender.
Yes. Good girl.
No… no…
Why? Skuld is standing it better than you.
How sloppy of you, Valkyrie.
But if this keeps going, I’ll lose my mind.
I keep telling you, no!
You're so soft... you seem to melt in my hands.
What a nice feel your body has.
And at the same time, you’re trembling.
This must feel very good to you.
If this keeps on going, I really will go insane.
I’m cumming.
I really am cumming!
Amazing! It's amazing!
After being forced to cum several times in front of Rook, his soldiers, and the nuns, I fell unconscious.
When I woke, I was alone on a strange bed.
I was imprisoned for days after that.
I had no idea what had become of the nuns.
I had no idea how the war between Midgard and the demon king was going.
I knew nothing.
Open up! Let me out!
Skuld!
Skuld tried to rescue me. She broke into the castle, but was then captured by the soldiers as well.
Ordinarily, she is a skilled girl.
Her swordsmanship is first rate.
But it seemed that this time the circumstances were different.
Oh no!
Freya-sama was a traitor?
I didn’t want to believe it either… but…
I’m sorry, Skuld.
My complacency has put you in danger.
Don’t worry.
Let’s rescue Freya together and escape from this place.
And then, let’s release Midgard from the demon king!
One look from Skuld’s fierce and warm eyes brought a spark of hope back to my despairing heart.
I thought that everything would work out for the best.
That’s right.
I mustn’t lose hope here.
I am a battle-virgin.
I have a sacred duty to protect the citizens of Midgard.
At that time, I made my resolve.
Rook-sama! Does it feel good?
Have you made preparations for the spell?
It can be ready at any time. I am honored for you to see it.
So hot. My rectum is burning!
I’m in pain!
My insides are being swirled around. They’re throbbing!
Valkyrie, you protested so much earlier, but now you’ve adjusted well to the insect.
How does it feel?
Don’t push so hard! It will cum out!
Oh? But you really want to cum, don’t you?
In that case, see?
Your boobs and your nipples are both so hard.
Fenrir… stop… please, stop it.
I’ll cum… I’ll cum!
The insect’s serum temporarily affects your own bodily fluids.
You want to cum so badly it kills you.
See? Look how happy Valkyrie looks.
Skuld, it’s your turn.
Freya-sama… if you touch me so hard…
Skuld will be unable to hold back!
Skuld cannot wait!
Skuld, wait. Together… together…!
So even the holy warriors cannot withstand the lure of the insect.
No… no…
Skuld!
Skuld too!
Oh, oh no!
I can’t stand not cumming!
Freya! Freya, help me, please!
Well? Aren’t you about to give birth?
To the sweet little insects.
It will feel very good.
So birth them quickly.
I feel the insects moving inside me.
I can’t stand it! My asshole is throbbing.
I can feel lots inside… inside… my asshole is tearing!
It’s coming out… my asshole is spreading out. It feels good!
You’re beautiful, Valkyrie.
No matter what the situation, you're always beautiful and dignified.
Birth it now.
Free it from inside you.
You will feel very good after that.
This makes me long for the day when they are truly impregnated.
Birthing… it…
Now you belong to we demon folk.
We will always take good care of you.
Didn’t that feel good?
If you stay here, you can feel even better.
Senpai?
Shh. Be quiet.
Let me take care of everything.
Skuld. What a sweet girl.
I have always loved you.
No! We need to escape from this place.
What a bad girl.
Your nipples are so hard.
Senpai, you’re teasing me!
Senpai! You’re amazing.
What’s that? You want me to be rougher?
I don’t!
Skuld, you are so sensitive.
A finger must not be sufficient.
I will do more for you.
No, senpai, not…!
Senpai!  Skuld cannot…!
Senpai, I always loved you.
I love you!
Well? How does it feel to be fucked by Valkyrie?
You still didn’t notice?
Oh no… it’s a lie!
No!
Under the spell Freya-sama cast, Rook disguised himself as me and toyed with Skuld.
It was just another scheme to make us fall even further from grace.
But at the time, we didn’t notice this.
I can’t hold back.
My pussy is so hot, I need something!
What a naughty way that virgin moves her hips.
Once she becomes a real woman, she will not be able to survive without a man.
That… feels good!
Oh my, oh my? What happened to your goddess pride, Valkyrie?
Well… well, it feels so good!
More!
Oh?
Very well. I will let Rook turn you into a woman.
Oh… I can’t hold back.
Rook, put it in.
Valkyrie, don’t you even know how to beg properly?
It’s “please put it inside, Rook-SAMA”.
What’s wrong? Shall we end things here?
What a stubborn girl.
You really want it inside, don’t you?
All the way into your womb.
I want it.
Rook-sama, your thick cock… I want it inside of me
Hurry!
It’s all the way inside.
But it looks like there’s no pain.
It’s rubbing against me.
Rook-sama’s thick cock is…
Rubbing all around in my pussy.
At last Valkyrie has turned the same way as the other girls.
More… I want more hot semen on me!
Skuld feels so good.
Oh, Skuld!
I feel good also!
Rook-sama’s semen… please spray it into me!
We needed to rescue Freya-sama and free her from their spell.
I freed Skuld and we ran together to Freya’s room.
Where are you going, you girls?
Freya-sama, you are being bewitched!
Please, you must come with us.
You misunderstand, Valkyrie.
I am the happiest I’ve ever been here.
You must hurry and become a sex slave like me.
You must taste the wonderful ecstasy with me.
You bastards! How dare you ruin Freya-sama!
Skuld?!
Senpai, please don’t lose your temper.
Let us all have fun together.
Skuld, not you too!
I’ve always, always loved you.
And now we can be together forever.
I am so happy!
Even the pure and sweet Skuld has fallen into their evil trap.
How could I have not noticed how Skuld felt when we’d spent so much time together?
It’s all my fault.
Senpai, you should join us.
I see.
What I wanted to protect all along... was Skuld.
Well, Valkyrie? Your pussy is very wet.
You can see it, can’t you?
You’re almost there, Valkyrie.
You’re on the cusp of being excited rather than embarrassed that you’re becoming like Freya.
No… I’m so disgusting!
Seriously. So much disgusting juice is flowing out.
Valkyrie, you really are a slut.
No, don’t say that.
My pussy is being rubbed and fucked up by Rook’s cock.
I had no idea it felt this good.
Please go in deeper.
Yes!
Rook-sama, I’m almost there…
I will cum plenty inside of you so you'll feel even more pleasure.
Please cum! Please give me your mighty cum!
Rook-sama, your tip is poking my uterus… so deep...
It feels great!
Yes! Oh no!
Oh, amazing!
Yes!
My asshole feels so good!
Oh no…
I feel strange… I’m going to cum!
What should I do?
I’m about to cum!
That’s not right, Valkyrie.
You need to beg Rook, not me.
You need to tell him that you need him.
Rook-sama!
I’m begging you. Please fill my uterus with lots and lots of semen!
If you receive my seed, you probably will get pregnant.
I’m… cumming… hurry! Hurry!
It’s going in.
Rook-sama’s semen is pouring into my uterus.
It feels great!
Please give me more!
We were dragged out to the village square,
and shamed by the demon king’s minions in front of our own subjects.
And when the people of Midgard saw how our bodies and souls had been transformed,
they hated us.
We three goddesses… and even the highest goddess Odin-sama… were all turned into sex slaves.
The holy kingdom ruled by the just gods was transformed into a land of sexual deviancy.
Please! Rook-sama, I want your thick cock in my pussy!
No, Freya-sama.
Rook-sama, Skuld is the best for you!
Rook-sama, you will fuck me first, won’t you?
My pussy is always available for you.
You three, how can you be so naughty?
Whose seeds are inside of your bodies?
You’re being unfair, Fenrir, keeping Rook all to yourself.
Rook-sama, this is perfect.
I love feeling your thick cock ripping through my pussy and stretching it out.
I’m about to cum!
Valkyrie, please watch!
I'm going to cum with a cock ripping through my pussy!
I’m going to cum!
Oh yes!
Rook-sama. Harder, deeper!
No, Rook-sama!
Yes, Rook-sama!
Deeper, please!
Oh no!
I’m so happy.
I’ve always been waiting for this.
Deeper… please, go deeper!
Oh, Rook.
You favor Valkyrie too much.
Rook-sama, we’re always waiting for you to thrust your cock in us.
Skuld too! Skuld too! I want Rook-sama to fuck her up!
So nice… the cock tip is hitting my uterus.
It feels too good.
I’m going to melt.
I don’t care what happens to me.
I will be your slave forever.
Don’t let me go, Rook-sama.
You are my…