Bakunyuu BOMB #3
Female Teacher - Wakatsuki Risa
W
What is it?
Does anyone out of all of you can answer it?
Who's the founder of this formula?
It's been seen...my big breasts...
You, answer it.
What's the matter? It's not really a hard question.
Hm..you think you're so smart?
Why don't you answer it?
"Nyuu Dekai Size"
(Big Breast Size)
Almost right, but It's "New Dhiru Seisaku".
The two of you, stand in the corridor.
Well, we're out of the time. Write a report and
assemble it before the next class.
Those boys are looking at my breasts with perverted eyes...
I can't hold it anymore, I'll just do like always...
I just think only about masturbation.
Risa Sensei.
Principal?
How is it recently?
If you have some free time between your classes,
why don't we take some time to talk in my office?
If the final test is over, I'll take your offer for sure.
Well, excuse me.
Just when I want to masturbate,
there's no one in here...
It feels good...
I'm getting excited by everyone looking,
on some pervert like me.
That principal who's like a pig also wants to smell something off me.
That pig is also excited by thinking about me.
Someone is coming, but I can't stop!
That teacher is a problem for sure.
Yes, she's good looking and also has big breasts
but, she's really arrogant.
That's whats good about her, right?
I just cant hold it, when I remember her.
That face of hers and those big breasts.
Even in a situation like this, I can't stop doing it.
Are you pissing youself, huh?
Ah, I want to do it with Risa.
Those boys in the next room...
Hey, did you hear strange noises from the next room?
Is that so?
What? Why is our female teacher in the boys toilet?
Risa Sensei?! What are you doing in there?
I can't even think that the teacher who always humiliates us
is masturbating in the boys toilet.
If you're like it, don't you feel lonely doing it alone?
We'll help you with that.
Two of you, stop it! Do you know the consequences of this?
You're gonna say something like that?
Then we're gonna spread this photo within this academy.
No~!
Your breasts are too big, so the water inside of it is flowing out.
Hey, It's also flowing out here.
What you're gonna do with me?
I can't hold it.
Sensei...
What are you...Stop it, you two!
How do you feel?
Calm down!
Stop it, that is...
Stop, two of you!!
Ah, I'm at the wrong place to put it in.
Me too!
Good...
Can't hold it anymore...
Sensei, I'm gonna cum.
Sensei!
Me too.
If you want to masturbate, this way feels good doesn't it?
From this time, we'll wait of you in this boys toilet
when it's the class break.
I can't hear your answer!
Yes...
Then the next time at class break in that place,
I've been played with like a toy in that toilet.
There's a rumor that some student is selling
a ticket to get inside of that place.
I don't know when the rumor started,
but when it's the class break there's a lot of boys
waiting in line to get inside of it.
That's not only the one,
after having sex with ten students my mind is filling with the sperm.
You've been working hard, I see.
Get out!
Get out? This is boys toilet, you know?
Get out!!
I know what you're doing all the time in here.
If I let the principal know about that,
you're gonna get scolded by him.
Well, why don't we take this chance?
I'll help you to get this over with,
Sensei.
Stop..Stop it!
It's gonna be poison, If you hold it up.
No.. let me go! No~!
No, you can't! I'm gonna piss myself!
That's why I told you let it out!
Or you want me to get it out?!
Is that..Is that it?
It's look like your liquid is going out before your piss.
It hurts..It hurts!!
It's really big.
No~! It hurts~!
No..No~!
It's amazing!
I haven't felt something like this before.
It's out..It's gonna come out..It's out..It's coming out!!
It feels good...
Is it okay? Is there something you don't know up 'till now?
If you look at your books, you'll know.
Then if there's no questions,
Sensei, If you don't feel good,
why don't you go to the infirmary?
We'll go together with you.
Let it go! Clamp it between your breast and lick it!
Risa Sensei~
You've become something like this?
Principal promised our graduation
If we let Risa be his pet, you know?
We don't have any problem, cause we still
have a connection with you.
First thing is, why don't you let me feel those big breast of your's?
Good..that's it..Risa Sensei..good..It's good.
It hurts!
Put you ass in the back and let me put inside this vibrator.
Yes, principal.
It hurts!
That's right, with this wetness I can easily put it inside.
No, you can't!
Oh right, do you want some more of it?
Good~!
It's good!
Good..good!
It's hot..It's gonna break out!! No~!
Good...
That's right..It's good..do you feel it?
Wait!
Good..I'm feeling of it!
Good...
Please let me cum!
I'm inside of Risa's!
Please~!
Please, go inside the deep of it.
Please!
Please..please more deep inside of me!
That is...how I become this academy's slave.