Harder! Move around inside me!
My insides… my insides are being caressed…
Oh yes… oh yes…
Freya-sama.
I'll make you feel even better.
No, Skuld, return to your senses!
In here. In my pussy too… thrust your dick inside!
It’s going inside!
My pussy feels great!
Amazing… this is amazing!
Please put your thick thing in me!
So deep!
Oh, I’m cumming!
More, harder!
Delicious...
I found something very interesting in Midgard.
Rook.
Fenrir.
This is an insect that was used in ancient Midgard magic.
They love the taste of female fluids.
And what’s more, there's an aphrodisiac in the insect’s saliva.
The dick… the dick is dancing in me!
My butthole is getting ripped apart!
It's swirling around inside me!
The insect in Freya’s rectum is laying eggs and multiplying.
I suppose the warm conditions in the large intestine are perfect for hatching eggs.
More… stuff me more!
Fill me up... Fill me up with dicks!
See there, Freya is already obsessed.
Valkyrie, you can become friends with them very soon.
Original story by
Rune
Shinshou
「I will give everything to you」
Ikusa Otome
Original story by
Rune
Original Animation Video
Chapter One  「The Night The Angel Fell」
Valkyrie
You still don’t have enough follow-through, Skuld.
I guess I’ll never defeat you.
Back then, we never knew that the battle with the demon king’s minions would end this way.
Year after year, our people would live in peace without any hardship.
And even if a minor battle with the demon king’s minions remained here and there,
we believed that our lives would always return to normal.
We never doubted…
Yes.
Until that day…
Skuld!
What’s wrong? Be strong, Skuld!
Oh dear, oh dear, I told her to please Valkyrie.
My insides are squirming… they’re squirming!
Skuld! I feel strange!
Oh no.
I’ve sent this insect into Skuld.
That’s too cruel.
Look at them.
Don’t they look happy?
There’s no reason for you to hold back, Valkyrie.
Stop it!
Not her!
Skuld…
But you hated the demon king’s minions so much…
That was reserved especially for Rook.
Meaning, she’s still a virgin.
Even though she’s such a whore.
Your pussy is… also supported by Rook.
More!
Fuck me more!
Skuld… Freya… I'll rescue you both!
The peace suddenly ended.
The squadron of demon minions led by Rook invaded us.
Soiled, the land of Midgard fell deeper and deeper into ruin.
The men were killed and the women were raped.
The demon king’s minions journeyed further and further into the land,
until the front line eventually reached the holy palace.
Please stop this, Fenrir. Don’t touch me!
Valkyrie, being sucked by Skuld aroused you, did it not?
You speak such nonsense!
But look.
Your nipples are very hard.
Please stop it!
It hurts, it hurts!
All lies.
You’re aroused, aren’t you?
Doesn’t it feel good?
No!
It’s okay. I don’t know what they taught you at the holy palace, but feeling good is not a sinful thing.
Skuld!
That feels great.
More!
Do it harder!
Spray lots of cum on me!
Soil me!
I want it… I want your cum on my face and body!
Don’t they all look so happy?
No! No! No!
Skuld and Freya, they’re only acting strange because of the insects!
They're not happy!
Oh, I see.
Then what about you?
Stop it!
Please stop it, Fenrir!
If you’re a soldier, please don’t do this!
Let’s fight fair.
But you’re so wet.
Stop it!
I don’t like this… but my body is getting used to it.
It’s falling on me.
So much hot semen!
I can’t let this happen.
I need to stay strong!
Well? Rook, does it feel good?
Fenrir… Why does she look so happy?
Under orders from Odin to meet the demon king’s army,
I was called by Freya.
Now, all that remains is to fasten this on.
Freya-sama? What is that?
Oh, now, you mustn’t let your precious place be pierced by an enemy sword.
How nice, it’s a perfect fit.
You look very valiant, Valkyrie.
You are the virgin best suited to represent the holy land.
I should have noticed it then.
That Freya looked strange.
It hurts!
What?
My tummy… my tummy is ripping…
It’s swirling!
They’re swirling inside of me!
Please. Help her!
Freya-sama is dying!
You fool.
Take a good look at Freya’s face.
No, that can’t be!
Oh please, do something!
Please!
Freya is experiencing so much pleasure she can’t stand it.
That gentle and noble Freya is now…
Freya-sama… your tummy is pulsating so.
Feels like they’re being born inside of me.
They’re moving.
It feels… good….
Freya is doing well.
But it looks like she’s at her limit.
Freya-sama, you're so beautiful.
It’s coming out!
They’re coming out!
I suppose birthing five of them felt too good for words.
Freya-sama...
This was inside the pure Freya-sama.
Well?
Don’t you want one of your own?
I would never want that!
Don’t fret, dear. In time you will beg for your own.
I will not give up hope!
I will never let you beasts break me!
More… Fill me up more.
My pussy, my mouth, and my butthole. Hurry!
That’s right. Amaz—
Act strong while you can.
All in time…
You will also become like this.
Please give me one too!
Oh, well, don’t worry.
Your body also has one of these insects.
I am interested to see how long you can hold out.
But first, let’s check to see just how far Skuld has fallen.
Then the demon king's army made it to our sacred church.
There is not an ounce of mercy in their souls.
There’s no telling what danger the nuns are in now.
I hurried to Midgard.
Who are you?
How rude!
This is not a place for you to enter!
Then what will you do about it?
These soldiers have lost their strength during a harsh battle.
So I must allow them to revive themselves by fucking the women here – that is my duty as general.
Unless you’re willing to take them all on by yourself?
How dare you even suggest such a thing!
What? Why does she react so?
Her service to her Lord lasted too long.
Her lust had been piling up.
I don’t mind, so go fuck the rest of those nuns.
You can’t… that’s not what you promised!
You brutes…
Going at it alone? I can’t decide if she’s being brave or stupid.
Let’s make her understand which!
You bastard…
Let’s watch just a bit longer.
So hot...
My pussy is… my pussy is…
Looks like Freya’s “gift” has started to work.
I see.
N-No, please don’t!
I’m cumming!
What a nice view.
I haven’t given up yet…
You’ve caused such violence. You must repent for that.
To think that that much of the memory remained – I’m impressed, Valkyrie.
But you must be at your limit now.
Not… yet…
The item of clothing Freya gave you works well, does it not?
No… you’re lying…
Oh, now, you mustn’t let your precious place be pierced by an enemy sword.
Freya-sama was…
I fell for an evil trap.
And in front of everyone’s eyes, I showed my sexual self.
But I still could not believe it.
That the sweet and noble Freya would have joined forces with the demon king!
And that… even Skuld was…
Rook-sama!
What was yesterday a strong battle-virgin,
today is nothing more than a little bitch.
Skuld, snap out of it.
Don’t abandon your pride as a battle-virgin.
Don’t worry about it.
Rook will make a woman out of you very soon.
Hurry!
Oh no!
Ouch! That hurts!
A virgin pussy sure is tight.
Skuld!
She looks so happy.
She’s lucky to be pleasured by Rook.
Well then, let’s go.
Oh, this feels great!
Harder, harder, faster!
Oh my, oh my, look at how obsessed she is.
Skuld!
I love that expression.
So beautiful.
Harder!
Ah yes, I must also…
What are you?!
I must also give you a beautiful present.
Don’t!
Don’t hold back. It will feel very good.
So good that you will not want to return to your former life.
No!
This feels great.
This feels great!
Skuld is your slave!
Skuld… is cumming.
I’m going to cum!
Oh no… I’m cumming!
Cumming!
I’m so… full…
Full of semen.
It feels great.
It’s going inside!
Into my butthole… into my intestines!
It’s squirming!
Fenrir, do something!
I look forward to it.
To see just how the both of you change.
I’m losing myself… I feel strange!