I'm a wife of some ordinary salary-man
as my husband,
with one kid in elementary school and one little baby,
living happily ever after.
Eh, where I put the clamp for my laundry?
Err...Hm...
I can barley see anything without my glasses.
Yes!
Bakunyuu BOMB #2
Beautiful Wife - Shiina Misaki
W
Madam, good morning.
Manager, good morning.
Sorry, If I'm disturbing you at the rush hour.
I'm here to collect your rent payment.
Then I'll need you to fill out this form for me.
Yes..Yes..please wait a minute.
Err..rent payment..rent payment...
I forgot where I put my glasses when I took them off earlier.
I have large minus on my eye, so I barely can't see without my glasses.
Sorry, If I make you wait.
Madam, you can give me your payment the next time.
Can I just have you sign this paper?
I'm really sorry. As soon as my glasses are found,
I'll give you our rent payment.
It's okay, you don't have to hurry.
Please sign at the bottom of that.
Yes.
I'll take your payment when we meet again next time.
I'm sorry.
Yes!
Ah, manager.
I'm sorry about the last time.
I'm totally useless without my glasses.
Madam, this isn't enough.
What?
Em..Madam, did you know about this persons debt?
Eh?
Since we came all the way here,
I'll take my way inside.
Madam, I'm sorry.
I'm sure it's though for you,
to be my debt insurance payment.
What do you mean by that?
Don't fool around!
We've got your signature on this paper.
I've was told by manager to sign those papers
as proof of my payment.
I'm sure you're an adult.
You don't give your signature freely for some paper that
you know nothing about.
Manager, please do something...
I can't even pay something large like 10.000.000 yen.
If you don't have any money,
you can pay it with something else, right?
That's how is this, Madam.
Even if it's hard for you, let's work on this together.
I want you to pay your debt as soon as possible,
so it can be beneficial for both of us.
No..No~!
For the time being do as I say,
and give us some service of your's.
Madam, you smell good.
That's right, Madam. You're good at licking it.
Your nipples are already standing up like this.
Is it the time your milk will come out?
Pl..Please stop it!
It's delicious. Madam's milk is really amazing!
No..No~!
Did you feel it already, Madam?
No..my husband gonna be mad at me!
Only with this body,
can you pay the debt within one year,
so you don't have to worry.
If this debt problem is found out,
It's gonna be Madam's fault.
What a noisy kid!
Stop it, please don't do anything with my kid!
So we just need to calm down that noisy crying, right?
There, your kid is also happy with that.
This wetness is a proof that you're feeling it.
Madam, don't you really like something like this?
No~!
Do you want something inside this too, don't you?
How is it?
You're finally honest with yourself.
If you want this badly, why don't you say it already?
Please put it inside...
Yes, Madam. It's a reward for you.
No...!
It's great inside of you, Madam.
No~!
Madam, do you feel it?
No...
There you go, Madam!
Quickly! Quickly!
It hurts!
Don't break that thing!
I'll have it then.
It hurts!
It's gonna break!
It hurts, but great!
Cumming!
Cumming, Madam? Why don't you?
It's cumming!
Next time, do as your Manager says and pay your debt.
Before the end of this month.
Please work hard on that, Madam.
Yes, Manager. Please treat me favorably.
Let me pinch this a little.
Let's give some of this to your baby.
It's good, Madam's breasts...
Like a dancer whose dancing around my penis.
It's good, Madam. Please put it in again
in your mouth.
Good..It's really good...
Madam, I'm gonna...
Cumming...
Madam, you really like doing it all this time.
Especially with someone like this guy, right?
Ma..Madam.
It hurts..please be more gentle with that.
Yes..I'm sorry, Madam.
No..licking my pussy like that...
It's..It's really..feels good...
Please be gentle.
It's amazing, you've already this big.
My pussy too...
Madam, you're feeling it too...
No, I can't hold it off.
Let it out.
Hurry..put it in...
Madam, I feel like crashing into your pussy.
It's big..because It's big so it must hit my womb.
Good!
Madam, can I really cum inside of you?
Good..lot of it..please cum a lot!
Welcome home.
There's something like this around here recently.
Why don't you warning Manager about this, okay?
It's true, is it?
I'll let him know about that next time.
Then, today I have some big news for you.
We have some new member within this family.