Oh, stop!
Oh!
What? It's too soon to stop.
I forgot something.
I think I left it on campus.
Drop me off there?
Forget about it.
Just get it tomorrow.
No, I need it tonight.
I guess I have no choice.
Here we are.
Thank you.
Are you sure?
You don't want me to come?
It's all right.
I'll be back soon.
See you.
I should have asked
Takashi to come with me...
I'm going in the right direction, I think.
Oh!
Takashi!
Takashi?
For the last couple of months...
...there have been incidents all
around my school, Heian University.
Did you hear about it?
Ghosts appeared again?
Again?
No kidding!
Miss Asada is a sophomore.
When she came to the
school with Takahashi...
What happened to them?
They've been hospitalized.
Asada was seriously injured.
It's so scary!
Yes, this ghost story is the problem.
Oh!
Nice to meet you.
My name is Kosaku Urano.
I am just a regular
student at Heian University.
If had to say that there was
something special about me...
...it would be that I am good at
being haunted by ghosts and demons.
Mr. Urano.
Oh, Kocho.
Sorry, waiting long?
This girl is Miss Kocho Enno.
She has come here to Japan from
Taiwan, in order to study astrology.
She is cute, isn't she?
Did you hear about that?
Yesterday, a ghost...
Appeared again?
This is the sixth time.
All right!
Our Astrological Society is
gonna uncover the ghost's true nature.
But we are not enough...
Don't worry.
We have Professor Kamo.
But seriously, isn't he
the last person to rely on?
That's the reason that
the ethanol compound...
At first sight, he looks like he
doesn't seem all that self-conscious.
He is our club's
advisor, Professor Kamo.
Kocho has come all the way from
Taiwan to Japan to study with him...
...but he doesn't look like
such a great person to me.
Ouch!
What was that for?
You spoke ill of me
during my class, didn't you?
Could you hear that?
Absolutely.
It's because you spent so
much time on the voice-over.
Anyway, let's forget about that.
Today, I asked you
here to discuss the ghosts.
This problem is escalating every day.
The interval between ghost
sightings has been decreasing...
First six months ago, then three,
then one month, then two weeks...
...then five days, and now yesterday.
The ghosts' activities
have recently turned violent...
...physically grabbing
and threatening students.
Therefore, our Astrological
Society will investigate the matter.
If we find evil spirits
behind these incidents...
...we will quickly move to expel them.
What?
Kosaku, I really wanted to see you.
We don't have many
chances to see each other right now...
...but next year, I will
be a college student.
I am definitely going to
enter Heian University.
If so, we can see each
other everyday. Everyday!
Everyday? I can get
some titty-booby everyday?
Titty-booby!
Hey, what are you doing?
Koran!
Oh, Sister, you are here?
Yes, I am!
This titty-booby is...
I mean, this girl is
Kocho's younger sister, Koran.
She's a nubile high school student
and the kind of girl who goes all the way.
She is full of sexiness but
has pretty superficial interests...
...so her charm is
the opposite Kocho's.
Why are you spending so
much time introducing her?
Leave him alone!
No!
Please stop, you guys.
You're killing me.
I'm impressed with
your popularity, Mr. Urano.
I thought only weird
creatures were attracted to you.
But I'm envious that
beautiful girls are surrounding you.
Since you have the time to discuss
this, why don't you spend it helping me!
I don't know...
Ouch!
I don't have to help such a lucky guy.
Oh, Kosaku, cheer up!
Everyone assemble at my place later.
Oh, Mr. Urano's spirit is departing!
His spirit is leaving his body?
No, Mr. Urano!
Please don't go!
All right.
Urano finally came
back to life, so let's begin!
Koran, you're so lucky that
Mr. Urano narrowly escaped death.
Otherwise...
It's your fault, you pulled him!
If you hadn't flirted
with him, I wouldn't have pulled him.
It's none of your business.
Look, you made him upset.
May I begin?
Yes.
Then, Miss Enno, go to
the middle of the symbol.
All right.
And take off your clothes.
Why do I have to take off my clothes?
Don't be foolish.
This is a divine
ceremony to summon a spirit...
...written in the sacred
literature of ancient days.
But...
You are a bad loser, Sister.
Well, why don't you do it?
Listen, I don't have the constitution
to summon a spirit like you do.
If I could, I would do
it without hesitation.
Watch your mouth!
I see, I see.
I have prepared your
outfit in the next room.
Right.
That's more like it.
Does that mean you just
wanted to see her naked body?
Well, are you ready, Miss Enno?
Yes.
All right.
If it's true or am I
dreaming, there is unlimited power.
It's the power I cannot see or touch.
However, if I have the chance
to picture it in my mind's eye...
...I will control the
current with my words.
Wind flows through the sky and
water flows through the earth...
...that doesn't only
happen in this world.
Why don't you show me how this
power flows through the dragon's body?
What is this?
No, Mr. Urano, don't
stare at me like that, please.
Don't act shy 'cause you've
already done that to death.
In contrast to my behavior...
Kosaku, look at me.
I wore this outfit for you.
What do you think?
Koran!
Enough of your nonsense!
Why did you guys leave me out?
Let's do it!
Yes.
Such indecent manners, Mr. Urano.
But, you too, professor.
Is that so?
I envy you, Sister.
You're the one who stands out.
Oh! Titty-booby, titty-booby!
Oh, it's coming off...
Titty-booby, titty-booby, titty-booby!
What are you doing?
Don't break the spell.
Remove your hands immediately.
Almost...
Keep it up, Kocho.
But...
Hurry up! Now!
All right.
Okay, almost...
I can't stand it any more.
Professor!
Mr. Urano!
Titty-booby!
Yes, and bouncy, bouncy, bouncy!
So good!
Everything is perfect.
Oh, I'm excited!
I have nothing to regret in my life.
Who the hell are these guys?
Here it comes!
Bouncy... bouncy?
Disappointed!
Never mind that, don't
forget what we're doing!
All right?
Miss Enno, use this.
Enno School: Bomb!
Why are you wandering in this world?
Who are you?
You are not just the spirit of a girl.
An evil spirit, just as I thought.
I don't think you are
the only troublemaker.
Tell me, now!
Shit!
We failed to capture it.
Professor!
This is a family crest.
Maybe, were trying to
summon some increditable spirit.
Professor.
Oh, wonderful!
Did you see that?
That was a real one.
Kocho, what's that?
What?
What!
Wow!
Anyway, you three start research
about the family crest at the library.
I will study every corner of
the campus using astrology.
Yes, sir.
Kocho, please don't cry.
This always happens.
You don't lose anything
even though they saw everything.
Also, thanks to you, we almost
found out the ghost's true nature.
I know, I know.
You won because you
showed everything to Kosaku.
I was beaten by you today, right?
I guess so.
I found it!
Where?
It's true.
It's a family crest, just as we thought.
So, cross-reference the history, and...
What?
Only this?
Okay.
Let's find out who Kiyomaru is.
The lord, Tokinaga
Nonki, was Kiyomaru's father.
He arranged a political marriage to
avoid hostility from the Miyasu family.
Tokinaga's strategy went
well, and there was a marriage...
...between Seihime Miyasu Family's
second daughter, and Kiyomaru.
However, Kiyomaru had
already had a fiancee, Riku.
That sucks.
Kiyomaru, who loved Riku, angered
his father, and they were separated.
That's too typical.
But, Kiyomaru ran way from
his family before the wedding day.
After that, he could not be found.
Every one of Kosaku's
servants killed themselves by hara-kiri.
Their heads were exposed for
public viewing at the Hirayasu mound...
By the way, what
happened to Kiyomaru?
Let me see...
I can't find anything
more in the reference book.
I bet that in his hurry to run, he fell
into the bottom of a ravine and died.
What happened to his father?
It says here that since he
screwed up the wedding...
...his relation with Miyasu family
got worse and finally he was destroyed.
Oh, it's a pitiful story.
Okay, I understand.
After studying campus, I
found out there was one place...
...with the strongest negative energy...
Here!
The pool!
Yes, I guess the Hirayasu
mound that you researched...
...used to be where the pool is now.
You mean...
Also, Kiyomaru's servants performed
hara-kiri exactly 400 years ago today.
That's quite a plot contrivance.
By the way, here, Mr. Urano.
Can you and Koran put these talismans
everywhere ghosts were sighted?
By sealing where the ghosts entered...
We can focus the location
where they will appear around the pool.
We don't have much time.
Why don't you start right now?
Right!
Miss Enno, you're going to the pool and
prepare the Ghost Summoning Magic.
Right!
I must finish the Four
Gods Summoning Talisman.
Everybody, be
careful, whatever you do.
Right.
That's it.
I finished my assignment.
Now, I have to go to the pool.
This is such a pointless errand.
I can't believe we can get
rid of the ghosts doing this.
And I still have so many talismans left!
I don't think I should
have to do physical work.
What?
Okay, it's completed.
I have to join them
as soon as possible.
What?
Who are you?
Stupid...
Do you think I will fall for such a trick?
Let me see. This is a...
Finally, all set.
Everybody else is so late.
Kocho.
Mr. Urano...
You've already
finished the preparations?
Yes.
How about the others?
Not here yet.
They are late.
We've gotta start.
Shall I look around?
Why don't you wait a little longer?
You think so?
Oh, god.
I can't move my body.
Paralyzed...
Listen, professor!
The ghost happen...
What?
I guess I don't need to explain.
Miss Koran...
They're here!
Miss Koran, use the
special charm behind you!
What?
Are you sure?
Wow, I did a good job.
Be careful, Miss Koran.
She is stronger than any normal ghost.
She?
I guess you lost your concentration
when you were flirting with her.
It's true?
Shame on you!
But you can't use
such a trap against me.
Hey, come on...
Baby!
Miss Koran, you're such a...
I wonder what
happened to Kiyomaru and Riku.
Let me ask you...
If...
If you had been Kiyomaru,
what would you have done?
You know what, if I had
been Riku, I would have...
What?
Oh no...
In such a place...
Mr. Urano, I don't wanna do it here.
What?
What's going on here?
What is this!
You went off prematurely!
Only 12 shots passed in the
animation and you've already finished.
I thought we were supposed to start
on the more passionate scenes now.
Am I wrong?
You're such a...
I can't believe you seduced me!
I need...
Koran, it's not all that unusual for
a man, why don't you forgive him?
Hurry up and get to the pool!
I'm really worried about them.
Fine!
You and your premature ejaculation!
What's wrong?
Why don't you attack me?
I know you can't.
If you attack, you will hurt this guy.
He's often been
haunted by spirits and ghosts.
What?
He's very comfortable.
I am glad to be inside this body.
Wait!
These two will fight against you.
Good-bye.
Mr. Urano!
Oh!
Professor!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, why don't you attack me?
Koran!
Here, use this!
Leave this to us and go after Kosaku.
All right.
Kamokamorablin Kamorablin!
With an adult caress there
comes adorable breathing!
I won't allow you to even
take a single step from this spot.
That was the most horrible
transformation sequence in history...
Mr. Urano...
I'll be right with you.
My holy four
guardian beasts around me...
...please act as my pike
and break the evil wards.
Genbu Showidan!
What the hell is going on here!
My red holy beast, Suzaku!
Use your wings for me!
Finally, I stopped.
You're doing good.
Mr. Urano!
I definitely want that body!
I've already told you I have this body.
If you attack, this body will be...
There is only one way to save him.
What!
My blue holy beast, Blue Dragon.
Become my clothes and
separate this world from the other!
Seiryu Reigekiko!
Are you stupid, or
have you gone crazy?
Oh! What?
Kosaku!
Where am I?
It's dark.
Don't look!
What exactly are you doing?
Miss Enno!
Is this your true form?
Shit!
My white holy beast, White Tiger.
Break the dark power
with your holy fangs!
Byakko Garetukou!
Are you Kiyomaru?
We finally found the cause of the
pandemonium concerning the evil spirit.
It was a combination of the
frustration that Kiyomaru felt...
...because he could not
get married to his girlfriend...
...and the spirits which had been
wandering around the mound area.
Kiyomaru tripped into a ravine and died
just after running away from home...
Bingo! Just as I said.
He was unsatisfied and...
But do we know what
happened to his girlfriend?
That's the point.
He felt that needed to risk his life
to prove himself to his true love.
The problem is that if he had been loved
back, she would have followed him.
Be quiet.
However, I think we, as
members of the Astrological Society...
...must send the spirits of
Kiyomaru and his servants to the heaven.
But there are too many, we
can't afford to pay for tombstones.
When we were
thinking about what to do...
I have a good idea!
The time has come to fight.
Yes sir.
Oh, they're acting.
Yes, they are.
In order to make money for their tomb
stones, they decided to put on a play.
The one who had his... squished
by Koran is an especially big star...
...as a female impersonator.
Kosaku!
What are you doing here, Koran?
Are you here?
Yes, I am.
Why don't you keep
yourself away from Mr. Urano?
Don't you forget, you told
me you lost to me yesterday!
I told you, just yesterday.
Today will be different.
Dammit! Shut up and leave him!
No, absolutely not.
I am telling you to leave him, now!