(I think we don't
understand the reaI seIf)
Nao, are you at home?
Hi, Takuya
Come on in.
I think neither you nor I
understand the reaI seIf
What are you writing about?
This is what I feeI right now
FeeIing.
You're redicuIous.
I mean it.
I'm confused.
So confused.
What do you mean?
What happened to you
in the athIetic team?
Did you get ripped-off?
SiIIy, no.
UnIike you who fooI around
in recreation center aII day
I have nobIe cares.
ReaIIy? NobIe cares?
Then teII me.
You know Momoka, huh?
Momoka?
The innocent young girI,
Yes. That's her.
I toId her that she couId
visit my home anytime.
It's coId.
I want a cup of
hot cocoa miIk.
Today Takuya said
he'd be home at 4 pm.
He might pay Nao a visit
on the way home.
In fact,
I gave her my home key.
So She wouId cIean the house
or do the Iaundry for me.
So that's the reIationship
between you two.
No. It wasn't
Iike that before.
AIice DoII
Episode One
You Don't Understand Me
Nao forgot to take out
the trash again.
It's coId.
I forgot that the heater
has broken down.
Bummer.
Yes.
I'II take a bath
untiI Nao comes back.
I'm so smart.
So she heated up the water.
Then you...
moIest her.
I did not!
Hear me out.
Peach aroma.
I'II use new
bath powder today.
It's nice and aromatic.
It freshened me up.
Momoka, are you home?
Nao.
You're back.
It's warm.
So you warm up your body
by taking a bath.
Nao, do you want to join me?
May I?
I'II go in.
Weird.
Why is my heart
beating so fast.
CouId be it's the first time
I take a bath with Nao.
What are you Iaughing for?
It's gross.
You use new bath powder?
No. I can't face you
when you're Iike that.
Do you want to
take a bath first?
I'II take a shower
outside first.
It's peach aroma.
Very nice.
You don't have to wait.
I can take a bath.
I am a bit off today.
Why did I suddenIy invite
him to join me in the bath.
Momoka, what is it?
Why are you not taIking?
If you don't mind,
I'II scrub your back.
Pass me the sponge.
I can hear Nao's heartbeat.
It hurts.
Momoka, are you okay?
Nao, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
You didn't mean it.
No.
ActuaIIy, I...
I did it on purpose.
Don't be siIIy.
Is it hurt?
Very much.
It might sweII.
Momoka, what are you doing?
I want to kiss you.
No.
PIease Iet me kiss you.
No. We're not a coupIe.
No.
Momoka.
I aIways want
this experience.
PIease.
What can i do with you.
Just once.
Nao's Iips are soft.
I reaIIy Iike Nao.
It's smaIIer than Momoka's.
OnIy one hair.
I know.
Stop touching.
It's soft and warm.
Stop. I said stop.
Why is it getting hard?
So that's what
happens to men.
I Iike this and Nao.
Nao, Iick it.
It's wet and uncomfortabIe.
What's this?
It feeIs so good.
I'm Iosing it.
What shouId I do.
In a pIace Iike this
Nao's cock enters my body.
Momo...
Momoka, stop it.
I'm cumming.
What's coming?
But I can't stop.
Momo...stop it.
Because she can't
controI her body.
Takuya.
Don't peek.
Oh. It's kaio.
Oh what?
Don't you go to recreation
center today?
I wouId if I had money.
Then come over to my pIace.
Dad and Mom are
coming home Iate today.
I aIways thought you
were stiI a IittIe girI.
didn't know you wouId
come on strong.
I'm back.
Are you Ionesome?
I didn't want you
to feeI Ionesome,
so I brought a guest.
So that's why she
brought me to her pIace.
I can understand
that you have a coIIection.
But you're not a kid anymore.
But Bangaro is adorabIe.
Bangaro?
Bangaro.
That's its name.
I can't beIieve her.
Now that I'm here,
today I'II definateIy...
Kaio.
What?
Today I'II definateIy...
I'II definateIy get it.
May I?
It hurts.
It aIways ends up Iike this.
The taste and the body
are stiII a kid.
So.
I want to ask for a favor.
What favor?
Takunya, pIease.
Make Kaio a reaI woman.
A reaI woman?
It's redicuIous.
It's not good to mess
with friend's girI firend.
It's fine.
I'm not interested in virgins.
PIease.
That's not the point.
And why me?
What are you taIking about?
Because I'm your good friend.
You don't ask a friend
to do things Iike that.
Don't taIk as if
you were a saint.
It's beacuse you're
a pedophiIe.
A pedophiIe?
Didn't I teII you that?
That was not Iike
what you said.
It was Momoka's probIem.
Who made her do that?
It was you.
Was it me?
I ask you, sincereIy.
Hope you can make her
a reaI woman.
PIease.
Gosh. Why me?
I think we don't
understand the reaI seIf.
What is it?
Momoka, you're here.
It's because
you're a pedophiIe.
It's hot and stuffy.
I just took out
the garbage for you.
I forgot that again.
Did you see Takuya?
He just went out.
No.
I haven't seen you
for a Iong time.
You've been busy with
the athIetic team, right?
Nao, do you get onIine?
OccasionaIIy.
They charge you
for Iogging one porn sites.
I think that's a
waste of money.
What do you think of me?
Mine is bigger than Nao's.
(It's because you're
a pedophiIe.)
Look.
Nao entered me from here.
Momoka.
Don't do that.
I didn't feeI weird when
bathing with her before.
But why now...
Because the room
is too bright,
I don't want it now.
Momoka.
Don't caII me Momo
But someone says
I'm a pedophiIe.
so don't do that.
It's fine. Let him taIk.
I just want
to make you happy.
Besides...
SmeII here.
Did you smeII peach?
Peach?
No.
I knew it.
I don't want to Iose
the peach aroma.
Why not?
I was afraid that
without this aroma
you wouId not wnat to
make Iove to me.
Momo.
You're putting me up.
Nao, stick it in.
Faster.
Stick your cock in here.
Momoka.
I'm aIways by your side.
I'm not a porn photo
in the computer.
Besides...
Momoka.
I am aIways fond of you.
take your hands off.
No.
Take your hands off.
I'm so happy.
Go take a shower.
Wipe yourseIf dry as weII.
What are you going to do?
I'm going out for a whiIe.
How can you do that.
Seems that
it's going to rain.
The garbage
has been taken out.
No Iaundry to do, either.
Momoka, i'm sorry.
I didn't Iike you beacuse
I'm a pedophiIe.
I just want to make sure.
She cut cIass.
CouId it be...
It's Kaio.
She didn't
attend the gym cIass?
Kaio, it's me.
I want to taIk to you.
Are you going to cut cIass?
Where did they go?
I pIanned to set up a trap.
If it works,
I'II have the chance to
have sex with her.
But if I don't find them,
everything wiII go down
to the drain.
Where on earth are they?
I got it. In the Iounge.
There's a strong odor of men.
It's the first time
I come here
and the first time
I cut cIass.
Whatever. Next wiII be
the IoathfuI math cIass.
I'm feeIing a bit guiIty.
FortunateIy,
I bumped into Nao.
Otherwise, I didn't know
how to kiII time.
Everything is fine.
I accidentaIIy entered men's
secret Iounge,
feeIing so excited.
The whoId setting is perfect.
Am I weird
to taIk so much aIone.
It's not Iike usuaI Kaio.
Is it?
How Nao thinks
of me aII the time.
I'm sorry.
I forgot you have something
to teII me.
I'II get right to the point.
Is Kaio sexuaIIy frigid?
Why?
SexuaIIy frigid?
What do you mean?
Nao is serious this time.
Kaio is to bIame.
It's far from usuaI
chiIdish kaio.
Nao, what's wrong?
Nothing.
I just wanted to ask
if you're sexuaIIy frigid.
No, you don't have to say it.
I'II know when I check it out.
Wait. Check it out?
Doing this is not Iike you.
You say you don't
but you reaIIy want it,
don't you?
No, stop it.
What no?
A piece of cIothes
cannot hide how hard you are
You're more sensitive
than i thought.
And you're enjoying it, man!
Weird. Why did they
both become siIent?
Did you cum?
You're far more sensitive
than I thought.
The pants are soaking wet.
No. You'II stain the pants.
So you want me
to Iick the inner side.
That's not it. No.
You're very sensitive.
That's nonsense.
Do you want it?
Do you want me?
to prove that you're not
sexuaIIy frigid.
Prove it to me now.
Someone said I'm a pedophiIe.
Someone said Kaio is
sexuaIIy frigid.
Why did Kaio
never do it to me before.
Kaio, you're reaIIy IoveIy.
Let's end it.
If it goes on, I might
hurt my good friend.
Why?
Why did Kaio seduce Nao?
Momoka, I'm sorry.
If I run away now,
I am not a man.
I'm cumming.
Here I cum.
(I think we don't
understand the reaI seIf)
What does it mean?
Kaio. It's Takuya
who asked me to do it.
I knew it.
Were it not for him,
who wouId mention frigidity.
So you deIiberateIy...
I didn't pIan on doing it.
But you woke me up.
Besides, you said stop
which made me want it more.
I shouIdn't do it to Takuya.
Forget about him.
He is not being romantic
when making Iove.
OnIy Takuya didn't know
that you're not a virgin?
You can't teII him the truth.
He'd be angry about it.
But he is eardroping now.
What am I doing.
I'm the onIy one
who is not in the know.