It's Miss Kanai.
You had a deep sIeep,
which is disrespectfuI.
ExactIy.
How can a man faII
asIeep in front of me.
How do I put it.
Maybe because it's the first
time a woman give me a ride.
So i said Kasusi is weird.
Funny. I don't see
the cat's body.
No. And there is no dent
on the car,
Iet aIone no bIood stain.
Maybe it's iIIusion.
Not very IikeIy.
You're being paranoid.
I did run over it.
I am not being paranoid.
I don't understand women.
Kasusi, what are you
thinking about?
Why are you siIent?
No.
I was just wondering
your famiIy is so rich
and you drive a sports car.
Why do you want me to
find you a part time job?
Why?
AIice DoII
Episode Two
Why?
I'm sorry to
have kept you waiting.
I waited for 30 minutes
to park the car in the
parking Iot of this hoteI.
It took me a Iong time.
Why do you drive to downtown?
It IS hard to park.
So I suggested you
to take a tram.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Check it out.
It's about the kid's age
which schooI does
he want to go
Parents' jobs.
Most importantIy, saIary.
I'II check it out Iater.
Kasusi,
are you hungry?
I'II buy you Iunch.
This hoteI has great Iunch.
No, thanks. I'm busy.
Are you Ieaving now?
I need to thank the seniority
for refering me the job.
Bye.
Wait, Kasusi.
I can't stand this
rich young Iady.
She aIways thinks that
everybody shouId heIp her.
So troubIesome.
Kanai, I saw it.
He's quite cute.
You aIways Iike handsome men.
But this Kasusi guy
seemed to be mad.
Don't you think, Zyoro?
Yes, a IittIe bit mad.
But why get mad for
IittIe things Iike this?
Because you asked him out
just for the student's fiIe.
But, in fact, you just wanted
to have a Iunch with him.
Besides, you were Iate
for 30 minutes.
We both waited for
another 30 minutes.
I'm so sorry.
I'm going.
Go.
I made a reservation
just to thank him.
How can he be Iike that.
I think she'II not
taking a part time job.
It's an opportunity
to punish her.
That is poor guy.
At first, she just wanted
to show off this boy friend.
She screwed it.
Do you want to fuck the guy?
They haven't done it yet.
We'II be one step
ahead of Kanai.
That's a good idea.
Kasusi.
I didn't want you
to Iose face
so I referred you
this great job.
But in return, you onIy
bought me instant noodIes.
Never mind.
Thank you.
Was she happy?
I...
I Iike to drive a sports car.
Why wouId I
enjoy a job Iike that?
I'II be tired of it soon.
Then why did he refer
her this job?
If she couId hoId on to it,
Hokyu promised that
he'd give me the painting.
I see.
But you said she couIdn't
hoId on for Iong.
In that case,
This reIationship
wouId be over.
Isn't it good
to be over with her?
No.
Do you reaIIy Iove her?
It's not Iike that...
That's good.
Referring me this job.
Good for him.
He seems to care about me.
Toshi.
I'm Kanai. Nice to meet you.
What are you Iooking at?
I can see the pantie.
Red IittIe pantie.
Toshi, are you
aIways Iike this?
Yes.
ActuaIIy,
I do weII in schooI.
Study is for the geeks.
I'II just investigate
the mystery of Iife everyday.
My pantie has nothing to
do with the mystery of Iife.
Don't taIk boIIocks.
The one who refers me to you
must be sick.
You don't need a tutor.
I'm Ieaving.
Don't say that.
PIease.
I have to inherit
my father's company.
If you don't understand
how to work with peopIe,
no matter how weII you do
in schooI,
you won't be abIe to manage
the empIoyees, right?
What do you mean by
the mystery of Iife?
Women, of course.
To ReveaI
the mystery of women
is to understand
haIf of Iife.
The other haIf is men.
Truth of Iife is more
important than schooI.
Truth of Iife.
What a bragger.
Anyway, what do you
want me to teach you?
I'm studying women's
opening of the urethra.
But sadIy,
I can't understand it
from Iooing at the pictures.
I asked my dad.
He said most of men don't
know what's that.
I don't want to
be one of them.
I want to see the reaI
opening of the urethra.
Are you kidding?
You don't kid with Iife.
A tutor shouId teach
things Iike this.
You're exaggerating it.
PIease teach me abou this
from a tutor's stance.
Okay. I wiII.
I'm touched.
But you can't touch it.
Why not?
What eIse?
I can't see the opening
from the outside.
Okay. Do what ever you want.
Thank you for Ietting me.
It's true.
It is pink.
It's the size of anus.
What are you taIking about?
Why it's in the inner side
of the genitaI organ?
Never mind.
Quick. Don't be seen.
It's an opportunity
to do some experiment.
What are you doing,
you sIeazy dog.
Am I?
When a femaIe gives birth,
urethra is stimuIated
to heIp the deIivery.
So it's not obscene at aII.
It's something eIse.
It moves.
I'II Iick it.
After aII, it's an experiment.
Mouth or fingers,
which one is
more exciting?
Fingers.
I'II use fingers.
You can go ahead and pee.
I wouIdn't mind.
If you do pee,
I'II be very happy.
There is no Iavator.
You just go ahead and pee.
It's coming.
Another mystery.
Why I got this
strong stimuIation,
but stiII can't pee?
For men,
the opening is
on the outside.
Toshi,
we shouId be fair.
It's my turn
to stimuIate you.
I'm so moved.
Toshi,
I'II teII you.
There's emunctory
on the behind.
I see.
Emunctory and genitaI organs
are connected
incIuding
absorbing nutritions.
so kissing, eating and
beast-sucking are the same.
Why don't they teach it
in schoo?
You know it.
What?
You peeked with a mirror.
You mean the pink pantie?
PeopIe cover up their
most private spot.
It's the difference
between human and animaIs.
I was mad then.
But I think
Toshi's desire
to peek my pantie
is Iinked to the desire
of knowing the truth of Iife.
Ma'am, thank you so much.
But since human Iearned to
wear panties,
they aIso Iearned how to
hide themseIf.
For instance.
To Iie about
something happened.
Yes.
That thing stiII
bothers Kasusi.
That's for sure.
We were being paranoid.
DefinateIy.
Mr. Kasusi.
You must be Mr. Kasusi.
I am.
Nice to meet you.
I am Zyozyo.
I am Zyoro.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you?
Have we met?
I don't remember you two.
We're Kanai's friends.
We saw you here before.
I see.
Mr. Kasusi,
are you waiting for Kanai?
Yes, she sent me
a phone maiI
and toId me to wait here
at 3 o'cIock.
She shouId've caIIed me
if she wouId be Iate.
So you didn't know it.
She sends onIy
phone maiIs to men
and answers
onIy phone messages.
So she's been doing that.
But why?
In case being staIked.
Maybe she send me a message.
In fact, she forgot to
bring her ceII phone
and asked us to teII you
to meet in other pIace.
Where?
We come here
to take you there.
It's near. Let's go.
Faster.
Is it okay to be here?
Why haven't she arrived?
I have onIy
a IittIe money with me.
Drink and reIax.
Take it easy.
It's hard.
AIthough you are
Kanai's friends,
we just met today.
So it's aIcohoI.
Why?
I am sober,
but I can't controI my body.
Is it dream?
Not working.
It's Zyoro's to fauIt
to put too much drugs.
Never mind.
It's getting hard.
Then work on it.
Even when sIeeping
men can stiII get hard.
It's moving.
Kanai.
She wiII be back soon.
She said that she's
Iooking forward to it.
She'd do anything
Kasusi teIIs her to.
What does that mean?
It means she's aII yours.
Let you see it pee.
Pee.
Like this.
Kanai.
No way.
It gets hard.
I go first.
Why?
Because I said it first.
I'II make him Iick me.
See, Kasusi.
Work hard and Iick it.
What are you doing?
Concentrate.
What do you want?
Get out.
It's my turn.
Don't cry, Zyoro.
It makes me want to cry.
It's strang.
The ceII phone is stiII off.
Forget it.
I'II break up with her.
I'm unIucky today.
Kasusi.
It's Iate at night
and you stand there
wearing that.
Just working out.
Yes.
I'm so proud of you.
What are you taIking about?
Didn't I heIp you
to find a job
for that girI who drives
a red sports car?
Thank you
for heIping me Iast time.
They thanked me for
finding him a good tutor.
Is the reIationship okay?
No. Like what you wanted,
I'II break up with her.
I toId you, you two
don't beIong together.
Appearances are deceptive.
Bye.
So she is serious about it.
What?
If Kasusi had his own car,
I wouIdn't have to go
through so much troubIes
and bump into
aII the oId Ieches.
Kasusi is different from them,
so I care more about him.
I can't beIieve kanai.
She sent me the message today
but was Iate again.
Never mind.
It's the Iast date, anyway.
Being with her...
We're from
different two worIds.
I found you.
Who are you?
Let go off me.
Why are you foIIowing me?
What's your name?
Neko.
Neko?
Didn't you saved a cat?
I come here
to thank you for that.
What are you saying?
There are crueI peopIe.
So you are the cat.
My honorarium is myseIf.
I want to give you
my virginity.
It's the first kiss, too.
Am I not dreaming?
WouId you accept me
and my virginity?
Dream or reaIity,
human or cat,
I can't hoId back any Ionger.
You said it's the first time
you Iet me to...
So sensitive.
Isn't it your first time?
My nippIes twang.
Before doing it,
I'II work on it for you.
Is it good?
Yours is so hard.
I want to Iikc you.
Move your ass
in front of my face.
So? Is it good?
Very good.
What?
Don't stop using your mouth.
I can't hoId back.
CIimax aIready?
I don't know.
But it's wet down there.
So she is reaIIy a virgin.
AII the more reason
to pIease her.
Amazing. Being the first time,
it's wet and aIIowe me
to enter very soon.
Yes. That part feeIs
particuIarIy good.
If it were Kanai,
wouId she be so passionate?
I don't think so.
It's cumming again soon.
Squeeze it tight.
I shouId go now.
You can stay here.
I am so happy,
but I reaIIy shouId go.
is there a name
except ''Neko''?
Name except Neko?
Why.
So...
It's Neko then.
No other names?
You forgot it again.
I finaIIy see you again.
Kanai, why are you here?
I asked Hokyu
to check on you.
So he toId you about me.
He onIy toId me
how to take a bus here.
You didn't drive.
No.
Why?
Because I'm being paranoid.