What did you want to talk to me about?
I don't have time for this. I need to
go home because my tutor's coming.
A personal tutor?
For the daughter of a murderer?
What is this?
This is...
As you know, our classmate Nanase
Hiramatsu's father was arrested...
...for murder the other day.
We are sure having a criminal for a father...
...has affected Nanase
Hiramatsu to some degree.
How can we let a classmate
like her be amongst us like this?
We must punish Nanase Hiramatsu.
What? Stop it.
No!
Please stop. Stop! No! No! Please! Stop!
I said stop!
It hurts!
Look at Nanase. She's refusing,
but she's dripping wet.
You're right. It's because she's the
daughter of a murder. She's a slut.
Ohbari, hurry up. How long are
you going to make me wait?
Calm down, we have lots of time.
Yeah... You're squeezing so tight,
you're going to make me cum.
It hurts!
I can't hold it anymore. I'm going to cum.
I'm going to cum. I'm going to cum.
Cum inside her. Who cares, she's
the daughter of a murderer.
Yeah. Yeah.
B... But...
I'm going to cum!
No!
Whoops. Sorry about that. It felt
so good, I forgot to pull out.
Okay, my turn.
No! No!
You know it feels good. Moan.
It's not good to hold it in.
Our country does not
prosecute the criminal's family.
But humans can change quite easily.
If anger is matched with subliminal
resentment and desire, it consumes them.
And they will seek to release
the pain through unsatiable lust.
I don't know who wrote the Atonement
Newspaper, but it's well written.
It's the voice of our class.
We need to thank that newspaper...
If that didn't circulate we might have
let a sinful woman like her roam free.
My experiment was a success.
The Atonement Newspaper
manipulated them into doing this.
I... I can't anymore.
Me either.
No!
This is the power of the pen.
Isn't this the epitome of the phrase,
"The pen is mightier than the sword?"
And I am the one who wielded this power.
Looks like Miho and Ohbari are going strong.
I'm so jealous. Maybe I should
get a boyfriend. Right, Nanase?
Nanase.
You're spacing out. Were you listening to me?
Sorry.
Miho Minakami. She's
from another homeroom...
...so she doesn't know about
the Atonement Newspaper.
And of course she has no idea...
...that her lover is one of the
leaders of a gang rape group.
Madoka Yuuki. She's one of the
most beautiful girls at our school.
She's completely out of my
league, but I hope to make...
...some kind of connection with her,
because her father is a famous journalist.
Yesterday afternoon, Nanase
Hiramasu was summoned...
...by a few male students from our class
and was sexually assaulted on campus.
She could have easily figured
out what would happen...
...but she chose to step into a trap.
She willingly submitted herself, to atone
for the sins of her murderous father.
Who can blame her for what she did,
if it was to atone for her father's sins?
Is this for real?
Is this allowed?
Who are the "few male students"?
What's with the commotion?
Come on, we're starting class.
Stand! Bow! Sit!
Let's continue from last time.
Open to page forty-five.
Nanase is acting strange today.
Something must be bugging her.
This is...
FOOD SCIENCES
Madoka!
Nanase, what happened?
I was so worried about you...
No! Don't come in!
Where's Mikimoto?
He ran out, saying he forgot
he had something to do.
What's going on?
What to do? The only ones who are
allowed to be here are the punishers...
...and the ones seeking atonement.
Madoka, which one are you?
Atonement?
Ohbari, you're wasting your time. It's
obvious she needs to be punished.
Yeah. That's right.
I see. I guess it'll make it more interesting.
Don't! Madoka hasn't done anything.
Leave her alone! Have your way with me!
No!
Madoka!
No. Stop.
I've got my future as a
journalist to consider...
I can't join in on assaulting Madoka.
But I have the responsibility of
publishing the Atonement paper.
I must observe what happens.
No! Stop!
Tastes good...
This one too.
Let's compare and see who tastes better.
Good idea.
It tastes different.
It's hard to put an end to this.
Let's switch. I can't eat
her out if you fuck her.
Fine.
I can't get enough.
Good eats!
Nanase's dripping wet
and she's twitching inside.
Slut.
Madoka needs to learn how to relax.
Not there! It's dirty!
It's not dirty. The hottest girl in our
class also has a great tasting ass.
Modoka's getting wet from her ass
getting licked. She's a pervert.
That's great. A hot perverted bitch!
We're going to have lots of fun.
Please stop...
Why am l...
I mustn't! I need to stop
paying attention to Madoka!
I need to calmly observe
the situation as a journalist.
What a great tool to have
in the Food Sciences room.
Fresh vegetables need good salad dressing.
You're such a pervert.
It's too early to relax.
It's our turn now.
Looks like you're feeling it.
That's right... You girls should be happy.
It's a perfect time away from studying.
I can understand Nanase, but it's
scary that they did this to Madoka too.
It's best to stay away
from what they're doing.
Madoka Yuuki? I wish I was
there to punish her too.
I wonder who did it? Do you
think it's Ohbari's group?
Who's writing the newspaper?
I see...
You're not that pretty. I wonder
why the guys like you so much?
Narumi... What are you trying to do? Tell me.
I read the Atonement Newspaper.
That article said everything that's
been on my mind all this time.
Madoka, you deserve to be punished.
Come on.
Don't move.
Don't move. I'm not a pro at this, so
if you move I'll end up slicing it off.
I have no idea how many
men you've fucked...
...but I doubt you'll want to
fuck them again for a while.
I did a pretty good job. Hey, look!
Oh, cute!
But it looks gross when it twitches.
Why are you doing this?
Because I'm popular with the boys?
Because the professors like me?
Who do you think you are!
Hurry up. I have relatives coming over
today, so I have to go home soon.
Let me see.
It's warm.
It's foaming.
I bet the guys would happily drink this
if they found out it was Madoka's.
Yeah, I bet we could sell it.
Hey, Madoka. Chug this.
I heard piss is good for you.
I guess your piss tastes nasty.
That's too bad. We can't sell it.
Please no more... I'll never do
anything to defy you girls...
Hey, do you smell that?
Yeah, I wonder what it is?
Ew! Madoka, this is pee. Stop joking around.
Madoka Yuuki was punished
yesterday in a female lavatory.
It was a justified punishment,
done by brave girls...
...against Madoka Yuuki, who was
acting as if she were the class queen.
Yesterday, an Atonement
Newspaper was published...
... citing the punishment done
by the women of the class.
That issue was a fake Atonement Newspaper.
Anyone who does not argue the
content, if another fake is published...
...will be punished just
like Nanase Hiramatsu.
This is a warning.
Hey, Narumi... Was it you who wrote it?
So what if I did?
I'm scared. You might get punished.
It's just a scare tactic. It's just a peeping
tom newspaper. It's not real either.
I'll keep writing if it brings
down Madoka's popularity!
No... No... No...
Good, Nanase. You came without
wearing underwear like I told you to.
You're getting wet.
Look at all these people around
you. You should be ashamed.
What?
Haven't you read the latest Atonement paper?
Hey, show her.
Here.
It's a grave crime to publish a fake paper
and create confusion amongst the class.
Meaning you're just as guilty and
in need of punishment as Nanase.
Don't hold it in. Tell us how good it feels.
No... no!
It's time to switch. It's
your turn to pleasure us.
There's still time until we
arrive at the school station.
Make us cum at least
once before we get there.
If you don't, we'll just have to invite
someone unrelated like Madoka again.
Nanase. Are you going to keep
committing these crimes?
Narumi, how about you?
No, I don't deserve this.
You don't?
Are you saying this paper is lying?
You leave us no choice. We'll
have to take the initiative then.
It hurts!
You're too loud. Are you sure you want
everyone to find out what's going on?
She's feeling it. She's such a slut.
Hey, I haven't cum yet. Let me at her.
Use her mouth. She's right there.
Good call.
Don't soil the train. We have
to respect public property.
Swallow all the cum.
Let's see... I want to be
satisfied a different way.
We're so lucky to have the daughter
of a murderer in our school.
Yeah, if we did this to
anyone else we'd get sued.
I'm going to cum.
Me too.
They're doing exactly what I want them to do.
My writing is making them do this.
Narumi Aizawa, how dare you write a
fake Atonement Newspaper twice...
... even when I warned you not to!
You're no match for my writing.