Encoded By www.hentaiparadize.net
Kimo...
The light is on
when searching every door
Did you call the policy
I am reporting this to you first
Master
Wait a minute
Underground...
Mm?
It seems there is a cell down there
Move Kimo over there...
But master...
I'll find out the murderer myself
Shouldn't I?
This must be some hints to me
from the murderer... No
Should be a kind of warning
Please... where is sister Kimo
She died last night
Oh!?
Who!? Who killed...
I didn't say she was murdered
Why do you think so
that's... that's because...
If Kimo was killed before
Susan was serving the master...
It's impossible
Wow!
Susan! What's wrong!?
Susan...
Kimo's room
How
Yes, judging from
Miss Sankon's telephone record
She was on telephone
Zunlio was cleaning the toilet
when I heard the sound
And I saw she come out
from the toilet
And she said she was to sleep
on the second floor
It can't be her
Jimo, get Judy to serve me
from now on
You are investigating, right
Ah-ha
If only I had such a nice room
What's this...
What are you surprised at?
You were forced
to have sex here by Dad
I don't know...
I don't know this place at all
Then ask your body
It's not proper for a lady to
have such postures
Judy
Master, why are you...
You are asking why
Listen, Judy
The suspect in old times is
to be tortured
Do you know why
Because clothes can cover evils
As the daughter of the director
your attitude
Is totally not appropriate
Why have I done wrong...
You must be the one
who wants to kill Susan, right
You were the only one
on the second floor
And probably it's you
that killed Kimo
Not me... please trust me
Be honest
No... please don't...
who told you to be so indulgent
I just wanted to be held
against your body...
It's just my wish... really
Please hold me...
You don't seem to understand
you are just a servant
What else do you need?
I don't want this...
I want you, master... oh
It seems
you haven't had enough of it
Then let's try what you said
the most disgusting thing in the dinner
No
You'd better keep your mouth shut
I can't... please, master
Then tell me the truth
Did you kill Kimo
and want to kill Susan too...
They got the chance to
serve you before me
I should be the one to serve you
Otherwise, I wouldn't have
sacrificed my body to the old man
I didn't kill her
Ok, go back
Good morning, master
Oh, master, I know
who wants to kill Susan
Really
Mm! My understanding is the one
who wants this
should be the soul of Kimo
Please work hard
Oh, how can it be this
Shall we go for a walk?
I thought here would be much warmer
it's the same
Still remember we always
played here in our childhood
Master!?
Ah
Yes, Susan seemed to divulge to me
something that night, right?
Yes... that time
master asked me about...
right... the relationship
between me and uncle
Yes?
Master! You and I are...
What!?
Master!?
It seems we are being locked
Zunlio
do you know where is master?
I don't know...
and Susan also disappeared
Thanks
Judy, did you see master
No
...oh
I am hungry
Master...
How about we search separately
Mm! Judy!?
Judy, help us, we are locked
Who!? Who's inside... Susan... no...
God!?
Master
Master, please cheer up
Oh... I just had a good dream
Where is Susan
She almost got pneumonia
but now after some warming
and eating something
she's better now
Where is Judy
We've sent someone to find her
should be here any minute
So it's not Judy who informed you
I was in the forcing house
Yes... how...
I'll go to find Judy
You keep an eye on Lily and Susan
You should know how to use this
take it in case you need it
It's all well-prepared
Mm!?
Judy!?
The key...
I was locked together with Susan
It's Judy, but who killed her...
Who killed her...
I finally got it, Zunlio
It's you who wants to kill Susan
Ha, what are you talking about?
I was in the toilet
on the first floor, how can I?
Throw a vase from the second floor
First you opened
the window of Kimo's room
to make others think that
she fell from there coincidentally
It's just the right place
from the toilet
A right place to throw a vase
You killed Kimo too
Why do you kill Judy?
She shouldn't...
it's her who locked you up
And the same person to help you too
Judy is the one who helped us!?
Wait a minute...
She's just covering the truth
To make others think
she committed suicide
Ah-ha, it went so smoothly
If I had killed everyone
then things will totally be the same
Why... why...
Why did everyone have to
add filth to this house?
It took me so long to get it clean
Get rid of the knife... Zunlio!
This is Zunlio's house
don't mess it up
This is not your house
Even you kill me
and all the girl servants
It won't be your house... never
Yes! Will... it will be mine
Master?!
She's an unfortunate girl...
It's father's fault
Although it's godfather
but he's cruel
Zunlio had long been
maltreated by him
growing up in a sexual
and violent environment
Zunlio can't get along well
with other people
Then... how about her grandfather?
Zunlio's mother killed him
What a liar!
It's true the real murderer
is Zunlio
But in order to cover for him
her mother took all the crimes
And Zunlio became an orphan
after she went to prison
I was a frequent visitor of
Zunlio's mother's restaurant
And I took Zunlio back here
since he got no where to go
But old master tries to
satisfy Zunlio
by putting her in another room
and maltreated her and healed her
oh... Zunlio really likes this home
And is very happy in working here
She said she would like to
stay in the castle
and always came here alone
She probably started to
believe from then
it's from a crush to
a desire of possession
Jimo, it's almost time of offering
Should be Zunlio tonight, right?
What are you talking about?
Zunlio almost killed you
She can't possibly keep us
in the freezer all the time
Call the police tomorrow
If it's Zunlio
Ask her to perform her duty
as a girl servant
It doesn't matter much
if she's late
Get Zunlio to come here tonight
Right, it's time to go
Father must be waiting home
Ha, you are really back today
Zunlio worked the night shift
And thought
that father was too tired
So she's going no where
This is the house of
Zunlio and her father
Father is exceptionally tender today
Father, you can do whatever you like
Mr. Jimo... is it all right
I'll have to ask your help in this
Father is a bit unusual today
There... father... great...
Father... more... more...
Do you enjoy this, father?
Ahah...
Ah-ha, I'll make you enjoy more...
I am coming...
No! I'll make you enjoy that too
Ah... No... I am coming...
Master... can you be my father?
Zunlio should have her own wishes
It's not that easy to get that
Or completely the opposite
After the death of Judy and Zunlio
The rest of us
Finally got
the secrets of the castle
Chapter Three: Stake of Summer