Encoded By www.hentaiparadize.net
How much has Dad exploited this...
That's a deal
I love you so much...
How can Dad use his niece
and employees as servants
Now the company is spitting over
the next heritor
Oh...
What's up...
Fancy meeting you here...
Hi excuse me!
Hi who are you?
And what are you doing here?
How can I go to jail
number 8 of level 4.
I'm the secretary of
Sinenger office.
Wow, she is secretary of level 4.
Ah, ha you are the new one,
brand new ha!
Ha, your boss is waiting for you.
You have to go to his prace right OK.
Come on fellow me.
Oh! Thanks.
Oh, Miss Sinenger.
That'a yellow skin monitor is here.
Yes, yes, yes he is.
He is a big bottle fatty guy.
I don't know whether
she can meet her or not.
OK, all right.
Now I understand.
Why the Mac boy
can do it colder here.
He wanted to hammer
the courage she has.
Now buddy.
I have a good idea.
I can kill you if I want.
And then put you into
the garbage can if you want.
I can do whatever I like.
But everyone would think
I didn't hide the tiny secretary.
She has been scared
and she ran away.
Don't worry about it.
Nobody would see it.
We don't like sticky troubles.
You bitch.
OK. You know what I mean.
Mr Simson
What's taking you so long... Milikun
I am so sorry...
I got some problems...
Hey, you are late the first day
to work What the hell is that?
Mm... leave this alone...
There is a urgent mail from home
Your father Simson Konsan Senior
passed away this morning...
Died... hahahah... really...
That man... hahaha
We must get the plane tickets soon...
It's not necessary
What that family will be like
got nothing to do with me
Leave it alone
What's up? Let's get back
It's master
Are we really
leaving all this behind
Doesn't matter... We are
through with the Simson family
Right... I lost father... that summer
On the seaside... and Mom was there...
that summer
Master, how about I drive the car
You can take a rest now
Taste of the tide
steps of the balcony
and the grins of
my mother besides me
You look great today
It's good to have some rest
Do you often do this?
Not really...
But it helps easy my stress
I t's also the duty of
being a secretary
By the way, about the death
of your father...
who cares...
Ithink you should inherit
all the properties
What then... if I get that
I'll give them away
I fully understand your feeling
but...
How about this
I'll make you
my personal secretary again
And you'll deal with all my money
I'll do as you wish... but master
To ensure the efficiency of
everything You should come back
Mm...
That's a deal then, master...
Can I interrupt you? Master
What's the problem?
About the inheritance of Konsan
I found some are not clear after
my investigation
So you should be the guardian and
move the headquarter to Japan
What do you think?
Surely all undergoing cases
shall be closed right away
So please board the plane
as soon as possible
This is the list of inheritance
We'll meet in Japan then
Oh... Thank you so much
the key to Dad's safe is lost
Where is it actually...
What are inside the safe
Welcome back, master
It's you, Jim... long time no see
We have been expecting you
for so long
He should...
Cut it out! I warn you
I am not intended to
take over this family
I am back to deal with inheritance
I am not getting involved
Master...
Please stay, master...
Your father's will says
that all properties of
Duke Bloomfield and other people
are to inherited by you
including this building
I know about the Duke
I appointed my secretary to deal with this
But... Leave alone the other things
this castle has the memory of
your mother and you as well
Cut it out!
I told you
I would get rid of all this
You'd better pack up
and find a new place
If this is the case
there is no way out
But before everything
is done away with
I'll still be a good butler
of Simpson Family
Want to be a boss
Watch your language
Do as you like
you are not
staying here long after all
excuse me
We'll send someone to
serve you later
This way
How about your long-lost house?
Can't be any better
Father even used his niece and
employers as servants
What the hell is going on?
How's your arrangement?
It's been going smoothly
But the company is splitting over
the heritor and factions
Do you have a key in your place?
I don't see any...
Some small things?
Do you still have them...
Really? Then please proceed
with the arrangements
keep in touch
Mm!?
We can't possibly send you
the stakes of the courtyard
Got it
Kimy, you are so sensitive
Don't be this... Zunlio
Then give me my best...
forgive me...
Kimy is old man's favorite
go on cleaning the room
...then tonight...
the little master doesn't like here
nor the stake
And we'll be driven out
of here soon
So... right
What!? Say it again, Jimo
Meal time, please order
What? Is this the damn rule
of Simpson family?
The what-so-called slave work
This is one of the rules
rule? And a man will put
so many servants around him
to enjoy the treatment of sex
Jimo, you think
I would like father's women
If you don't like
we'll arrange others
I think it's unnecessary
Get me Kimo
What are you doing? Come over
Yes
It's just as I expected!
In order to protect father
they'll have to kill me, right?
How audacious!
They are thinking of killing me
what offerings
And you all have been trained
by that man sexually
haven't you?
Then I'll se here
How much has Dad got out of you...
You are only sensitive when tied up
How lecherous... and this one
Oh, no...
What seems to be the trouble
Oh no...
Aren't you enjoying this yourself?
How's that
...I am coming... No, I am coming
Oh, it's here
Oh...
Informing me to visit...
What?
This painting is weird
It should be a painting
based on Virgin Marry
How come I got an ominous feeling
when seeing this?
Really? It has been here
since your childhood
But since it's that man's favorite
It can't be any better
Let's forget about the key
Let's deal with the heritage soon
Why do you specifically
ask for Susan tonight
It seems you have
some own thinkings, Jimo
I want to confirm if
that man ever touched his niece
If he did that to his own relatives
I'll do as what I said
I'll completely cut out
from Simpson Family
and leave this goddamn place
right away
I'll arrange Susan
to serve you tonight
What can I do?
The master didn't know that
Susan
This is your mission tonight
In order to protect the master
we are to check your body
...yes
Susan, tell me honestly
did my father...
Did that man treat you like
he treated Kimo
Master, please believe me
uncle he...
Yeah?
Forget this, master, I am...
Master, I am Jimo
What the hell is going on, so noisy
I am sorry, some urgency came up...
What?
Please come with me to the main room
Kimo...
I found the light
when searching the windows
Are these stakes against me?
I think it's a warning, Jimo
Preview of next chapter
Who did all this to Kimo...
The master started the investigation
and showed his valor
And the red petals will fall on
the white snow tonight
Castle of Black Snow, Second Chapter
is soon coming