Encoded By www.hentaiparadize.net
Don't you feel this strange?
I spread the rumor of inheriting
this farm
It's now going everywhere
So the one who wants it
will come to kill me
Nothing surprising
But actually...
Instead, the girls got killed
Master, are you taking sympathy
with them
How can it... I am not
If it's Susan who has been with me
Then I would not be surprised
It's not as intense as before
Master, you must want
this farm and castle, right
It's Zunlio who did all this...
Really...
But I think Kimo's death is related
to Zunlio, he killed her
because she's standing in the way
She must have known something
that she shouldn't have known
Killed by other guy
instead of Zunlio
Stop it, Master
it's too violent... oh
Really, but it doesn't tell me there
Oh Oh...
Before Kimo died
There's also the flower
It's you, Jimo
I finally got you here...
According to your instruction
the bodies of Judy and Zunlio
Have been placed in the freezer
This...
Before the death of servants
is investigated
You are also in danger...
Is it better to leave castle
for a while...
Oh... I told you it's unnecessary
If these people's target is me
Then I shouldn't leave at all!
They won't let us go easily
If someone wants to attack me
They should be planning something
By that time
everything will be clear
Virgin Marry
I don't know what to do
My secret with uncle
My secret with master...
We are actually brother and sister...
(Sobbing)...
Sorry to have messed up the place...
Clean it at one...
No, it doesn't matter
You can retire, Susan
But... I...
That's enough... thanks
You should sleep well tonight
Please, Mr. Konsan
What's the matter?
Why are you only calling
Kimo and Zunlio to serve you
instead of me...
You want me to
change you into a woman
No... no... but... but...
Mr. Jimo said to serve man
is woman's duty
ha...
I can't require you to do this
Besides, you are waiting for him
right?
A guy who won't return, probably
If someday, anything bad happens to me
And you become alone
You can find something under
the podium of Virgin Marry
Then you understand everything
I saw that before uncle died
And I was not sure what it's about
Now I know I am the child of
mother and uncle
I don't want to know this secret
Master is my close brother...
Susan, can you trust me
with this envelope?
And is this the key master is after?
The photos are interesting
what are they
This... Not this one
Don't run away!
Why do you know about the key!
No... please let me go
I won't forgive you for this
What the hell! So noisy
Master...
What's up... you two
The old photos and
the key to the safe
What's inside there, Susan
Yes...
Mm
Ok, take this key
And do away with everything
in that safe
I understand
Just as if nothing happened
Sister Lily, why are you keeping
this secret for me
The things in the safe
is troublesome
It'll not be good
if it's known by others
Take this
Why don't you say this to master?
The secret about this photo
This is the daughter of Mr. Konsan
Oh, really... let's carry on
with the investigation
it's really here
Oh...
I thought you would be here
That photo just now...
I seem to have seen it
when I was a child
have you...
Mother showed it to me
and said to me
Susan is my sister
Oh, I see
So you are related in blood
He seems to want to conceal this
So when mother passed away
I used to tell him
he's a bastard
I am fed up with his way of
treating Susan
I want to take Susan out of
this house
Really... maybe that's better for me
Never presume
I have given up this idea
That day, you were out
with aunt by chances
You were out...
Stay with me if you can't go home
and fell to sleep unconsciously
When waking up next day
It's already on the own bed
If only I had been at home
that time...
Then we could have been together
And wandering out life out
Sleeping in some deserted houses
and sneak into the supermarket
at night
Susan...
We can't have that kind of life
Master and I are brother and sister...
If one day master finds out
I have a boyfriend... I
Master...
What the hell is
so great about a brother
I want to say this all the time...
Come with me
let's go to US together, Susan
Dear...
How about this...
I only heard of that picture
for the first time
Try not to fool me!
Then Susan is really
the daughter of Mr. Konsan
Yes, it's true
Although unrecognized
Susan's affairs
including her education
was all done by me...
Who knows about this too?
No one...
Mr. Jimo
I am sure you are aware
that if Master gives up
Then the eldest daughter Susan is
to inherit everything
She'll be the one in charge
You mean accordingly
we should get rid of
everything clearly, right
Now I am telling the purpose is to...
If my intuition is right
Then the one who can save
the Simpson family
is you besides master...
Me...?!
Let's not pretend
I am in need of your help
Ms. Sankonlee
...
Lee, I am coming in
I have left a note knowing
that you'll come
The thing of the safe that you need
I'll go get them
stay and wait for me
Susan, come with me to the America
I can't... I can't... Dear
We are brother and sister...
That's really unacceptable...
that's too painful...
Oh... I never thought of
being turned down
Oh!? Right...
The picture here is a bit strange
It should be a picture of
Virgin Marry
How come I got an ominous feeling
Really? Has been here
since childhood
But since it belongs to the old man
can't be any good of it
Jimo?
Do you need something, master
No, thank you
Do you know why I want you here
Why... why do you have to kill Kimo?
Jimo!
Because... she threatened your life
I want a better excuse
Why it's me... really?
You knew this before, right
I used to confront with Kimo
Nonsense! Who else, besides you
Got to keys to this house
and move freely
Let's go from the beginning then
Before the old man died
And you were still not back yet
Zunlio wanted to kill all of us
Because he wanted
everything of the house
Kimo had been worried all day
of being kicked out
and gradually lost her mentality
So she had been thinking of killing
you when serving you
I found her having a knife
in the corridor that night
We had a fight...
Then the flower was left by you
She lost her dignity
when she made
the decision of killing you
About Zunlio and Judy
were also done by you
Yes
The daughter of boss Judy
She knew about
the cruelty of Zunlio's plan
She wanted to win over your love
And she tried to utilize Zunlio
to get her own way
Zunlio's behavior became more crazy
That's why Judy got killed
But I can't help all this
You were so cruel being an onlooker
I am not gonna argue for myself
You did this all to protect me...
That's for sure!
And about the picture of Susan
I almost have to
deal with another body
In order to divide the properties
the one who carries
the blood of Simpson family
I, should avoid all these
from happening
It's more important than
anything else
I see! Jimo
You were saying something
about blood
I have to confirm with you one thing
This is what Lee got from the safe
It's left by father
The second picture
that was given to Susan
And together with the one Susan has
Compared them together
We found some clues
Susan's real father... there is
You such a hypocritical and
abject bastard
The real reasons of protecting me
are all in these pictures
Jimo! You are... my real...
No! ...Master, you are
the oldest son of Simpson family
Time is running short, we got to go
Call the policy?
It's to give Kimo
and others justice...
Jimo! Leave the house alone
We are not going to
hire a new butler...
No need
I have spent all my life here
I don't regret
since I chose all this
A man can't carry many secrets
Or he can't know about himself
I think my case best explains this
Jimo...
Master... The time to depart
Wish you happiness forever
Susan!?
I am here to serve you... master
What's up...
Why are you dressing up
like a servant
I am at your disposal tonight
Susan...
Comfy
Oh, yes... very... comfy
Then... What wouold be of Susan
Master... master... I'll have orgasm...
You are too much
You are making me enjoy all this
It's me who should serve you
I didn't ask for that
Susan
I want you to enjoy this with me
Brother...
I am thinking the same thing...
Being with brother...
Susan
All right
It's inside me...
Keep moving
Brother... I... I...
Are you enjoying
Mm... Like this...
No need to be shy
let's enjoy together
brother, I love this
Oh, me too
Brother... brother...
Are you coming?
Almost...
Susan...
Susan! Where are you!? Susan!
Where has she gone...
You should know this, master
What's going on
Susan appears as an inheritor
She became one member of
the Simpson family
In order to avoid
the suspicion of the Duke
We got to hide Susan somewhere
What!?
All things that happened here
days ago
have been known by the duke
It's a game between money mongers
If the government is involved
Then the secrets safeguarded
by Mr. Jimo
for so long would be exposed
Right
I don't want to get involved
with the Duke
You think you are doing
the right thing
By giving up the right to inherit
You and Susan
Won't be threatening the Duke
anymore
No matter how much you know
The minute you were born into
this house
You can't escape
the monitoring of us
Like the conflicts we have about
the inheritance
In order to avoid further trouble
I was picked to be the one
I understand! You bitch
Yes... I was the one appointed
by Duke Bulafla
That's my real identity
I can't conceal myself
at this moment
I am really sorry
How's Susan now
Can't help you with that
Say it!
She is in a safe place now
Now Susan's real identity is known
You can't
continue living like before
Please give me some more time
Are you kidding me
Please trust me... master
This is what you wanna say?
I think Susan should contact you
by then
Probably you won't keep me here now
right
Nonsense!
Then... Here I am off
Master...
You can't escape life
The only way is to confront it
One year later, LA
Boss, air mail from Japan
Merry X'mas, have a good weekend
Ah ha
Oh oh
Mr Jimo and I
have reached an agreement
Merry X'mas, master
The next mission for Miss
Can't possibly meet again
Master... wish you happiness
The assessment of the land.
It couldn't be.
There's only one choice.
No, it's still in Japan.
The off-coast island called Stone-Huan
That looks pretty.
The lad lives a wonderful life.
Now, the instructions are
all done by the fingers.
What we gonna do?
I can't make it there.
Anyway, it will be solved though.
As time like this, we still
have to waste our energy into this?
Forget it, we want to go home now.