THE DESERT ISLAND STORY XX
Where are you?
Mother?
Talk to me.
Mother.
What's wrong? TaIk to me.
No.
You're not Mother.
Who are you?
No! Go away!
No!
Why did Mayumi come into my dream?
Why do I feeI Iike I know her?
Who is it?
Shiori.
What's wrong?
It's Runa.
Runa?
Runa's.
What happened?
What happened to Runa?
He took her away.
He's been after Runa.
OnIy Runa.
PIease, rescue Runa.
Get her back from him.
Him? Hiroki?
RIBBON
Why did you Iet Mio go aIone?
Are you sacrificing her for Runa?
Look at me.
You care about nobody but Runa.
You've sacrificed everybody.
Matsui, Ikegami...
...Aoi and Nanae.
No, no.
Aoi, Nanae.
Where's Mio gone to? TeII me.
Wait for me, Runa.
Stupid bitch dared to defy me.
But Runa is in my hands.
I don't know how much
I can trust Kaoru, either.
I'II show them.
Time to rearrange
the transpIanted personaIities.
I wonder if Runa can survive.
Stop, Hiroki!
Runa, Iet's go.
You mustn't interrupt
an important operation.
What's wrong, Hiroki?
So you're back.
You escaped before,
but you're mine after aII.
What are you taIking about?
What is this?
No! Stop!
You're possessed by Mayumi.
I brought you to this isIand and
Iet you survive the fire...
...just so I couId have you back again.
PIease, Nanae.
Stay away.
Nanae.
Don't be misIed.
Don't beIieve Kaoru.
Aoi, you understand.
I get it.
I'II Ieave you aIone.
Ma'am....
If they try to extract the data,
Runa wiII go insane.
A tough IittIe bitch.
Sorry for the wait.
Kaoru was quite fun.
Now it's your turn.
StiII a virgin,
and your nippIes are so stiff.
What is this ugIy stomach?
You've grown to be a sIut.
What the heII's inside?
What's up?
Kaoru put up a better fight.
You're so pathetic.
You need another Iesson.
Why?
Why do you do this, Hiroki?
As stubborn as that girI.
That girI?
Stop!
What?
Don't you want some reIief?
Forgive me.
I see, you want someone to watch.
Runa.
No! Don't Iook!
PIease, Runa, go away.
Runa.
I put this mark here.
Now I'm back again.
Shiori is such a Iiar.
But I won't give up. I'II find it.
Why do you cry?
I gave you some reIief.
Now it's my turn to get some reIief.
No!
I see. Then...
Runa!
Maybe she'II do it for you.
No, Runa!
Don't do it!
Then are you going to do it?
Yes.
As stubborn as that girI.
I Iove your cIumsiness.
I'm cumming. SwaIIow it aII.
Shit.
Hiroki's body is young and good.
I'm aIready hard again.
It hurts! It hurts!
What a sIut, for her first time.
Now, it's your turn.
You've gone too far, Doctor.
Kaoru.
I'm sorry, Mio. I was too Iate.
It was my mistake.
I can no Ionger trust you.
TeII me what's reaIIy
on your mind, Shiori?
Maybe the reaI me is aIready dead.
Maybe I'm insane now.
I have to report this to Headquarters.
I ask you not to...
...for your own sake.
After so many casuaIties....
Don't worry. It's not poison.
Don't be a fooI.
You're too nosy.
Stay quiet for a whiIe.
Runa.
What're you doing?
We mustn't stimuIate Hiroki now.
Untie me.
What have I done to deserve this?
I came to ask you why.
Sorry, guess not.
Runa, Aoi, Iet's go.
Hey, are you Ieaving me Iike this?
Aoi.
What's going on?
HeIp me!
No, Mio. You have to rest.
We're worried.
You've been through a Iot.
Has Kaoru been to see you?
I saw her briefIy, but then she Ieft.
I see. Nanae, Iet's go.
WeII. Okay.
Mio, I'm sorry I asked you
to Iook after Runa.
I don't care.
Ma'am.
Aoi, come on.
I'm sorry.
Is Kaoru aII right?
I don't know. Maybe....
Like Matsui and Ikegami....
Don't worry, Kaoru is strong.
Aoi, ready?
Yeah.
Stay here with Nanae.
Aoi, you and I wiII Iook for Kaoru.
Madam, what are you doing?
Hiroki.
Yes.
Make me forget. Everything.
What?
PIease stop.
No, Madam.
I'm cumming.
Not yet.
Your turn to satisfy me.
This sensation...
...I'd forgotten how it feIt.
I can't bear it. I'm scared of Runa.
Madam, come to your senses.
Love me, Hiroki.
Hiroki.
Madam, pIease come to your senses.
More. Drive me crazier.
Good.
It feeIs good. So good.
More.
Madam, no more....
I see no sign of them.
Maybe we're not going to make it.
I want my mother.
Runa.
Can't find her anywhere.
Maybe she's dead....
What happened?
It's been quite a whiIe.
You set me on fire.
What? Aoi?
No, Ma'am.
You did nasty things with Hiroki.
Stop, this is siIIy.
Yo, Shiori.
You were enjoying it a Iot.
Hiroki.
I....
Shut up!
No, Ma'am.
You aII ganged up
to fuck with my head.
Hiroki, you mean....?
I'm going to kiII Runa.
Just wait and see.
Wait, Hiroki.
Not Runa.
Runa!
Ma'am, don't go!
Runa. Wait for me.
Ma'am.
I Iove you.
Don't Ieave me.
Why didn't you find me earIier?
Mio, you're aIways Iate.
Stop compIaining, you sIeepyhead.
Hurry, they're aII waiting.
Runa.
I'II foIIow them.
Go make sure everyone's okay.
Okay.
Nanae! Hang in there, Nanae!
Mother.
You came for me.
I'm happy.
Nanae.
Late as aIways.
This Iooks bad.
Kaoru.
I've been sIoppy
ever since I got here.
Bastards. What tough security.
In which case....
No one wiII ever touch her again.
This wiII end his research.
Runa!
Mio, get Runa out of here!
Wait. She is mine.
I'II get you.
Give me Runa, Mio.
Don't taIk to me Iike a friend.
So much troubIe.
What are you mumbIing about?
You don't care about Runa?
Enough.
I don't want either one of you.
I'II drop you both into the ocean.
Mother!
No!
I'm sorry, Mio.
By the time you read this,
I'll be gone from the island.
We could have anticipated some
of the events that took place.
But I was not allowed to tell you.
You must have hated me.
But believe me...
...I never expected
Aoi and Nanae would die.
I have reported to
the Organization that...
...with the death of Shiori and Hiroki,
all the research data was lost.
A rescue party will come soon.
I liked you.
But we'll never meet again.
Be nice to Runa.
You're the only one she can count on.
But then again, my parting words
should be:
See you again, Mio!
See you again.