THE DESERT ISLAND STORY XX
Hurry, Nanae.
The way Aoi is feeIing,
we have to make our own breakfast.
Kaoru!
What happened?
I was sIoppy.
This is horribIe.
Who did this?
It's nothing.
Nothing, reaIIy.
What're you saying?
Look at yourseIf.
I'm fine.
-Bastard.
-Kaoru?
That bastard!
Bastard, bastard, bastard!
Who's this bastard? Kaoru?
No!
I can't take it.
I want to go home. Mommy!
NECKLACE
Where's Mio?
She said she wanted
to check on something. She Ieft.
That's just Iike her.
Ouch.
Don't push yourseIf.
You're kind, Nanae.
But I've got things to do, too.
Wait, Kaoru.
Kaoru, you, too?
Thanks for worrying about me.
But I'm fine now.
Hey.
I need proof.
Something's going on on this isIand.
Hey, you.
What are you doing, Mio?
WeII, Shiori asked me
to do a IittIe research....
I see. Madam asked you?
Liar.
She never toId me.
Let me go, Mr. Matsui.
Won't you teII us about it?
Runa.
What's the commotion?
WeII, Madam, she was snooping
around the room, so....
Runa, go outside with Mio.
Mr. Ikegami, Mr. Matsui,
I have something to discuss with you.
Stay with me, wiII you?
What's going on? TeII me.
It's not your fauIt, Hiroki.
Nanae.
PIease. I don't know.
What's going on?
You're both so tense.
Aoi, you're not afraid of me?
Aoi?
Yo, Ikegami.
About what Madam said.
What do you think?
There won't be any rescue.
They're going to Ieave us on this isIand.
I was hoping not.
You know the research
they were doing here.
We couId very weII get kiIIed.
No, no.
So, we shouId do as we pIease.
I can't Iive with this.
Another faIse Iead.
Another dead end.
There must be some vaIid data.
I got it.
So, Hiroki was a subject.
This personaIity attacked me.
Where is the password for
switching his personaIity?
Mayumi?
I don't think there was
a Mayumi in the Iab.
You made that seasheII neckIace, Runa?
Yeah.
You're reaIIy cIose to Shiori.
I'm envious.
How beautifuI.
Yeah.
I'm tired. Things have been crazy.
I hope nothing eIse happens.
What's wrong, Runa?
Runa!
You're Iucky, Runa,
your mother's very nice.
I've been aIone aII my Iife.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm taking off.
Aoi, wait....
I'm sorry, it was just me.
So don't be afraid of Hiroki.
What?
I have to go.
See you tomorrow.
Yes, Mayumi.
I need information on her. Over.
Let me know as soon as you can.
Over and out.
My point of attack shouId be...
...Tricky, but Hiroki, I guess.
Hiroki!
Sorry. I saw you going into
the jungIe, and I was worried.
Thank you.
WouId you waIk me to the Iodge?
WeII, sure.
PIease stop, Mr. Matsui.
I'II report to Shiori.
Shut up, she's nothing.
No!
They have abandoned us.
We're trapped on this isIand.
No.
It seems Madam is responsibIe
for that fire.
Nobody orders us around.
If detaiIs of our experiment got out,
it wouId be a catastrophe.
The organization wants to bury
the whoIe thing.
We might get kiIIed, too.
So Iet's be friendIy now.
Nice body you got.
You can't teII when you're wearing cIothes.
Nice skin.
I need perks Iike this,
or I'd go crazy.
Not there. No!
Fight back. That's even better.
No!
You bitch!
No, Iet me go!
I hate women who fight.
I need to heIp you reIax.
No. Forgive me.
My mother died
when I was very IittIe.
I don't know anything
about my father.
I'm sorry.
You just Iost your father.
But at Ieast you've got a nice mother.
Yeah.
Mio.
Kaoru. Hiroki.
So it was you.
I toId you it was them.
You did?
You're so bad, I didn't know
you couId say such things.
Sorry, sorry.
We just run into each other,
right, Hiroki?
WeII, yeah.
We shouId aII go back.
It's getting coId.
Let's go back, Runa.
Yeah.
It feeIs Iike you're fIoating,
doesn't it?
Extreme bIood Ioss heightens
your physicaI sensitivity.
It's about time you removed the needIe.
Got it.
Is she aII right?
No need to worry.
She'II be fine tomorrow.
It feeIs Iike your whoIe body has
become an erogenous zone, doesn't it?
It sure Iooks that way.
I'm hot.
I'm hot aII over!
Crazy. I'm going crazy!
It's twice as good as usuaI, isn't it?
It's never been this good, has it?
You're home, Runa?
It's Iate.
I'm sorry.
I took her here and there.
Go to bed now.
I never guessed you were
such a sIut, Nanae.
We shouId have raped her sooner.
It's good. It's good.
I'm meIting away!
Runa Iooked sad.
You shouId have stayed with her, Mio.
I'm going upstairs.
I don't want to be a nuisance.
So nice of you.
I won't Iet you sIeep tonight.
What? Hey, Kaoru.
Good night.
Nanae!
It's horribIe.
What is this?
Things didn't work out the way
I expected today.
What?
Who do we do next?
No need to worry
even if they find out.
I can't wait.
This is the second time.
You're in charge now.
Don't get so excited.
Have some tea.
Kaoru, there are onIy three men
on this isIand.
I don't think it's a good idea
to antagonize Mr. Ikegami and Mr. Matsui.
By the way.
I understood there had been
three victims.
Ma-yu-mi.
Professor Tadokoro's daughter
by his first wife.
I don't know much about Mayumi.
She had died before
I married Tadokoro.
I see.
I'II see you Iater.
That seasheII neckIace....
BeautifuI.
Runa made it for me.
You're so cIose to her.
Kaoru.
Yes?
About this incident....
Let me handIe it.
Nanae.
Don't Iose heart!
I'm here for you.
Forget about the whoIe thing.
I'II punish the peopIe
who did mean things to you.
Aoi.
That hog.
She thinks I'm nothing.
I'II make her pay.
Mr. Matsui.
Why him?
He must have sIipped and drowned.
Too bad. He was a good man.
Runa, stay away from here!
Runa, Runa!
Get a hoId of yourseIf, Runa!
Don't go! Come back!
Runa!
How's Runa?
Nanae is taking care of her.
I'm impressed.
She's just gone through heII herseIf.
And Matsui?
Hiroki and Ikegami buried him
in the woods.
I pity even him.
You'd better teII me now, Kaoru.
Look.
Her!
You know her?
She's in a fiIe buried far inside
the system.
Her code name is Mayumi.
Mayumi.
How's Runa?
She's caImed down.
Shiori's gone home, too.
Thank you, Nanae.
Mio.
I'm here, Runa.
I....
Yes?
Matsui.
What the fuck!
It's my turn next.
Bastards.
I have to ask Shiori about
this Mayumi person.
What?
Ma'am...
...I did it weII.
Good girI.
But, I feeI sorry for Matsui.
He went too far.
But Ikegami is smart.
He'II be good for a whiIe.
What the heII?
It feeIs good.
As sensitive as aIways.
No!
Right there, Ma'am.
Forgive me.
Shiori had Matsui killed?
Before they catch me....
If you do it Iike that...
...I'II go crazy.
Liar. You Iike it.
AIways do as I teII you.
I wiII.
I'II do anything you say.
No more!
You can cum. Cum.
Cum for me!
I'm cumming! I'm cumming!
I didn't mean to spy.
Runa, don't get mad.
What, at this hour?
If you'd come a IittIe Iater
you'd have had quite a show.
Hey, hey.
You're hanging out with Runa
aII the time.
I'm getting jeaIous.
Kaoru, what're you saying?
Be carefuI around Runa.
UnIess you want to
end up Iike Matsui.
TO BE CONTINUED
Preview
Who's crying?
Is that you, Mom?
The sonata goes on
through the silence of the afternoon.
The lost memory that nobody knows.
Today, that person will be the victim.
The veiled mystery.
RUNA; Mayumi is the one who's crying.
The Desert IsIand Story XX - FiIe 3:
Piano.