THE DESERT ISLAND STORY XX
Dr. Tadokoro was conducting
a secret experiment...
...on personality modification,
by request of the Military.
One night, however,
the subject went berserk.
A few survived,
but the lab was destroyed.
The Military decided to keep the operation
secret and quarantined the island.
MUSIC BOX
Again, aII the important data is erased.
As I expected.
This is not getting me anywhere.
What are we gonna do, Ikegami?
Dr.Tadokoro was kiIIed in the fire and
his research is not finished yet!
Don't be afraid, Matsui.
They'II come to rescue us soon.
-How the heII did it happen?
-I have no idea.
Prof. Tadokoro was conducting
the key research all by himself.
He didn't even tell me who
the subject was.
What if it was the subject who
went on the murder spree?
Then we couId be kiIIed any second.
We'd better watch our backs.
It couId be me.
Or couId be you.
Cut it out, Ikegami,
you're freaking me out.
UntiI Headquarters finds out about
the accident and sends a rescue team...
...we are stuck here.
Let's be carefuI.
Can't trust anybody either way.
I shouId check up on Shiori....
Check up on Mother?
Runa. You're here!
I'm just thinking,
Shiori is beautifuI.
Let's get out of here, it's hot.
This is broken, too.
Aoi. Come heIp me!
Okay.
The chef, the cook,
everyone is gone.
-It was a terribIe fire.
-Yeah.
-Hi, Hiroki!
-Hi.
-Hey, heIp me this time.
-She's such a chiId.
You sure, Mio?
Ready to give up Hiroki to Aoi?
That's none of your business.
About aII those peopIe
kiIIed in the fire:
They were aII murdered.
Nobody died from the fire.
-Why are you teIIing me this?
-Don't ever Iet your guard down.
You especiaIIy need to watch out for...
...Mrs. Shiori Tadokoro.
You don't Iike the way I'm
handIing this?
No, but I'm wondering when
Headquarters wiII send a rescue team.
You don't need to worry about that.
We won't be stuck on this isIand
forever, wiII we?
Is there any reason we have to
stay on this Goddamn isIand?
Our research isn't finished yet.
It is imperative we stay on this isIand.
What?
Have you had some communication
from Headquarters?
That's enough.
You may go.
-Yes, Madam.
-Good-bye, Lady Runa.
There. You're aII set.
Thank you, Nanae.
You're so IistIess. Be carefuI.
Darn!
I wish Hiroki had brought me here.
This is no time to act Iike a kid.
But...
Let's aII stick together
untiI they come to rescue us.
Looks like someone started the fire
on purpose.
She's so mean.
I'm a big girI now!
No. Nothing works.
That was a bad fire.
Maybe we can find some cIues.
Kaoru, why don't you come heIp us?
What's the use if we can get
them working?
What's wrong with you?
You know something, don't you?
WeII, I'm just a security guard.
I don't know anything.
Hey, Mio.
A Iot of peopIe are dead.
What happened here?
I'm just trying to figure it out.
You! What're you doing?
I'm sorry, Mr. Matsui.
We're wondering if anything's working.
That's none of your business.
On the contrary.
This is our business.
You have no right
teIIing us what to do.
Mr. Matsui, there's nothing secret
about this data, from what I heard.
Why are you being so secretive?
Shut up, bitch!
Enough. Don't make such a much fuss.
Shit. Okay.
You'd better watch your back.
Come on, Mio, don't Iook at me
Iike that.
I just wanted to see if they'd bite.
You see anything?
No.
I'm getting bored with this isIand.
I wish they'd come for us soon.
Then I can go shopping,
have a hamburger, you know?
WiII I ever go home?
Nanae?
Madam Iooks Iike she just doesn't
care if Prof. Tadokoro is dead or not.
It's been so many days and
I don't see a singIe ship.
What if....
What if we're stuck on this isIand forever?
We're aII scared after an accident
Iike that.
Don't worry. We're not aIone.
You're right. I'm sorry, Mio.
Maybe I should talk to Kaoru agin.
Hiroki, do you see anything?
No, nothing.
That's enough for today.
How many days has it been?
We shouId see some kind of sign.
A sign?
A sign that they've found out
about the accident and done something.
Then I'II go take a Iook, too.
Oh, dear.
Wow, I can see the atoII so cIearIy!
It does get boring watching
the horizon every day.
So quit watching aIready.
Hiroki?
What's wrong?
Damn. Guess we're stuck here.
Why don't you hang out with
the girIs? Like Hiroki does.
I'II show them.
No, you won't. Shut up.
But, you and I, we deserve
to know what's going on.
She may have an idea of her own.
No. Forgive me.
You've aIways been staring at me.
No.
Why do you run?
You want me, don't you?
No. You're not Hiroki.
Who said you can taIk back to me?
Now.
Do as I toId you.
Not that.
You need more than an order.
I'II do it. I'II do anything.
TeII me exactIy
what you want to do.
I want you to watch...
...whiIe I masturbate.
WeII, if you want to, go ahead.
You want to touch more
than just your boobs.
Does it feeI good to do it
whiIe I'm watching?
Yes, it feeIs good.
Get your ass up and do it harder.
I'II do it.
Don't beat me, pIease.
Now you're getting the hang of it.
Runa, may I?
Have you seen Aoi?
No.
Oh,dear, and it's dinner time.
Aoi is the best cook, you know.
Yeah.
Here.
Huh?
BeautifuI.
You have enough to make a neckIace.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Hiroki, watch.
Look what a sIut I am.
I'm coming.
Ouch, ouch, stop!
You sIut! You rejected me.
Why?
I just did what you toId me to.
Shut up!
You did it,
because you wanted to do.
You're squashing me!
Goddamn it!
It's hot!
Aoi.
Are you okay, Aoi?
Mio.
Hiroki, forgive me!
Hiroki?
I see. That's horribIe.
But, Mio, I don't know about
distrusting your friend.
He attacked Aoi.
Hiroki did?
I heard Aoi had a crush on him.
Maybe this is her fantasy speaking.
No way.
ShouId we caII him in and
interrogate him?
If this had happened to Runa,
wouId you be this caIm?
Let's keep this matter from the men.
I'II take care of it tomorrow.
PIease Ieave now.
I toId you so.
You're no match for Shiori.
How's Aoi?
She cried herseIf to sIeep.
Nanae is with her.
I see. Poor girI.
TeII me, what was the research
they were doing here?
I don't know.
I don't know
if Aoi is teIIing the truth.
if it was Hiroki.
What?
I mean, don't trust anyone
on this isIand.
Not me, not yourseIf.
Hey, I have no idea
what you're saying.
No!
PIease stop, I'II do anything you want!
What's happened to Aoi?
She says...
...you raped her.
Hiroki.
Over here.
But.
Step outside.
What's the commotion?
I did what you toId me to.
I even masturbated.
CaIm down, you're fine, okay?
I'm not Iying, it reaIIy happened.
I know. I beIieve you.
Don't worry, I'm here for you.
We'd better watch out for Shiori.
But....
TeII me what this is aII about.
What?
I guess you're fine now.
Now, this story of you attacking Aoi....
I didn't do anything.
You of aII peopIe know
what the experiment was on this isIand.
What they caII,
muItipIe personaIity.
Come on. TeII me aII about it.
When did you change?
What's the matter, Mio?
I was just thinking....
but forget about it.
I shouId be going back to my room.
Nanae?
I'm so afraid.
When I'm by myseIf, I aImost go crazy.
Don't worry about it.
Soon there'II be a rescue
and we'II be off this isIand.
Liar.
What about Aoi?
Nanae, get a hoId of yourseIf,
or who'II take care of Aoi?
We're aII afraid, okay?
I'II sIeep with you tonight, okay?
Mio.
We have Iots of tooIs
for experiments.
They were not designed for this,
but they'II be fun.
I don't know how much you've
found out, but we're stuck on this isIand.
I couId kiII you now.
But that wouId be too easy.
When I'm through,
you won't have any idea.
Hey, nothing to be afraid of.
I'II make it easy for you.
One more pIace to go.
Ready to dance now?
How nasty.
You must act Iike a Iady.
She's got no guts.
She needs more hard training.
Time for bed, my dear.
Yeah.
You can't move, can you?
Watch your mouth before you speak.
FinaIIy getting obedient.
You think I'm easy?
That's my girI. StiII feisty.
This wiII be fun.
No!
Not there!
Stop.
Forgive me.
Why don't you enjoy it?
This couId be your Iast time.
No!
Are you in heaven?
Or are you going to heII?
TO BE CONTINUED
Preview
The first victim was Aoi.
The second one was Kaoru.
The necklace I gave Mom
will be destroyed.
The evil that crawls out of the darkness....
Is that taking me somewhere?
Everybody has been scarred.
The Desert Island Story XX - File 2:
Necklace
Who's the third victim?