THE DESERT ISLAND STORY XX
How is it, Nanae?
FeeIs good, doesn't it?
I know.
Now you're just Iike me, Nanae.
Madam wiII be happy for you. I bet.
You're so cute, Nanae.
We'II aII have fun together.
PIANO
Runa!
What are you doing, Mr. Ikegami?
I won't take orders from you.
I'm not going to end up Iike Matsui.
You're not Iike Mr. Matsui.
The Organization appreciates you.
Runa.
I knew it.
I just couIdn't beIieve it.
That fiIe was accurate, after aII.
Stop!
Runa is--
Runa is an exception.
PIease, Mr. Ikegami.
Madam, you know how I feeI.
Okay. If that's what you want....
ReaIIy?
WiII you trust me?
Of course.
Runa, go outside for a whiIe.
Mother.
I see.
It was no coincidence
Hiroki survived the fire. Over.
I got it. I'II check up on that.
Over and out.
It's a IittIe risky,
but I need Hiroki again.
This body for the oId professor....
What a waste!
Not yet, keep it on.
Just Iike I imagined,
soft and nice.
That won't do, Madam.
Raise your arms.
WonderfuI,
just Iike my mom's boobs.
Time to take a Iook down beIow.
Runa.
Mio.
What happened to your ribbon?
PIease.
Huh? Oh, you undid it.
Doesn't Shiori do this for you?
Be careful around Runa.
No, Nanae, no!
Madam's doing this for me.
It's a dream come true.
Mr. Ikegami. About Runa....
I know.
Satisfy me first,
to prove our friendship.
Okay.
If that's what you want.
You're good, Madam.
This won't do, Madam.
You have to swaIIow it aII.
You made a mistake,
I have to punish you.
Hey, Mio, come in and join us!
We'II aII swim together.
It feeIs good.
Mio, come join us.
Why not, Mio?
Nothing ever happens on this isIand.
Let's have fun.
Kaoru.
You're so bad, Kaoru!
It feeIs good.
Are you suffering?
Matsui suffered a Iot more.
Your beauty is an advantage.
You Iook beautifuI no matter what.
What's wrong?
ScoId me Iike you aIways do.
IncredibIe.
You're Iike a fIood.
Now.
This is too gentIe and
unsatisfying for a frustrated Madam.
Here you go.
Moaning gets boring.
You're drenched.
I see you can't wait anymore.
No!
Ikegami.
No, not that.
What's wrong?
Don't you want me to stop?
I'II make it good for you.
Not there!
PIease. PuII your finger out.
Don't be shy. PIease enjoy it.
What is this?
It's strange.
I'm hot.
You've been hoIding back too much.
I wiII satisfy you.
You're so tight.
It hurts. It hurts!
Madam.
You're squeezing me too hard.
It's good.
More. More. More.
I can't.
I can't--
Cum inside me. Cum!
It was wonderfuI, Madam.
One more time?
What's wrong with everybody?
Aoi and Nanae are happy,
as if nothing had happened.
I'm scared.
I'm out of the Ioop.
HeIp.
Someone heIp me.
PIease. What about Runa?
We've had enough sex and I'm bored.
But your promises...
...tend to get broken.
I don't want to end up Iike
Matsui. Sorry about this.
Don't hate me.
The fun is over.
You two....
Madam.
Hiroki.
I'm so embarrassed.
Why did you stop me?
She's got it in for you, too.
What do you mean?
I don't want to die! HeIp!
Runa, you're home.
Good. You're aII right.
Your ribbon is not right.
Let me fix it.
Don't touch me.
You used to be nice
onIy when other peopIe were around.
I'm not aIone. Not aIone.
They're aII going to die.
Sorry.
I knew you'd come right away
if I said it was Mio.
I have a favor to ask of you.
I want...
...your pendant!
What're you doing?
Too Iate. I'm done here.
See?
That's Runa's.
Don't be siIIy, give it back to her!
Is this siIIy?
We're aII suffering because of this.
What? How?
Now you know. Let me go.
Give it back to Runa.
WeII, weII.
I didn't expect you to be
a good girI.
Do I have to muscIe my way past?
Give me a proper expIanation.
It's okay.
Why, Runa?
Now that she says it's okay....
Why?
Shiori, it feeIs good.
This is your weak spot, Nanae.
Ma'am.
What a needy kid you are.
You're cute, Aoi. You're jeaIous.
Nanae.
Ikegami soiIed you here.
I'II cIean it for you.
No.
Madam has to enjoy it, too.
It's you again.
I warned you.
I'II kiII you if you interfere.
I was sIoppy back then.
Happy to taIk to you again.
Care for a trade, Dr. Tadokoro?
How did you find out?
Impressive. You transpIanted your
personaIity in Hiroki.
If you come up with
the data for the personaIity transpIant...
...a prestigious position is
waiting for you.
I think I underestimated you.
Thank you.
What do you want?
I toId you not to foIIow me.
Enough.
Say something interesting for once.
Out of my way.
Don't be so mean.
What? I don't want to see you.
I don't want to see you, either.
I want Runa.
This is for her.
Kaoru.
You don't Iook pretty
when you're angry.
Is that it?
Don't you owe me an expIanation?
Take care of Runa.
Runa.
Mio.
Look, Runa.
No!
It was wonderfuI, Ma'am.
When you cum,
Shiori, you Iook so beautifuI.
Thank you.
Ma'am, what happened to that
beautifuI seasheII neckIace?
It's broken.
I kind of Iiked it.
I'm sorry. I threw it out.
Don't throw me out.
Don't be coy, Aoi.
I know you want to go home.
I'II get you home.
When I'm done with this isIand.
Yes. When it's aII over.
She's here.
Mr. Ikegami.
Dead men teII no taIes.
Who's doing these terribIe things?
We'd better bury him.
Kaoru, wouId you and Hiroki
take care of it?
Where's Hiroki?
Hiroki?
TO BE CONTINUED
Preview
Quietly and sadly...
...Mayumi is calling
from the darkness of the night.
Aoi is gone, too.
So is Nanae.
My soiled half is falling down...
...in the dim light.
Quietly and sadly...
...Mother is being covered with blood.
The Desert IsIand Story XX - FiIe 4:
Ribbon