There was few recollection for youth age
In the three years
This was complaint told by the
senpai on commencement day
The few recollection included
The girl admired got in lower class
my heart palpitate once
I met her in the campus
sometimes I saw what I shouldn ' t see
It couldn ' t go away,
so I forget preparation
All the recollection was about girls
I thought senpai was
concentrated on studying
so I am surprised
Do all the man like this?
Put the question aside
If you ask me why I become like this
There was hard talking reason
In the final analysis
All begin from that day on winter vacation
I met the senpai
after the christmas day
The first chapter
Miyuki, Karen and the courage of a man
Senpai, Sanshiro senpai
Are you fine? Sanshiro senpai
I am fine··· I just recall one thing
senpai, do
you have any trouble too?
Tomomi, do you have any trouble too?
Isn ' t it about the entrance
exam of university?
No··· no, but···what can I say···
The girl at our age often like this
Always talking about
shaping or favorite boy
compare each one ' s worry
at each meeting
Oh··· that it is
I am not worried about the entrance exam
You are cheating us if
you said you were not upset
But I can enter Teidai
university without interview
senpai,
you assist me to remedial
I trust you
Whatever I do, you will pass the exam
It ' s better to open the window
and have some fresh air
Ryunosuke is not home today too
Oh··· although I have been here
As a teacher for long time
I never saw him
We often chatted like this before
But···
The day we chatted last time
was nineteen september
That was one week ago
she remember clearly
Because he always seemed busy
Yes
Youko
I know you will call me
I saw the notice for depreciation
Tomomi asked me to go with her
Anyway Tomomi is a
lady from noble family
It ' s amazing that she buys
depreciation goods too
It seems what she dressed is big name
Never mind, might buy the same
No way, I like that too
What do you mean
To avoid catching cold,
I will call you later
I see, bye-bye
Wait, mother, I take a shower ahead
What did you said, it ' s fine
that we take shower together
Oh, Yui
Had Ryunosuke gone?
Brother always sleep late
before the winter vacation
Need me to wake him up at last
It seemed he was busy at vacation
Yes, mother
Remember to tell brother
his coat was ironed···
No, you needn ' t, I tell him by myself
It will be more lovely
if there was a miracle mirror
At that time, brother···
It ' s right to me
to dress narrow dress
Are you fine?
Oh? Is that Karen?
Yes, that is Maijima Karen
sorry··· sorry! I am hurry
Are you fine?
Watch yourself
I got it
Yui, you are good at playing machine
Anyway, I am expert of playing machine
Who are you?
Karen?
shit
she is distaste
Can you lend me a hand?
It ' s headache trouble that be
alone without competitor
Do you often come here
You should keep the secret
For the noble man in future
I want to be more beautiful than anyone
Azumi, you are already very beautiful
Junko, you have sweet mouth
You won ' t benefit for flattering me
Fight against?!
I will begin before long
such as hide at somewhere
But···
Because I must work continually recently
I am not allowed to go to school
Even have vacation
Oh, it is, it ' s hard
to be an idol
I don ' t want to be a person
admired by everyone
But one person
This is my first time to
come into such restaurant
Now
Am I an ordinary girl?
It was wrong that you did like that
Used by you like that,
the camera will be poor thing
Is Ryunosuke fine?
He is fine, he went out this early morning
He was dating with a girl
It must be···
Date with
The girl from Yasuhachi school?
I don ' t know, why did you ask like this?
There is no special reason
He is welcome, charming
my photo is art
I don ' t allow you disapprove it
You will understand if you take picture
Got it
Please stop!
my···my camera
sorry···
You···wait and see
Mother···
Oh?
Do you remember to clean
the swim pool?
clean the swim pool?
The boys and girls clean the
swim pool every year by turn
The first time I met you
I remember
It was taken place before long
I got here by changing school
As we mentioned,
I hadn ' t made uniform at that time
Everyone said shouldn ' t let
the idol clean
so they didn ' t willing me to assist
But, only you came forth
And asked me to clean together
I was delighted at that time
I paid attention on you from that time
so, I feel a little tense
chatting with you like this
I··· I see nothing
No··· I just see a little
But I will forget
Are you Sanshiro-san
Mi···Misako-san!
I··· really see nothing
see··· see you
Don ' t turn around
Oh, Tomomi
From my point, you should
beware the day like today
Nobody will watch old woman ' s underwear
But
A lot of different persons live in this town
Get out here
I won ' t···
All is due to the
uniform skirt is too short
Excuse me···
Sa··· Sanshiro senpai
Do you know me?
No···, do you have
anything to ask me?
I am looking for a person
I want to ask you whether
she had pass away
Are you looking for a girl?
Yes, she is short, big eye
cure hair, lovely···
she is a girl
I thought only you were different
But men are the same
Excuse me
Karen, your house is large
That ' s the reason be called
as Karen Basilica
Only my family, here is too large
I think so
It's quite scary
Scary?
Because it ' s too large
I feel your tongue is lovely
come to sit down
I want to chat with you
It ' s no problem, I am free, but···
Hikari-san
This is the most important time for you
If this was known by the office
Which don ' t want you be
popular any more···
To be anywhere and do
what I want at freed time
It ' s my freedom
Anyway, you can ' t go alone from now on
Oh? Sanshiro Senpai!
Ah Yui? Are you Narusawa Yui?
Haven ' t seen you for a long time
who is he?
He is our upper classman Sanshiro senpai
graduated last year
He was enrolled by Imperial University with
exemption of exam
He has been honored to be the best since the
school establishment
And to be known by everybody
You are really wonderful
You are too exaggerating
better meet you by chance than invite you
Brother, come to have a cup of tea
Thanks··· for you good will,
but I am looking for someone
sorry for the disturbing you
Ok, now I am going to have piano lesson
You have trouble?
You are right. You have trouble
with love
Let me tell you
The trouble of meeting with girl friend
I··· I have not···
Wait···wait
Yes, there is result
she has no interest towards you
But she seems liking you
The proof is···
Listen, she is calling you
I heard this is your work, teacher
I also hope myself
To compose not long after
But you seem forgot all of it
sorry
That school uniform really reminding
Right, I hear teacher was also
The graduate of Yasohachi school
But
Nobody around me to ware
that short skirt
should I try it? Teacher
May be I also want to have a look
Right here
sorry, excuse me
I have something to ask···
How could you···? No way! stop
Miyuki-san
What is the relation between you and
Sanshiro senpai
When I was being disturbed
by a weird man
This noon he saved me
You seem don ' t believe it
I might think about it
If the lover is our senpai
I absolutely support
so, I too, support this
What are you two talking about?
But I am happy today
I have not had such free live for
a long time
You will start hard work tomorrow
Karen, don ' t you have work today?
Yes···
so···
so she is Miyuki-san
could I see her tomorrow
That depend on you
If you wish to be the main role in others life
You need courage and activity
What an unexpected harvest
Use these photos, she would···
You need to be active to take good pictures
I am mostly disgusting the guys to chase
Girls around with nothing to attend
But you have terrified me
What I have suddenly said to
be against the manager
Has been the trouble to you
I will only act in the film tomorrow
I will enjoy slowly tomorrow morning
Hikari-san will look for me everywhere
tomorrow morning
Will the resistance be successful?
We are asking for the free time, right?
Brother··· no
Mother, never tell this to Ryunosuke
He called just now
He said to spend night in Akira ' s home
Do you allow him to stay out for night, Mom?
Karen-san
Don ' t be too familiar with Ryunosuke
You have seen all of it. This boy is jealous
Are you, so Ryunosuke is not at home
Do you feel a bit lonely
Karen, you have been to Ryunosuke ' s room
For fun not long ago
sorry, here is also your home
I came along without prior notice to you
I am only envy you
Though live together, I have never tried
To talk with him in his room
Ah Yui, I envy you
You have the chance to live with such
a good man
It seems bit smaller for
two living together
But I am very happy,
like graduation journey
I have been long to it
To talk with friends about the boy you like
And to enjoy the childish conversation
I felt to be the ordinary girl
You like to wear the ribbon quite often?
The guy I like used to say
He likes girls wearing ribbon. so···
I decided to take off only before that man
You really sleep like that?
I always sleep naked at home
somebody says that would keep fit
But today I wear underwear
Really?
Better for me to sleep that way
from now on
Why do you wear like that?
Because Ryunosuke likes me that way
so I sleep with skirt
Karen, you are better
You have elegant body
mutual and big breast
And seems to be larger recently
May be it was because of someone
Karen, you have boyfriend again?
Though I want to tell you I have
Only single way love now
What about you?
I have in my heart
Lie, you are welcome so much
Even though he likes me
I will only bring trouble to him
Because I ask him to like me only
That is embarrassed
You look at me again
You have been watching at my column
From time to time
sorry··· I feel that beautiful
You want to touch?
what?
I feel you are beautiful
With small hip
I think you are better than me
to be the model
I have big hip and when
have swimming suit on
someone laughs me as the sexual star
Are you? But I jealous you
This Lishi underwear is lovely
Is it, it is special today
Because in front of you today
I cheat you. I like Lishi underwear
This underwear is the same suit
with that bra
Do you like
Let me introduce my favorite
shop to you
Must suit you. Let me chose for you
I··· I could not afford that price
I am poor this month
There happened nothing then
When I entered his room
He only discuss with me and then
sent me home
It is true, I swear
Not that serious, I am not distrust you···
I don ' t want you to guess
I understand
Nobody told me we have outdoor picturing
Don ' t be the way as you like
This is work
I have warned you so many times
Where did you hide last night?
Forget it, remove shirt quickly
have requested to postponed it till afternoon
Ah Yui
Sanshiro senpai
Ah Yui, have you been waiting for long?
E
To wear bikini even in this cold day
Don ' t you think unreasonable?
E···Karen
Better for me to wait outside
Never mind, I am through right now
It will be troublesome to be found by
Hikari-san
Ah Yui, could you give me a hand?
The zipper is locked
Do I at last have to go the sexual star way
It is open, thanks
Don ' t worry, how old are you, Karen?
You could also be the model
Do you mean I am childish?
No··· I don ' t mean that
I cheat you. Besides, senpai, excuse me
What do you think of the piano
teacher Miyuki
What do I think··· oh···
Wonderful, all of them are famous brand
swimming suit
You could try them
There will be no one to come temporally
Really? Iet me try
I really like her··· very much
I want to see her, so I stay in this city
You see, what I said is correct
When I listen to teacher Miyuki to play piano
I sometimes think
The teacher is waiting for someone
Like the price?
The man will change her life
Miyuki-san···
Senpai
Women rely on charming and
men rely on braveness
You have seen mine
No··· only slight of it
Please keep it secret
The matter I always with underwear
Because there will be crinkle
I should not wear when taking
pictures with swimming suit
Actually I have expecting also
Men rely on braveness
Generally you have to date her to walk
Senpai,
what are you talking about
Nothing···
stop the here. Yui
Sen···pai, what is happening?
Painful···
Senpai
I refuse, please release
You have been changed very charming
I··· despise you
Good words
First I will return what you owe me
two years ago···
No
stop
Who are you
Sanshiro-san
Miyuki-san, please run away
But you···
never mind me, run quickly
Alright···
stop
I have not finished
I am coming to meet you, please release her
Are you an idiot?
You will pay high to show up
Before the women
Power···
could not even protect yourself
Don ' t dream to protect women
Miyuki-san··· I··· to you···
Are you alright? Sanshiro senpai
I···?
You fainted and so I called brother···
No, I asked Ryunosuke to
help you back
Is it?··· thanks, Ryunosuke
Ryunosuke?
Ryunosuke···
What is that matter?
What is the matter with you?
Ah Yui you are too free at home
He felt not interesting
And he said your skirt is too short
Nobody will watch at home, never mind
And
The miniskirt could cover
my short legs disadvantage
But you will not be happy to
be Ryunosuke
I only wear it before you
They have very good relation
Always good to each other
But there is a long way to love
I also understand a matter
It is painful to fall in love
Sanshiro-san will be alright
Sanshiro-san···
What incredible