I haven ' t been so relaxed
for a long time
Then, just come to me!
To be together with you,
I am willing to go everywhere.
While we live together,
can ' t we be together on the street?
That means we have no chance
to go to the movie
And have meals hand in hand···?
Stop, Yui, Ryunosuke
will be embarrassed
No!
I am prone to speak out// //what I think
Yui···
Brother,
I could give all my possessions to you
Just look
I have grown up
I come to know what you are thinking
But I also keep on enduring
Regardless of what they say
I won ' t be scared as long as
be together with you
Then, is it ok for me to live alone?
Then, you and I could become···
Schoolmates of the same grade
Brother···
Brother··· so stupid!
The third chapter
Swimming pool,
love and cherry blossom!?
I am coming
You ' ve quarreled with Ryunosuke?
No··· It ' s just that I get angry
Wandering alone
I ' ve been this way
since a long time ago
Every time, when quarreled with him
Yui, you will come to my bathroom
Sorry for coming here in so abruptly
I understand the mood you are in
I want to speak it out too
Telling him I am no longer a child
I just don ' t want him see
my pictures only
Although I am not willing
I have to go to him making apology
I could not live by myself
Life without him
It ' s hard to imagine
Great, Yui
This makes me think of
what Misako said
The words from Mum
She said you shouldn ' t get inferred
The younger generation
will grow up by themselves
Now you have grown up
to be a slim girl
You make fun of me
Brother and I had a severe
quarrel this January
At that time
Senpai ' s love affairs
have a turning point
Very lovely!
Isn ' t it fantastic?
Senior will be greatly pleased
I haven ' t dressed this way
for sometime, I am somewhat upset
But···
I want Sanshiro-san to···
Look at me,
I am different from the usual
No! Miyuki-san!
Be sure to wear the Mini-skirt
Show people your lovely underwear
Is that··· so?
This one may be quite good
But
Miyuki-san, the ones with
dark flowers are better for you
This one is very lovely!
Have you been waiting for long?
Your face look red
Do you have a fever?
It ' s···because of the bad weather
I am to blame for kept you waiting long
Do you feel somewhat warmer?
Sanshiro-san
How about talking while walking
Ok···! I like walking!
Senpai
The belt of your shoes
Let me help you fasten it
I am good at knotting the butterfly
Thanks
Senpai
Were there are a sculptor and a critic
The sculptor is
confident in his capability
Spending long time
designing perfect articles
While for the sake of criticism,
the critic keeps on
Collecting the data concerning
sculptures day and night
Yes, I ' ll help you fasten it
Thank you
I am not meaning which one is better
Senpai,
I think you are confident in yourself
Being an industrious sculptor
Sculptor···
These words···
All from the Katakiri sensei
Even an outstanding critic
Wouldn ' t know the essence of sculpture
Let ' s go
Yes
More efforts! Senpai!
Bad! I have dated Izumi!
Last time,
the man annoyed me in the park···
With me··· have some connections
I was born in a rigid family
So he shows special emotion
towards me
They look hooligans, good at fighting
Being gentle to the girls
At that time, I consider him to
be an ideal boy-friend
While he completely
ignored my feelings then
I began to feel puzzled
I questioned the falsehood
of his daily gentleness to me
So you asked me that
question last time
You···why are you so gentle to me?
So meaningless
Wearing a···
Making your stature
more eye-catching
Quarrelling again
I don ' t want to get involved
in their business
Sorry··· for your trust on me
It doesn ' t matter
But, don ' t be conceded
When summer comes
You could go to
the sea to have a bath
Katakiri sensei
Yui, it ' s you
Then···
To be the main character
in other people ' s life
One need courage and consistency
I think you are confident in that,
Senpai
An industrious sculptor
Miyuki-san, I ···you···!
Oh, Miyuki
Yousuke···
Yousuke, who is she?
Come after me, Miyuki
Hey! Yousuke!
You may go now
Hands free! I won ' t go there!
Miyuki-san!
You still wear some
childish underwear
Let me give you some advice
That has nothing to do with you!
You···! Don ' t be so rude in words!
Don ' t interfere!
Sanshiro-san!
I ' ve mentioned it last time
It ' s bad for a useless man
pretending to be somebody
Trying to protect women
Ok, follow me, Miyuki
Please···wait a moment!
What do you want to?
I am asking you what you want to do
Raise your head!
Don ' t hurt Miyuki-san
Shit!
I beg you···
Stop!
I like Miyuki-san!
So, I don ' t her to be hurt!
Please, don ' t ply with her
You haven ' t the dignity?
Don ' t get in!
Let ' s go!
Wait! Yousuke!
Please raise your head,
they have already gone
Sorry··· I am really sorry
You needn ' t make apology,
Miyuki-san
I can ' t fight, I am to blame···
Just thinking of that way
Are you serious by saying that?
You like that
I am not deceiving you
But!
I···!
Without that qualification···!
In fact, you and her are
of the same grade
But, she stayed home
because of sickness in the beginning
Then, she will be our
under classman in school?
What ' s up? You don ' t have bath?
She hasn ' t got used to that
The nurses took care of her
when she was in hospital
She feels puzzled when she is alone
Come in, Sakurako-san
Come in
Let ' s have a bath together
The bikini assigned by the school?
I ' ve always been in hospital,
I don ' t have any bikinis extra
Are you Narusawa Senpai?
Yes··· that ' s right···
You cohabit with Ryunosuke
Senpai won ' t defeat me!
Who is that just now?
She seems to be···
Tsuzuki Kozue, a first year student
It seems that Ryunosuke
is popular among people
It ' s my consistent dream
To go to school wearing this uniform
Then, your dream will soon come true
Wish every dream would be fulfilled
What?
No··· nothing!
Very short··· exposing too much?
I never pay much attention to it
Some think you wear the sport socks,
making you higher
You think it ' s nothing, Yui-san?
Unless some people
keep on watching me
Yui, your telephone
Yes
I am sorry,
I can ' t send you back home
It doesn ' t matter,
I alone know the way back
Then, I ' ll be catching time, bye bye
Although I am not sure
if you are waiting for somebody
You seem to be waiting for something
It ' s the same with me,
so I know that
It won ' t do just waiting
You and me
With Yousuke then··· a little bit different···
My heart···beats so hard···
Take it easy
The business tonight,
I won ' t forget all my life
Sometimes,
I think of making myself small
Then, I could come into your pocket
We could forever being together
Dreaming?
Ok! I will come to school tomorrow
Helping Brother clean the desks
If you want to turn off the lights,
just tell me
Don ' t you ask me about that?
You seem to be unwilling
to ask me about that
I ' ve hurt the heart of Sanshiro-san
I don ' t know what to do now
Yui-san···
Please remain unmoved
Wait···what ' s the matter with you?
Please feel my heart
Doesn ' t my heart beat quickly?
Because···
I ' ve met something exciting today
The heart-beating tonight,
the only one in life
I ' ve the feeling
it ' s my fortune to like somebody
I hope you, Miyuki-san···
Could feel what I ' m thinking
Yui-san···
Does he like her?
Perhaps, he probably thinks
It ' s my plot designed in the beginning
I am sorry for being late, Tomomi···
I··· can ' t see···!
I see··· but I could forget it···
Senpai···
Do you think I am too thin?
Oh··· how to say··· not at all
Very···
Underwear?
Very lovely
Really?
Yes
Owning to the courage you spared
me in the spring hot
I decided to face him bravely
So···
This is decisive underwear
Decisive underwear?
Sorry!
Then, please wait for a while
Yes
But, Ok
Tomomi seems to have
settled all the troubles
On the contrary, I···
You seem to be unhappy
You···
Intend to give up this way?
It probably was a face-losing
business for you then
But
It ' s your qualification to determine it
This is the last magic
Please adjust your mood
7 o ' clock sharply
What ' s the matter, teacher?
You play different tones from the usual
Boiling as well as gentle
Is that··· so?
What ' s more, you dressed up
different from the usual
The fragrance is different, yeah,
the fragrance of Yui
It ' s···your illusion
I have been waiting for you
At 7 pm, be sure to come
She wants me to grow excited
by watching naked woman
The female ' s bathroom
Three, no need to give the changes
I pay for myself!
This is the public bathroom
How could Miyuki-san
and Karen···?
Bad! We run out of shampoo
You have the bath
without taking off the clothes
Just speak it out here
if you have something to say
I ' ve nothing to say,
I just want to know
The woman once Yousuke liked
Embarrassed
Yes···
Senpai!
Aren ' t you confident
with your naked body?
Ok! I ' ve brought here nothing!
Your purpose here is
to see the naked girls?
No··· no!
In fact, I am not sure myself···
Embarrassed
Sanshiro···!
I thought you ' ve made love
with Yousuke at least once
But you seem to be a green hand
That··· has nothing to do with you!
So annoying
You may go back now
Please···please wait!
But··· so fantastic!
The bathroom runs
out of water suddenly
Everything was Ok in the morning
I haven ' t finished the story yet!
You are disgusting as well
I have made it clear that everything is Ok
Is it Ok here?
Some other place,
without any people!
Oh, you don ' t like me to be nearby?
Karen!
Yui
What ' s do you mean?
I heard you said it to Yousuke
Just look at me if
you want to be my lover
Refrain from controlling your feelings
You seem to have considered Yousuke
as a bad people
Anyway, have you tried your efforts?
Have you even tried to
understand him
Love aiming at harvest
is just likes cooking meals
To have relationship
with women like you
Men feel nothing but pain
So, I said that
He is poor for kneeling down
on the ground
You ' d better get disappeared
from Yousuke
You voice could annoy the neighbors
Miyuki-san···
What ' s happened?
I don ' t know, something bad probably
What do you mean by saying that?
Have a look
Please wait!
My business with Yousuke
Probably you are right there
But···my relationship
with Sanshiro-san is different
Meaningless,
that has nothing to do with me
That ' s your problem
Sanshiro-san!?
Miyuki-san···
Sanshiro-san··· I···
Can you see me?
My breasts are not big enough
I don ' t like to be fat
Now, I am trying very
hard to lose Weight!
Only the hip is too big···
the source of my anguishes
But, this is the my real side
I just want you to know more of me!
I want to make a complete response···
The courage you ' ve manifested,
Sanshiro-san
I want to know more about you,
I like you!
Miyuki-san···
Because I want you to
turn your head back looking at me
So I prevented to be gentle···
There is no genuine
gentle in the world
I have no confidence
In those I don ' t like···
Despite this,
I still think you could make it!
Miyuki-san···!
Wish everything would be
smooth with Senpai
That ' s fine
In this city
There is a god for lovers
The first time
I saw you remove the ribbon
I thought my dream had come true
You have beautiful hair
Probably, I will envy the rivals
I belonged to him
The one I love told me
there is another one in his heart
But, I won ' t give it up
You are included, of course
I remember··· once
Senpai asked me
a very strange question
He asked what
the decisive underwear is
Why did he ask such a question?
End