You are ready,
But I haven ' t the experience of taking plane.
You wait for me bringing the message
Karen-san,
it seems you don ' t wear the underwear
Having nothing on frequently
when taking bathes
Karen-san wears nothing when she sleeps
Yui, how could you know that?
It ' s a secret
Wait a moment!
I want to go there too
Very big!
It ' s fresh
That ' s right
Jump into the water, Yui
Are you two alright?
You are so naughty,Karen
Sorry
You asked me
why I decided to go to the spring abruptly
I will make the explanation later
How will the love story develop?
Boy··· incredible
The second chapter
"Minori, Tomomi and the hotspring travel"
In fact··· I am coming again
Is she ok?
You are rare here,
how about go back to the school having a look?
oh, Yui, what are you doing?
Because, all of my
underwear seem childish
If I dry them in a detectable place
He will make fun of me
Ryunosuke has already been out
Did he come back this morning?
I have been searching for that underwear
In fact, this underwear is not mine
It turns out to be mother ' s
I even asked Brother about this
Don ' t make a fuss on such a trifle
Because··· it ' s very expensive
But, it isn ' t suitable for you
But, Brother seems to like the one riper
Were I wear underwear of that kind
Perhaps he will show love towards me
But underwear is not something
for people to see
Although it is so···
I will ignore it!
That is something of feeling!
You are my daughter
Take it easy,
you will be very beautiful in the future
So beautiful
hat Brother will turn back his head to see me
Put your heart at rest,
just be confident in yourself
Minori
Sanshiro senpai
Are the flowers ok?
Yes, during the vocation
Nobody will come to the
garden to destroy them
The plant mark
you sent me on the graduation ceremony
I still keep it good up to now
No!
Find a place drying the suit
Senpai, what ' s the matter?
Minori···?
Yes, I am Minori
I am sorry for being rude to you
I have been covering my genuine feeling
Having no confidence towards others
Because I have no friends
only you could hear me out!
It seems that I could be
changed because of one person
But···
What shall I do?
I··· I don ' t know for sure
The most important thing
is to open your mind
What ' s more,
you have to apologize to him
For you have cheated him
What shall I do if he won ' t forgive me?
You have to make consistent
apologies to him
Until the time he forgives you
Were it me, I will do the same thing
You believe me
Senpai, I will try to apologize to him
I will try to face him earnestly
This···!
oh···
Senpai, one more thing
When coming back to school
Be sure to wear the uniform
and take the school bag
But
I will say goodbye to the
school uniform soon
I like wearing it
The students in the other school like it too
You see···when wearing the uniform
It ' s better not to jump
Why?
That··· oh···
You are so fantastic, Sanshiro
You and brother are alike
in manner of speaking
Brother? said the same thing before
The brother you said···Ryunosuke?
Please keep it a secret that
I call him Brother
Either coffee or cake is ok
As well as the fried meal,
I will treat you
otherwise, Brother will hate me
I won ' t··· tell it to the other people
Are you serious?
of course
Tomomi
It doesn ' t matter
Take it serious!
Put your heart at rest,
I won ' t slap your face
Because I am only interested
in your lower part
Stop!
Tomomi···?
Things like that···
I will never allow it happen!
Then, showing it to Ryunosuke···
Tomomi, what ' s happening?
Yui! Sanshiro senpai
Mother!
I am fine···
I have something to handle···bye
Tomomi! Wait··· a moment!
Sorry!
Senpai, excuse me
Yui!
It hasn ' t dried yet
Get a temporary job,
no other way out
Tomomi, are you in?
oh?
oh···me
Sorry, I made a mistake
I ' ve got it,
you are in the convenience shop
Thanks··· for sending me
Better than walking along
Then, I will go first
In fact, she and
I are in the same school
But, I haven ' t seen her before
Yui-san
Miyuki-san
Do you know the Mizuno
residence nearby?
Your mother worries about you,
so, she contacts me
She made a propose
Mother being that way again
I learned playing piano
when I was a child
What ' s more, I have no time for that now
Tomomi, you seem to be so tired
You have been listening to my complains
Anyway, I will help you
I am ok,
if there is something wrong with me
You are the first that
I will turn to for help
Even if it is approaching the exams
Resting is a necessity
How about shopping together?
It sounds great
Is it having something to do with piano?
one can ' t play piano well
If improvement made only in skills
Because piano reflects
the heart of the player
To make the strong melody
Eliminating the pain of the heart
is a basic course
Although it is so
I thought there are no bathing
clothes in the winter
It could make people have
a better rest temporary
I don ' t believe it
ok, let it be so now
It ' s adventurous of me to do that
Very lovely
Tomomi, you ' d better to try it on
I ··· I won ' t try it···!
Don ' t say that, come on,
how about wear this one
Come on, hurry up
Wait.. wait a moment! Yui!
Don ' t worry about it, I will handle it
ok, I take it off myself
Tomomi, you have a perfect stature
oh
Thanks, but my stern is too big
Try it on, Sister
I come here just to escort Yui
Don ' t say that,
I think this one is very suitable to you
Have a look
No···
With only one belt through the waist,
I have no confidence wearing it
How could you know
since you haven ' t tried yet
Then··· I···
Like all the men
You could never understand them
while standing by
Sometimes women should
take the initiative
··· Tomomi,
you are suitable to wear the lovely style
Is that so?
Very lovely
Really?
You are welcome
Hello
Is that?
Sanshiro-san
Now it ' s your finest moment
Is that so?
Sometimes
when you want to have the anguishes
It probable won ' t come
Just like me at this moment
Women become more beautiful
when they are in love
While it is a furnace of heart
for men in love
I am tired because
I haven ' t fallen into love
Well, are you free?
Sanshiro-san, how do you like this one?
Something I will wear this
kind of clothes in the street
I··· I think it is suitable for you now
Dida teaches people to flatter the other
But I am very happy,
I will show you something
I haven ' t wear it for people
to see for a long time
I am nervous
Who will have this kind of underwear?
It is probably suitable for Karen-san,
so matured
As well as suitable for Yui
I am not interested in it,
because I am not in a hurry
It ' s enough for me to wear this
Yui, Miyuki sensei
What are you doing in such a place?
I have just left the film factory
Karen, something good happened?
Why?
Because you seem to be
happier than before
I have a week off from tomorrow on
It turns out that you could
have the vocations!
Perhaps it is dependent on revolting
Misako-san is very beautiful
But, I haven ' t seen
Miyuki-san all day long
Do we have no destiny to be together?
I have made it clear that
It won ' t do just waiting
No other way out, you are so poor
Wait and I will give you a chance
Just this time
Sir, if you want to have a bet
Could you give me the ticket?
Very happy today
Jianzhong, It ' s better to be this way
oh?
Youko
So innocent, without dressing up
But, the skirt is too short
Anyway, boys like it
Yui, girls of your kind
What happen?
What ' s wrong with Youko?
You come back
Mother, what ' s wrong with Youko?
Youko-san ask me to give you this
What ' s this?
The invitation card for hot spring travel
It seemed that Akira gave this to her
She said she got this by lucky draw
Why did she give it to me?
She mentioned Ryunosuke,
and said continually
If go with you, that guy should go too
So left the invitation card
And it ' s two tickets
As you mentioned,
she seems absent her mind today
Mother! Your clothes···
Is it lovely
Yes
Sorry, call you in middle night
I am delighted that you ask
me to enjoy the hot spring
It ' s just spend one day
But I expect
Ladies and gentleman
I appreciate that
You take this bus
I am the tour guide Nonomura Misato
We will get to the hot spring
about three hours later
Now
Please enjoy the view along
Sanshiro-san
We have no chance to meet from last time
Are you fine?
Miyuki-san, Miyuki-san
Yes
What are you thinking?
Nothing ···
It ' s better to dip in
the hot spring at once
Don ' t waste time
Let ' s have a rest, we are tired
You don ' t know
You should change bath gown ahead
before you dip in the hot spring
Really? I don ' t know
Don ' t take it as truth
Isn ' t it right?
Shit! There is somebody stay in the car
Sir, please wake up
We have got to there, sir
Sorry ··· sorry
It seems you have nice
sleep along the way
So I didn ' t awake you
You will be more
lovely if you are bound
Miyuki-san, won ' t
you take off the bra?
I feel shameful···
It doesn ' t matter, there is only women
You needn ' t be embarrass
It ' s cold
All is because you sleep at such place
Go to the open air hot spring
and get warmer
In fact I am going
Go along this way and turn right,
there is the hot spring for man
There is the hot spring for
woman on the left
Thank you
oh? It ' s right about
Count it, well, I ' d like to get warmer
I keep well
You are lucky, I never take airplane
Wait me to take present for you
Miss tour guide,
come to dip in the hot spring
Yes···
Karen-san, you don ' t wear underwear
Generally, we wear nothing
under bathing gown
Karen wear nothing when she sleep
Yui, how could you know this?
It ' s a secret
Wait!
I will go too
Anyway, I can ' t compete with the young girl
Your mouth is so large that
it can contain a stone
Stone?
Stone in finger guessing game
You are kidding
Yui-san, you are funny
I feel special
If you participate in
the comic dialogue contest
You might bring play
your astonishing talent
Yui, you ' d better play with me
Anyway
I still want to play piano and violin
I can teach your playing piano at any time
Miyuki-san, why did you study piano
In fact, I have other intention
I loved one music teacher
when I was in primary school
I want him to praise me,
so I begin to study piano
We ' d better be closer
Let ' s explore
It might be funny
Go, go
I will stay here for a while
All the men from urbane are randy
You can ' t go to such place along
Mother, you don ' t understand me at all
Have no idea
originally, here is so large too, tough
Are you the landlady
Let us dip with you
It ' s comfortable
Please enjoy yourself
Sorry··· sorry, I thought there is nobody
Fine··· I thought we have been seen···
What are you doing at here?
No··· oh···
oh, you are the one just now···
Don ' t misunderstand···
I thought this was for man
Didn ' t I indicate wrong···?!
What sound this is
Isn ' t anybody swimming at here?
Let me have a look
I go with you
It ' s fantastic to be young,
have so beautiful shape
Smooth skin
Don ' t··· don ' t kidding
Did you ever been touched by man
You won ' t be involved in a love affair
By close your heart, lady
What happened
Does he wan to watch?!
No··· no, he has reason hard to say
Sanshiro senpai
How could I be here
It was said the hot spring
is too hot that you faint
But, you looked fine,
I set me heart aside
I was too worried to fall
in sleep at that day
Thank you
Did you be beaten by that man at that day?
All was result from I didn ' t know how to fight
You didn ' t know how to fight but for me···!
No···
I am delighted, the man before was···
But
I never thought I can meet you at such place
I feel it ' s the fate
Then··· then, I am delighted
Sanshiro-san
You think what is to be tender to others?
You···why did you ask such question
Because to be tender to a person
You want he to be tender to you too
or thought you are tender
Because love the one
Because want he love you
Want he think you are tender
Then, to be tender
Is just the way to cheat
Miyuki-san···
I think really tender is
To scarify yourself and don ' t ask return
But that is···
Sorry··· sorry, I
concentrate on talking
Could I answer you later
I don ' t know the answer right now
So, I will seek for it,
I must find it
Yes···! I wait for you
Excuse me···
Could I come in?
I··· I dip in the hot spring once more
Senpai, it ' s fantastic
In my past life and love affair
I only taste pain and sadness
Tomomi, anyone at any time
Have sad story more or less
That is the proof to exist
The most important thing is to face it
only the one could face it '
Can smile frequently
Senpai
Sorry, I know nothing
and tell flub and gulf
I saw you were sad
All depend on you, I am fine
Senpai
Please don ' t scare us anymore
Senpai, why you are here
Didn ' t you chase me
No··· no
I win the invitation card by lucky draw
Luck draw?
It ' s comfortable to dip in the hot spring
Can you teach me piano
when we are back
With pleasure
It seems I can play nice music now
You seemed happy
All depend on senpai
Your remark help me taking easy
Sanshiro-san···?
I won ' t escape again
I will let he know he is wrong
But
Senpai is amazing
I think each of his remark
Comfort person
I have one thing don ' t understand
It ' s about you
Miyuki-san, if you don ' t mind
We ' d better meet along next time
I have some thing to tell you too
At two o ' clock on third January
Let ' s meet at Yasuhachi park
Yes
I want to know more about you
It ' s fine, senpai
About the hot spring,
I will keep secret for you
Please forget I am naked
as soon as possible
Make a deal