I am Madoka Misaki, 19 years old.
I have almost finished my first year at the
university.
There is a help center for full or part time jobs.
"University Girls-Special Counseling"
There are 2 guys at the center.
One is very hot, but the other is ugly.
I want to talk to the hot guy today.
I was bubbling with anticipation.
Ah, good. This is the best!
Ah~teacher, really?
Do you really like mine?
So tight. Ummmm.
Ah... really.
I'm glad. Ah... more...
Okay. I make you moan.
I'm happy. Ah... good... more...
Ah, great. Ummmm...
How great!
Excuse me.
Ah~, teacher. Ah~
You're tightening. Ah...
Feel good. Ah...
Ah... but... good... good, teacher.
Ah... I feel good... so...
Ah... Great.
Ah... good... good...
Ah... there... good...
Here? Here?
Oh, no. The man of my dream was
doing... nasty thing with another girl.
Oh, no. No way...
He looks so nice, but...
Ah... something is bad.
Ah... bad...
Feel good... ah... teacher.
No... no, teacher...
I see.
I'm sure you are shocked.
Because you really liked him.
Ummm, I got more than that.
And then, what are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
Do you want to quit?
No~
I won't give it up so easily.
Okay. Why don't you try him again.
I want to do it, but I'm scared.
I understand, but you need to solve this by
yourself.
Ummmmm.
Okay, you need to try harder.
But...
What? You don't look like yourself.
Go for broke!
Nothing ventured, nothing gained.
You must go there.
Nothing to loose.
Okay. I got it.
I don't like to give up.
Excuse me.
Um... Um... Who are you?
My name is Misaki, Madoka.
I'm a freshman, literature major.
Oh, okay. So what's up for today?
About a part time job?
No.
Well... I...
I saw that you engaged in an indecent act with
a student in this room yesterday.
Oh, okay.
It happened sometimes.
My job is to solve all kinds of student's
problems.
Ha, ha, ha...
Oh... well...
What happened?
Madoka?
Ah, Literature major.
I wonder if you're romantic.
What? No...
Okay. Why do you want to ask my advice?
Well...
Do you want me to guess?
Um... You want to ask about...
Ah, I... really...
What happened, Madoka?
Okay, Madoka.
Ah... no, teacher, no...
Don't be shy...
Here... like this...
Ah... Ah... Teacher... Ah...
Look, it's so wet.
You feel it so easily.
Ah...
Let me lick it.
Ah... teacher...
Now, your turn.
Ummmmm.
Ummmm, good. Yea. You're good.
Ah... good. Yea.
Ah...
With your hand.
Ah... good.
Yours is so good.
Yea? How many dicks you have sucked so far?
Um?
No, I can't answer that. Ummm.
Okay. Ready?
Ah... teacher. Very good.
Oh... good, good. You are good.
More, more, teacher.
Ah... nice...
Ah... great... Ah...
Look. Next is this.
Ah...
Oh, good.
Ah... teacher... I... I can't...
I'm going to teach well today.
Ah... teacher... Ah...
Come on... Cum... Cum.
Teacher, I can't hold...
Come on. Come on.
Ah... I'm cumming... Ah...
I'm cummming! Cumming! Ah... teacher... I'm...
Cum... You can cum...
No... No... Ah... More... More...
Okay. I'm going to make you cum.
Come on. Come on.
Ah... teacher... Ah... teacher... I can't hold...
You have big breasts.
D? E or?
Ah... I use an F cup.
There is F, too? I like that.
Ah... I'm so glad.
Teacher, I'm glad.
I like you very much, teacher.
Me too. Me too.
Ah... teacher... I'm going to... cum... again.
Ah... me, too.
No...
No. I can't hold back any more... Your pussy is
so good.
Ah... teacher... cum together... Ah...
Here you go. Cumming.
Ah... teacher... Ah...
Ah... Madoka...
Um... You did it.
Thanks for helping me, Yooki.
And now, what are you going to do?
We're going on a date.
Wow. How did you do it?
I didn't do anything special.
I just let him do whatever he wanted
You must have a great pussy.
No, Yooki.
But he liked my F cup breasts.
I see. They did for him then.
No, Yooki.
Please don't try and fuck him to, Yooki.
I don't want to be a rival against you. Okay?
What? Against me?
Don't worry. He is not my type.
Oh, really?
Can you promise me you won't say anything?
Yea. What?
Don't tell anyone.
Okay. What is it?
There is the another psychology teacher
working in the same room. Right?
Yea. He looks very serious.
Yea. I have a relationship with him.
What? You're lying. I can't believe it.
What? I didn't know you had that kind of taste.
What taste!
You're still a child.
There is much more between a man and a
woman.
Do you want to know?
No really. I don't care about him, but...
I just want to know why you're into...
How do I say...
We have the same taste for one thing.
One thing?
Yea. For some reason, we're getting along.
How do you like it, teacher?
Stepped on by an university girl's boots.
How do you like it?
Ah... Queen Yooki, I'm happy.
Step harder!
Okay. How do you like that?
Woo, kooo... pain... more...
More? Stronger?
Your face is going to be crushed.
Wow... glad... Please do it.
Like you to a cockroach.
Ha, ha... You're a cockroach, teacher.
Okay. I'm going to crush your face. Here you
go.
Wow... ah... good...
How about this?
How do you like to be choked by university girls'
leg?
How do you like it?
Oh... great...
Queen Yooki, it's the best scarf.
Stupid. My leg is not a scarf.
Ouch. I'm so sorry. Queen Yooki, forgive me
please.
I won't. Take it.
Woo... pain...
Pain? Look, you want more?
How do you like it?
I'm going to do this as you like it.
Oh... Queen Yooki, forgive me.
No, I won't. Come on.
Ah... Queen Yooki... ah...
Ah... good... Queen Yooki... ah... I'm cumming...
Ah... Good... Ah...
Ah... Queen Yooki... I'm so happy.
You can't cum 'til I cum.
Okay?
Good.
Ummm.
How do you like it? It's fun, isn't it?
I have heard there are such people, but you and
that teacher are...
You may like it once you try it.
No. It's ugly.
Today I'm going to meet him. You want to come
with me, Madoka?
What? I...
There are dominant and there are submissive
people, each play a sexual role.
If you are both the same, commonly neither is
satisfied.
If both are different, it's more likely that you will
have a great time.
What's that?
Freud.
Usually the woman is submissive and the man
is dominant.
But there is also the opposite case.
Somehow, the mind is affected, even the tiniest
thing, will turn it around...
When you have experienced it, you'll
understand it well.
It's like the study of psychology.
You're going to be okay. Let's go?
Ummm, I need more experience. Okay.
How are you, teacher? We have a nice guest
today. Are you glad?
I'm happy.
Ah, He doesn't feel pain?
Don't worry about it, Madoka.
This man is my servant right now.
Is that right, teacher?
Yes, it is.
I'm miserable, poor and valueless.
Please trample on my feelings.
You really understand it. That's right.
You're a valueless and useless human being.
Take this.
Madoka, don't hesitate. Do it much harder.
Ah... more... so happy...
Hey, teacher. Serve our guest.
Yes, my pleasure.
Ah~feel good... Ah~
Hey, lick it a lot like you do it to me always.
Ah~his tongue... inside of me...
Yea, I teach him. How do you like it?
Hey do it seriously.
Your life is lived only to serve us.
Besides you're useless.
Hey, come on.
An~ great.
He is reaching far inside.
What a tongue!
Why don't you try to tighten it?
Ah~No~Ah~
Come on!
Ah~good~
Come on, Madoka! Hold his head and push it.
Ah... no... I'm cumming... cumming...
Ah... feel good. You can cum, Madoka.
Ah... good... Ah...
Madoka, press his back with your heel.
Okay... like this?
Ah... great. Ah... his tongue... Ah... I'm
cumming... Ah...
Okay, teacher. My turn.
Madoka, whip this man.
Okay. I got it. Like this?
Come on!
Stronger! More!
Like this? Come on! Come on!
Good. Good.
Am I good?
Ah~more and more~
Come on! Come on!
Like this?
Madoka, you have a sense.
Ah... feel good.
Ah, teacher.
Pain?
No, good. I like you, teacher.
Madoka, ah... me too. Me too.
Ah... Ah...
Ah, so tight...
Ah~teacher.
Good? You like it?
Yea, teacher... there...
Ah... there... ah... don't stop.
I won't. I like it so much.
Teacher... ah...
Madoka...
No...
Do you feel here?
Yea, good... nice...
Here... here...
Ah~teacher, nice...
Madoka's... very cute...
Ah~teacher, don't stop.
Good... nice...
Oh... you're taking my hand...
Ah, teacher... good.
Oh, next is this... like this...
I love it... ah~
Nice, ah... teacher... more, more...
Look, Madoka, take the same rhythm.
Like this?
Yea, great.
Ah, teacher... nice... more... more...
Like this?
More... ah...
Oh, Madoka... great... go up...
See? You can tighten...
Ah... teacher... this is... my first time...
Look, up at me. Look into my eyes.
Teacher, nice... ah...
You look like the goddess.
Ah... teacher... nice... teacher... ah...
Ah, great...
I like you, teacher.
Madoka, really...
Very nice.
Ah... you look like the goddess. Beautiful...
Really? Really?
Ummmmm. Ah, Madoka, I feel like being
controlled by you.
I want to ask you, Madoka.
What is it, teacher? Tell me anything.
Really? I want to be your slave in fact.
What?
Could you torment me?