I can't play this flute.
I cannot bring such suffering
to Maria.
Yaku.
We will have to rely on your
sense of smell.
The Shikima guards haven't
returned from their search...
...and we still can't find
Miko and Nin-Nin.
Please!
We'll have to wait for
the full moon.
There!
Miss Miko!
Nin-Nin!
I got it! See?
This is it?
They smell alike.
Good job!
It was tough digging up this
cherished collection.
It's Ranjatai, the most famous
since the Muromachi Era.
Ranjatai? What's that?
The name of this incense.
Buddhist temples kept
its name a secret.
The Ranjatai was a secret
possession of Todai Temple.
It was so treasured
it never left temple.
A treasured incense?
No peeking!
Look the other way.
I just wanted a little whiff.
It's hard to believe the old
lady actually had this.
It must have been passed
down from the Tensho era.
Recognizing it for the power
that it had...
...it's said that it was taken by
the Ashikaga Shogun...
...and Nobunaga.
Miss Miko!
This is strange.
There's another fragrance,
besides the incense.
It's making me crazy.
I can't take it!
This amorous fragrance must
be caused by the incense.
Don't watch, Nin-Nin!
I'm so embarrassed.
Do something!
Do something?!
What could I do?
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Look!
Another victim.
Yaku.
Shanahime. My Shanahime.
Come back.
Come back to me.
Shanahime. Is it you?
Kyoshiro.
Here you are. This time
you won't get away!
Bitch!
Such weaklings. Is that the
best the Shikima can do?
I'll show you!
What?!
That flute can no longer
harm us.
Kyoshiro now understands
that I didn't betray him.
Shit!
Fubuki! Here!
I'll get you!
Don't move! You're dealing
with the best of the Shikima!
What's so funny?
Do you think this is
just a regular blow dart?
Why do you hesitate?
Why do you hesitate to use
the poison dart?
Because deep in your heart
you want me to violate you!
Not true!
Perhaps I should give you
what you want.
The best of the Shikima
is no match for me.
Women are so wretched.
Kill me instead of making me
succumb to this perversion!
Nice try. Let me give you
what you really desire.
What such amorous
convulsions?
Where am I?
What?! No way!
The Warring States period!
Goddamn Danjo.
Danjo?
You're no longer needed.
I'm going to bring your
head to the Shikima...
...and show them that I have
avenged your betrayal.
The Spider Kettle!
Kyoshiro, I took Shanahime
for my own.
I will lay your place, with the
beauty of the 3,000 realms.
And I will take command
of the Shikima realm!
As long as Kyoshiro's alive,
I can change the future!
Hidemasa's possession will
end if I save Kyoshiro!
Kyoshiro!
I can't forgive Shanahime
for doing this to him!
I can't forgive her.
It's all her fault!
Kyoshiro and Hidemasa
wouldn't have been cursed...
...if it hadn't been for her.
Fuck!
You fucking bitch!
Give me back my member!
You bitch!
Kyoshiro!
You bitch, Shanahime.
How dare you swallow
my member!
I am not going to die
so easily!
I am a Shikima
of great powers.
I am not going to die.
With my blood...
...these will be cursed
with my hatred.
As long as this flute exists,
as long as this kettle exists...
...my hatred will
remain forever.
Shanahime!
Poor Shanahime.
Gamara's to blame!
He's the one that caused
this madness!
I'll put an end to this evil,
here and now!
The male flute!
The female flute!
Nin-Nin.
Miss Miko.
Where were you?
I went back 400 years,
to the Karimara fortress.
Really?
Yes, and I was able to
find out the truth.
My father was wrong.
The Chidori urn was
groaning and moaning away.
I couldn't leave it.
I was called back by the male
and female flutes!
I just heard them too!
Where?
That way.
I hope Fubuki and Yaku
are okay.
Miss Miko! Wait!
Yaku! Fubuki!
Look, Miss Miko!
Fubuki!
Miss Miko!
-Yaku!
-Have they been killed?!
Nin-Nin. You get Yaku!
I'll get Fubuki!
Wake Fubuki up with that
medicine! I'll get Yaku!
Hurry!
Nin-Nin.
Miko.
Thank goodness you're both
all right!
You tricked us! You two
were just playing dead!
I failed! I can't face
you, Miko.
The female flute has been
taken!
So the female and male flute
just now...?
They've gone after the King!
We can't just stand around!
The flutes again!
Father! Mother!
How did they do this?!
They'll destroy the Shikima
with power of the flutes.
Father.
The Anti-Shikima are
attacking!
Save the King and Maria!
Darling!
Maria, forgive me!
I cannot stop this curse
of the Anti-Shikima.
Darling!
King! I resent
what you've done to us!
You drove apart our love
with your evil plot!
We won't forgive you!
You deserve to be punished!
Wait!
I won't be punished by you!
You have no shame!
You shall suffer the wrath
of our hatred.
You've both fallen under the
curse of the Anti-Shikima.
I wouldn't kill your mother,
who was my own sister!
What?!
Kyoshiro, don't be fooled
by him!
Wake up! You're under
by the curse of the Kettle!
Prepare to die!
If you're going to hurt
someone, hurt me, not Maria.
Darling!
How sweet. Showing off your
love while denying ours.
You can't kill me
with those flutes.
Since your deaths, I became
King.
As the Shikima King I can
live for 1 ,000 years.
What?!
Then take the curse of
this flute for all of eternity.
What's this?
Are you going to interfere?
No.
I came because I want
to see your love realized.
What?
It's not the Shikima you
should bear a grudge against.
There's a curse on the
Spider Kettle and the flutes.
You're trying to trick us!
You two have returned to
fulfill your love.
It'd be tragic not to.
That fragrance.
What is that incense?
Hidemasa.
That incense.
It belongs to Shanahime, who
has caused me such suffering.
Shanahime.
Are you the real Shanahime?
I couldn't bring
Hidemasa back.
Shanahime! You're the real
one, aren't you!
-Miko!
-Look out!
Fubuki! Yaku!
Don't hurt him!
Which is the real one?
You wretch! Are you trying
to steal my Kyoshiro?!
No, I just want to bring
Hidemasa back.
That's all.
Hidemasa?
I don't understand.
Kyoshiro.
We cannot fulfill our purpose
until the Shikima is ruined.
The truth! I want the truth!
The spell has clouded your
mind! Listen to your heart!
If you were the
Anti-Shikima...
...Father, I mean the King...
...would use his power
and destroy you both.
What?!
Nonsense!
The reason he doesn't...
...is that his sister is your
Mother, Kyoshiro.
He is being merciful
to you and your bride.
Miko.
If he destroyed you,
you'd only come back.
But my Father...
...he didn't want to make you
suffer like that.
Miko...
Cast your resentment
onto me.
You will be gone, and I will
forever bear your grievances.
How dare you!
Good-bye, my Hidemasa.
You're that woman!
I'll never forget this hatred!
I will not die now!
Hidemasa.
Miss Miko!
Nin-Nin!
I got it!
Miko. Put the female and
male flutes inside it.
Only you understand them,
and can break the curse.
Miko.
We've found our way.
Thank you.
Kyoshiro.
At last, our love
can be fulfilled.
Kyoshiro, I'm so happy.
Shanahime.
Kyoshiro, come to me!
Come to me!
Miss Miko.
You did it, Miko.
Your Majesty.
What will happen
to Hidemasa?
The Anti-Shikima curse is
broken, so he should be fine.
Really?!
I'll go check.
Hang on!
Got to watch her. Nin-Nin!
Hidemasa!
I wonder how Miko's first
love will work out?
My hands are tied, even
though I'm the Shikima King.
A little sweet, don't you
think?
No, as long as Hidemasa
likes them!
Sure was nice of Miko
to invite me over.
We're celebrating your
recovery! We were worried.
It's funny though, I can't
remember a thing.
All kinds of things happened
to you. I'm glad you're okay.
Hurray for Miko's first love.
But I do envy the guy.
Oh, hi.
Haven't forgotten our date,
have you?
Uh-oh. I did forget.
So what's new.
You were supposed to meet
my Father!
I was invited out by a cute
friend of mine.
So she's more important?
That's not it.Just a second.
Nin-Nin?
What's Miko going to do
when she hears about this?
I can't tell her!
Hidemasa!
I can't wait to see him!