Miss Miko!
Kyoshiro Karimara!
He's come back!
That flute!
Stop playing that flute!
Miko!
-Miko!
-Fubuki!
Fubuki!
Miko!
You're one the Shikima!
Perfect.
I'll get you to lead me
to the Shikima King.
You've got to be kidding!
I'll put an end to you
here and now!
How deluded of you.
This time it's going to
be different.
I'm the strongest woman
of the Shikima!
You fool! I'll put you in your
place!
You Shikima woman!
Let's see if you can bear my
amorous powers.
You are a woman after all.
You appear to be delighting
in my tentacles.
You slimy sea cucumber!
You cannot take your eyes
off me!
How about here?
Look into my eyes.
Does that feel good?
Do you want me?
Don't stop!
Want me to drive it
into you?
Yes!
You can touch it if you want.
Feel my shaft inside
your mouth.
Once you do, you won't be
able to stop.
Wrap your lips around me
and flick it with your tongue.
Or your passion will
burn within you.
Please!
Imagine the friction of my
penis rubbing inside you.
It will bring you to ecstasy,
and you won't want to stop.
Please!
Hurry! Come on!
Do you want to lick it?
Want me to stick it
in you?
I can't stand it any longer!
Please! Hurry!
Please! I want it!
Please Kyoshiro!
I'm about to
burst with desire!
Then you must show me the
way to the Shikima realm.
My sweets.
I'll give you what you desire.
To the Shikima...
You've succumbed to my
amorous powers.
Wake up, Miko!
Miss Miko!
What happened?
Thank goodness,
you're all right!
Where's Fubuki?
She went after Kyoshiro, but
we don't know where she is.
Well we can't just sit around.
You two go find Hidemasa
and Shanahime.
What about you?
I'll go to the Shikima realm.
The resurrected Kyoshiro...
...could be going after my
father for revenge.
Understood!
I must face the north
and masturbate...
Unreal!
You idiot! How can I
concentrate?!
I'm sorry.
It's just that I haven't seen
this for a while!
Your Majesty! Maria!
Oh, Yaku.
I heard of the troubles
in the Shikima!
Thank you for coming.
Where's Miko?
She's with Fubuki, pursuing
the Anti-Shikima.
-Your Majesty!
-Darling!
What's going on?!
It's the cursed male flute
of the Anti-Shikima.
Kyoshiro Karimara must've
entered the Shikima realm!
Kyoshiro?
-An intruder!
-Follow the flute!
Yaku!
Miko!
Mother!
Play the female flute!
But that means you'll...!
I think that's the only way to
stop the male flute!
Miss Maria!
Miko, hurry!
Hurry!
Yes.
Stop it!
Stop playing that flute!
First among of the
Mido, Yaku!
Your enemy!
Fubuki!
Miko!
Give me back that flute!
Why are you crying?
Why do you cry?
-What makes you so sad?
-Stop! Please stop!
Are you a friend or foe?
Why these tears?
Please, give me back
my Hidemasa.
Hidemasa? Who's Hidemasa?
Stop! Stop playing that flute!
You bitch!
Miko!
I can't defeat him.
Fubuki!
Do you recognize me?
Your Majesty!
What happened to me?
You were possessed by
Kyoshiro.
You almost tried to kill me!
Miko!
I'm so glad you're all right.
I see. So that's what was
happening with Miko.
It didn't seem like her,
the way she was handling it.
Miko seems to be back to her
normal self.
That's good!
But Your Majesty!
Why does the female flute
drive Kyoshiro mad?
When he died raging with
hatred...
...the female flute of
Shanahime was playing.
Love and hatred battle
with the sound of the flute.
You understand Kyoshiro's
weakness.
I am originally
of the Mido clan.
I know the secret
workings of the two flutes.
I can't imagine Kyoshiro
giving up so easily.
I'll get him next time for
certain, and redeem myself!
That's more than you can
handle!
What are you saying?
I never make the same
mistake twice.
Leave this one to me!
You both have a special
attachment...
...to the person Kyoshiro has
possessed.
You're not right
for the job.
That's true.
I'll destroy Kyoshiro!
Wait a second.
What's with you? Insecurities
about your large breasts?
Take back what you said
about my breasts!
You flat-chested wench!
Flat-chested?!
That's a low blow!
Cut it out!
We have to join forces
to fight the Anti-Shikima!
This is not the time for us to
bicker amongst ourselves.
Listen well to Miko.
She must be strong and
overcome her first love.
It could save the boy's life.
Call Miko.
You three must
work together...
...to defeat Kyoshiro,
with his magical powers.
Something awful has
happened to Miko!
What is it?
I can't find her anywhere!
Miko!
Shanahime.
Shanahime, why did you
betray me?
Why?!
Where's that gift
from Shanahime?
The essence of your being
intoxicates me.
Why did you betray me?
Those tears.
Shanahime?
If you are the real
Shanahime, tell me the truth.
I want to know the truth.
Kyoshiro.
Like you, I was also used as a
pawn by the Shikima.
What?!
That despicable Shikima!
I want revenge!
Please listen to what I have
to say!
The Karimara fortress!
Oh Kyoshiro! Kyoshiro!
If you've escaped somehow...
Please answer me with
your male flute.
Kyoshiro...
Kyoshiro!
Shanahime!
You made it out alive!
I hoped to see you!
I was betrayed by the
Shikima, and almost killed.
The Shikima?
That's right.
They envied that I'd rule
the world and the Shikima.
The King and my father
conspired against me.
They used our engagement
as a pretext.
If I joined with you,
of the royal line...
...I would have gained the
power to ward off the King.
And if that happened, I would
have become invincible.
Kyoshiro!
You're the only
one I'll ever love!
Now's our chance!
We'll pledge our love,
and get back at them!
Kyoshiro!
We'll use our love to take
revenge!
Shanahime!
Kyoshiro! Come to me!
Come to me!
Is this what you want?
Yes!
That symbol of our love.
I want it within me!
Who are you?!
What are you saying?
That isn't Kyoshiro's penis!
What?!
I am Shanahime, of the
royal line!
Don't you think I'd recognize
Kyoshiro's member?!
Bitch! I won't let you go!
I'll force you to take this,
if I have to.
Submit to me!
I'll make you mine,
no matter what.
Then I'll reign over the
Shikima and the world!
King of the Shikima!
You tricked me!
You bitch!
Give me back my member!
You fucking bitch!
Kyoshiro!
You bastard, Shikima King!
You made me think
Shanahime had betrayed me!
I'm so angry!
I'm so angry, Kyoshiro!
I want to claim my revenge
with you!
The King and the Shikima
destroyed our relationship.
They deserve our revenge!
I was such a fool!
Is there any way to bring you
back to life?
With women's honey-essence
in the spider kettle...
...and the curse of the Anti-Shikima,
I will be returned.
Shanahime.
I will claim our revenge!
Where's Miko?
Can't find her.
Where are we?
The Shikima have
already searched this park.
But they've got to be around
here!
The Chidori incense urn.
It's a rare antique.
I thought you'd like it.
Why do you cry?
Why are you crying?
If Kyoshiro used Hidemasa's
body to come back...
...then killing Kyoshiro
means killing Hidemasa.
What should I do?
In order to protect Father,
Mother and the Shikima...
...Fubuki and Yaku will be
forced to fight to the death.
Along with the other Shikima
people.
In that case, I must deal with
Kyoshiro myself.
I can't let everybody
be destroyed.
Miss Miko!
Nin-Nin!
I knew you'd be here!
I saw the Chidori urn was
missing...
...so I figured you'd brought
it here to Hidemasa's!
Nin-Nin! Will you help me?
I don't want anybody else to
lay a finger on him.
Miko.
I know you better than
anyone else.
Thanks, Nin-Nin.
Miko! That Chidori urn!
What about it?
We can use it to summon
Hidemasa's soul...
...that Kyoshiro stole.
What do you mean?
Bathe in the fragrance
of this incense.
If only Hidemasa can
recognize that fragrance...
...then the curse might
be broken.
Let me see that urn!
What are you doing?
Finding out what kind of
incense has been used.
Let's see.
I wonder if we can find
the same type.
This urn is from
the Tensho Era.
Hidemasa said it was
rare and valuable...
...so the incense is probably
expensive and hard to find.
The matron who died
ran an incense shop.
Didn't you know?
She did?
I'll search everywhere
and see if I can find her.
Good luck, Nin-Nin!
Leave it to me!
If we can rescue Hidemasa's
soul from Kyoshiro...
...we'll be able to break the
curse of the Anti-Shikima.
Grandma! Help me!
Lend me your power!
Yes!
That feels so good!
Shanahime Lady Blue!
I can't play this flute.
I cannot bring such suffering
to Maria.
Yaku.
We will have to rely on your
sense of smell.
The Shikima guards out
searching haven't returned...
...and we still can't find
Miko and Nin-Nin.
Please!
We'll have to wait for
the full moon.
There!
That came from Yaku!