Miss Miko! Wait!
Miss Miko!
This blizzard of leaves isn't
fair.
You can't try to get rid of me
and go off by yourself.
I have express orders from
His Majesty and Maria.
Even if you're the heiress
of the Mido family...
...following your clan's ancient
traditions...
...you must still go to college
like a normal woman.
Are you listening to me, Miko?!
I hear you.
Just shut up for a minute.
I'll get back to my classes.
First I want to try the secret
leaf reading.
Read the leaves?
What for?
Like I said, it's a secret!
You won't even tell me?
Not fair!
How can I look out for you...
...unless you tell me
everything?!
''Predictions about
first love''?
You idiot! Don't look!
There's nothing to be
embarrassed about.
You don't know a thing
about a woman's feelings.
That might be true, but still...
Think about it.
Ever since that incident with
my grandma...
...I've been stuck in the
Shikima Realm...
...living a life of perversion.
I haven't had time to enjoy
my life as a woman.
Yes, but that's your fate.
Don't you feel sorry for me?
I am a woman after all.
Why can't I experience first
love at least once or twice.
First love is just once.
Don't nit-pick! Get off my
back and quit bugging me!
I wanted to do this since I got
back from the Shikima realm.
All right!
It says that I'm about to meet
the man of my dreams.
I'm choking! Miko, are you
sure it doesn't mean me?!
How could you possibly be
the man of my dreams?!
What's going on?
Wait! What on earth is this?
What's up, Miko?
You keep sighing.
Well, you know.
Got a crush on someone, huh?
No way!
You're blushing, Miko.
So who is it? Just tell me.
I promise not to tell.
I told you, you're wrong.
Something's up.
What are you gossiping about?
Miko says she's fallen in love!
Who?!
No, you're wrong!
There's nothing to hide!
Just tell us!
Yeah, she's right!
Who is it?
Nobody.
It's tough looking for love
like this.
Everyone else at college
seems to have someone.
And then there's me.
I can't even find someone I like,
let alone love.
Even my leaf divination
trick isn't coming true.
Rain?
Oh no!
I'm gonna get drenched!
You all right?
Yes.
Wanna get up?
Oh, I'm sorry!
That rain sure was sudden.
Doesn't look like it's gonna
let up, either.
Miss Miko!
I was just coming to get you.
Just when things were
going great.
You know him?
Yes. He's my little brother.
Loves to play ninja.
He's such a handful.
See?
That's what happens
when you play rough.
Where does it hurt? You'll be fine.
It's nothing serious.
Thanks, I'm all right now.
Go wait for me upstairs.
Miko.
Um.
If you'd like,
I can lend you this.
No, I'd feel bad.
No, really.
I'm home now.
I know you need it, and
we have lots upstairs anyway.
Please take it.
Here, really.
Okay, I'll borrow it.
I can't let this package here
get wet.
Don't worry, you can bring it
back any time.
Thank you.
I promise I'll bring it back.
What's your apartment
number?
Room 901 . I'm Miko Mido.
I'm Hidemasa Matsunaga. I go
to Tensho University.
After I've dropped this scroll
off to a client...
I'll bring back your umbrella.
Okay.
Is that a scroll in there?
I appraise antiques, just as my
deceased father did.
It might seem like a weird
interest for someone my age.
No, I think it's wonderful!
Look at me, going on
about myself.
You should hurry and
get out of those wet clothes.
Don't want to catch a cold.
See you.
I won't forgive you, Miko!
It feels so good!
Sanae? Aren't you finished
changing yet?
Sanae?
Come on, what's taking you?
What?!
No!
That's so good!
I'll give you
even more pleasure.
Oh, yes!
You belong to me now!
Kyoshiro! I'm coming to you!
I'm coming!
Hey, Nin-Nin.
I thought I just heard a flute.
Where? What? You're just
imagining things, Miko.
Really? That's strange.
Miko.
You'll be late for college.
What are you doing?
I was wondering if we have
any good antiques in here.
Antiques?
Yes, so I can get Hidemasa
to appraise it for me.
Hidemasa?
That guy you met outside?
Yeah.
Or else he'll just bring back
the umbrella...
...and I won't see him again.
To think you've got the hots
for a pansy like that.
He's the first guy who's
ever made me feel this way.
And considering that you
already have me here.
What are you sulking about?
There's nothing wrong with
me falling in love.
How do you know this is love?
My heart's been going
pitter-patter since I met him.
Where? Let's see!
Ouch!
What are you doing,
you pervert!
Keep your dirty hands off!
I'm saving myself
for Hidemasa.
Oh, Miko!
Help me, Nin-Nin!
Can you go find some
kind of antique...
...to help me with my
first love?
All right? Pretty please?
No way.
I see! Well you've got nothing
to be jealous about!
I want to lose my virginity to
the one I love...
...just like anybody else.
Virginity?
But you won't help me.
All right!
If you refuse to help me...
...then just stay out of my way!
You faked crying!
If Hidemasa comes to return the
umbrella while I'm at college...
...don't you dare accept it.
I want to take it myself.
I know!
Nin-Nin!
Just pretend you're not home!
Pretend?
See, I told you,
you're late for college.
You're just going to have to
wait until I get back.
I'm in love, and I'm not going
to let even you get in the way!
So this is what first love is like,
so painful.
He was worried about me
catching a cold.
Maybe he caught a cold himself
and he's sick in bed.
This is terrible, not being able
to see him.
Kimie and Sanae skipped out.
Do you know what's going on?
No.
I've got my own problems
to think about.
I'm back!
Did the doorbell ring?
Did Hidemasa come?
Hi! You're back.
Fubuki!
Here I thought you were
studying so hard...
...but instead you've gone
and fallen in love.
Well uh...
Nin-Nin! You blabber mouth!
There's nothing to be
embarrassed about!
So, what's he like?
Can I meet him?
But this has nothing
to do with you.
I'm not going to steal him
away from you.
How far have you gotten
with him? A kiss? Or...?
A kiss?!
Don't be stupid!
What are you thinking?!
It's not like that at all.
I just lent him my umbrella.
Is that all?!
Don't make fun of me. What'd
you come here for, anyway?
I got so wrapped up in
Nin-Nin's jealousy...
...that I completely forgot
what I came for.
The Anti-Shikima?
That's right.
Many strange things have
been going on in the Shikima.
Maria says that it's a sign of
the Anti-Shikima's curse.
Have you ever heard
of the Anti-Shikima?
No.
So what's going on in
the Shikima realm?
Well...
Darling! What's happened?
Your Majesty!
Get a hold of yourself!
A strange flute has been
sounding throughout the realm.
The sound of the flute...
...has been affecting his
phallus.
Father?
The flute strangely resounds
through the Shikima...
...and forebodes the revived hatred
of the Anti-Shikima...
...stemming from an incident
that happened 400-years-ago.
Four hundred years ago
would mean...
The middle of the warring
states period!
Somehow that haunting flute
was recently discovered.
And if it's played in this world,
its power is amplified...
...causing psychic activity in
the Shikima realm.
That's what's been causing
His Majesty's suffering.
I wonder if that's the same
flute that I heard.
I thought it was
my imagination.
Have you noticed any
strange things happening?
Oh no!
Are you so caught up in your
first love...
...that you don't notice these
things anymore?
Well!
For once, I was just trying to
be a normal college student...
...and that's all I've been
thinking about.
Fubuki! You mustn't be
so hard on Miko.
Nin-Nin.
I know I might have been
jealous...
...but it's not like I don't
understand how you feel.
Really Nin-Nin? Thank you!
This is Hidemasa Matsunaga.
Would Miko Mido be in?
It's him! What should I do?
How come you're so flustered?
You're hilarious!
Hello.Just a moment.
Relax, Miko.
Since when are you so bashful?
You've been waiting for
him all this time!
Come on!
But, what should I do?
Well hello!
Hi!
Thanks for the umbrella.
Not at all.
Please accept this as a small
token of my appreciation.
All I did was lend you
my umbrella.
But thanks to you, I kept that
package from getting wet.
It was valuable, so I really
appreciated it.
So please, accept this.
Well, thank you.
Please, don't make a big deal
about it. It's really nothing.
Why don't you open it up?
Wow, look at this!
It's a Chidori incense urn.
It has quite a history.
I don't deserve something
so valuable.
I thought you'd like it.
Thank you.
I have to stop by another place,
so I'd better be on my way.
He's great, Miko!
Got it!
What are you trying to
do to me, Fubuki?
Sorry!
But what a nice urn it is!
Wow! It's the first time a
man's given me a present.
I can't stand this anymore!
I'm impressed, Miko!
If you didn't want him,
I'd sure take him!
Fubuki!
Don't worry! Think I'm going
to steal him away from you?
I just might!
I'll never forgive you if
you do!
Just kidding.
Don't get so mad.
Besides, we really
have to find out...
...what's up with the
Anti-Shikima.
You'll have to put that love
of yours on the back burner.
Nin-Nin! Don't take your
eyes off Fubuki!
We have work to do, but we'll
still have to watch her.
You bet! Anything for you!
My one chance to see
Hidemasa again...
...and I wasn't able to get
any further with him!
I thought you'd like it.
How embarrassing!
Fubuki! What's going on?
The sound of the flute!
It's burning me up!
Miko!
What are you doing to Miko?!
Miko! Get a hold of yourself!
Miko? Are you all right?
You're awake.
Fubuki! Nin-Nin!
What happened to me?
Thank goodness!
You were being assaulted
by a hideous old ghost!
That's right.
I heard the strange sound
of a flute in the bath...
...and this weird sensation
came over my body.
How embarrassing!
You weren't the only one.
It happened to me, too!
It must be the female flute
of the Anti-Shikima!
Female flute?
That's right.
Maria said there's a
female flute.
It responds to the male flute
that's been torturing the King.
In this world, the flute makes
a strange, intoxicating sound...
...that brings forth an amorous
rapture in virginal women.
But for the Queen...
...the sound of the flute
causes unbearable pain.
Mother?!
With the sound of that flute
just now, Maria was...
Hang on, Maria!
The effect must've been
amplified in the Shikima...
...and no doubt caused her
great suffering!
If we can't get the flutes
back from the Anti-Shikima...
...we can't save Mother and
Father from their suffering!
Right.
But how are we going to find
this Anti-Shikima?
The flutes are steeped in an
ancient curse.
Miko. Hidemasa is familiar
with antiques.
I wonder if he'd know
anything about this.
But I don't know
where he lives.
How about his university?
It's Tensho University.
Let's go!
There'll be nobody there
at this hour.
This is our chance then!
We'll find out his address
from the university!
Let's get going!
It must be that estate
over there.
He sure lives in a big place.
I wonder if he's there.
Miko, what are you so
tense about?
Forget about your crush
on him for now.
We have to save the Shikima
and His Majesty.
I know.
This is the end of
my relationship.
As soon as he finds out I'm the
the Shikima King's daughter...
...he won't want anything
to do with me.
Matsunaga
Who's there?
The food lady?
Excuse me. It's me, Miko.
Miko!
Hidemasa! Are you sick?
I haven't been feeling well
since last night.
What are you doing?
And what's with that get-up?
Don't laugh.
We have our reasons.
Well, come in.
The lady who brings me my
meals isn't here yet...
...but I can offer you
some tea.
Don't bother, you're too sick!
Thank you. Sorry about that.
I know this might seem like
an odd thing to ask.
Do you know of a 400-year-old
legend about a flute?
Do you mean the male and
female flutes?
Yes! You know about them!
Recently, I was cleaning up
the storehouse...
...and I stumbled across
one of them.
I only found the male flute.
I tried to play it, but I heard
another flute...
...as if it were answering.
But I'd feel sharp chest pains...
...so I stopped playing it.
And then I heard the
other flute calling me.
The female flute.
I think so.
Thank you.
I found an old book that
described the male flute...
...and mentioned the existence
of another flute.
But how come you know
about those flutes?
Well, I might as well
tell you the whole story.
That's the same flute
from last night!
That weird flute!
Hidemasa!
Miko! Fubuki!
What's going on?!
Nin-Nin!
Kyoshiro! I love you!
My beloved Kyoshiro!
Where are you, my Kyoshiro?
I will take revenge on
the Shikima.
Come back to life,
my beloved Kyoshiro!
Awake! Awake!
Who calls me?
Take this!
Know the depths of my
karmic suffering!
Why?!
Why are you doing this?!