I have an important mission
for you.
In order for the Carnal
Underworld to reign supreme...
it is necessary to install
Lord Onimaro as ruler...
and to turn the mortal world into
a carnal world of debauchery.
I see.
However,
before that's possible...
we will have to eliminate
the ones who protect Onimaro...
the cursed Amatsu twins
of the Amatsu clan.
This is the plan.
I will have you,
Kurodama-Hoshi...
the most heinous sorcerer of
the Carnal Underworld...
eradicate Ai and Mai Amatsu
from the face of the earth.
It will be my pleasure.
I will remain
in the Carnal Underworld.
Missing Dialogue.
- Kurodama-Hoshi...
- Yes, Master.
You must complete your task
by the time I have taken...
another one hundred pure virgins.
May you enjoy your pleasure.
Ai Amatsu! Mai Amatsu!
Whether you are dead or alive...
you can be sure that my rod...
will churn inside you until the
agonizing orgasm of death!
Inju Seisen Twin Angels
OAV 3 & 4
Original Fansub: #hentai-legacy@irc.rizon.net
Timing & Edits: elgringo14@www.abika-online.com
Have a good trip.
- Well, then, grandmother...
- Ai, Mai.
Don't forget what I told you.
Don't worry.
You're always after us about it.
It's burning our ears.
You are leaving the Tenjin shield,
after all.
You will have to be extremely careful.
Don't worry.
It's only three days and two nights.
That's right.
And we're going to the
Sanuki Tenjin Shrine, after all.
I'm sure the Tenjin spirit will be
watching over us.
I hope so.
Oh, no!
All the freshmen should be
waiting by now.
We'd better hurry.
- Be very careful.
- See you later!
May Lord Tenjin guard
and protect you!
If we're late, we'll never be asked
to be group leaders again!
So, those two are
the Amatsu sisters?
This may not be fair to
Lord Oniyasha-Doji...
but first I will get my fill and
rape and ravage them...
to my heart's content!
Hey! Dekunobo!
Let me out of here!
You must stay right where you are,
Young Master.
It looks like
you're planning to go on a trip.
Where on earth
were you planning on going?
Where do you think?!
I'm going on a journey together
with Ai and Mai!
But you can't do that.
Both Ai and Mai...
were picked as group leaders on
an important freshman class trip.
They would not have the time
to deal with you.
I'm just going to tag along!
That's all!
I won't cause them any trouble!
Master...
Okay, okay.
Everyone settle down.
I have your room assignments here.
I've made copies.
The schedule's on there, too.
So make sure you review it.
Pass them back.
Everybody, listen up.
We'll all be staying in the sleeping
quarters of the Tenjin shrine.
It's not a hotel or inn,
so make sure to behave yourselves...
in a manner that reflects the
reputation of Tenjin College.
- All right.
- Excuse me, I have a question!
What is it?
We know that
you and Mai are twins...
but who is the big sister?
Can't you tell?
The cuter one is the younger!
Thank you.
You two are a big help.
Don't mention it!
You just have to go along
for the ride.
You can leave everything to us.
We went last year,
so we know what to do.
It's nice to be able to rely on you.
This is my first year as a teacher,
after all.
- I appreciate it.
- No problem.
Trips like these sure are fun.
Right, Ai?
Even if it's just to get away
from that little brat.
Don't say that too loud.
Prince Onimaro is our sworn master.
Who cares.
I wonder
how my Lord Onimaro is doing.
He may be annoying to have around,
but when he's not...
I worry about him
like he was my kid brother.
Ai, Mai! Why did you leave me?
Hey, kid. What's the matter?
I can't find my Mommy!
- He's adorable!
- Sure is!
So cute!
- Do you live far from here?
- That way!
Fine, get in.
We'll take you home.
Really? Thank you!
Missing Dialogue.
Master!
Master, where are you!
Dekunobo, is Lord Onimaro
missing again?
I thought that he was taking a nap.
We must all go
and search for him.
Madam Genshu!
Lord Onimaro's
backpack is missing!
What?!
He must've gone after Ai and Mai
to Shikoku.
But I'm sure he wouldn't know
how to get there.
He'll use his nose to find them.
Missing Dialogue.
Then he's going after
Ai and Mai's scent?
Exactly.
If there's something he likes...
he'll track it down all across
Japan with his nose.
Get in touch with Ai and Mai
and let them know.
Yes, ma'am.
Missing Dialogue.
I'll go and get him.
Hey, kid, would you like
some soda?
How about some cookies?
Or perhaps an apple?
Missing Dialogue.
Hey, kid.
What's your name, anyway?
- Oh. Uh, I'm Ohnny.
- Oh, how cute!
Let me feel your cheeks.
Wow!
They're so soft and smooth!
Missing Dialogue.
What was that?!
I saw some kind of shadow!
Who knows...
Master!
Missing Dialogue.
We're here from Tenjin College.
Oh, yes. I'll be right there.
Well, well.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Thanks for having us again.
Thank you.
Come in and
make yourselves at home.
The bath is all ready for you...
if you'd like to freshen up
after your journey.
I'm Miss Sakurai,
the teacher in charge.
This is my first time
as a field trip leader.
I hope you can bear with me.
Don't worry. Ai and Mai are
old friends of this shrine.
So, please feel rest assured.
Sure. Thank you very much.
Um, sir?
Yes? What is it?
Oh, uh... It's nothing.
I thought you were someone else.
Master, how far have you gone?
Missing Dialogue.
- Are you sure this is all right?
- Yeah.
Missing Dialogue.
Take care.
Bye, bye, you gorgeous babes.
All aboard! Last ferry!
Ai, Mai! I'll be with you soon!
Hold on, I'm coming.
Hello. Yes,
you've reached the Tenjin Shrine.
Yes. Ai and Mai Amatsu?
They should be arriving shortly.
As soon as they get in...
I'll ask them to give you a call.
Sure. It's my pleasure.
Good-bye.
Why was Sanuki picked
for our field trip?
There're Tenjin Gods
all over the country.
Oh, come on. Don't you know?
This is the land
where Sugawara Michizane...
first set foot and
began to preach his ways.
Wow. You sure know a lot.
Actually, I asked Ai Amatsu that
just a while ago.
I thought so.
Hey, look at that painting
of Lord Michizane there.
It seems like those eyes are
staring right at us.
You fool. You'll be cursed
if you say things like that.
We have to eat bland
shrine food again?
I was hoping for something
a bit better this time.
Hey, Mai?
The priest's gold teeth.
Weren't they further back
in his mouth?
What? How could I remember
something like that?
Right... Maybe I'm just
imagining things.
It's not like I check out people's
teeth to make sure who they are.
And also, one more thing.
Can't you smell something
about that priest?
Come to think of it...
Hey! He makes us eat
this lousy shrine food...
and he's probably off eating
garlic steak or something!
That's not what I meant.
That stink isn't from food.
Maybe he hasn't taken a bath.
Yeah, right...
No, he smells like a barnyard animal.
That's it.
You're thinking too much.
Thinking too much about this.
I'm ready for my bath.
Then, we'll eat.
Well, well. Miss Sakurai.
- How can I help you?
- Well...
You'll have to excuse me if I heard
wrong about what you said.
Now, what is this about?
Well, I believe there was
a telephone call earlier...
Oh, yes, yes...
And you said that the
Amatsu twins hadn't arrived yet.
- No.
- Is that so.
The two are clearly here.
I thought maybe you told them
that they hadn't arrived.
Well...
I'll switch it to the public phone
over here. Please wait there.
What are you doing?!
What are you trying to do, sir?!
Please! Stop it! Please!
It's too late,
now that you've heard.
I was going to kill you right away...
But that would be such a waste,
with that body of yours.
I can still get a
good taste of you first.
Your mouth may say no.
But your pussy says yes,
as you can see.
I'll take you to a world of pleasure.
Please, no...!
That orb of orgasm will soon
start to take effect.
And I'll be sure to take
good care of you.
That feels so good.
That's funny.
I dialed this number a dozen times
but I can't get through.
Maybe this phone
doesn't even work.
Forget about the stupid phone.
I just need a bath!
- Have Ai and Mai called back yet?
- Not yet.
They should've arrived by now.
What could've happened?
Dekunobo, hurry!
- It's so quiet.
- Yeah.
I mean it's too quiet.
On the bus those freshmen just
wouldn't shut up...
They took note of your warning.
They're just behaving
as you told them to.
I hope you're right.
Come on. We'd better get out
and head back.
It wouldn't be fair to those
starving freshmen waiting for us.
I wonder if Miss Sakurai has
had her bath yet.
Yeah, really.
I wonder what she's doing.
Sis...?
Lord Onimaro!
Missing Dialogue.
- Nevertheless...!
- What do you think?
I... I...
I came here because I was worried
about you and wanted to protect you!
No one asked you to!
Missing Dialogue.
- Why are you so angry?!
- Wait!
Missing Dialogue.
- Lord Onimaro!
- Wait up!
No way!
She's really angry at me!
Of course I am!
Well, does that feel good?
It feels so good...
Take me from behind. Please...
You slut.
How's this?! How's this?!
Yes!
You will never be able to live
without my rod.
- Lord Onimaro!
- What?
- Did I hear Lord Onimaro?
- Please, don't stop!
I need more. More...
- Wait, you little punk!
- No way! No way! No way!
Missing Dialogue.
More...
What have you done
to Miss Sakurai?
Who are you?!
You're not the real priest here!
I am the greatest sorcerer
of the Carnal Underworld...
I am Kurodama-Hoshi!
I didn't think Lord Onimaro
would be coming here.
Missing Dialogue.
The orb of orgasm,
the special tool of this sorcerer.
All who take the orb shall
succumb to eternal orgasm.
Even you two will eventually
become like this.
Mai! Don't look at the orb!
You'll fall for his sorcery!
Do you want to feel pain?!
- It's the priest!
- What?!
Please... More... More...
Why, you!
My orbs of orgasm...
I'll make you eat them like she has!
Ai!
You shall succumb
to the carnal pleasure!
Mai!
[Start of OAV 4]
Hold it!
I'm not going to let you
touch my women!
What the...?!
- Mai!
- Ai!
You're not getting away!
Missing Dialogue.
Ai! What about the Freshmen?!
Where?! Where are they?!
You guys! Where are you?!
Ai! Mai!
- Lord Onimaro!
- Ai! Mai!
In the bathhouse!
- Lord Onimaro!
- Where are you?!
Ai!
Mayumi!
Emi!
Yukari!
Th-This is horrible!
All of these women have
already fallen under my spell.
Without the carnal pleasures...
that writhe within their
mouths and pussies...
they will no longer be able to live.
There you are!
Lord Onimaro!
I'm dizzy... I feel dizzy, Mai...
How detestable!
Say what you will.
Without pleasure,
what are their lives worth?
Their lives will be used to
bring about carnal ecstasy!
Enough with your garbage!
It's human nature.
Abandon your body to carnal
pleasure. Your resistance is futile.
I don't want to hear any more!
I will spare their lives if you are
willing to submit yourselves...
as sex slaves to Lord Oniyasha-
Doji of the Carnal Underworld!
Or else...
Take a look.
Watch the orbs placed in the
mouths and pussies of your friends.
What have you done to them?!
Eventually,
in the climax of ecstasy...
the orbs that are swallowed...
will expand and expand
in the womb until they burst!
- No!
- Then come with me!
As carnal brides to Lord Oniyasha-Doji
of the Carnal Underworld!
I'd rather die!
Missing Dialogue.
Stop it!
- Ai!
- I'll go!
So, let my sister and
these women go free!
No! I'll go!
I don't want you to go, Ai!
Mai...
Such a beautiful display
of sisterly love.
But I need both of you to
come together.
Missing Dialogue.
Fine. We'll both go.
But you have to return our teacher
and friends' bodies back to normal.
Fine.
Missing Dialogue.
Get them!
Mai!
Wait!
Lord Onimaro!
Don't you dare touch my women!
I'll go!
So, let go of Ai and Mai!
Otherwise...
Missing Dialogue.
Oh, my...
Lord Onimaro...
What are you just
standing there for?!
I am here to serve you.
I will submit to your will,
Lord Onimaro.
Good.
Now get away from those two.
Missing Dialogue.
But the Amatsu twins have
made us suffer greatly.
As a lesson,
I will take them outside!
What?!
I have my pride as a sorcerer
who has been given...
full powers
by Lord Oniyasha- Doji.
Whether they live or die, as one
who gives himself up for them...
I hope you can accept
the consequences.
The Bridge to Heaven
of Mahoroba...
By the powers of the crest
entrusted to the heavenly nymphs.
Fall gently... Fall gently...
I pray to thee to protect
my granddaughters,
the guardians of Tenjin.
I pray to you!
Master!
Ai! Mai!
Missing Dialogue.
What are you going to do with
Lord Onimaro?!
We won't forget this!
After I deliver Lord Onimaro,
I will return to ravage you slowly.
Until then, you can enjoy
the orb of orgasm...
and let your bodies melt
as you spill forth in ecstasy.
Keep a good watch on them
and enjoy!
Missing Dialogue.
Another one dies.
Next!
Lord Oniyasha-Doji,
there is not one left.
What?! None left?!
How many was that?
That was 96.
Missing Dialogue.
I suppose I'll have to go out
and get some more myself!
It's so wet,
the amulet is coming loose.
This one's so wet,
I think it'll drop out anytime!
Ow! What was that?!
That's...!
Ai! Mai!
What a shameful display.
Dekunobo!
We can't just sit here. We have to
go to the Carnal Underworld!
Then, Master's been...
But how, Ai?
Ai! Mai!
Grandmother's calling!
The holy statue...!
Grandmother!
Gently falling...
I pray to the Amatsu Tenjin god!
Break the spell that has been cast
upon my granddaughters.
And give them
the power of the crest!
Gently falling... Gently falling...
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten!
Fall gently upon them!
Grandmother!
- Is that Ai?
- Yes.
What about Mai?
I'm right here.
My prayers have
reached the heavens.
The Carnal Underworld can be
fought with the Plum Cyclone.
Can you see outside?
The plum...
The plum blossoms...!
How could the plum blossoms be
blooming now?
Grandmother!
The plum blossoms... The plum
blossoms are coming out in full!
I did it.
Ai, Mai...
Now is the time to realize
the value of all of your training.
With the power of the crest.
The ultimate Plum Cyclone!
The crest... The ultimate...
The Plum Cyclone!
Rise up!
Destroy the evil!
Well, Lord Oniyasha-Doji!
Well, well. Lord Onimaro!
What do you think,
Lord Oniyasha-Doji?
I'm impressed. To think you've
already brought him here.
Now that's a great sorcerer
of the Carnal Underworld!
Missing Dialogue.
With the orbs of orgasm that
I've placed within them...
they are all wet and
now only await to be pierced.
A sacrifice to the Underworld.
Well done. I will ravage them.
I will ravage them!
But this is out of season!
You pompous demon
of carnal pleasure.
The plum blossoms reveal the
weaknesses of carnal demons.
That voice!
Demons who sully the world...
The crest of the Amatsu
shall not forgive you!
Why, you! How did you...?!
- In the name of heaven...
- We shall destroy evil!
Why, you!
The ultimate power of the crest!
The Plum Cyclone!
Mai!
Lord Oniyasha-Doji!
Please retreat!
Kurodama-Hoshi!
May your hundred
virgin rampage succeed...
and glory to the Carnal Underworld!
Take this!
Ai!
Now it's time for you to chew on
your own balls!
May you burst with ecstasy!
That feels good...
Why are you running
away from me?!
I'm the one who saved you two!
Missing Dialogue.
Don't be silly.
Let me do it!
I wanna do it!
Sorry, no Karaoke for the ending song.
Hope you enjoyed the shows in their true form :D