Shanahime.
How dare you betray me.
You shall now pay for what
you have done unto me.
Miss Miko!
Kyoshiro!
Miko!
You bitch!
Hidemasa!
I won't let you interfere!
Wow! Full frontal nudity!
Nin-Nin, don't be such a fool!
What are you
so excited about?!
Miko!
Hidemasa!
We've done well!
We got the female flute back!
I don't understand.
The man on the scroll
looked just like Hidemasa.
There could be a deep
connection between the two.
There must be.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
No mistaking it.
This is Danjo's female flute.
What do you mean?
It was about 400-years-ago...
...the Shikima asked the
Mido clan to find the flute.
One of two flutes they've been
desperately searching for.
400-years-ago?
That was when Oda Nobunaga
ruled.
That's right.
fought for supremacy...
...there was an evil man called
Danjo Matsunaga.
He betrayed Nobunaga and hid
in the Yamato mountains.
Matsunaga?!
Danjo?!
He poisoned the owner
of his refuge and led a revolt.
He subjugated Yoshiteru, the
Ashikaga Shogun...
...and burned down the hall
of the great Buddha.
He had even gained supremacy
over all of Kyoto.
It was the Shikima that
helped Danjo in his quest.
What?!
Danjo, indulging in some
debauchery as usual.
Gamara!
I've come from the Shikima
realm...
...in order to make a request
of you.
This time I need your help.
Anything to humiliate
Nobunaga...
...and take control away
from him.
You are indeed evil.
I'm thinking of launching
a coup in the Shikima...
...and taking the title of King
for myself!
Gamara!
This evening, I will kill your
son Kyoshiro Karimara...
...and take Shanahime from
the Karimara fortress.
What?!
There was a young man
called Kyoshiro Karimara...
...whose blood was the
melding of two realms.
The product of Danjo
and his wife...
...who had been offered to
him by the Shikima.
It's late!
Mother, will Shanahime come
to this fortress as my bride?
You must be patient, Kyoshiro.
It is an agreement between
your father and the Shikima.
As one who carries the line of
Danjo and the Shikima...
...you will no doubt be the
supreme ruler of this world...
...when you receive
Shanahime of the royal line...
...said to be the most beautiful
of the 3,000 realms.
If it worries you, just play
this male flute.
Shanahime will respond to you
with her female flute.
So the male and female Danjo
flutes are love flutes!
The beautiful lady that came
to Hidemasa's house was...?
Shanahime of 400-years-ago.
An ancient curse must have
called upon her.
That's right!
Hidemasa said he was cleaning
out the storehouse...
...when he came across the
male flute.
He must have played it.
And that's how he called
Shanahime.
Miko!
Isn't Hidemasa from the
Matsunaga family?
He must be a descendant of
Danjo, or rather Kyoshiro.
Is that right?
No, Kyoshiro was killed at
the Karimara fortress...
...before he could
pass on his seed.
Huh?!
Kyoshiro.
Can you hear it?
The sweet sound of
the female flute.
Mother.
Mother!
Father!
Danjo, have you
lost your mind?!
Mother!
You killed Mother!
Die, Kyoshiro!
With poison coursing through
your body...
...you won't be displaying that
renowned skill of yours.
Why...?
To betray the royal line.
We have joined forces with
Shanahime...
...who's ambition is to
control the world.
You... you treacherous
bastard!
You will have to die.
I cannot let you take
reign over the world.
I will make Shanahime mine!
Prepare to die, my son!
You betrayed me, Shanahime!
That's terrible!
Killing your own wife and son
to further your ambition!
What Shanahime did
was unforgivable!
But why would she join
forces with evil...
...to fight against the Shikima.
Shanahime was betrayed
by the Shikima.
That's the only possibility.
Was the Shikima King, my
father, alive back then?
Yes, it was just before he
took control of the Shikima.
The one who becomes King
can live 1 ,000 years.
When the previous king died
and the throne was empty...
...the Shikima began to
splinter apart.
Then what is the
Anti-Shikima?
It's a branch that
was destroyed...
...at the hands of your father.
Miko, that man in the scroll.
Does he resemble this man?
I thought so.
The image on the scroll is
Kyoshiro Karimara...
...who died 400-years-ago,
full of hatred.
There's no doubt about it.
Shanahime was also calling
him Kyoshiro.
Miko, Shanahime is trying to
bring Kyoshiro back to life.
Hidemasa is the necessary
sacrifice.
She'll return to take away
the female flute.
Besides, the male flute is at
Hidemasa's house!
We'll have to find her and
get Hidemasa back!
Miko!
Be careful!
Shanahime has powers...
...beyond our understanding.
Nin-Nin?
Nin-Nin? Where are you?
Hello? Excuse me?
Is Hidemasa in?
She's beautiful.
I wonder if she's Hidemasa's
girlfriend or something?
And who are you?
I'm Sayoko, his cousin.
When I spoke with him,
he said he was feeling ill.
I came to check on him.
Hidemasa isn't here.
Oh.
Miko!
Nin-Nin?
I found this tea kettle with
the flute, up in the storehouse.
It seemed important so I
brought it along.
-The Spider Kettle!
-Huh?!
That's the Spider Kettle I'd
asked Hidemasa to find.
It's an unusual tea kettle from
the Tensho Era.
Who are you?!
You may fool others...
...but you can't deceive us.
We're trained in the ways
of the Shikima.
Don't move.
Or I'll slice his throat.
Nin-Nin!
This is mine.
You've revealed yourself!
You hellish beast!
I will take your lives,
along with the female flute!
Be warned!
She got away!
This is terrible!
Sorry Miko!
The flute that causes
Father to suffer!
Miko, something about that tea
kettle worries me!
What if it creates another
disaster in the Shikima?!
You're right.
We'd better go to
the Shikima for now!
So Shanahime has taken the
Spider Kettle.
Father, what is Shanahime
trying to do anyway?
She's trying desperately to
bring Kyoshiro back to life.
The old lady said...
...that Kyoshiro died full
of hatred for Shanahime.
She wants to clear her name.
She's using the Anti-Shikima's
treasured Spider Kettle...
...in an attempt
to settle an old score.
You mean, she didn't
actually betray Kyoshiro?
I was vying for succession to
the Shikima throne then.
I bring news.
Danjo has betrayed
our arrangement...
...and has killed Kyoshiro
at Karimara!
What?
What about my sister?!
Karimara has burned down
and they're both dead.
You bastard, Gamara!
You betrayed us!
Find him! No matter where
he is!
Danjo will pay for this too!
Sir!
We tried desperately to bring
back order to this realm.
That's when we joined forces
with the Mido clan.
Look! Karimara fortress is
burning down!
The Karimara fortress!
Kyoshiro! Kyoshiro!
If you've escaped somehow...
please answer my flute.
Answer me with your
male flute.
Kyoshiro!
It is unclear what misfortunes
later fell upon Shanahime.
Some say she drowned in a
lake.
But I was not able to hear
the truth from Danjo.
Whatever Nobunaga may do...
...I have the power of
the Shikima behind me!
I'll never give up the
Spider Kettle.
Just watch!
If I drink the kettle's
secret potion...
...I'll become immortal
and acquire magical powers.
I will never give it up
to Nobunaga!
Danjo!
The King of the Shikima
has forsaken you!
Danjo perished at Shigisan
Castle in Yamato.
It is thought that the
Spider Kettle...
...coveted by Nobunaga, was
also destroyed in the fire.
But that was not true.
So in all the confusion,
the Spider Kettle was saved?
That's correct.
But for the past 400 years,
no one knew what came of it.
Those who revolted were
deemed the Anti-Shikima...
...and they were all destroyed.
But along with the curse, the
Spider Kettle had vanished.
So Shanahime got hold of the
amorous tea kettle?
The curse of the tea kettle will
be used...
...to bring Kyoshiro back to
life.
Miko!
You must stop Shanahime!
She is not of the real world.
To preserve her youth and
keep her human form...
...she'll destroy many women
to use their bodies!
Mother!
Miko, you must draw her out
with that female flute!
But...but this is the flute that
causes you so much suffering!
I'll bear it, if it means
putting her to rest forever.
Now hurry!
Maria! Your Majesty!
I promise to look after Miko!
-Thank you!
-Fubuki.
Guards! Protect the two from
the curse of the Anti-Shikima!
Help them find Shanahime!
Yes, Master!
Did you hear they found a
mummy in the locker room?
Yuck! That's gross!
Maybe it's Kimie or Sanae.
They're still missing, right?
What a predicament!
Oh, that fragrance!
It's coming from over there!
Kyoshiro.
The night is ours.
I've waited for you
over 400 years.
I was called by
your male flute.
The one who called me
back to this world...
...was one who so resembles
you, Hidemasa Matsunaga.
It is you, and yet it's not you.
But finally,
the Spider Kettle is mine.
I will sacrifice this
Hidemasa...
...with the power
of the Anti-Shikima.
I will bring you back to life.
Kyoshiro.
My body is so...
...my body is so on fire
for you.
Kyoshiro!
I love you!
I'll use the curse of the
Anti-Shikima...
...and the power of this
Spider Kettle...
...I will bring you to life.
I will!
What's that?!
Mummies at the college?!
She sucked the life out of
Kimie and Sanae...
...to hang on to her
own youth.
And to think I was right there!
This is awful!
Miko!
This isn't the time for crying!
We must concentrate all our
Shikima abilities...
...to track down Shanahime.
Fubuki.
Can you hear anything?
Fubuki's taken the Shikima
form, to be more vigilant.
I can hear it.
The call of the water fowl!
Kyoshiro's double.
I love you!
I can't stop myself.
The park.
Towards the Water Park!
Kyoshiro.
Feel my passion!
The flute.
It's the male flute! Come on!
Who plays my flute?
Kyoshiro!
It stopped!
I can't hear it anymore.
You go that way!
I'll head this way!
Okay!
Miss Miko!
Kyoshiro, it's me!
It's Shanahime!
Shanahime?
Shanahime! You betrayed me!
You're mistaken!
I implore you!
Listen to what I have to say!
I won't forgive you!
You betrayed my mother
and I. Puppet of evil.
I cannot forgive you.
I will never forgive you.
Kyoshiro.
That cry...
You shall be purged from all
existence...
...along with the Shikima
who destroyed me.
Prepare to die, Shanahime.
You treacherous beast!
I have no love for you!
Kyoshiro...!
Pathetic fool!
Miko!
Fubuki!
Hear that splashing sound?
Yeah, and I heard a woman's
cry just before that.
A victim! Shanahime must be
somewhere in this park!
Play the female flute!
That's all we have
to draw her out!
Miko! What's that?!
Kyoshiro Karimara!
He's come back!
That flute!
Stop playing that flute!
Miko!
Fubuki!
I have returned.
I will destroy the Shikima
from all of existence.