Ladies.
This is the Carnal Underworld.
You shall now become my love slaves
and indulge in licentious acts.
What the...?!
We are the Tenjin Guardians!
Angel Mai!
In the name of heaven,
we are the defenders of decency!
We shall drive away all evil!
Twin Dolls!
Inju Seisen Twin Angels
OAV 1 & 2
Original Fansub: #hentai-legacy@irc.rizon.net
Timing & Edits: elgringo14@www.abika-online.com
What a beautiful woman.
I wonder if she's a model.
You think?
Wait up, Ai!
- You useless ones.
- Well...
Is this a Guardian shield?
As you can see.
Make sure they don't make any noise.
Don't get noticed.
Yes, ma'am.
Make sure
you capture Lord Onimaro.
But with this Tenjin shield...
Don't rush it.
Wait for your opportunity.
What I need is sacrificial lambs
for the Carnal ritual.
I leave the rest to you.
I understand.
Master.
How many times have I told you
not leave the villa?
Hey, let me go!
I want to go to Tenjin College!
Missing Dialogue.
Let go! Let go! If you don't let go,
that's insubordination!
Please wait! Wait! Master!
Master!
Just lay off!
That's...
Gee. I wonder who's going to be
our teacher today?
I hear she's a brilliant scholar who
graduated tops from Tenjin University.
Then we can expect a totally
uptight intellectual type.
Hey! Ai, that's the woman
from this morning!
Come on. Sit straight.
You've got to sit straight.
I will be teaching this class
for a while.
I am Utako Daigo.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
My specialty is Japanese poetry.
As you are all aware,
the <i>1 00 Great Poems</i> ...
is a compilation of the work of
Japan's greatest poets.
Before we get started
with class today...
I'd like all of you to drink some
rather unusual tea that I've brought.
I'd like somebody to give me a hand.
- Let's see. Ai Amatsu?
- Yes.
- Mai Amatsu.
- Yes!
Come over here.
I will prepare the tea myself...
so I'll have Ai
pour it into the bowls.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
And I'll have Mai hand out
the sweets to everyone.
These sweets look so delicious.
- We might've met this morning.
- Yes!
Oh, my...
My lady!
What in the world is going on?
Well, my dear, Dekunobo,
take a look at this.
What? This is...?!
I do not know what this is...
it seems the ritual of the Carnal
Underworld is quickly approaching.
Listen carefully, Dekunobo.
No matter what happens, you must
not let Lord Onimaro out of the villa.
Well, actually.
I have no excuse for this.
But Lord Onimaro has left to go
and see Ai and Mai.
My lady!
We Tenjin Guardians are
three times the age of humans.
In other words,
in human time...
Lord Onimaro will undergo the
adulthood ritual when he is 21.
But isn't there a risk that...
half his heritage, the blood
of the Carnal Underworld...
will stir and take over his soul?
Then, are you saying he will
reach adulthood earlier...
as a result of the ritual of
the Carnal Underworld?
That's right.
If he were to attain adulthood through
the power of the Carnal Underworld...
then...
he will become the lord
of the carnal realm...
beyond all notions of
good and evil.
And he will throw this world...
and all other worlds
into a carnal hell.
Dekunobo...
we must make sure
Lord Onimaro is not taken.
Yes. Right away!
- You two go as well!
- Yes, ma'am!
Ma'am, it has the aroma
of some kind of herb.
Yes. It was said to be brought back
from China in ancient times.
It's an unusual type of tea.
It's very difficult to
get a hold of it here...
but we've been cultivating it...
in the herbology department
at Tenjin University.
Is that so?
It's good for your skin, too.
And for your diet, of course.
Oh, for my diet?
I wonder if I can lose some of
the fat around my waist.
Now that we've set the tone
for the class...
I'd like to begin my lecture on
Japanese poems.
There's no need to get all formal.
Let's enjoy this class
as we have some tea.
She's so beautiful!
When they say beauty and wit,
they must be talking about you.
The way you handle class is
wonderful, too.
- I think we might fall in love!
- Hey.
Ai! Mai!
I'm going to be seeing you soon!
Damn useless cretins!
Lord Onimaro finally
left the shield...
and has given us an opportunity
to capture him!
Something's weird.
This journey I take...
High atop
the golden Mount Tamuke...
Under a veil of shimmering maples,
the light of eternity shines...
This poem was written for the
eternal glory of Lord Tenjin.
In other words, a poem read by
Lord Michizane of Sugawara.
The meaning of this poem...
Could anyone tell me
what it means?
Ma'am, my body feels so hot...
Me, too... my body feels funny...
On the surface, it refers to autumn.
But it's more of an Indian summer.
It's okay.
Take your uniform off and relax.
Ma'am, how about I put on
the air conditioning...
Mai!
Air conditioning isn't very healthy.
We do have the windows open.
I'm sure we'll get a
nice, cool breeze soon.
No one is going to see.
Let's take our clothes off.
I'll go first.
All right?
The meaning of the poem is
about Lord Michizane...
when he traveled along the
border of Yamato and Yamashiro.
He wrote it
as a wish for a safe journey.
In the old days,
when crossing a border like that...
it was a custom to make a wish
and pray to the local god.
Ma'am, what are you going to do?
You all just have to relax.
Just as described in the poem...
I will lead you to a wonderful
world that's beyond description.
Stop it, Mai!
Th-This smell...!
Ai,
the smell of this nectar...
is the smell that flows from the
hidden valley within you.
You must stroke it nice and slowly
with your hands.
A beautiful smell will flow
from deep within.
S-Stop it, Mai!
Why are you the only one
not doing this, Ai?
It just feels so good...
Miss Utako, who in the world
are you, anyway?
Well, I've already told you.
An angel who will guide you to
the world of dreams.
Then you must be... you must be
from the Carnal Underworld!
Ai! Mai!
Reveal your identity!
How could you not succumb to the
power of the Carnal Underworld!
Ai, can you not feel?!
Hey, Ai! You're here!
Lord Onimaro!
Who are you?!
Fujiwara Tokihira!
I thought he died!
I am immortal.
I can change my face,
my appearance...
and resurrect myself
as many times as I want.
Get out of here, Lord Onimaro!
His real identity
is the Oniyashadoji!
I've been looking for you...
...Lord Oniyashadoji.
Missing Dialogue.
I will go ahead.
Ai! Mai!
Lord Onimaro!
You're up against me!
You take the sacrificial lambs.
I'll take Ai and Mai
and be right with you.
I won't let you!
That's enough.
What do you plan on doing
with everyone?!
Would you like to know?
They are to be the sacrifices
to the Carnal altar.
What?! But they're innocent!
Foolish one. You think
you can save them alone.
You and your sister shall also be
sacrificed to the altar!
Even your stubbornness,
when faced against me...
will give way and
turn you into a horny sex slave.
Well?
You say you don't like men,
but this is proof otherwise.
If you're going to kill me,
then just do it.
You want me to kill you?
I will only kill you
after I have had my fill...
and you are about to
reach your climax!
Well? Does that feel good?
How dirty!
Eventually,
your body and spirit will melt.
Mai!
Miss!
Damn Amatsu Guardians!
Miss Ai! Miss Mai!
You must go after them!
They've taken Lord Onimaro,
Dekunobo!
The Master?! Master!
Mai!
- Get a grip on yourself, Mai!
- Ai...
Don't tell me...
the amulet that grandmother
placed within your...
You didn't take it out, did you?
That was close.
Ai... Ai...
Master!
- Lord Onimaro!
Where could Master have gone?
(Long) Missing Dialogue.
Where could he have been taken?
- This smell...
- Is the smell of carnal pleasure.
Then, he's in here?
Master!
[Start of OAV 2]
My lady, please tell me,
are they going to be all right?
I have taken out as much of the
perverse poison as possible.
Hopefully,
they're out of danger, but...
it is a strong potion of the
Carnal Underworld.
If only I had been
a little bit faster...
they would never have to suffer
like they are now!
- Don't blame yourself.
- My lady...
Ai and Mai have powerful
Tenjin blood in their veins.
They'll be all right.
But...
Onimaro is who I'm really
worried about.
When I think of all the suffering
that he must be enduring...
I only wish he was suffering.
But, my lady...
If he is experiencing the sensual
ecstasy of the Carnal Underworld...
Lord Onimaro's heroic sexual
appetite may take him from us.
I'm so very sorry!
- Dekunobo...
- Yes, ma'am!
Do you think we are the only ones
who know the secret...
about Lord Onimaro?
Yes, ma'am.
Even Lord Onimaro himself
isn't even aware of it.
It is better that he doesn't know.
Listen to me.
I have something to tell you.
Our young Lord Onimaro,
whom we have sworn to guard...
is a direct descendant of
Michizane Sugawara.
In other words, Lord Tenjin.
As you all know...
Michizane was the son of a
wizard goddess.
And from that time on,
the ones dedicating themselves...
to guarding him
are the Tenjin Guardians.
It is the Amatsu clan that has
been charged with this duty...
as the successors
to a long line of Guardians.
But...
There was a horrible tragedy.
Lord Michizane was defeated by
the Fujiwara clan and banished.
After he died while in exile...
his celestial spirit returned to
seek vengeance on his oppressors.
To calm his rage, the Fujiwara,
which had banished Lord Michizane...
began to worship him
as the Tenjin god, but only...
with the help of
the Carnal Underworld.
And our Lord Onimaro is the
descendent of a woman...
with Lord Michizane's blood, and
the lord of the Carnal Underworld.
That is the secret that
has been handed down...
for generations through
the Tenjin Guardian clans.
It is the secret to
the ancestry of Lord Onimaro.
Missing Dialogue.
Although Lord Onimaro was taken
to the Carnal Underworld...
we do not have to fear
for his life...
since he was taken by those who
represent half his ancestry.
- But the problem is...
- The problem is...
when Master faces
the ritual of his adulthood.
Once that happens,
no one will be able to control him.
Lord Onimaro will then turn into
an evil and corrupt overlord.
Dekunobo.
Were Miss Ai and Mai's friends,
the women from the Tenjin College...
taken as well in order to
speed up the ritual process?
My lady!
No! I must consult
the Tenjin Shadow Calendar!
Miss!
Miss Ai! Miss Mai!
What happened?
Where's Lord Onimaro?
Grandmother!
In the sunlight,
it is the Tenjin Calendar.
In the moonlight, it becomes
the Tenjin Shadow Calendar!
Oh, my heavens!
Tonight is the night
of the Carnal Confluence...
when all the demented devil
spirits are at full power!
What!?
Where could Lord Onimaro be?!
Behind Tenjin College, deep in
the garden near the rock shrine!
But you can't get through that
with human power.
There must be some way to cross
the border into the next world.
Border...
The road across...
Ai!
Mai! It must be Lord Michizane's
poem we heard in class!
Feel the pleasure! Feel the pain!
You have come to
where you were meant to be!
Today we go beyond the borders.
To the pinnacle of pleasure.
Reaching the climax
of life and death.
Now!
Rejoice in lust!
Writhe in ecstasy!
Show the Carnal Underworld!
Missing Dialogue.
Miss Ai! Miss Mai! How can we
break through to the other side?
A poem!
Yes. Lord Tenjin's poem will
guide us on our way!
What?
- Mai.
- Right.
Lord Tenjin, please...
Please allow us to pass...
Missing Dialogue.
This journey I take...
High atop the golden...
Mount Tamuke...
Under a veil of
shimmering maples...
The light of eternity shines...
This journey I take...
High atop the golden...
Mount Tamuke...
Under a veil of
shimmering maples...
Have mercy
on your loyal Pilgrims.
You cannot pass...
You cannot pass.
What path is this?
It is the path of Lord Tenjin.
Those with no business here
cannot pass.
Miss Ai! Miss Mai!
Feel the pleasure. Feel the pain!
Missing Dialogue.
Give us the carnal powers,
so we may rule the universe!
Missing Dialogue.
As you take part in this
great carnal ritual...
you will reach heights of
pleasure like you never have.
Now it is your turn,
Lord Onimaro.
To make it easier for you...
I have made them wet
with nectar...
so that you may heartily enjoy
all the pleasure you deserve.
More!
I want more in my mouth!
Missing Dialogue.
Enter their every orifice.
Ram yourself deep inside.
See, the harder you thrust,
the wetter they get.
Oh, what a wonderful smell...
All of these women are ready to
give themselves totally!
For the ritual that marks your
attainment of adulthood.
Missing Dialogue.
I shall be your final experience.
I am Ai Amatsu
of the Amatsu Guardian clan!
I am Mai Amatsu of the same!
We are here to get Lord Onimaro!
Missing Dialogue.
Ai!
You moths have flown into
a dangerous flame.
The perfect sacrifice for
Lord Onimaro's carnal ritual!
Ai!
I will peel you sisters naked...
and relish the look of you
writhing in agony!
Mai...
Let's see what we'll do.
Now! Take off their ribbons!
Missing Dialogue.
Oh, heavenly snow-capped
mountain...
Oh, flowing, shimmering lake...
Oh, most holy Mother of the
Heavenly Maiden, hear my plea!
Save these holy children,
the descendants of Tenjin.
Guard them. Protect them.
Give to them the power to
turn aside the danger...
and guide them out of the way.
Protect them! Protect them!
May the plum blossoms
send out their scent.
May spring come to you,
even without your master.
- My lady!
It's worked! Our prayers
have been answered!
Look at the plum blossoms!
These blossoms are a sign.
An indication that the spirits are
communing with us.
I implore you to
save our daughters!
- It flew!
- That's right.
Lord Michizane consoled his soul
with poetry as he hid in the capital.
The plum blossoms are
a sign of that legend.
Missing Dialogue.
Your resistance is futile.
Soon, you will be begging me to
thrust into you...
as you will feel that
you cannot live without it.
Mai! Don't give in!
Missing Dialogue.
What? Let's see it!
What? What about her?
Your mind resists,
but your body responds!
Any such remaining defenses
shall be washed away...
by your flowing juices!
No one can resist the power
of the carnal urge!
Enjoy it. Enjoy it.
To prepare you
for Lord Onimaro's ritual...
I will make you submit
to the power.
Stop this!
Lord Oniyashadoji!
Missing Dialogue.
Rise up!
The Angel Twins!
What?!
Why, you!
I've had enough, Amatsu sisters!
Feel the devastating fury
of the carnal power!
Ai!
Come back my children!
Bring back Lord Onimaro!
What?
Let's go, Mai!
The ultimate Tenjin power!
The plum storm!
Prepare yourself!.
How dare you mess with me!
Come on!
Let's get out of here!
Ai, Mai...
Don't leave me here,
please don't leave me here.
Of course we're taking you
with us!
You fools!
You think you can escape
from the Carnal Underworld...
and return to your world safely?!
Hold on tight, Lord Onimaro!
So we don't lose you!
Feels pretty good to me!
Strike the evil!
Ai, are we at the opening yet?
Destroy the evil!
I'll get you!
He's still coming!
You'll never escape!
Ai, behind you!
I'll rape you to death!
Wha....?
- Mai!
- I can't!
You can't defeat me,
silly little girls!
Grandmother, I'm sorry!
We have failed!
Over there!
You die!
Master!
You are finished.
I will take Lord Onimaro!
- Tenjin Angels!
Rise up!
Destroy the evil!
The Divine Might of Tenjin!
Drive away all evil!
We're saved!
Missing Dialogue.
Wait for me, Ai! Mai!
Don't misunderstand me!
Missing Dialogue.
You're ten years too early!
Lord Onimaro!
Missing Dialogue.
Conclusion: The US version is a slaughter >_<
See ya for the second part ;)
Love, no matter how
Your heart,
it might be leading me
You like,
we can't continue solely on
Forever, my love for you alone
Love, suddenly
Wake up,
don't say you'll let me go
Don't say, at a time like this
Please, don't make me hesitate
You're seducing me with your words
And they're the only love
I get from you
It's last thing that I need,
painful tears.
No, they're not for me
Gentleness has a real meaning
I wanted more
It really means much more
It's really something
that's important
Ah, can you see?
Gentleness has a real meaning
It is true love
I hope you can feel it
deep down in your heart
That's the kind of guy
that I wish you could be