Multi-celled organisms
are metabolic creatures.
In other words, life is maintained
as a result of new cells...
...replacing dying cells.
There are also cells that never die
and replicate indefinitely.
These are the cancer cells.
If we can satisfy two conditions...
...that of maintaining indefinite
cell replication...
...and of gaining control
over replication...
...then people will be able to
attain immortality.
This was made possible
through alchemy in medieval Europe.
Master Gen.
Master Gen?
It's time to go.
Please get yourself ready.
Master Gen...?
What are you looking at?
The cherry blossoms.
But haven't they already...
Oh, my!
What a fright, Master Gen!
You surprised me.
I thought
my heart was going to stop.
Now, will you please
get yourself ready?
Master Gen!
You mustn't do that.
It's time to go...
Please stop...!
Master Gen!
You mustn't, Master Gen!
Please don't do this!
You've got to go!
You'll be late for college!
When Gen's eyes turn golden...
...he's like a runaway train.
His metabolic rate runs amuck...
...and just before he expires...??
That is why his semen turns gold and
he cannot control his libido.
It's his fate.
The fate of the Hiraga bloodline.
Because he will not live long...
...his blood urges him on...
...to produce a progeny.
All for the sake of the eternally
blossoming cherry trees.
If it weren't
for the immortality gene...
...Gen's overheated metabolic rate
could be stemmed.
But...
Is that all right with you?
What's the point of asking me now?
I want Gen to be able to live
the life of a normal person...
...and break free from the cursed
fate of the Hiraga family.
I don't ever want to feel
that sorrow and despair again.
If he could live out his life...
...I would be happy.
What happened to you, Beth?!
It's nothing! It's really nothing!
He couldn't have!
Gen!
Hiraga?
Could you excuse me for a minute?
Hiraga,
what time do you think it is?
Why are you so late for college?
Hey!
What happened?
Your eye color's different.
Hey, prez...
Yes?
I love you.
What do you mean?
No! Stop that!
Mr. Hiraga!
Check that out!
That's pretty bold!
No!
No! Please stop!
Mr. Hiraga!
Stop it!
Come with me.
Ayumi!
Hello, Ms. Rokuhira.
What's the matter?
Please...
Huh?
Could you leave the two of us alone?
This man's in danger.
Please.
I never thought I'd be the one
looking in from the outside.
Ms. Ito?
Well, uh...
I have a stomachache again.
Let's do it later. I'm busy now.
Huh?
But...
Didn't you hear me?
Now, go back to your class.
Yes, ma'am.
It's just that...
...there's no room for me
in there right now.
I'm all right.
I'm not afraid.
All of your fears...
...and sorrows...
...I will receive them all.
Forget all of those,
just for now.
You've done nothing wrong.
What is this feeling?
I remember
being held like this before.
Mother?
No...
...that was...
...the one in my dreams...
...the woman I saw
under the cherry tree.
That was...!
Ms. Sakurako!
Ms. Sakurako...
Who are you, Ms. Sakurako?
Have you woken up?
Grandma...
What happened to me?
Am I sick?
What's all this for?
I'm sure I was at college...
...with Ms. Sakurako...
Huh?! I did it with...!
There's no need to
feel bad about it.
It's all the fault of
the Hiraga bloodline.
Sakurako knows about that
more than anyone else.
Sakurako?
It's finally about to end.
The ominous curse
of the Hiraga bloodline...
...and your suffering.
My...
...suffering?
It's an ancient, ancient story.
One of the early ancestors of the Hiraga...
...obtained immortality using...
...the methods of alchemy.
However...
...perhaps as retribution
for violating the laws of nature...
...that ancestor was the only one
who became immortal.
All of the children and
grandchildren...
...died of unknown causes.
There was a serious defect
in the genes of the descendants.
That's right. As with your mother...
...and with you right now...
...it had wrecked
the wheels of nature.
What is this about, Grandma?
Realizing the gravity
of the sin committed...
...that ancestor began
looking into ways...
...of returning those children's
physical conditions...
...to their normal states.
That ancestor had met a woman...
...who came from a legendary European
family known for its immortality.
And after meeting with scholars
who studied...
...the nature of immortality
from a scientific perspective...
...a treatment was finally uncovered.
No way...
To live forever...
...means that all of
the sufferings of life...
...also continue forever.
This is the fate that I have had to...
...bear.
No...
My selfish...
...disgraceful desire...
...had resulted in the suffering
of all of the Hiraga.
That's right.
Gen.
Even you.
You've got to be kidding...
Ms. Sakurako.
My...
...woman of my...
...dreams.
I intended to keep up the charade...
...of the masked grandmother
until the end.
However...
...out of some capricious need...
...I revealed myself to you
as Sakurako.
I never thought you would remember.
Just once, 1 2 years ago.
The night when your mother
Sakurako brought you.
Ms. Sakura?!
You promised not to show yourself
in front of Gen!
It is all the result of my errors.
Not only did I play with
the lives of people...
...but I had also
committed a grave sin.
I am the capricious ancestor...
...who caused such damage
to the family.
Grandma...
After this...
...you will go toJennifer's university.
And you will receive treatment.
They will keep your symptoms
in check with medications.
And over time...
...they will gradually
bring your body back to normal.
You will live a life...
...separate from Beth and myself.
You will not hold on to
the vestiges of our past.
That's why I've revealed myself
from behind this unsightly visage.
Please understand.
Grandma...
Well...
...she hides behind her mask
'til the end anyway.
Huh?
Excuse me.
Have we met before?
What is your relationship with him?
Him?
Gen Hiraga.
My relationship with Gen...
I don't know...
You did have sex
behind the campus 2 months ago.
What?! You saw that?!
What is your relationship with him?
Who are you to Gen, anyway?
I'm...
...the class president.
Is Mr. Hiraga all right?
He wasn't normal.
Even today, his eyes were all golden...
Hey! How much do you know?!
Do you know why?!
If you know something,
please tell me!
What's...
...happened to Gen Hiraga?!
Are you sure this is all right?
Why is it that you did not order me?
If I were to use the cursed
power of my family...
...Master Gen would be all right.
Jennifer Collins' help
would not be necessary.
You would've been...
...able to continue living
with Master Gen.
That's impossible.
Gen and I were
never supposed to meet.
Living together...
...was always forbidden.
Then why did you
take Master Gen in?
Taking the name of Sakurako...
...and revealing yourself
to Master Gen.
You must have
had feelings for him.
Whatever the reason
why people live...
...they certainly are creatures
that bear heavy burdens.
However...
...I cannot force this man to suffer...
...the same lives we have.
Gen must have the same purpose
as an ordinary human.
That is, the happiness
that comes from being normal.
It is something...
...that you and I lost long ago.
No.
I don't want to...
...Grandma.
I don't want to be separated.
I want us to stay together forever.
Gen...
Why do we have to separate?
Whoever you may be, Grandma...
...I am...
No, Gen...
Why?
We only just met.
That was a mistake in the first place.
That can't be...
I always thought...
...it was strange.
I've seen it,
the same dream over and over.
But I realize that was
something that actually happened.
I remember now.
Back then...
...when you held me in your arms.
I remember.
You smelled the same as my mother.
Gen...
I'm so glad...
...that we've met again.
I finally understand.
From that time on...
You mustn't, Gen.
Ever since we first met
under that cherry tree...
...on that night...
...I have always loved you.
Gen...
You're beautiful...
...Grandma.
The same scent as my mother's.
I sensed it even in my dreams.
The same face as my mother's.
The same warmth.
When she...
...when Sakurako gave birth to you...
...she was a daughter
who resembled me very much.
You too, Gen.
Even you show a resemblance
to another ancestor...
...who lived long ago...
...and remains
deep within my memory.
You must have been lonely...
...until now.
You are a kind man.
We will remain together forever.
It sounds like a dream.
It's not a dream!
It's not a...
...dream.
Are you really my grandma?
Yes, I am your grandmother's...
...grandmother's...
...grandmother.
Are you afraid of me, Gen?
I am the cherry tree.
The tree rooted in the garden
where our family sleeps.
A cherry tree that never wilts...
...blossoming forever.
Mr. Hiraga!
I wish you could at least stay
until graduation.
You will come back
when you're better, right?
It feels like we'll never meet again.
I'll phone you when I get there.
I'll write you too.
Well, take care.
- I guess this is it, Hiraga--
- Ooops!
Oh, I'm sorry!
You too,Jennifer?
Your grandmother did
ask me to watch over you.
So, I'm going back to
graduate college.
I guess you could say
I'm like your guardian.
With physical relationships.
Hey, stop that...!
Get away from me!
Let's do lots of research
when we get there.
Hey!
Don't say it like that!
- You're crazy! Do you have a ticket?
- What?!
Get away from Hiraga!
I was just kidding.
That's the trouble with virgins.
I'm not a virgin.
Still in bloom...
...the cherry blossoms.