Art Preparation Room
Yeah. . . lt's great.
Saki, make sure you tape it!
Get a close up of her face!
l can't believe Professor Mikami
is doing something like that!
Did he do that to Mao? He didn't. . .!!
Private Sessions Episode 2
Stop her!
Shoot! Shoot!
You did it! Wow! She's so amazing!
Thanks!
l'm beat.
Me too.
Yeah. . .
l'm going to go to the bathroom . . .
...so everyone go ahead and finish up.
OK!
Restroom
Huh?
You're awake.
You're. . .!
Shh! What are you going
to do if someone comes?
Do you want people to
come and see you like this?
You want them to see the most popular
basketball player on the team . . .
...getting molested?
No.
You want to go to the U.S.
to become a pro, right?
lf this video gets out, it's
not going to be good.
You just need to give
me some of your time.
As long as you don't open your
mouth, it won't be that bad.
lt smells great. The scent
of fresh sweat from sports.
Your salty, sweaty skin is tasty.
lt smells sweet, yet
sour. lt smells delicious.
You're really wet. l bet
my fist would fit in there.
lt. . .it hurts. . .
Don't worry, it's not going to rip.
lf you give into this...
...the underclassmen in the basketball
team are gonna laugh at you.
Yeah. . . No wonder you're good
at sports, you're a quick learner.
But you need to do it faster!
Faster.
Faster!!
That's not good! l was just getting off!
Take your responsibility
seriously and finish the job.
l'm not going to forgive you
if you do a half-ass job.
l'll clear up your insides. . .
lt's really good for your body.
Health is the most important
thing for an athlete, right?
You don't have to hold
it. Just let it all out.
Come on, go ahead.
Saki, make sure you tape this.
Good job. Saki, your filming
has gotten much better.
She's acting like she doesn't
want it but look how wet she is!
Can you believe her?
Takumi. . .
Fuck me.
Look at the face of the
basketball club's captain.
The students will be so
shocked if they see this. . .
...cause she's so popular.
l want you to fuck me, Takumi.
l'm helping you out so much!
What are you. . .?
l'm in love with you.
l really hate taping it..
...but l'm reluctantly doing it
because you asked me to.
Do you know it's really hard for me...
...to watch you have
sex with other women?
Sorry. . .
l didn't mean to upset you.
Takumi.
But there're tons of tasty
fish swimming around me.
lt'd be wrong not to catch
them fresh while l'm here.
l'll fuck you after the temp job is up.
What?
Why am l in love with someone like him?
l can't explain it. l'm in love with him.
What?
Just as l thought. Mao was
raped by that professor!
l have to tell the police. . .
No, l can't do that yet, l have
to think about Mao's future. . .
First things first, l have to
get that videotape back!
Enjoy.
Please, give me the tape.
lt's not here.
Does he have it?
Yes.
Please tell me where
he lives, his address. . .
No -
way!
Why?
Because. . .l'm in love with him.
He has committed a crime!
As a woman. . .
...how can you forgive him
for doing something like this?
As a woman, you should
understand this too.
Even if l know how evil he is, l
can't rat out someone l love.
Miss Sakurano, l feel
sorry for your sister. . .
...but you shouldn't make
any more of a fuss.
Or else the situation may get worse.
Are you saying l'll get raped too?
l know his game!
He may be stronger, but l'm not
going to get raped so easily!!
Art Preparation Room
You're. . .
Professor, please give
me my sister's tape.
Don't stand!
What you did was lower than a dog!
lf you try something, l
won't hesitate to stab you!
l swear l'll stab you!
Ok. . . So calm down and
let's talk this over, OK?
There's nothing to talk about!
l'm just here to get my
sister's tape! That's it!
l haven't made a copy.
You have no choice but to believe me. . .
You saved me. Thanks for telling me.
Now. . .what should we do about her?
You're thinking about telling
the cops, but l'm fine with that.
l'm not afraid of prison.
You have to be prepared for the risks. . .
...to continue this kind of thing.
Oh, what's wrong? You were
so courageous earlier.
We're going to be taping
a documentary now.
lt's better for the heroine if
she's taped looking pretty.
lt's about time you answered. lt's Mikami.
Sis. . .
Good guess! l'm impressed.
l'm with your sister right now, but...
...she's saying she's going to go to
the police and tell them about me.
l'm thinking of doing something to her
so you'll never see her again, but...
What are you going to do about it?
No! Don't do that!
Then come by yourself.
You know what's going
to happen if you don't.
l'll be waiting.
Both sisters have a nice ass.
l can't decide whose is better.
lt's about the same temperature
inside but l think Mao's a little wetter.
Minori, you're losing to your sister.
Saki, make sure to tape this!
This'll be interesting footage.
You both can raise your
voice, if it feels good.
Don't worry about people hearing
you, everyone's left the building.
She's responding nicely.
What do you think?
You've probably never seen your
sister make a face like this.
You're with your sister. Writhe in
pleasure as much as you like.
lt feels so good.
Don't be in such a rush.
l only have one so you have
to be nice and gentle to it.
Good. . . lt's your sister that you love.
Confirm your sisterly love for each
other as much as you need to.
lt feels so good!!
What a dependable sister.
She's so assertive.
As her younger sister you
should make her feel good too.
Mao, yes... lt feels really good.
Sis, me too.
How does your sister's pussy taste?
lt tastes really good. lt's sweet
and sour. l might get hooked.
Sis, l'll do you too.
Mao. . .Mao. . .
Sis. . .Sis. . .
lt hurts! Sis!
She's being loud. Shut
your sister's mouth up.
l thought Takumi's lust had
reached its perverted limit. . .
. . .but things kept getting
more and more perverse.
The days passed...
...and his term as the temporary
professor had come to an end.
The day has come...
...for Professor Mikami, the
temporary art professor. . .
. . .who had come to teach classes
for a month, to say good bye.
Also, this is a little sudden but. . .
...Professor Shiraishi, who has
been teaching Japanese. . .
. . .for three years, will also be
leaving us for personal reasons.
But...
Oh no. . .
Professor Shiraishi is retiring. . .
...because she is going
to be married soon.
She will be marrying Professor Mikami.
No. . .that can't be!
What's going on!? Explain yourself!
What do you mean, 'What's going on?'
l can't be single forever.
l have to have a wife and
prove myself to society.
Don't you think she'll be a great wife?
My parents and annoying family
members will be happy with her.
l'm grateful to you.
You got me a job, and on top of
that, you introduced me to her.
You're terrible.
What do you want me to
do? l've already decided.
SEVERAL MONTHS LATER
You're beautiful.
No. You're going to ruin my makeup.
Then. . .
l can't wait. . .
Not here.
lt's all right.
The attendant's going to be here.
This feels so strange. . .
lt'll be a nice memory.
Yeah. . .
lt feels so good.
l can't hold it anymore.
You're going to dirty my dress!
l love you.
l love you too.
The bride and groom are
done changing their outfits.
They will be entering the room.
Everyone, please welcome
them with a round of applause.
l am sure everyone is
enjoying themselves. . .
...but please turn your
attention to the monitor.
l would like to present a
video that will show. . .
. . .the bride and groom's personalities
as well as their childhood.
l wonder what kind of surprise
and family footage will pop up?
Everyone please enjoy.
What the. . . What is this?
Th-this is. . .
This is a mistake! This is
someone's malicious prank!
Someone hurry up and stop the tape!!
Please. . .
l have made copies of the tapes.
Takumi used the tapes to
blackmail and silence them.
l used it to ruin him.
Now, all Takumi has left is me.
Finally, he's mine and mine alone.