Yes!
More! Keep doing it!
You're begging?
Since when did you get
so high and mighty?
Not in a hundred years will you
have the right to give me orders!
lt. . .it hurts!
Come on! Hurry up!
You're gonna get it if you use
your teeth! lf l wanted to l could. . .
ldiots are like scissors. . . Always
around when you need to use 'em.
You're not that bad like this.
Let's wrap this up.
Private Sessions Episode 1
Takumi. . .
What?
Are you bored of me?
Of course l am. How many years do
you think l've been looking at you?
l'm sorry, l'm not that flattering.
And stop moaning so
loud when you're into it.
lt's so lame, and you
know it spoils it for me.
But it felt good. . .
l think it's over between you and me.
No! Don't dump me!
You idiot! That was dangerous!
l'm sorry.
lf you don't want to get dumped
help me get a job at your college.
Takumi, are you thinking of
having sex with the students?
l just want to work.
But there's no opening
for an art professor. . .
On top of that, at the last college you. . .
Then you have to do something about it.
You want to get dumped?
At his last college, he sexually
assaulted one of the students.
No.
l never want him to do
something like that again.
Although our relationship
started in a similar fashion.
lf Takumi only looks at me, l'll be okay. . .
No matter what kind
of rough sex he wants.
ln the end l followed Takumi's orders.
l didn't want him to leave me.
Professor, what's wrong?
My stomach suddenly. . .
Professor, are you all right?
Professor!
So...
To fill in for Professor Wada
who has been hospitalized. . .
. . .please welcome Professor Mikami. . .
...the substitute professor who will
be teaching art for the next month.
Please to meet you!
l'm Professor Mikami.
l'll only be here for a short time, but
l hope l get to know all of you well.
l'd like to have a memorable
time with everyone. . .
...even outside of class,
with club activities and such.
No one knows who he really is.
Knowing that the other professors trust
me, l submitted his false resume. . .
All of the other professors
are totally deceived.
l hope his teaching time will
end without any trouble.
Professor Azuma.
l heard you went to college with him?
He's really charming.
ls he your boyfriend?
No. . .not exactly. . .
Really? But l bet he must
be seeing someone, right?
Your drawing looks really good.
Mao! Good for you,
you got complimented.
Professor, she's in the Art Club. . .
...but Professor Wada who's in
the hospital never praised her.
Really?
l don't see why he wouldn't.
Professor Mikami!
Hey! You're not supposed
to run in the hallways!
l'm sorry.
Did you need something?
My name is Minori Sakurano,
second year, classroom B.
My younger sister, Mao is in the Art Club.
l came to introduce myself because
you'll probably be working with my sister.
Mao Sakurano. . .
Oh her! She was just in my last class.
Your sister has really good taste.
Really?
But praise coming from a
temporary professor like me...
...probably won't do much anyway.
That's not true!
She's kind of timid and shy, so she has a
lot of trouble communicating with people.
So l'd appreciate even the littlest things.
Oh, l see what you're saying now.
Professor, there's no need to force
yourself to compliment her, but. . .
. . .l'd appreciate it if you could
talk with her as often as you can.
Sure. How can l refuse
a caring sister's wishes?
Thank you very much!
Oh, stop that. Everyone's watching.
Come to the Prep Room later.
l know a really good sketch
technique. l'll teach it to you in private.
Yes sir.
Bye!
See you tomorrow!
Let's go to...
Hurry up! Come on!
Bye!
See you!
Art Preparation Room
Hello?
Professor Mikami?
Professor Azuma?
You're in love with me right?
l really like you too. . .
. . .so l'm going to give you a special
lesson to help you sketch better.
The fastest way is to learn
a man's body first hand.
Or else, you'll never be
able to draw the real thing.
Saki, tape it!
Do you understand?
Everything that's going to happen
here is going to be taped.
lf you tell anyone, you do understand
what's going to happen, right?
lt's been a while since l've smelt a virgin.
l love the taste.
Saki, make sure you tape all of it.
You act like you don't want it
but it looks like you're feeling it.
Your clit is getting big.
Let's see. . .
Well, it is your first time.
To make it a more
memorable experience...
you should have a hot, fat cock from
your loved one pounded into you but. . .
...life is a bitch.
Does it hurt? Just hang
in there, even if it hurts.
You have to go through some hardships
in order to be able to draw better.
That's right. You're not that bad.
You have to use your tongue and
lips. You can use your left hand too.
Good girls get rewards.
This girl is way better than you! lt'll be
interesting to see how she turns out!
l'm gonna shoot my first load now.
Don't spit it out! Swallow it!
Good girl. You're a good student.
You should have more confidence.
No. . .No. . .
lt turned out, just as l feared.
But l can't say 'no' to Takumi.
Because l'll lose everything that's
important to me if he dumps me.
l want you to understand
and appreciate this.
This is a 'Private Session'
that l'm having only for you.
There you go!
So, are you also fans of
that guy, Professor Mikami?
Oh, of course not. . .we're not his fans.
Right?
Y-yeah.
l hope so. . .
l guess everyone seems
to be falling for him . . .
...but it would be a shame
to sell myself short.
There are tons of other men in the world.
Can l join too?
With pleasure!
Professor Mikami, pay attention!
'Even monkeys fall out of trees.'
There you go!
Got it!
Over here!
Yukari.
You're so cute. l'll show
you a really good time.
Yukari. . .lt feels really good.
You're so wet. You're such a dirty girl.
Yes. . .You're doing great.
Same here, Yukari. . .
What am l doing? This is a
crime! lt's a heinous act. . .
. . .but, Takumi ordered
me to. . .Takumi ordered. . .
lt feels so good Takumi. More. . .harder. . .
l can't. l'm going to cum.
Saki, l love you.
Takumi. . .
That's. . .
l hear your family is very
prestigious, and for generations. . .
...the head of your family
has been the mayor?
Yes.
lf everyone finds out his
only daughter is a lesbian. . .
...l'm sure it's going to hurt your
father's election campaign.
lt's all right. Don't look so worried.
l won't leak this information.
l just have a favor to ask.
A favor?
Mao, you there?
l have something important to talk to
you about. Can you open the door?
Mao, open the door!
l said open the door!
Hey, what's wrong?
lt's been three days since you last talked.
You've always told me everything before.
Did l do something to piss you off?
And l thought you were
having fun at school lately. . .
Something happened at school?
l'm right, aren't l? Who? Who
teased you? Tell me who did it!
Someone in your class?
Or was it a professor?
A professor?
Was it. . .?
Worthy of the hottest girl on campus. . .
l've never seen such beautiful skin.
lt's as white as snow and smooth as silk.
Are you going to get your period soon?
You're getting pretty wet.
This'll fit right in.
No? l see. . . You don't want it?
Then l guess instead, l
want you to take a piss.
lt's been a while since
l've seen a piss show.
lf you can't do it, l'll have no choice
but to shove this in and play.
lt tastes like a young, healthy woman.
Whoops, sorry! lt slipped.
Women like a fat dick right?
Then this isn't that bad.
Why are you so quiet
now? lt's no fun then. . .
Saki, make sure you tape both of
them in her. l want to watch it later.
lt's really tight and great! You're
the best fuck bitch on campus!
Your tits are great too.
The size and feel of them . . .l
have nothing to complain about.
You arrogant little bitch!
You think you're better than everyone
else because you're prettier than them!
Don't you!?
There are girls like you who just don't
seem to understand something.
You're the same as all the rest of them . . .
. . .when you're getting fucked like this!
Nice view.
A hot honor student that's the
daughter of a prestigious family. . .
...is riding my dick in heat!
This suits you well, Miss Priss!
The light in the Art Room is still
on. Professor Mikami is still here.
l have to ask him. Professor Mikami
must know why Mao is acting strange.
Art Preparation Room
Excuse me. . .
Yeah. . .Your mouth is great too.
Just by thinking such a hot
babe is sucking my dick. . .
...l can keep on cumming.
Saki, make sure you tape it!
Get a close up of her face.
l can't believe Professor Mikami
is doing something like that!
Did he do that to Mao? He didn't. . .!!
For the first time, Takumi's real self was
witnessed by someone other than us.
But neither Takumi nor l had noticed her.
What is going to happen to
Takumi's 'Private Sessions'?
We have yet to see. . .