SLAVE ACADEMY (FIRST SEDUCTION)
You're so tense!
Let it drain out of your shoulders.
Relax!
But...
That's why you get taken
advantage of all the time.
I can't teach class now.
It's always the same thing...!
The longer I teach here,
the less confidence I have.
All right, then!
I'll help you out with this.
Come to my place tonight.
Your place?
This will settle everything.
Settle it...?
How does Keiko get on
so well with the students here?
You have to treat them like adults.
But how?
That's what I said
I'd teach you tonight.
Yeah, we can just take our time.
But why'd she ask me
to dress for a date?
Keiko, it's me.
Come right in, Professor!
Keiko! She seems a little hesitant.
Because she's upset about
what you did to her today.
Oh, that.
We were a little rough on
you, but just relax.
Wh-where's Keiko?
Hey, knock it off already!
He's telling us to
knock off for the night.
Hi there.
We're having some lessons tonight.
Extracurricular activities,
you could say.
Extracurricular activities?
Yes.
Getting on well with the students means...
...having to do a little
after-school coaching.
Right, Koh?
After-school coaching... I like that.
I'm hoping for some strong
coaching from Prof. Miyuki. Thirsty?
It's nothing too hard, just something
only a female instructor can do.
A little of this and that.
Gotta spread yourself for it.
Spread myself?
God, you're dense.
Physical relationships!
Your lack of effort is
affecting your classes.
Mr. Koh here needs your guidance.
Wanna see?
Hell yeah, we wanna see!
Show us your teaching materials!
Oh, man! Lookit the prof's bod!
You begging us?
Silly boys!
Can we touch it?
You gotta use two fingers, dumbass!
Hands washed? Nails clipped?
Yes, Professor.
Koh and his friends certainly
aren't slacking off with THIS lesson.
Slowly, slowly... That's it.
Three fingers, not two. Yeah, yeah...
Slowly, slowly... Slowly, okay?
Mm, you've gotten better, Kubo.
No shit! I'm giving this my best!
You can just keep on doing it.
Can I be next, Prof. Keiko?
Koh, your next lesson's starting.
Koh's lost interest in my guidance.
Now that I think about it,
it started right after...
...you were transferred in,
Prof. Miyuki.
Meaning Koh has been teasing you...
...to try and get your
attention as his instructor.
No... Why is my head spinning?
Because your tits and your cunt...
...are taking up all
the space in there.
You're serious?
This one's for you, Keiko!
Yee-HA!
What's with him?
Never mind. Just concentrate.
Yes, ma'am!
What's wrong? Hurry up?
You want me, right?
Oh yeah! You bet!
Kubo, pay close attention.
Later, you have to
give me a... report...!
Prof. Keiko, I can't see!
How about... now...?
Oh, yeah. I can see.
Can I... let it go...
Professor...?!
Not till the lesson's over!
Okay...!
I see...
Keiko, you work so hard...
I guess.
Prof. Keiko's talk was
very stimulating. Wanna drink?
Doesn't hold her beer, does she?
I'm kinda surprised, myself.
Well, we're on schedule, at any rate.
On schedule?
What do you... mean...?
That's right, Prof. Miyuki.
What's wrong with me...?
She looks to be around 36-24-37...
You have independent
study from here on, guys.
So, it begins...
Don't touch her, though.
Seriously?
We can only take pictures?
What're you gonna do with the pics?
Prof. Keiko requested it.
They'll be useful in
many ways later on.
Many ways...? Meaning what?
Oh, yeah. 36, definitely!
Do it!
I don't want to force it.
I want her to say "Take me, Koh!"
Hmph! A real romantic, huh?
Hiroshi!
Who's Hiroshi?
Her boyfriend who's
in L.A. On business.
They're getting married next year.
Oh, man!
Hiroshi, I've waited for you!
Hiroshi! Hiroshi!
Good night.
Later.
You surprised me.
I'm sorry.
Why did a little beer
set me off like that?
It was amazing!
I'd never have expected
it from looking at you.
Amazing?
I can't remember a thing.
What's wrong with me?
Shall I tell you...?
Please, I have to know!
Those three students have
a better opinion of you now.
Looks like it's going to work out.
They promised they'd
keep this a secret. As do I.
You'll be teaching here
for a long time, Professor.
And those boys will
be coming to you...
...for all sorts of help,
Miss Miyuki...
Internet access is so easy lately.
These pictures can follow
you all over the world.
How did this happen...?
Now, for the finishing touch...
Koh!
I'm sorry about before.
Go home!
I'm not surprised
you're mad at me,
but I wanted to tell you one thing.
Prof. Keiko asked us
to take those pictures.
She's jealous of you, and wanted...
...to protect her position.
That's why she...
I just wanted you to notice me.
I won't disrupt class anymore.
I just wanted to tell you that.
Well, see you later, Prof. Miyuki.
Koh!
I'll see what I can
do about those pictures.
It's all right.
It was my failure as a teacher...
...to not understand
her student's feelings.
Failure?
Yes. I'm going to resign.
Thought she'd turn him away.
He said he had a great idea.
Wonder what it is.
Yeah, well...
Professor, don't say that!
I've decided. Tomorrow,
I hand in my resignation.
I see. So, your students
don't matter? I don't matter?
What do you mean?
Since you came, I've been going nuts.
I was so pathetic,
I thought playing pranks...
...was the only way you'd notice me.
What am I supposed to do
once you leave tomorrow?
Koh...
Dammit all!
I appreciate how you feel, Koh.
But...
Professor!
Don't leave us, Professor!
Please!
Stop it...
How'd he do it?!
A little "making up" drink
and Koh's natural sincerity.
Definitely 36.
24, 36...
Hey!
Shall we begin?
That's enough.
Don't. This is a special
exercise for the professor and me.
But, Koh...!
That's no fair!
Not till the lesson's over.
Lesson One!
Can you hear them?
Can't make it out.
You think he's making fools of us?
Yeah, well...
Amazing...
Hiroshi... Hiroshi...
Hiroshi!
Hiroshi...
I'm so happy, Hiroshi...
Hiroshi!
Lesson One, complete.
Koh!
No fair.
You asked me to do it, Professor.
Huh?!
Don't you remember? Oh, jeez...
Well, after all that beer
and whiskey, I'm not surprised.
Koh... Stop it! Stop it! Stop!
Koh, please!
This is only the beginning.
No! No!
Please, no more...!
Professor... Professor...!
I'm so glad.
You're not quitting.
Everyone's so happy.
R- Right...
Glad I helped you out.
Aren't you?
Y- Yes... We've reached an
...understanding.
I see. Splendid.
It's strange...
Huh?
Prof. Miyuki, you seem
a lot sexier these days.
Oh, no! It's your imagination.
Uh-uh, it's true.
Please don't tease me, Prof. Keiko.
The other professors
are all talking about it.
They say you must
have a new boyfriend.
A lesson in the music room, huh?
Gotta love this school.
You can stop now. Lesson Two...
Don't rinse your mouth out, either.
That's part of the lesson, too.
I can't do that!
The lesson's only just begun...
Koh...
That's it for today.
What's...?
Lie face down.
N- No! Koh, stop it!
So pretty on your white skin...
This is Lesson Three!
Why? Why are you
tying me up so tightly?
That face...
It drives me crazy!
Girls who get off on
S&M drive me wild!
This lesson's too hard for
other students to try, Professor.
You're cruel!
Lessons! Lessons!
Please, Koh. That's enough!
Not yet...!
Oh, God, I'm going to...!
The lessons will continue.
Until you graduate.
Koh...
Don't cry.
It's a lesson, remember?
Extracurricular activities, huh?
Yep, these extracurricular
activities are the best!
You guys forget what
I teach you so quickly!
Allow us to review with you!
Review! Review!
I hope that little stuck up bitch
gets fucked by the whole school!
What's wrong, Ms. Hara?
Um, excuse me...
I'm a little sick...
Koh!
Looks like that
laxative is working now.
No! Get out! Now!
I'd like to say you've put
up a good fight holding it in...
But first, Lesson Four.
Please...!
I have to let it out now!
First, suck me off, Prof. Miyuki.
You'll just have to hold it in.
But, I...
This is Lesson Five.
Ow!
Wanna do it in the middle
of the staff meeting, Professor?
No, stop it! Stop it!
So cruel...
Discipline is a part of education,
isn't it, Professor?
No! Have to concentrate...!
All right. Good girl.
You worked very well.
Please...
Please, get out now, Koh!
I want to stay.
Why?
Didn't I do what you wanted?
Take your shit in front of me.
That's another lesson.
No! Please, I can't!
I really can't...!
Please, stop it!
Koh...! Koh...!
Professor...