What's happening to my body?
I've never felt this way before.
I see myself becoming
dirtier and dirtier...
...and I'm scared.
When will this nightmare end?
SLAVE ACADEMY (SECOND SEDUCTION)
Looks like Prof. Miyuki's enthusiasm
is rubbing off on these losers.
We have to practice seriously!
Exactly what we want to
hear, Prof. Miyuki!
I have great expectations for
this year's inter-campus music festival.
Well see, Prof. Sugai.
You need to demonstrate
for us, Prof. Miyuki!
Oh...! It feels so good!
Don't stop, please!
Is she like that?
She's more soprano. Right, Koh?
I don't believe this!
A professor and her students?!
I don't believe it!
It's a rumor. Just a rumor.
The innocent Miss Miyuki,
spreading her legs for her students?!
This old pervert!
I know what he wants to do!
They swore they'd keep it a secret!
Um, what can I do for you?
Are preparations for the
inter-campus music festival going well?
I think things are improving, but...
You think?
That doesn't sound promising.
Should I be worried?
We don't know how
good the other schools are.
And might there be a
more direct reason for it?
What are you doing?!
Stop that!
Oh, it's okay for your
students to do it,
but the school vice
president can't?!
How did you know...?!
So, the rumors are true.
Prof. Sugai, don't do this!
The vice presidency
has some perks.
I hope he fucks
the little bitch in half!
Please, don't.
Not here! Please!
I'm afraid not.
As vice president, it's my duty
to inspect the campus Madonna!
Wait, please!
Don't do this to me...!
I should be able to tell how
much you've been...
...fucking your students
by how tight you are...
No!
No! Stop that!
Hm, no moisture yet.
Let's speed things up!
Ah, now you're
getting wet, Prof. Miyuki!
Prof. Sugai always seems
like a perfect gentleman...!
Very tight and very wet,
Prof. Miyuki!
You're getting wetter and wetter!
There we go...
Like it or not, the body
does not lie! Look? See?
No!
Since you're all ready,
why don't I unleash my secret weapon?
Turn towards me.
I'll give you a memory
to last a lifetime.
Amazing, isn't it?
In anticipation that
this day might come,
I injected it with
10 units of silicone!
I can't fit that
thing into my mouth!
Don't call it "that thing!"
Say it's incredible!
Madonna Miyuki,
going down on my silicone rod!
It's like a dream come true!
That's it, suck my rod hard!
Use your tongue more!
Use your hands, too!
Until Miyuki came,
I was the school Madonna.
I'll ruin her!
What, tired already?
I can have you fired in
a microsecond if I wanted to!
I'd suggest you do what I say.
Ah, THAT opening down
there isn't tired. Excellent.
Here we go!
Wonderful! There we go!
Ah, wetter, still.
If you do what I say and
do well in the music festival,
I'll keep the Madonna's secret safe!
If I just hang in there,
this will all work out.
You've got mail!
Did you hear? The vice president's
in a great mood today.
Really...
He says we're going
to win the music festival.
Confident little bastard, isn't he?
Really? Wonder why he thinks that.
Did anything happen
with you and him?
N- No! I d-d-didn't do anything!
Prof. Miyuki, people tend to stutter
when they HAVE done something.
Honestly, I didn't do anything!
Wanna come to my place tonight?
We can have some drinks with
Koh and his friends, like before.
That was a mistake! I'll never
do that with a student again!
Well, well, two lovely
ladies in one place.
What won't you do
with a student again...?
Oh! Vice President...
Nothing, sir.
A little music education talk.
Right, Prof. Miyuki?
Yes, well...
This is good timing.
Prof. Miyuki, may I discuss
the music festival with you?
Come to my office, please.
Y- Yes, sir.
Well then, I'll be waiting.
Vice President's Office
Our school has a proud
musical tradition to recapture,
so we must win this
festival at all costs!
So I want you to help out as well.
In any way...
What do you mean? I have the
students practicing every day.
I'd like to make
things a little safer...
...by bringing the
judges over to our side.
Is that possible, sir?
It is, if we use your lovely body.
What? Sir...!
Are you saying you can't?
Oh, well. No choice, then...
What are you doing?!
The vice president will
take what he is owed!
No! Stop this...
Forget it! You can't get
out of these that easily!
Just accept this!
Please let me out! Prof. Sugai,
what's wrong with you?
Have you lost your mind?!
An instructor should
watch what they say!
Or else... THIS!
Great, isn't it? An improvement
on dog training methods.
Another dose, my dear?
Example given. All clear?
Y- Yes, sir...
He always seemed so straitlaced.
I'm impressed.
If you can do this,
you must be a pervert!
I'm not!
Don't talk back!
Know your situation!
From now on, Miyuki Hara
is mine to play with!
I don't have to fantasize
and masturbate anymore!
Oh, bliss...!
This is getting me seriously horny.
The boys had better
work extra hard tonight!
Is that all you have?
Say something!
I'm listening. I get it...
You need more stimulation.
Okay, then!
Oh, there we go!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
I'm coming! I'M COMING!!!
Did you just hear something?
Yeah, something...
Prof. Keiko, you're amazing tonight!
Never mind. You, join in, too!
Prof. Keiko, you're just
totally wet tonight!
It's Miyuki's fault. Oh...!!!
I'm outta here!
That's it! Oh, yes!
Our selection process
leads us to one choice.
But you say you want
victory to be ensured.
I have something prepared
to ensure the outcome I desire.
Something prepared...?
We're not that easily bought.
I think you'll find
this most acceptable.
Now then, let me show you.
What happened?
What's going on here?
Come on, get in here!
Well, well, well.
The campus Madonna, huh?
Yes, Prof. Miyuki, our
campus Madonna, in the flesh.
Hey! Don't look away!
Don't you care about your students?
You have to do what it takes
to get the judges on our side!
Those idiots have so many fetishes,
you'll be the perfect bait to offer them!
Oh...! This is great!
The most purely sex-crazed
teacher in our school, sirs.
The day is dawning on
your school's victory.
As you say, sir.
Let's have a pre-victory toast.
Koh!
I... I...
What should I do? What?
Hold me tight!
Make me forget all
the awful things!
Tighter! Tighter!
Dammit, Koh! What do
you see in Miyuki?
What's going on?
Why's she so worked up?
Has something happened?
I wish the music
festival would go away!
Before I'm covered in filth for life!
That was great!
I can't wait to try her out.
Yes, well, after the festival,
you can do what you like with her.
Oh, I can't wait!
Almost time.
Right. Leave it to us.
And then later...
Right! As promised.
Waiting Room C
Change into this.
The judges want to see you in it.
Also, put this up your cunt.
And make sure you
move as sexily as you can!
Do what I say,
or else I tell everything...
...about you and your students!
And this is for my fetish.
I always wanted to try this.
If you can't control yourself,
feel free to masturbate on the podium.
We must offer some
perks to ensure our victory.
This is... This is too much!
It's a blasphemy against music!
How can you do this to me?!
As promised, all
preparations have been made.
These are the panties
straight off the Madonna.
This is certainly
heightening the mood.
I'd like to get this music
festival over with already!
Ah, our school is up!
Next is Sobu Academy.
Prof. Miyuki Hara, conducting!
Jesus!
How can she wear that outfit?
I can see her nipples!
No panties and a vibrator.
I'm already getting hard!
I'd say your win is
in the bag with this.
Oh, thank you, sirs! This is all
thanks to the professor's fine work.
Congratulations! Bone-breaking effort
went into that amazing performance.
That performance was so great,
I didn't even hear the music!
Here, have some more.
Forget the drinks!
I wanna take out that vibrator.
You're all ready, aren't you?
Yes, of course I am!
I was sure she'd run away,
but she kept herself under control.
I gotta hand it to Miyuki.
I'm going first with her.
Oh, this smell... I can't take it!
There's one more bit inside of her.
Here we go!
Wet little bugger, isn't it?
Look at that!
Look how wet the Madonna is!
I'm a little jealous!
Oh, I can't take it.
The thrill of it! The taste...
Working up from the ass...
I'm getting seriously
horny seeing this.
When do I get my chance with her?!
And now for my reward
in exchange for your victory.
I'll do whatever you
wish for your reward.
I take pride in using
my sexual techniques...
...to fulfill gentlemen such as you.
A little fellatio first, huh?
Oh, my. That's...
No, stop...
Prof. Kunisaki usually
likes anal, you see.
I see... Oh, this is too much!
Bravo, little music teacher!
You're hitting the
right spots in perfect rhythm!
Oh, yes! Yes! Yes!
Your technique is
wonderful, Miss Madonna!
The real service
is just starting, sir.
Now what are we doing?
Please.
Like this?
Has she snapped?
This is sort of scary.
Be gentle with me.
Here I go, you perverted,
fat fuck!
I'll get this all over
with as soon as I can!
I'll spread your ass apart
and lick it down deep!
Oh, yes!
Next, I'll fondle his balls,
then finger around his prostate.
Oh! Whoa! Hold on there!
What's wrong, sir?
The service has just begun.
Don't tell me you don't
want me to take you all the way.
A music judge doesn't run
when the song gets too loud!
Soon, now.
Hang in there, Miyuki!
Oh! Oh, no! Stop!
I can't hold it!
Now, Miyuki!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
A little more.
Just hang in there, Miyuki!
Bondage after the vibrator?
Still, Prof. Miyuki's
holding up very well.
Too tight?
Getting into it, Prof. Miyuki?
Go on, lick it!
Your tongue-work's as
great as your apparent innocence.
You have every right to
be proud of your technique.
Let's have some real service now,
to show your gratitude.
Oh, in we go. In... There!
Just let him do what he wants.
Let this all end soon!
Almost there! Hang on, Miyuki!
Magnificent!
I'm going to come!
It's over... Everything...
What's happening to my body?
I've never felt this way before.
I see myself becoming
dirtier and dirtier...
...and I'm scared.
When will this nightmare end?