Until that day...
Until that day,
everything was fine.
Maybe I was just resisting
an urge that existed inside me...
But now...
Yumi!
The Yumi I saw in the video
was under the control of a man.
The things that he was
doing to her were cruel.
- No, please!
- But I was powerless to stop it.
NO!!!
- Because I really did want
to have sex with her.
- No!
I couldn't deny the feelings
I was hiding inside of me.
And as if to provide
the proof of this...
...the man in the video was
none other than myself.
I wonder which one is the real me.
You smell nice.
Okay, now let me see.
Let me see... everything.
Stop it!
Stop it, please!
- Master...!
- Big Brother...
Didn't I tell you not to resist?
Until that day,
everything was fine.
But, Master...!
Look at that!
- But my heart has been swept by...
- Such a pretty little sheen it has.
...these feelings for a long time now.
- You were worth all the money
I paid for you!
If I had just suppressed
these feelings...
...which hurt so much
to keep inside me...
...perhaps our peaceful days
would have continued.
I'm changing, little by little.
Little by little,
ever since that day.
In my heart...
In my body...
So inexperienced...
Just the way I like them!
Master, please stop!
If you don't, I'll...!
I'll lose my mind...!
We're just getting started.
You're going to be my special pet.
Yes...
...Big Brother...
What Does Big Brother Want?
This is Yukio Hashiba.
And that's his daughter Yumi.
Yukio, this is my son.
Yuuto Sanada.
How do you do, sir?
Yukio Hashiba.
It's a pleasure.
Go on, Yumi. Say hello.
I'm... Yumi Hashiba.
The beach is nice
in the spring, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Yumi?
Y-yes?
I know you must still love
your late mother a lot...
I think remembering her is
really important for you to do.
But even as you treasure
your feelings for her...
...it's all right to accept
having a new family, isn't it?
No matter what,
I want you to think of me as family.
I'm also an only child...
I always wanted a big brother.
Could I maybe...
call you "Big Brother"?
And... I can just call you Yumi?
Big Brother...
Yumi.
Yumi...
Big Brother.
Big Brother, it's morning!
Time to get up!
Breakfast is ready!
Morning.
Morning!
Mom's away again?
Yeah. Business trip.
She phoned and said
she'd be home tomorrow.
Sorry you have to do all this
for me every day.
No prob.
I like doing stuff like this.
In the end, we became a family.
Five years have passed.
Looking back, I've loved Yumi
since the moment I first saw her.
And my feelings for her have matured
over these last 5 years.
But I never let Yumi know
how I feel about her.
And I've been tormented by
these feelings day after day.
I'm visiting her grave today.
Huh? Grave? Whose?
Who do you think?
Oh. Right. Your real mom's.
Sorry, I forgot.
It's okay.
So, is Yuki...
I mean, is Dad going with you?
He has a meeting at the office.
He said to meet him there.
He'll be going back to the office
and spending the night in a hotel.
I see.
5 years ago, I was full of hope.
I thought everything was
going to work out perfectly.
But, as the years
rolled by so quickly...
...life for us changed radically.
And our parents' relationship...
...isn't what it once was.
I'm off!
Sure. Take care.
Well, I should get going, too.
Shall we go?
Right...
I can't forgive my mother.
Want to get something to eat?
Oh, no.
I have to make dinner.
Yuuto!
Oh, sorry.
What were you saying?
Penny for your thoughts.
You look like
something's bugging you.
Both my parents will
be away tonight, so...
...you're afraid Yumi
will be all alone?
You really worry about
your sister, don't you?
Oh, well. Let's just call it
an early night tonight.
I'm really sorry.
Forgive me, Kaori...
But the truth is...
My real feelings are...!
Well, I'd better get back to work.
Sure. Oh, Dad?
Hm?
Once in a while...
Can we all eat together?
Together, as a family?
Yes, of course.
Well, see you.
How long...
How long can this family last?
How much longer
will I be Yuuto's sister?
Our parents' divorce is
a question of "when," not "if."
That's why I want to spend
every second I can with Yumi...
...before the end finally comes.
Whoops!
Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
Hm...?
This isn't mine.
It's yours now.
I'm home.
Yumi isn't home yet?
There was no label on it.
A strange feeling filled my body...
Isn't there anything
recorded on it?
And now for the last girl
of the day, gentlemen.
Have a look at this one!
The item for sale
is a virgin of rare beauty!
Okay, 4000! 4500! 4700!
This girl is our
finest offering today...
... and she's worth a high price!
No other bids?
Right! 4800! 4850!
Y-Yumi?
- Wh-where is this?
What's going on?!
- 6000!
- Wh-where is this?
What's going on?!
- 7000!
- Wh-where is this?
What's going on?!
- 7000! Do I hear higher?
- Yumi... Yumi isn't a thing to be sold!
- 7500!
No other bids?
All right, 7500...
Ten thousand!
What?!
Ten thousand! Ten thousand?!
All right, ten thousand!
I have ten thousand!
Ten thousand, ten thousand,
any higher bids? Ten thousand!
Impossible... Impossible!
That voice... That man is... He's...!
No other bids.
Sold for ten thousand!
Ten thousand... My God...
It's me! No, it can't be!
I wouldn't buy Yumi
like a THING!
Hm... What's your name?
- It's Yumi, sir.
- Don't touch her!
Don't touch my little sister...!
- I see. A pretty name.
- Don't touch her!
Don't touch my little sister...!
Thank you, Master.
Y-Yumi...!
I think I like you.
Welcome home, Master!
Hello, Nobuhiro.
I acquired a fine thing today.
Oh, she's lovely.
An excellent deal, Master.
The preparations are set?
Yes, sir. Enjoy yourself
to your heart's content.
Now, then...
Y- yes...?
Strip.
Wh-what's he...?!
Didn't you hear me?
I... I did.
- Then be quick about it.
- Yumi, don't! Stop it...
Y- yes, sir.
This... This isn't what I want!
- Y-Yumi...
- Are you pleased, sir?
What are you saying?
You still have some clothes on.
Surely...
just this is all right?
- Oh, dear... The girl seems to be a bit slow.
- Stop it! Stay away from her!
I own you, understand?
Y- yes, sir.
Do you remember
what I paid for you?
Y- yes, sir.
You have two choices:
Either pay the full price
to me right now...
... or else devote yourself to me,
body and mind.
Which will it be?
I can't... pay you the money.
Then you only have
one choice, understand?
Yes, sir.
- So beautiful...
I suddenly realized that,
bit by bit,
I was beginning to feel
like the man in the video.
What he saw, I was seeing.
What he thought, I was thinking.
If I didn't control myself...
if I didn't stop this...
...I was going to
turn into him completely.
I felt her.
So soft, so smooth...
The sensation of what he touched
was transmitted to me.
I was beginning to lose myself...
Oh, you feel so wonderful.
You almost seem to cling
to the palm of my hand.
I really can pick them, can't I?
But there are more essential parts
to test, aren't there?
Wh-what's he saying...?!
Stop it!
No...! Stop it!
Stop it...
NO!!!
STOP IT!!!
Big Brother!
Sorry I'm late.
I'll get dinner started right now.
S-sure!
Welcome home, Yumi!
Wh-what on Earth...?
Sorry for the wait.
Dig in!
Let's eat!
Hey, this stuff's great!
Really? Well, eat all you want.
Great! More, please!
Our peaceful life together.
But if the feelings I held for Yumi
were ever released...
...this happiness
would crumble away.
And now there's
this video tape which...
...seems to reveal what I keep
buried deep in my heart.
It was going to destroy
the peaceful life I shared with Yumi.
What was it, exactly?
Why did it have to exist?
It's morning...
God, your expression
is so forced!
Oh, morning, Big Brother.
Morning.
Nice to see you, Ruri.
Pardon the visit.
Morning, Big Brother.
Morning.
What's with the uniforms?
It's kinda dorky to wear them
after graduation.
Graduation pictures
for our scrapbooks!
Big Brother, can you get
a two-shot of Ruri and me?
Okay, here we go!
What does a mouse like to eat?
- CHEESE!
Okay, Yumi, you
take the next one.
Huh?
Get a two-shot of
me and Big Brother!
Ruri...?
I wish I was as
straightforward as Ruri.
What's wrong? Take it!
Oh, s-sorry.
- Why do I feel so strange?
- Sorry, I've gotta run.
Oh, darn it. Is it a date?
No, no, it's not that.
I'll just bet it isn't.
I'll hang out with you
next time, okay?
That's a promise, right?
C'mon, let's not do this.
Just relax.
He doesn't have anything
like that in here.
I'd be more worried
if he didn't have one!
Let's look for it while
we have the chance!
There, you see? Suspicious goods
found almost immediately.
Looks like he watched it
all last night...
...and just sort of
tossed it to the side.
No label, either.
It's GOTTA be...
Ruri, let's just stop!
Huh? Why?
Because!
Let's watch it together.
Count me out!
You can watch it by yourself.
Jeez...
Ruri, I have to buy
some groceries for dinner.
Can you mind the house
for me while I'm gone?
Sure. Take your time.
What exactly was that video?
I returned to the park
where this all began.
I couldn't find
any clues there, until...
Looking for something?
You... The girl from yesterday.
Am I?
The video...
You dropped it, right?
I'd like to return it.
That isn't necessary.
I said it was yours now,
remember?
So, it WAS you!
Why did you give me that...
that... disgusting thing?!
Is it really?
It's a magic video tape.
It has the power to show its owner
what will make him happy.
Make me happy?!
That thing will just destroy people!
Yes, if it's misused,
it can become...
...a cursed video which
will invite disaster.
So don't let anyone else
view or touch it.
Otherwise...
Otherwise... what?
Yumi, no!
Don't touch that video!
Now then, Ruri...
... do you understand
what this service involves?
Yes, Big Brother...
I've memorized the methods
and theories of service.
I lack practical experience,
so I'm just an amateur...
... but I wish to devote myself
to being the best I can be!
Very well said.
Then let us begin.
Yes, sir. If you'll excuse me.
I see. You're a novice,
but you have been practicing.
I like that.
Thank you... sir...
Okay, you're tolerably good.
Don't be so monotonous!
Use your tongue!
Synchronize your licking!
Yes, sir!
Hmm... Not bad.
Concentrate!
Your tongue-work's getting sloppy!
Yes, sir!
Big Brother... Big Brother...
I've always...!
Nobuhiro?
Yes, sir?
Lick Ruri's cunt!
Huh?!
M- me, sir?
Be quick about it!
As you command, sir.
No!
He can't do that!
It can only be Big Brother!
Oh God!
It feels so good...!
Big Brother... Big Brother...!
I'm going to...!
Fool! Who told you
to stop?! Continue!
P- please, Master!
What?!
I want you! I want IT!
I want YOU inside of me!
Then pay attention!
Now continue!
Y- yes, Master.
Nobuhiro, Ruri is proving
to be unsatisfactory.
Stick yours into her.
What?!
But, sir...!
Just do it!
As you command.
No, please! Anything but that!
No! I want my first time
to be with the Master!
I told you not to stop!
I'm ready, Master.
Hurry up!
No! NO!!!
Well done!
She's close to coming!
Big Brother...! Big Brother...!
I'm coming! I'm coming!
Master, I can't hold it anymore...!
I'm ready to come, too.
Yumi! Yumi, are you home?!
Yumi!
Ruri...?
Oh, no!
Ruri, what did you see?
Was it the same thing I saw?
I'm home!
What's going on?
Why's the door wide open?
Ruri? Are you in here?
Ruri? That's strange...
Is that... Big Brother's...
porn video?
That's the videotape
of happiness.
But don't let
anyone else watch it.
Otherwise...