Whoops!
Sorry, I'm in a hurry. Hm?
It's yours now.
Huh?
It all began that day...
That strange experience.
This is Yumi...!
Ooohhh...! No!
The "me" in the
mysterious video...
- No... Oh... NO!!!
...who was raping Yumi
was nothing like the real me.
Okay, here we go!
- Just what is this thing?
- Okay, say cheese!
To the real me, the girl who had
become my sister a few years ago...
...was angelic, an ideal girl
who I could never touch.
It's a magic video tape.
It has the power to show its owner
what will make him happy.
But, if it's misused...
...it can become a cursed video
which will invite disaster.
Yumi!
Ruri!
Oh, crap!
Yumi 's friend Ruri had apparently
watched the tape.
If Yumi ever found out
what was on it...!
It all began that day...
N- no!
No!
Big Brother, I'm Yours...
You're already wet,
aren't you?
Y... yes...
Oh, I feel so ashamed...
But my pussy throbs so much,
I can't help it.
It almost feels like it's waiting
for Big Brother to touch it...
So inexperienced...
Just the way I like them!
Little by little, ever since
that day, I was changing...
Ever since the day
the ecstasy...
...of my brother licking me
seemed to race through my body.
If I had gone on hiding my feelings,
as I had till then...
If I had,
we might still be happy.
But that day,
everything changed suddenly...
Look well, Yumi.
I'm going to stick this into
your lovely little mouth.
No! Have mercy on me!
Is this Big Brother's...?
Seeing a man's cock
for the first time...
...nearly took my breath away.
Go on! What are you
waiting for? Lick it!
Y- yes, sir.
My mouth resisted...
...but to please my brother,
I wanted to do it.
Delicious...
That's the way, Yumi.
Suck it down deep!
His cock was hot,
and it swelled to fill my mouth.
That's it! That's it!
Suddenly, Big Brother thrust
himself roughly into me.
As it pressed deep down my throat,
tears came to my eyes.
Big Brother's body
gradually began to tremble.
Hot, sticky fluid erupted
from his swollen member.
- It flooded into my mouth.
- Swallow it all, Yumi. Understand?
I swallowed it all
with great relish.
What an indecent dream...
That's right.
I have to just think of this as a dream.
I can't believe I'd ever
actually do it for real.
Big Brother would hate me...
Thinking that, regret filled me.
Big Brother...
Confused,
I began to cook the meal.
I knew this was my dream alone...
...but I'd die of embarrassment
if I heard his voice then.
Yumi. You're back?
Y-yeah.
We're actually all eating together
as a family for once...
...so I wanted to
get started early.
Just hang on and
I'll make us something good.
Right.
Give me a yell when it's ready.
Sure thing.
I walked Ruri to the station...
...then wasted some time
in a book store.
The lie spilled from me
so quickly...
That weird dream had made me
forget all about Ruri.
It took all my strength
to face my brother...
It's open?
Yumi never leaves it open.
Did she...?!
The same old tension in the air...
Yumi senses it, too.
Say, dear?
Hm? What?
Where did you go last Sunday?
Here it comes...
Nowhere.
Just out for a walk.
I see.
You came back so late.
So what if I did?
It's none of your business.
I think it still is.
We are still...
This again?
I'm free to go wherever I want!
No, you're not!
We are still a family!
I see how you might
be mistaken about that!
Dammit!
I'm done!
Um, I'll get it!
Yumi, I want to believe
you didn't watch it.
Please show me
that I'm wrong!
Hello, Hashiba residence.
Yes. Good evening...
Big Brother, it's Kaori.
What's she want now?
Hello?
Oh, Yuuto.
Can we see that video you
promised to show me tomorrow?
Oh, you're calling about that.
Look, I always let you take off
to be with your sister.
How about a little
me time for once?
Don't make it sound like that!
But that was Yumi
who answered just now, right?
You're all alone?
With our parents!
Later.
Kaori was definitely
my girlfriend,
but ever since Yumi became my sister,
she'd become almost obsessive.
That's why I hid
my feelings for Yumi.
I'd told neither of them.
It was my secret.
But I was more
worried about Yumi.
I don't think Yumi
would ever take...
...a video from my room
without permission.
But the way Ruri was acting...
And the TV left on in Yumi's room...
Filled with dread,
I viewed the tape again.
That same sweet smell
seemed to come from the tape.
- Master... Master...
That same sweet smell
seemed to come from the tape.
That voice...?!
Where is this now?
It's a different video than before!
- Master, are you sure you want to do this?
- Huh? It's Yumi...
Relax.
I do what I want to do.
You needn't worry about it.
A me that wasn't
really "me" again...
Still, if the mistress
sees you like this...
She'll get mad again, right?
Oh, Yuuto...
What are you doing?
- Mistress. Good morning.
- Huh?! What's Kaori doing here?
- Cleaning, as you can see.
Doing that low-class
work again...
- W-well, I don't mind.
- When does this take place?
- So, what are you doing here?
- I heard Kaori's family was
rich back in the 1920's.
- Nothing. Everything bores me.
- I didn't expect to see her this time, too.
What about that horse
you just bought?
Bored with it already?
Yeah, I tired of
that horse ages ago.
You said how much
you wanted a thoroughbred...
... but you lost interest
in your new toy again?
Does the son-in-law
dare criticize me?
First of all, quit cleaning.
How about studying
to be a politician?
Are you really my fiancee?
- What? Fiancee? Politician?
What the hell...?
- This is a type of study, too.
Don't be ridiculous!
I won't have it!
Yumi, what about you?!
Don't let my fiancee do this!
Y- yes, Mistress. Excuse me.
H- hey! Cut it out, Kaori!
She did nothing wrong!
M- Master!
Don't touch me!
What are you doing?! Pervert!
P- pervert? Hold on here!
We're engaged!
So what if I touch you?
We're not married yet,
so don't push your luck!
Kaori!
Dammit...
Master...
Are you all right?
Y- yeah. Sorry for
getting you in trouble, too.
It's okay, really.
I think Mistress Kaori is mean to you.
It can't be helped.
I'm the lowly fiancee, remember?
No, she treats you a lot worse
than you deserve!
Maybe so, but...
Don't you want
to get back at her?
Huh?! What are you saying?!
At this rate, marrying her
won't improve your situation.
You know what'll happen.
You want to be henpecked
for the rest of your life?! So...
I couldn't believe my own ears.
That Yumi would say
something like that...
Yeah... You're right.
Okay, let's do it!
Lmpossible! Are they serious?!
Stop it! Don't!
Since watching that video...
...which made me have
that indecent dream today...
...I find I can't
resist temptation.
Yuuto, I'm here!
That voice... Kaori...?
It isn't the same video as before.
Sorry to call you out here.
Big Brother? What's he doing
in this storehouse?
So, what's up? What was so
important you had to show me?
Yuuto, what are you doing?!
I'm going to shut
that mouth of yours.
MISTRESS Kaori...
What are you doing?!
Stop fighting me already!
Big Brother,
what are you doing?!
Stop it!
Yuuto!
What's the matter with you?!
What's the meaning of this?!
I'm your fiancee.
You should let me touch you all over!
Stop it! What are you saying?!
D- don't be ridiculous!
Let me out of here!
I can't. Not until...
you bow down to me.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're marrying into
MYfamily, after all!
You don't seem to
understand your situation.
Stop it!
What a fine look for you,
Mistress Kaori.
That's... I'd seen Kaori's body
many times before...
...but it had never excited me
the way it did now!
Yuuto?!
Your nipples are getting so-o-o hard
from the stimulation, aren't they?
You never allowed me
to touch them before.
I'm impressed, Kaori.
You have a lovely body.
What are you doing?!
I never had to do this
to get Kaori to fuck me!
Y- Yumi?
Yumi, don't you think
Kaori has a lovely face?
Yes. It's lovely, Mistress.
Mistress,
you look so lovely now.
What are you doing here?!
The Master and I are working together.
Do you understand?
Y- you both...?
Are you ready?
Yes, Master.
It's your fault, Kaori.
All you did was insult me.
Big Brother, don't!
I wanted to shout that...
...but my body also grew hot
at the thought of...
- Come on, Yumi.
...giving to Kaori what she
was getting in the video.
- Let's have Kaori lick your wet pussy.
...giving to Kaori what she
was getting in the video.
- Let's have Kaori lick your wet pussy.
No! Not that!
She'll never be able to do it.
Kaori values her pride
more than anyone else!
Yumi! Do it!
Straddle Kaori's face!
- Right!
- Right...
Just as I thought.
Look how wet you are, Yumi.
Go on, straddle her! Do it!
Yumi! You lick, too!
Lick Kaori's crotch!
B-Big Brother... Why?
- Why are you doing this?
- Go on, lick each other! Lick!
R- right!
Lt... feels so good...
But I want to do it with you
more than Kaori, Big Brother!
So strange...
Like a dazzling trance...
But I want Big Brother
inside of me!
- Last night's video showed
some pretty weird stuff.
- Come in.
- Doing that to Kaori...?
- Knock-knock!
Here you go, Kaori.
Thanks.
Haven't seen you in a while.
You doing okay, Yumi?
Y-yeah...
You're as cute as ever, Yumi.
Graduated yet?
Uh, yeah.
I see.
So, you're legal now, huh?
K-Kaori!
What are you saying, Kaori?!
I... I wouldn't do that...
My, my, what an
upright young lady.
Oh, no...
Still, that was how we celebrated
graduation, right, Yuuto?
C-c'mon, Kaori!
Quit saying that stupid stuff!
It's hardly stupid.
Lovers need excuses
to do things like that.
Anyway, you came over
to see a video.
Thanks, Yumi. See you later.
R-right...
What does Big Brother
see in a girl like Kaori?
I mean, she's pretty
and stylish, I guess.
But she's selfish and says
weird stuff without any cares.
I could never like
anyone like that.
Kaori, what's wrong with you?
Saying that in front of Yumi...!
So what if I did?
You say too much stuff
that'll have a bad influence on her!
Worrywart.
Yumi's 18 now.
You don't have to worry
about her so much.
Kaori!
Right, right. Understood.
I'll just watch what I say
from now on, okay?
Okay. Thanks.
Jeez, you're so straitlaced
when it comes to her.
I know you don't think much
about what you say...
...butjust be careful what you say
in front of Yumi now.
I have to go meet
Akechi right now.
Huh?
It's okay. I'll be right back.
Well, pick up some potato chips
or something while you're out.
Sure thing.
So, now what do I do?
Why not check out what
we'll be watching tonight?
Th-that's me! Where was this...?
What's going on?!
- Well, Kaori?
Are you ready to submit to me?
- Yuuto? But it's not Yuuto. Why...?
Yuuto, let me go!
Let me out of here!
What is he doing to me?!
Why...?
Let me go and I won't
tell anyone what you did!
I'm pathetically begging him...
- What do you want? Money? Social status?
- What's going on?
Kaori, what I want is your body.
What're you saying?!
Are you mad?!
Your body and your heart
shall become my slaves.
Slaves...?
That's what I've
said to you so often.
What? Why am I
struggling with Yuuto?
You don't want me.
You want to own me and
then brag about it to everyone.
You'll only be satisfied
by their jealousy!
Isn't that it?!
Don't be so egotistical!
I'm shutting that mouth
of yours right now!
What are you doing?! Stop it!
What are you saying?
The fun's just starting now.
That's right, Mistress Kaori.
Yumi? What're you doing here?
Now then, Yumi,
what shall we do with Kaori?
Well, there's something
I'd like to see.
Oh?
Wh-what do you
think you're doing?
Sure. Do as you like.
Thank you, Master.
No, not that! No, let me go!
What a fine sight.
See how round her cunt is?
So, what do you want to do?
I've always wanted to see
another girl piss herself.
No! There's no way I'd do that!
Meaning what?!
You don't seem to understand...
... you're in no position to object,
Mistress Kaori.
Go on, Ruri.
Lick Mistress Kaori's cunt, would you?
Huh?
Huh? That girl...
- Isn't that Yumi's classmate?
- The bitch licks her puppy's
crotch to make it piss.
R-right...
Pardon me.
S- stop it!
Stop it! Have mercy!
Ruri, move your tongue more.
Yes, sir!
Ruri, no...!
Well, Mistress Kaori?
Starting to like it?
Of course I don't!
Not like this!
But you won't know
unless you try it.
No... No more...
You must bear this, Mistress.
I can't hold it in...!
You're starting to leak.
What a dirty, dirty
little lady you are!
How lovely, Mistress Kaori!
Don't look at me!
How cruel...
Sorry I took so long,
Kaori... Hm?
First, Ruri... now Kaori's
seen that video.
At this rate, everyone's
relationships will be ruined!
What'll I do?
Since I had that strange dream,
I can't resist that video.
Its sweet smell...
still hangs in the air.
Big Brother is humiliating Kaori,
beating her with a whip.
But I don't pity her.
Yes...
Maybe, in reality, I hate her.
Now do you see?!
You're my slave!
Seeing the arrogant Kaori
brought low by my brother...
- Have mercy, Yuuto...
- Her pride in tatters...
- It was like a dream come true for me.
- All right, Kaori. What shall we do now?
Big Brother was delighting
in his humiliation of Kaori.
Master...
Why not use this now?
No, please!
A candle. How intriguing.
Yes.
All right, you try it.
No! Yumi, you're
just a servant!
I'm a servant,
but you're a slave.
Too hot!
I love her expression!
She likes it so much...
- her nipples are swelling!
- This is a dream.
The real me could never do that.
But if it's a dream,
anything I do is all right.
Realizing that, I began to enjoy
the secret cruelty in me...
...which let me
humiliate Kaori like this.
So hot!
Master, the candle's
dripped into her cunt.
Oh, has it now? Yes, it has.
That wet pussy of hers
is starting to harden.
Don't look at me!
Well, you can't use it now,
can you?
What are they talking about?
I can't believe how cruel...
- we're being to her.
- Let's see if I can use this or not, shall we?
Big Brother...!
He let down his pants and...
- pulled out his huge, wonderful cock.
- Well?!
And then...
How do you like getting it from
the rear, like a horse?! Or a dog?!
You like it?! Like it?!
But I... I wanted him
to do that to me, not her.
No... I don't want to see this!
No!
I'm coming!
Lt... It made me too jealous!
My head was filled
with an unbearable longing!
Yumi...
- I heard my brother's voice calling me.
- Yumi...
When I came to,
Big Brother was holding me...
...in the video.
M- Master!
Watching me and Kaori
must have aroused you.
No, I...
- Before I knew it, my master
had taken off all my clothes.
- I...!
- Before I knew it, my master
had taken off all my clothes.
- I know. Now I'll reward you.
- Before I knew it, my master
had taken off all my clothes.
My heart was pounding so fast...
...I thought I might die...
- Th-thank you, Master!
...as what I so wished for came true.
I began to cry, because
Big Brother and I were finally...
Oh... Master!
Are these...
- Are these my real feelings?
- Even your breasts are pretty.
- Impossible...
- Your nipples are so pert.
You're embarrassing me.
Ah, and you're so wet
down there, too, Yumi.
Down there...!
Big Brother slipped his fingers
into me to tease my wet cunt...
Yumi, let's do it!
Oh... Big Brother's...
His huge, enormous cock...
Yumi... So pretty...
Oh! Into me! Into me!
Th-thank you!
Yumi! Yumi!
In the dream, I could
have sex with my brother...
- Yumi...!
...right in front of Kaori...
- It feels so good! So good...!
- It was only a dream...
- Yumi! That's the way!
...and yet happiness
overflowed inside me.
Master!
In the dream,
I could be honest with my brother.
But in reality,
the dream could never come true.
He must never know
about the dirty dreams I have.
- Big Brother...