Sigh.
As is usual of space journeys...
the ship travels with many dreams.
But I am...
Captain! It's time for departure!
Please hurry back to the ship!
Ah? Captain,
are you listening to me? Captain!
Hey! Hello! Captain.
What? No!! Please stop it!
Wait a minute. Stop it!
Please!!
My real journey has not yet started.
Oh, a shooting star.
If I make a wish,
my journey might finally start.
I may get to meet
a new man somewhere.
Ahhhhh!!
Like this?
Yes, push right there.
Here.
Do you want to see this?
Who are you talking to?
Never mind. Keep going.
All right, Kei.
Please, let me meet a
wonderful man on this journey.
Ah... not there!!
I want to meet...
...a wonderful man!!
I said!!
Uh, I wonder how long they
will be doing this?
Ms. Jannis.
How long do you plan to sleep?
I'm tired because I just had sex.
Ah, can't I sleep a little more?
Uahhhhhh! Hey, hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Put this on.
H... hey, what is this?
You look very nice.
What are you trying to do?
Uaaaaa!!
Now he's caught in a headlock!
Uaaaaaa!! What is this?
What the hell did you build
on the bridge of my ship?
Well, let's start.
Hey!!!
Why don't you listen to me!?
Taiyo's cultivation of aesthetic
sensitivity series. Episode 265.
"New married couples love dinnertime.
Hold me in the sunset"
Action!
I still don't understand, but...
...why are you making me do this?
Ms. Jannis, the miso soup is boiling.
What!?
Ah!? Ouch, ouchchch.
As I thought, Ms. Jannis has a
talent to be a playful new wife.
Taiyo, follow me.
Ah!? Yeah.
But, is this?
This is a part of your education.
What am I supposed to do?
Just look.
Keep looking, keep looking...
It's a little too high.
OK, stop right there.
Taiyo, this is what we call
"The Naked Apron." It makes men crazy.
Naked Apron?
Say louder!
Ready!
Naked Apron!!
Touch it.
Yeah.
Noooooooo!!
Did you get crazy?
Did you get excited?
I don't really know.
Something's wrong. This is
the legend of the Naked Apron.
You guys are what's wrong!!
What is this thing for?
I have been teaching various
kinds of sex to Taiyo, but...
Some techniques are
really hard to learn.
Still, there are so many
setups we haven't covered yet.
Ms. Jannis, the miso soup.
Ahhhhhh, hot, hot, hot.
There is dust here.
Uh, I'm sorry.
No, what am I saying?!
You guys are wrong!
You know?
Newly married couples are shy, and
they have some bittersweet feelings.
Your miso soup is very good,
Ms. Jannis.
Oh, I'm glad.
Too salty,
and you cut the daikon unevenly.
Sorry about that!
By the way, Kei, you said you have
something you have to look for.
What is it?
It's Virginia.
Virginia?
What the hell is that?
Virginia is the central
circuit of Agga Ruter.
It's necessary in order
for me to accomplish my primal mission.
Your primal mission?
Do you have a mission?
Besides the role of Taiyo's sex machine?
Ms. Jannis, that's too much to say.
I... is it?
I can't talk about my mission
to anybody except my master.
It is locked by a privacy circuit.
Humph!
But how can we look for Virginia?
I accessed the secret network with
the computer of this ship, and...
...it's searching the data now.
What? You used the computer
of my ship without asking me!
Yes, I did.
Access OK.
Show me on the screen.
Stop! That computer is...!!
Hi, everybody! How are you?
How are you!?
How is Morokichi doing today?
Doing all right! I'm too good!
So I'm peeing.
Peeee!
Well, I will talk about Virginia today.
Heeeei!
This is an interesting computer.
I said stop using it.
Virginia is in a luxury ship
named Millennia Mule.
A luxury ship
you can even have sex inside.
Millennia Mule was made by a
multimillionaire of the galaxy, Mr. Narcis.
Mr. Narcis carries jewelry
on his ships as a symbol.
One of them is Virginia.
He must be a showy guy.
Morokichi, watch your mouth!
Ouch!
Therefore, if you want to get Virginia,
let's go on the Millennia Mule!
Let's go on the Millennia Mule!
Go!
I don't recommend that.
That's a big luxury ship.
We should assume it's well armed.
If we go there with one pirate ship,
they'll blow us up instantly.
Virginia was originally ours.
What if we ask them to return it to us?
Ridiculous! I'm a pirate,
and I know what I'm talking about.
We will never win
if we play fair.
Then let's take an illegal action.
Illegal action?
Looking for a part-time job?
Yes!!!
I will decide where you should work
based on each one's qualification.
Is that all right?
Any way you want!!!
Umm!
I guess he didn't realize.
I perfectly fooled
the human resources computer.
Now we just have to look for Virginia.
For the time being,
let's investigate by doing work.
Then I will go clean up the ship.
I am a hostess at a restaurant.
Let me know
if you find something!
And, I am the airhead waitress.
Uh? Hey! Is this
the work I'm qualified for?
Uahhhh.
Uh?
Oh, I can't help it. Ahhhh. Uhhhhh.
Stop it!
We are on the luxury liner.
You should be discreet
with a dignified attitude!
Oh, I'm sorry.
But do you really
think they'll be here?
I'm absolutely sure.
I've already checked
that Jannis accessed this ship.
Because of that, I found out
where Virginia is.
I see. It was a case of killing
two birds with one stone.
An inheritance of the Fighter
Civilization, Virginia.
We will get it first.
After that, we will have our revenge
on Jannis, and take care of the others.
I'm sorry.
I'm not so used to this.
I will bring a
replacement right now.
Table number three.
One beef bowl!!
There she is.
We found her so easily.
Humph! The people from the
Agga Ruter must be around too.
I will find them no matter what!
Here's your soup.
Uh?
Ah?
Oh no!? Where am I?
Wow!!
This is beautiful.
Oh? There is already
another visitor here.
Hello!
Yes! Hello!
How did you get here?
This place isn't even on the map.
I saw the star.
But, why is this place
not on the map?
This place has been kept secret
since the owner made this ship.
I accidentally found it too.
Hey! Why don't we sit down
and talk a little while?
Yes.
I'm Martha.
I'm the captain of this ship.
I'm Taiyo.
Taiyo, let's keep this place secret
between you and me.
All right, but why?
If a lot of people find out about this,
it will get too noisy.
I see.
I visit here often
when something bothers me.
This place calms me.
But it's not good that
I always look up at the sky to relax.
What is wrong with that?
A long time ago, I got excited from
just looking at the stars.
Words like dream, adventure,
and freedom made me so excited.
When I talked about it with my
colleagues, our eyes shined with dreams.
The reason I joined this company is that
Mr. Narcis paved the way to outerspace.
But he got too old,
and couldn't move anymore.
So this company changed too.
There is a peace maintained by
the defense force on this safe route.
We can't achieve the victory
on our own anymore.
It's not that I don't like it,
but I still don't want to give up!
I expect somebody may take me away,
and take me on a new journey...
...I'm still thinking of that.
If it is such a journey,
why don't you quit work and go?
It's not as easy as that.
There are so many things to do
as a captain.
Those things are more important
than your journey?
I think you should go on the journey
if you want to.
It's not a good thing
to lie to yourself and others.
Kei told me that.
You are strange.
Am I?
By the way,
did you join to become a sailor?
No, I came here to get Virginia.
What?
What????
I heard it's on this ship.
So I came here with Kei,
and pirate Jannis in disguise.
But, we couldn't find it at all.
Are you a pirate?
No!
I'm Taiyo.
What!?
Where is Virginia?
It's in the captain's cabin.
Can you let me have it?
You say that
without any difficulty?
Virginia is a symbol of this ship.
This ship must have it!
Then can I have the whole ship?
Whaaaaat!?
Uh... you surely have a big dream.
But it is the captain's job
to manage it.
If you want it,
work hard and become captain.
I can't spend
so much time to do that.
No way! The only person who carries
the key to the safe is me, the captain.
I will give it to you
if you could come to the captain's cabin.
I just go to the captain's cabin.
I think it's not so easy,
but work hard and come pick it up.
Yes, I will!!
Uh, I'll be waiting for you.
"I'll be waiting for you," Humph!
Kei, and Ms. Jannis.
How long were you standing there?
But, it might be a setup.
But we don't have any other clue,
let's just try going there.
Well, the captain's cabin is over there.
And the strategy is?
Just bang in there,
and escape quickly.
Uh.
Captain?
Ah!?
Hello, Taiyo is here.
Taiyo?
What are you doing here?
I came here to get Virginia.
Are you still talking about that?
Hello!
What? Ah... Ah...
May I come in!?
I'm coming in.
I have been looking
at so many stars.
"Tell me saint darling
Galaxy War Series"
But I finally found
the most beautiful star.
The star is inside your eyes.
Well, I didn't know
it was like this.
Did she get this far?
She must be really enjoying it.
What's wrong?
You said come and pick it up.
I'm sorry to bother you.
We'll leave as soon as we get Virginia.
Captain, are you there?
I'm Assistant A.
I'm here to give you the regular report.
Can you take care of that?
Why don't you do something
before you ask another person!?
What? What? What!?
She is reading Ms. Martha's DNA.
DNA?
What is she doing? Captain!
What if she's tied up
with masking tape by three pirates?
If it is so, I shouldn't just wait here!
Captain! I'm coming in.
Is there any problem on the ship?
N... nothing serious
to cause trouble on our voyage.
I see. You can leave now.
You are so beautiful...
Captain,
were you doing it again?
I asked you not play the game
when you're on duty!
Oh, shit!
I must confiscate it.
It's not necessary.
That kind of thing should be...
...erased!
Darling...
Is this OK with you?
You should pull out
the code from the bottom.
Oh God, all the data must be gone.
Then I will go back on duty!
Thanks for the report.
Now, let's get Virginia.
Uh.
Kei!!
W... what's the matter with her?
Are you all right? Kei.
What's wrong?
Morning sickness?
Taiyo... Uhh.
What are you guys doing?
In this kind of situation!
In this kind of place!
Doing such a thing!
Hey, hey!!!
Kei needs strong close contact
when she captures DNA inside her.
Don't say "Ah."
What can I do about these people?
Oh well, I'm going to get Virgina.
You guys should keep
your eyes on the captain!
Hey, hey! I can't help them.
Well, why are you looking
at them so attentively?
Oops, don't turn your head away!
Is this the first time you've seen
your own sex scene? I guess so.
What a dirty look she has!
She sweats all over, screaming,
and even chokes with tears.
What's wrong? I know
you want to see yourself having sex.
That's you!
That's your real desire inside of you.
Don't say no!
You also want him.
Your body is getting hot.
I can smell female
pheromones from you.
It's not only your body.
You also want him from
the bottom of your heart.
Just like you finally met a man for whom
you've been waiting for a long time.
Aren't you envying the one
who is having sex with him right now?
Don't you want him to do
the same thing with you?
Hey, why don't you say
what you want him to do?
What's wrong?
Taiyo.
Can you make love to me too?
Sure, Martha, come on.
Now, in the meantime, I'm...
That must be it!
Where is the lock?
Wow! This is challenging.
Let's see.
I will start from the top.
Wh... what is this?
What's happening to me?
Uh... I barely finished one.
Well, next,
let me do the bottom one.
No!! I can't do that!
N... No!
Don't look! Don't look!
Little by little.
Uh... Uh...
I guess I could somehow handle this.
I will come.
I will be finished!!
All right! I can finish!
This is the last card!
Calm down. Calm down.
Here we go!
C... come!!
This is it!!
Damn it!
It's very close.
I got it!
Yes, indeed! They are the
pirates on the wanted list.
They broke into the
captain's cabin, and now...
they must be going down
to the seventh dock.
Who am I?
I'm nobody.
I'm just a good citizen.
Humph! Are you preparing?
Yes! Perfectly!
All right!
Hey! I've got Virginia!
We shouldn't stay long.
Let's move quickly!
You guys are too much!
The Rayler is anchored
at the dock.
We'll be in danger
if we don't escape quickly!
OK, now it's safe!
Will Martha be all right?
She will wake up soon!
It might have been too much
for her to deal with you guys.
Is that so?
Well, I hope she's having
a good dream.
Tai... yo.
I left the cleaning kit there.
Do you like to clean up so much?
But, I work part-time
with the cleaning crew.
Why don't you stay here and
seriously do your work?
We've got Virginia now.
Who wants to stay in such
a place for so long?
By the way, can't you tell me
why you need this?
I'm sorry, but I can't tell
anybody but my master.
"You can't tell anybody
but your master"...
Well, if you say so.
Anyhow, we can escape without any
problem because of your appearance.
Oh no.
Space pirate Jannis!
You are now completely surrounded.
Just put down your weapon
and surrender quietly!
W... what are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
We already know everything!
I don't know anything.
I don't know either.
We will take everybody into custody.