I can't wait any longer...
...make me come.
Uh... not yet.
Ah...
I can't stand this.
Little more... ahhh...
...just wait a second.
Captain! Those pirates have
started to take action!
Such bad timing...
I'll be right there.
So, is that it?
Well, let's continue
this again later.
Drop your weapons and
surrender obediently!
W... what the?
What's going on?
What's this all about?
You can't escape anymore!
Release the hostage and the captain.
Space army...?
Who the hell reported us to them?
If you harm the hostages,
or don't surrender...
...we will open fire!!
Damn!
Hey, Kei.
Yes.
I'm the one they want.
I'll surrender for now,
and rescue me later.
I understand.
Uhhh. Wow.
She is the real one.
This is the real one!
There is a tag on her.
- Just move your hands away!
- Yeah, I can't see.
- I guess they discovered the truth.
- Yes...
Take them!
Let me go! Hey!
Why are you touching? Bastard!
Imprison the pirate in Minamo!
Medic!
Take the captain to sick bay!
Humph!
What is going on?
Somebody reported us
to the space army! Damn it!
Who did it?
Who knows?
By the way, why did they make me
wear such a weird outfit?
I think
because you were too violent.
So, what should we do now?
Let's wait and see how it goes,
and find a way to escape.
I understand.
Let's keep Taiyo as a "hostage."
Hey, hey, hey!
The money I loaned you has now
accumulated to 100 Ryo with interest.
I want you to pay back the
entire amount by today!
I only borrowed 3 Ryo!
How come you say 100 Ryo?
Everybody knows you have to pay
interest on the money you borrowed.
If you refuse to pay,
I will take you to the police!
Please, can't you wait one more month?
Just one more month.
You must be joking!
If you say you can't pay me back...
N... no!
Then you should pay me back
with Miyo's body.
Kei... what does he mean
by paying back with her body?
He wants to have sex instead
of paying back the money.
Is sex something
that can be used as payment?
Please don't...
Please don't touch Miyo.
Shut up!
Taiyo's cultivation
of sentiments series. Episode 266.
What is it?
No!
Don't touch me!
Please don't... please.
Shut up.
Hey!
Why don't you take mine off too?
I can't do that.
Why not?
We need that rope
for today's education.
What is it? No!
Taiyo.
Yes?
Look at this.
- No, not that one.
- No!! Grandpa! Help me!
What is it?
Men get very excited when they
force a woman into physical contact.
But it seems like she's hating that.
You shouldn't just look on the
surface and make a decision.
Some men seem to think
that no means yes.
Even if she says no, you can make
the relationship deeper...
if you handle the situation right.
Hey! Don't misinform him!
It's too difficult
for me to understand.
Then let's just try.
What's going on?
No!
Let me go!
Such a debt will kill a woman!
Paying off with her nubile body.
Ready! Action!
What? What? What?
What can I do?
Just follow the video!
Yeah.
Turn!
Great turn!
Well, what's next?
Let me taste you before I sell you.
Uhhh. Miyo.
Noooo.
Taiyo!
You shouldn't look!
Ah.
Hey!
You have a great body.
You can get lots of customers.
Stop!
Jannis, your acting is great.
I really want him to stop.
Why?
Because that old man is
looking at us.
After you go through it,
being watched makes you feel excited.
This book says so.
That is a lie!
Taiyo! Keep going!
Yes.
No!!!
Your mouth doesn't lie.
It's already wet.
I don't like this,
but my body is very hot.
No.
No!!!
Don't shoot this!
Do you want me to stop now?
No!
Don't stop.
Please.
Well, do you want me to stop?
I keep telling you to stop.
It's time to give you
my wild shogun!
Oh, no.
It's bigger than Shinkichi's.
Uh? No! No!
It's not romantic at all.
Somebody is watching us, and
you are almost raping me!! No!
It's for Taiyo's education.
Be patient.
Then, go to heaven with this!
Nooo.
What?
What happened, Kei?
I guess it's broken.
Then this will be...
...the end too?
We have no choice.
Whew.
We will continue after we repair it.
No!
Yes.
I see.
They said they would investigate us.
Investigate?
I understand. Is that so?
You mean, that boy is a hostage.
Yes.
I see. Then I will release only him.
Well, then.
Excuse me.
Can I go back to the ship?
Yes, you can.
Taiyo.
You are free to go.
What about Kei?
What about Jannis?
They will be executed soon.
You can't do that.
It's space law to execute pirates!
You can complain to Captain Claire!
Captain Claire?
What is this?
Hello.
Hurry. Hurry up.
No, I can't.
You should. I don't have much time.
Be a good boy,
and be patient for a while.
Forgive me.
I can't be with you anymore.
Don't say such a thing.
I'm just a tool to you.
I'm coming in.
Let me come in.
Ahhh, one moment.
Please! When I finish this...
It's somehow dark here.
You are always saying the same thing.
"When I finish this."
What is there after that?
If you leave now,
I can't finish this on time.
They will be here any minute
to pick this up...
That is not my problem.
Good-bye.
Ahhh.
Nooo.
What's wrong with you?
I just made him work for two days.
How can he leave me?
This must be a bug!
What else could it be?
Well, I finished 107 pieces.
But I only made 1,700 in Gold...
Excuse me.
I don't have time to do this,
while I'm working...
Excuse me.
Are you Ms. Claire?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I still haven't finished
this month's quota yet.
What?
Yes, I'll pay my debt back!
But please wait
just one more month.
One more month?
Oh!
Well.
Don't be ridiculous!
Then what am I supposed to do?
If you can't pay me back...
I will take your body!
What?
Hey!
Hahaha.
Turn.
Uhh. Miyo. Please forgive me.
I will taste you before I sell you!
What are you doing?
You have a great body,
so you can get lots of customers.
No...
Uhh.
It's not time for me to do this.
Hey, the Captain is calling us.
Just ignore it. She just wants us
to help her with her side job.
Once we go there, we can't come
back for at least for 2 days.
You are right.
What's going on?
Why is nobody answering?
This is an emergency call.
Why?
When did you take off my clothes?
No.
Oh, no. He's a technician.
Why did you stop?
- Well.
- Yes.
What should I do after this?
What?
Who are you?
I'm Taiyo.
Aren't you the loner?
No.
What?
No!!
Why didn't you tell me that first?
Why didn't you?
I'm sorry.
It felt good though.
I have something to tell you.
What am I thinking?
I have things to take care of right now.
No! I'm very busy right now.
I can help you if you want me to.
But I can't pay you.
You don't need to.
Then help me! Please help me!
Sure.
Helping me for free?
What a nice person you are!
Oh, well. I have to hurry.
Hey, please hurry and help me.
Are these all flowers?
Yes.
I guess you like flowers very much.
I'm not doing this because I like it.
Then why?
To make money!
But you are a captain
in the space army.
After I pay the debt
that my parents left for me...
my salary disappears
every month.
I can only make a little money
with this kind of a side job.
I don't even know
when I can pay off all the debt.
Is it true?
Then, why did you join the army?
Well, listen. The army is...
...when you are first recruited...
...they give you room, uniform and,
...three meals a day.
And you can get certain licenses,
degrees, and they'll give you a salary.
After I lost everything, the army
was a great place for me to be.
I see.
The army must be a good place to stay.
Reality is not
as easy as you think.
Their training is very hard, and you
have to study hard, without sleeping.
After I went through all of that hell,
I was assigned to the ship...
...the royalty and nobility,
and aristocracy...
and other prestigious people are
the only ones who get promoted fast.
They don't care for people like us.
I know it!
If I came from a high-class family,
I could be promoted much quicker...
and my salary would get
higher and higher.
I could even get a
place that had a bathtub.
Where can you find the officer
who goes to the public bath?
Uhh, who are you?
I'm Taiyo.
You were a hostage of the pirate.
Yes.
What do you want from me?
I want you to release Kei and Jannis.
What makes you think
I can do such a thing?
They're pirates.
We had a reason for doing that.
I can't release them
no matter what.
If I let pirates escape,
I'll be demoted.
In the worst case,
I'd get fired under martial law.
How can I pay back my
debt if I get fired?
Therefore, I can't do that!
Please,
they are not bad people.
I think you're a nice person.
You helped me out for free...
but if I let the pirates go
after we arrested them...
Don't you believe me?
But we just met each other...
and we don't even know
each other that well.
What am I talking about?
Ah, then I have a good idea!
To get to know each other.
Huh?
Physical relationship.
We just did it a little while ago!
No! I don't have time for this.
No, no, no.
Taiyo!
No also mean yes... yes... yes...
I see Kei.
What?
Ah... wha... what? What?
Ah... no, no!
Your mouth down here is very honest.
It's already wet.
No! No!
How is it?
Do you want me to stop now?
I'm telling you to stop!
N... no!!
Uhhhh, Miyo!
You grew up
in front of my very eyes.
No! Stop!
It's time to give you my wild shogun!
Oh! It's big!
Dirty sow! You can't pay back money!
So go to heaven with this!
Miyo!
Well,
I don't know what to do after this.
I don't have time...
Oh, well.
No, no.
Uhhh. Quotas... my quotas...
I couldn't tell about Taiyo.
What am I thinking?
F... finished.
Ms. Claire?
That's it.
Ms. Claire! Ms. Claire!
Please let me sleep.
No, wait!
Hello!
Did you finish this week's task?
It's all over there. Just take it.
All right.
Hey, move these things out!
OK.
What a dirty room!
Ah, I'm sorry.
I will clean up right now.
Cheapest price in space.
We don't need this.
I will come back next week.
I will deposit the money
to your account as usual.
Ms. Claire, excuse me.
Where is the master key of the jail?
I told you it's over there,
so just take it!
Ah, this is it!
Then!
I'll borrow this for a while.
Turn off the light when you leave!
Yes.
Good night.
Answer!
Why did you try to steal Virginia!?
What is your purpose?
How do you do, KA-3?
Shiunk!
Oh, do you know me?
You are the one who killed
Taiyo's parents, right?
Unfortunately,
I can't remember anything right now.
I will check my diary
when I get home.
It's just like
what's written on the epitaph.
Please take her carefully.
I got it.
Terrorists are on the ship!
Terrorists are now in
eight different places.
The number of terrorists are unknown.
We are sounding the emergency alarm.
Level 3, level 3.
Sending the emergency call.
Don't send any more soldiers
to the medical room.
Close the bulkhead immediately!
Check terrorist movement
within the bulkhead!
That is...
Captain! Captain!
Please give us an order.
The passengers' safety
is the first priority.
All the security guards should be
armed to engage the enemy.
Call the destroyer "Minamo"
for help!
I will go over there too.
Roger!
I have to talk to Taiyo.
I'm back.
Taiyo?
Jannis, where is Kei?
I don't know.
We were separated.
Well, we'll find her soon.
What?
Taiyo, it's me, Martha.
Martha.
I will just tell you once,
so please listen carefully.
Terrorism has struck the
Millennia Mule right now.
One of the terrorists took Kei
and is going to the dock.
Did you hear me?
Did he take Kei?
Sh... Shiunk...
There is the Lyla and
Agga Ruter in the dock.
He's causing a panic and
is trying to steal everything.
I have to save her.
Wait a minute!
Why? We have to hurry.
They have guns, so we have
to arm ourselves too.
But how?
Hey, old man! Can you
stay outside for a while?
Taiyo, do it quickly!
Ahhhh.
Ahhh, that is...
Passenger ship guards
don't have any guts to fight.
And they all act like cowards.
Don't resist!
Uh, what is it?
Ahhhh. You're too hard.
Terrorists have broken into the ship!
Eliminate them without hurting
any passengers!
Repeat! Terrorists have
broken into the ship!
They have to go through here
to escape.
Hurry! Look for the Agga Ruter!
It must be in this dock.
Stop!
Release the woman
and get down to the floor.
Terrorism is considered
a serious crime.
If you resist,
I will shoot to kill.
You sound brave, now that you've
shown us your naked body.
Shut up!
If you don't listen to me...
You're the one who
should put down the weapon.
You're...
Soldier A!
Why are you doing this?
I always hate it when you
call me "Soldier A," Captain.
You assign me difficult duties
and don't even call me by my name.
You always play games...
and try to be a
heroine by looking at stars.
I got fed up with you...
and thought about becoming a
pirate as a nice diversion for my stress.
Who wrote him such long lines?
Then Mr. Shiunk hired me.
Uh... no.
Our situations are now reversed.
Now, you are the one
who will get down on the floor.
It's a serious crime that
you tried to shoot me.
Even though
you can't fight back,
I will kill you now.
Taiyo.
What?
From the elevator!
Kei, Martha.
Taiyo.
Damn you!
You monster!
Taiyo.
All right, I will take
Kei and escape quickly.
Martha, Kei, are you all right?
Oh, no. Kei's gone.
Oh, why is this happening?
My entire plan is...
Are you all right, Kei?
Ah, yes. That's it!
Zuppon mayonnaise.
Otto dokkoi sucharaka chacha.
No, no, but I like it.
Can I do it little bit?
No, no, don't do such a thing.
Please watch episode 4 too!
Taiyo.
Kei, I guess you are all right.
Yes, but Shiunk is...
Shiunk is gone.
He also took Virginia.
We must escape right now!
Blow the hatch with bombs.
But our fellows
are still inside the ship.
Don't worry! Just do it now!
Yes.
Damn it! KA-3!
I almost got everything.
I will make you mine someday.
You are mine!
Prepare to start quickly.
Fill in the energy!
I'll be happy to.
Start engine.
Open the pressure valve!
I got it.
Connect the fly hubcap!
Fill in the energy! 120%.
I'll be happy to.
Ms. Jannis. You are being too loud.
Be quiet.
I guess she doesn't understand.
Taiyo!
Yes.
Oh, good cat. Nice cat.
Well, let's go over there.
I forget how far I went.
Let's start all over again.
- I'll be happy to.
- I got it.
Start! Open display!
Martha,
we will follow the pirates.
Be careful, Taiyo.
Radar has detected something
on fore deck.
It's space battleship class A.
Project it on the screen!
A battleship?
Cameraman!
Don't get so close!
I think this is beautiful.
Don't you think so?
Who am I talking to?
We captured the object!
Uhh, it's good. Very good!
There is a large passenger ship
and spaceship cruiser close to us.
Uhhh. Don't worry.
No need to worry.
If it gets hit, that's it.
Main gun! Open fire!
A strong energy wave
is rapidly approaching us.