Doctor!
How is the Mistress?
How is she, Doctor?
Yvonne... Yvonne!
Mother!
Oh, my beloved Yvonne. Uh!
I have to leave you now...
Aah... You are going to be OK!
Mother!
You are going to get better.
The doctor says so, too...
so... Mama.
There is something
I have to tell you before I die.
Mother! Don't try to speak.
I will go get the doctor!
Mother.
Yvonne, darling. Listen to me. I have to tell
you about the dark secret of our family.
The horrible tie that binds Ayano women,
that even your father did not know.
Mother!
I don't have long.
Accept this horrible fate as
your mother has done. Understand?
No!!!!
Yvonne, you have this
horrible blood in you as well.
Mama.
Don't ever let this
secret out to anyone.
It is a disgrace to the Ayano family!
It will disgrace all our ancestors!
Mama...
Yvonne. You must be strong.
This is a cross you must bear
as an Ayano woman. Be strong.
Yes, Mother.
Mother!
Yvonne, I will always
be watching for you.
I love you, Yvonne...
Mother!
Oh no! Mother! Oh no!
Mother...
Mother!!!!
Ha! A dream...
A report to you, Miss Yvonne.
There's been an
explosion on Milleni Amour.
Furthermore, we have a report that the
ship you inquired about has departed.
Miss Yvonne...
who is more beautiful
than flowers in full bloom...
Understood. I'm coming!
Main batteries, fire!
Impossible to avoid.
The starboard engine is on fire;
impossible to extinguish!
Energy leak from the fire;
possible chain explosions in each block!
Attention all crew on board,
prepare to abandon ship! I repeat...
What does this mean?
This means you will die
if you don't get out.
We are going to die!
Target's engine is on fire.
Ability to attack: 8.7%.
Drifting towards 9 o'clock at
.168 cells per second.
My main batteries are astonishingly
accurate as always.
Beautiful Captain. We have an energy
response from within the target...
which seems to be coming from
another ship. Do you wish to attack?
Would you like to attack, Miss?
Negative!!!
These are the guests
I've been waiting for!
Prepare to welcome them
immediately.
Yes, Miss.
Lyla...
Jannis, take it easy.
High energy response
from the surroundings.
Gravitational and
structural oscillation detected.
Space Fleet.
Kei, it seems
we've been caught.
Yes, we've been caught.
What should we do?
Let's pay them a visit
and say hello.
You must communicate well
with them.
OK.
Long Live Miss Yvonne!
I am the Captain of this ship,
Yvonne F. Ayano.
Welcome to Dedra Bots!
Kei, Taiyo. Huh?
It, it is prohibited to bring pets
and dangerous articles on board!
Taiyo!
How can it be?
She was so small,
yet now she's become so big.
Such a comment is a...
...no-no.
Yes, I remember now!
You, you!!
You, you, you!!
You are putting everything
on display.
You are the stupid broad who
whacked us without warning!
You won't get away with this!
Be ready to suffer!
Hey, what are you looking at?
I was looking at your boobs.
What! You sank the Lyla and now you
are going to criticize my boobs, huh?
If you want to see boobs,
why don't you look at your own...
Ah! This is...
Ja, Jannis!
What have you...
What are you doing to Janni...
This is horrib...
How can you...
Taiyo. Under the circumstances,
we shouldn't resist.
I guess you are right, Kei.
Do something. Hey...
We've shown the pirate
to quarters downstairs.
Now, you two will
to come to my room.
This luxury suite is mine.
Nobody asked.
These are my maids.
Excuse me,
can I have this cake?
Please wait until
we finish exchanging greetings.
How about tea?
No.
Please finish your greetings.
Then, once more.
My name is Yvonne F. Ayano.
I am the captain of this ship.
I'm Taiyo.
I'm Kei.
Now.
I have something to tell you.
I said not until
we finish greetings!
Seconds.
Would you please listen?
What is it?
Essentially, my mission
is to subdue pirates.
However, recently,
we've found a mysterious person...
That's great.
A man called Shiunk.
Shiunk...
He doesn't pay any attention to
freights or passenger ships.
The only ships he attacks are
treasure hunters.
Don't you think it's strange?
It is strange, isn't it?
So, I conducted an investigation
and discovered what he is looking for.
The legacy of
prehistoric civilization!!
Kei! You!!
That's no use.
You, Virginia, and the Agga Ruter.
Those are Shiunk's targets!
Though I don't know
the reason why.
And, what are you trying to say?
Frankly, I want to know the secret
hidden inside you.
So what do you say?
Would you cooperate with our
research staff at our newest facility?
What are you going
to do with the results?
Nothing!
I just want to kill some time.
I'm afraid
this may sound absurd...
but pirate hunting is too easy for a
woman of my abilities, and I'm bored.
Being too competent is not
always so good, don't you think?
What happens to Jannis?
She'll be sentenced to death,
of course.
You can't do that!
But, the penalty for piracy
are stated in the Space Fleet Code.
Jannis had retired from pirating!
Do something, please!
Hmmm. Let's see.
Yes, Kei?
Jannis is an important teaching
material in Taiyo's sex education.
Release her, or
I won't cooperate in any fashion.
I see. I have no choice.
Then...
However, under certain conditions.
How about this?
We are heading to the
prison planet Arca Deala.
We will sentence her
to imprisonment there.
Furthermore, Kei, you are to see
someone there. Agreed?
Yes!
Any other questions?
Yes, Taiyo?
Why are you wearing
something like that on your head?
Something like what?
Something that makes you look silly.
Nothing but a complete fool.
What is this!?
Who! Which one of you
put it on my head?
Yes, that was me.
I couldn't resist since...
What are they doing, Kei?
It's a form of physical contact.
Looks like she's abusing the maid...
Some people like to be abused.
We'll try that on Jannis later.
Hey! Help me!!
I apologize for the
disgraceful scene in your presence.
No, no. Thank you
for the entertainment.
We are grateful.
By the way, how long
will Jannis' sentence be?
I'll try to make it
as short as possible.
You can do that?
For me,
it's a simple matter!
I see. So, it all
depends on your heart.
Uh... Well, I suppose it is.
My breasts ache. If we are
to be chased by the Space Fleet...
my breasts will tremble
with foreboding.
Your generosity has moved
my breasts, Miss Yvonne.
What's wrong?
Did I do something to make
your breast, eh, make you upset?
No, never mind.
Show her to the laboratory!
Yes, Miss.
Then, I'll go to the laboratory.
I'll start cleaning around here.
- See you!
See you!
Miss Claire is here to see you.
Let her in.
Claire.
Nice to see you, Yvonne.
Lieutenant Colonel Claire.
Please keep in mind that I am your
superior. Please leave us for a while.
Yes, Miss!
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Not there.
Why?
What is this? I am not a student
who didn't do her homework!
That's right!
You are not a student.
You have responsibilities that are
far larger than homework!!
Lieutenant Colonel.
Your blunder caused the Space Fleet
to lose its prestige.
Usually, you would be
court-martialed.
However, since it had happened during
the rescue efforts of Milleni Amour...
you are suspended for a month...
and you will be demoted to work
under my command.
Understood?
Understood!?
OK, OK!!
Answer properly!
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for your generous
consideration, ma'am.
I feel a little better now.
Eh, nothing.
While you are under suspension,
you can be my slave, I mean, maid.
Oh, then, about the pay.
I'd like this much.
That's too high.
How about this?
That's too cheap! A fast food
restaurant would pay more!
No kidding!
I can't pay more than this.
You gotta be kidding.
At least this much.
A financial giant
doesn't waste its money!
I'll give you a special rate.
If that's your special rate,
then...
- Are you going to put that on me?
- I was going to.
You!!
Excuse me...
even if I'm hired as your maid,
it wouldn't be to my taste.
It's not my taste either...
There! Your first job!
OK! Hey! How's it goin'?
This is Miss Yvonne's...
Claire! How vulgar!
Huh? A stowaway
in the Agga Ruter hangar?
Martha!
Martha Igrie.
The captain of Milleni Amour.
Yes.
Why would someone like you
sneak in?
Because...
Because?
I cannot have any more
unauthorized persons on board.
You must return to your ship.
May I stay
if I'm part of the crew?
Taiyo, Kei.
I sent my resignation to Narcis Inc.
Please take me with you.
What do you mean? Why?
Please take me as a
crew member of the Agga Ruter.
I have my resume.
I'm healthy.
The reason I chose your ship is
I feel my old self again with you.
What are you
babbling about, huh?
For one thing,
it's too sudden for...
That's fine.
Let's go together.
Thanks, Taiyo.
Wait a second!
So, Yvonne, you have one
more crew member.
Hope you don't mind.
What's this?
Anything wrong?
You can't even gain access
or analyze the data.
The only thing we can inspect
is the external factors.
Tell me what you know so far, then.
Yes, the inspection tells us
that she has a nice body.
And what are we supposed
to do with that knowledge?
That's all we know.
This facility has the latest technology,
and that's all we can find out?
The design is based on a
completely unfamiliar idea.
If we proceed,
we may cause damage.
There's absolutely no way to analyze her?
How about her breasts?
Breasts?
Eh, ah, just joking.
Forget it. Never mind.
Tra-la-la!
Let's mop the floor, mop, mop!
Polish and shine the floor,
mop, mop! Make it clean and shiny!
Making it clean is so fun!
Scrub, wipe, polish well!
Where else can we clean?
The headquarters, engine room,
and Yvonne's room.
Let's divide up the work.
Yes, yes!
Then, I'll do Yvonne's room.
Strange. With Taiyo,
even cleaning is fun.
So true.
I thank Taiyo for the way I feel.
I guess he was born with the
power to change lives around him.
Yes. He pleased me all over,
body and soul...
What? You didn't...
Huh? What is it?
You did it!
You did it with him!
You did! You must have done
it with Taiyo!!
Stop it, Claire!
Well, then. Claire,
you do the headquarters.
Hey...
No matter how many women
there are, you are my only partner.
Let's dance. Tonight's party
is just for you and me.
Tra-ra-ra-ra! Tra-ra-ra-ra!
Wonderful!
Beautiful. Gorgeous. Elegant.
Those words were invented just for you.
Those well-contoured breasts.
Ample breasts are the symbol of beauty!
A woman with small breasts
does not deserve to live!
Smaller than C cups...
The production staff for
this game have dangerous ideas!
Take them all to Planet Yvonne
and brainwash them!
What's so great about ample breasts?
Big breasts... Breasts...
Breasts... Uhh...
I'm going to take a shower!
Leave me alone.
Yes, Miss!
Tra-la-la! Let's clean with gusto!
Let's go, let's go cleaning!
Hello. To clean your...
Huh, nobody's home.
Taiyo.
No, Yvonne, don't have such
worthless thoughts.
You don't need men.
For some reason,
I'm going to start here. Eh?
The boobs fell?
Excuse us!
What happened? Ow!
No! No! No! No! No!!!
What am I going to do?
The secret of the Ayano family...
A secret?
A secret? Ah, this is to make
your breasts look bigger.
This material is...
Yes. The artificial skin made
by a prehistoric civilization.
Our ancestors were all small-breasted,
so we invented this breast enhancer.
Just as my mother's, my breasts are...
The size and shape...
This breast part was for androids
from that prehistoric civilization.
It was my only means
to make them look ample.
Why bother?
Because...
My mama told me that all
men like big-breasted women!
That's why I never had a boyfriend!
It must be the reason!
Yvonne is crying. At such a
time as this, a man must make...
Physical contact!
Right!
Mama... Uhh...
Yvonne. Why are you crying?
You have such a beautiful body.
You are lying.
The size doesn't matter.
The heart inside is what counts!
But... Ah!
How can you show
your heart to someone?
I'll teach you how. Feel it.
With your heart.
Am I really beautiful?
Yes.
Mama. Even with small breasts,
I am loved.
I am... I am...
Just as I thought.
The technologies of breast enhancement
from the prehistoric civilization.
No matter where she got it from,
she won't need it anymore.
Good-bye... Mama!!!
Where is Taiyo?
Martha! Claire!
You were waiting for me?
Thank you for the good work,
ladies.
Yvonne. I mean MISS Yvonne.
Your breasts...
No, Claire. That's OK.
Call me Yvonne.
I learned the importance
of generosity and the beauty of love.
It's all thanks to Taiyo.
Taiyo, you didn't...
You did her?
Oh, Claire. Cut it out.
You won't punish me anymore...
Hey, don't forget about me!
Let me out!
Let me out of here now!
Taiyo, help me!! Eh?
Hello!
Thank goodness! Did you bring
a prison breaking kit?
Here we go.
Take care.
I am a princess
in captivity.
Where is my knight
in shining armor?
That's the Arca Dealer?
I can't believe such an old
heap is still being used.
How long will Jannis
have to be there?
I'll make it as short as possible, darling.
With my power.
Humph. That bitch of a captain.
What does she want?