Space...
It's romance in the infinite prairie...
This story will be...
Oh!!
This story will begin here.
I... it should be starting here...
Uhm... it's here.
Uh, uh...
The story will start from here.
- Oh!?
- Uh?
No, it's not there. 1.5 centimeters
more to the right.
I... I see.
Ahhh. Ahhhh. It's right there.
No, it's not there.
Here?
Y... yes, right there.
- Actually, you moved too far.
- Sorry. Here?
One more time!
We'll start from the beginning.
Here we go.
Ah... Ahhhh... y... yes. Taiyo.
R... right there.
M... mother.
Th... that's it.
Yes, yes. Stop right there,
and click, click.
Ah... yes. You are doing very well.
Ah... ahh.
M... mother, I'm already...
Ah.
Taiyo?
Ah?
Here.
Y... yeah.
Ah... ah... ahh... listen to me.
You shouldn't even slightly
move from the right point.
Here you are, Taiyo.
Yeah.
Uh... Uhhhhhh.
Y... you're doing great, Taiyo.
I... I feel very good.
Give it to me. Right now!
Ahhh.
Th... that's right. How to move your
hips is the important point.
M... mother.
More, move more intensively.
Ah... ahh... ah...
That's the ship.
Tractor beam, engage!!
Is this pink ribbon OK for you?
Anything is fine.
They're captured!!
A cinch! This is too simple.
Congratulations!!
Uh, activate the
communication system to Shiunk.
It's activated.
Hello, Shiunk? This is Jannis.
Shiunk! Can you hear me?
Jannis, what do you want?
What do you think?
I captured the ship that you requested.
That was quick.
You are quite skilled.
It's just an easy job
for a pirate like me.
By the way, be sure to prepare my
reward of one million in gold.
All right. We'll make the exchange
at the rendezvous.
We'll meet there
24 hours from now.
No social grace, as usual.
Pull in the tractor beam!!
Here we go!!
Uh?
What's the matter, Mother?
I guess somebody has captured us.
Who?
My name is Jannis!
I've captured your ship.
Everybody should surrender quietly,
if you want to save your lives.
What are we going to do, Mother?
Well, it might be a good
opportunity for us.
What!?
Taiyo, you've become
19 years old, as of today.
You are now considered an adult.
Therefore...
I approve of you communicating
to other people besides me.
Make use of the knowledge
I have taught you.
Have pleasant, enjoyable, and pleasurable
relationships with a lot of people.
But, Mother...
Why don't we change
what you call me?
Just call me Kei from now on.
- M... mother, but it's so sudden.
- I'm Kei.
Uh, can't we make love anymore?
I am always yours, Taiyo.
But you are no longer just mine.
Do you understand?
I understand, Kei.
Are you listening?
I can blow up your ship immediately!
Hey!!! Anybody listening?
Hey, you!
Look at me!!
Oh!!
As I announced, I, Jannis,
have captured your ship, Agga Ruter.
Everybody should surrender immediately!
I... I said everybody!
There are only two of us
on board the Agga Ruter.
What?
W... why are you staring at me?
It's impolite without even greeting.
You have to give her some
gift in these situations.
"Reioh Bland Soap"
- I see. Mother.
- I'm Kei.
Thank you for inviting us today.
This is some worthless thing, but...
Ah!?
It's really worthless.
I'm Taiyo, she is my Moth...
I'm Kei.
Ah!?
You guys are now captured!
Are we?
We are.
Hostages should act like hostages!
Hostages?
What are we supposed to do?
Uh... Well...
For the time being... why don't you
clean up inside the ship.
I guess they are really dumb.
What kind of education did you get?
I think I just raised him
by following the data.
Uaaaaaa!! That's enough! Disturbing!
Don't follow me!!
Jannis, aren't you going to
clean up with us?
I haven't slept
since I first watched your ship.
I'm tired! I'm exhausted!
So I will rest! Don't disturb me!
Clean up well!
See you!
As you wish.
Who the hell are they?
They have nonchalant faces, too.
Still, why is Shiunk offering such a
large prize for an ignorant pair like them?
They can't be
his separated wife and son.
Maybe there is
something inside the ship.
Besides, I've never seen that
type of vessel before.
I guess I'll find out from them
after the nap.
Wahhhhh!!
Wh... what is going on!?
It's an emergency!
Somebody's accessing
Ms. Jannis's top secret data!
"I fell in love with you since
I first met you at the shore"
What!?
- "I fell in love with you..."
- What?
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, Ms. Jannis.
While I was cleaning up,
I found this switch was blinking.
Then I pressed the button
without meaning to,
then this handsome man,
ljuin, persistently...
This is my game!
- You can't touch it!
- Then I will turn it off.
No, stupid!
You have to save it!!
I love...
Uhaaaaaa!!!
My darling, whom I created...
The data I spent a year writing...
Uh? Did I do something wrong?
You!!!!
Lyrical Magic, Lyrical Magic.
What!?
I cast a spell of love.
I want to tell my heartbeat.
I run in the morning dew.
A young woman's heart
is always fragile.
So please, with this little magic,
I will shoot my love to your heart.
No! Please don't look at me.
Oh!?
Don't say "oh"!! Don't read my
poems without permission!!
You too!
Why did you broadcast that?
Is this!?
Don't look!!
What?
August 6th, sniff...
I am all alone again today.
I wish the prince from the
stars would come and take me.
Don't read my diary!!
Is this your lingerie?
No, no, no!!
Jannis's heart is
on the shooting star.
Stop!!! Don't read it!!
- Album?
- No, don't touch it!!
My heart is painful.
She must be exhausted.
Let's leave her alone.
Well, what should we do now?
Let's clean up the other
rooms in the meantime.
I guess so!
"Food tickets machine"
"Ramen" "Sake" "Men's bath"
- There're many things here.
- It's just to get people's attention.
I wonder what this room is for.
Let's open the door.
I don't know if that's OK.
It's locked.
Don't worry, just open it.
Is it OK?
It's OK.
Hello.
Uh!?
What is this room?
This is...
What is Ms. Jannis
using this room for?
What are you doing?
I'm asking you what
are you doing here?
What are we doing?
Of course, we're cleaning up.
You don't have to do it here!
I will do it by myself.
But...
Get out!!!
Let's get out, Taiyo.
Shit!!
- Mother.
- I'm Kei.
Ms. Jannis!
What's this all about?
She should stay here
until I bring you guys to Shiunk.
Why just Kei?
Because,
I have something to ask you!
I have to be with Kei.
What did you say?
Taiyo, I will be all right.
Why don't you go and talk to Ms. Jannis?
But...
What you need right now is
to meet lots of people.
Be friendly to her as I taught you.
As you taught me?
Yes.
I understand, Kei.
Uh!?
I don't have any secrets.
Don't play dumb!
Shiunk is offering 1 million in gold.
It shouldn't be an ordinary ship.
Do you or that woman have
any hidden secrets?
Both Kei and I are
hiding nothing.
Anyway, what's the relationship
between you and her?
You guys are mother and son?
Kei is my mother,
but she's not my real mother.
Kei raised me.
She taught me so many things
so that I can meet lots of people...
and get along well with them.
Again! Don't say things that
don't make sense!
It's true.
You better answer for your own sake
while I am asking you nicely.
What is that ship?
Who the hell are you guys?
Can you stop it?
Ahhhhh.
Well, what did you just do?
I'm sorry.
I accidentally pressed your vital point.
My vital point?
Yes, the point that makes you feel good.
Kei taught me that.
Ms. Jannis,
you must be very tired.
Can you just tell by touching?
Yes, give me your hand.
Ahhhhhh.
Do you feel good?
Uhhhh. It's so good.
This is a trick, isn't it?
Answer me! Who are you guys...
That really works.
Ms. Jannis,
why don't you just lie down.
W... what are you trying to do?
There are more vital points
that make you feel good.
No, don't do that there.
Right there!
Don't you feel good?
Ah?
What are you doing?
Uh.
S... stop!!
Ahhhh. Uhhhhh.
I guess Kei was right.
Ah, n... no!
Ahhhh. Ahhh.
N... no, not there.
Ahhhhhhhhh!!!
Ahhh. Ahhhh.
R... run away!
Huh?
Run!!
Run away. Ahhhhhh.
Taiyo...
"Open"
Did you come? You came, didn't you?
Then please rest well.
Ms. Jannis.
What's the matter?
Ms. Jannis?
Be careful of yourself!
What's wrong with you?
Ms. Jannis?
Why? Why is this happening?
Have sex with her.
K... Kei. Why sex?
Just do it now.
You should make her orgasm.
Do you understand Taiyo?
You must use deep communication,
as I taught you.
Yeah.
OK, OK.
You don't have to be afraid.
I will be very gentle.
Here we go.
Boss is making love in her room.
Shh!
Uh?
Huh?
Noooooo!!
I don't remember anything.
Where I was born, or who was my mother.
When I realized it, I was already alone.
When I was four years old,
the head of a circus took me in.
He was sweet.
He was a very nice person.
When I was nineteen,
he did it with me...
It was the first time for me,
but I didn't feel so bad.
Everybody is doing that in the circus.
But, when it was done,
his dead body was on the floor.
I did it,
when I changed into the beast.
I was scared.
I was too scared to stay there,
and I ran, and...
...I was alone again,
and so I ended up...
...being a pirate like this.
The scratches in that room are
from when you were masturbating?
If I had sex with somebody,
I would kill that person.
I am... I am the woman who
can't make love to anybody!
How did you find out?
I analyzed the data with
the claw marks you left in the room.
You are a descendant
of a reformed human.
What?
Did you say I am a descendant
of a reformed human?
Yes. The reformed human created
by the Fighter Civilization.
You are a descendant of
the Jannis-T type.
What is that?
Humans who reformed their DNA to
survive in extremely severe environments.
Although your basic form has
already returned to human...
the phenomenon to become a beast
has remained as a side effect.
Reformed human?
Who are you?
Why do you know about such things?
Do you want to know why?
Yeah.
Do you really want to know?
I am...
Boss! It's time!!
Oh, is it already time for the trade?
Shiunk is a very dangerous person.
If you aren't careful,
it will become a fatal problem.
Kei, do you know him?
Taiyo, Shiunk is the
man who killed your parents.
W... what did you say?
Fifteen years ago, the shuttle
you were in beached on the Agga Ruter.
It washed ashore from the other ship.
Shiunk is the person
who attacked the ship...
and killed all the crewmembers,
except Taiyo.
He was an enemy of your parents.
Ms. Jannis,
you shouldn't trust Shiunk.
are you trying to bring us to Shiunk?
Ms. Jannis.
Captain Shiunk, it's time for
the deal with the Rayler.
Did you prepare?
- Uh? Prepare one million in gold?
- Don't be silly!!
Prepare for battle!
I will open the communication
circuit with the Rayler.
You're late.
It took a while to prepare.
Sorry about that.
It's not a big deal.
I brought the ship.
Now, give me the money.
Don't be rash.
I have to get the ship first.
Money first!
Ship first!
Humph! Greedy man!
Take it!
The Agga Ruter has been taken.
Excellent.
Now, give me money.
You are too gullible.
What?
You have to be a little more
careful to live in space.
- Do it!
- Roger!
Shiunk! You bastard!
You should be a
little more careful.
- If I push,
- when I push,
Let's push!
Like this? Push!
What? The Agga Ruter is...
N... no, it seems like it's a fake.
It looks like crystallized metal.
Captain! The radar is jammed.
Those metal fragments are causing
too much interference.
Operate on a
visual recognition system!
Roger!!
Visual recognition system operating!
All hands stand by!
The port side and bow!
All clear!
The stern of the ship!
The aft of the ship!
All right!
I found the enemy ship
on the starboard side, ahead!
Fire!!
No, it won't work.
The bombs are reflecting the
metal fragments around us!
No choice! Everybody get out,
and remove the metal fragments!
Hey, look!
What?
It's weird.
There's nothing around there.
That's true.
What's that?
Ah!
"Hair Growth"
"How to enjoy whisky"
"Change the commercial system"
Ahhhhh. To the front!
W... what's going on?
Agga Ruter!
The great inheritance
of the Fighter Civilization!
Finally, finally!
Engage tractor beam!
But, it's in the
enemy's firing range!!
Anti-mater bomb loaded!
Fire!!
Agga Ruter!!
Where is the Agga Ruter?
We did it.
I... is it OK to do such a thing?
It's a big mess.
Shiunk may not survive this.
No, I limited the power,
so he must have escaped.
What?
Why didn't you just kill him?
Shiunk was your enemy, wasn't he?
That's not for me to decide.
To get revenge on him, or not,
is for Taiyo to decide.
But he is not old enough to make
that decision yet.
Today, this was just our way
of saying hello.
You are more scary than you look.
Am I?
Then, what will we do now?
We have something to look for.
And now you're grown up
enough to look for it.
- So let's go on with the journey.
- Yeah!
Well then, Ms. Jannis. So long!
Hey, hey!
Are you leaving me?
You are the only person
who can handle me.
I'll follow you anywhere.
Of course you won't say no!
Will you? Will you?
I guess you've already got
a new friend.
...Yeah!
Well, let's continue our lessons.
Yeah!
The next episode of Space Opera
Agga Ruter is...
"A Brave Dwarf is a Troublemaker"
See you soon!